<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="7c2a2a5635bc13dd3ede7940dd8182ef">			Strings of lights are also an inexpensive way to decorate for the holidays. You can use colored or simple white lights. Other types of garlands can look very attractive. Faux garlands of holly or other winter leaves can look pretty on holiday displays. Make sure when you are adding decorations that it enhances the look of your retail display, but that it does not get in the way of what the retail display is meant to do - display your products. The retail display should still be able to turn, open or showcase the items without obstruction. You can find holiday themed garlands at party stores or discount stores. Celebrate Everyone's Holidays An important factor to keep in mind about your holiday decorations is that you want to make sure your holiday decorations embrace everyone's idea of the holidays.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although retail store owners refer to the winter holiday season as &quot;the Christmas season&quot; - there is also Hanukah and Kwanza to consider. While some stores may wish to cater to a specific religion, such as a store with religious items or Christmas ornaments - other stores will want to be welcoming to other holidays and faiths. It simply makes good business sense to give good holiday greetings. Do your best to select holiday decorations for your retail displays that express your store's character - but also are expressive of other faiths and holidays. You'll be pleased with the results. Vinyl clings can also look attractive on retail displays. You can find winter and holiday themed vinyl clings that will look great on your retail displays. You simply peel off the package and stick them onto your display. Make sure the glass or plastic is clean before you stick them on. They will peel right off when you are ready to take them off. These can look very charming and come in so many styles.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can find vinyl clings in party supply stores and even in educational supply stores as many teachers and schools use them. Yet another beautiful means of enhancing your retail displays for the holiday is to spray faux holiday snow! This is regularly available at your local craft store and is not reserved only for indoor trees. The faux snow gives your displays an instant holiday aura, and when coupled with holiday lights, you have an amazing ambiance for selling! Dressing up your retail displays for the holidays is a great way to celebrate the holidays. It is fun and shows your holiday spirit. Celebrating the holidays also makes good business sense!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use these display ideas to make the most of your slatwall, gridwall and showcase displays. Learn what benefits these store displays have over other forms of product merchandising.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using slatwall in a retail setting can be really beneficial. Once the slatwall panels are installed, you can quickly and easily change up your displays. You can also buy sections of grid wall that clip together to create custom retail floor displays. You can make a wall of cubes that fit in odd spaces. For example, underneath a staircase. This unique feature helps you to utilize what would have otherwise been wasted space.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gridwall and slatwall both help customers see what you have to offer. You can keep a nightly inventory to prevent employee theft as well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcGVlZHByb2Nhcm9saW5hcy5jb20vZ3JlZW5zYm9yby9wYWdlcy9TZXJ2aWNlcy9jYXQvMQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;retail displays&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="a47b91f436568c798d3b5048bcc8ebd1">			Typically commercial properties come with fluorescent lighting, however this does not do much in the way of ambiance.  Consider track lighting, recessed lighting, halogen lighting, spot lighting, or &quot;retro&quot; style light fixtures. This is one of the most important efforts to make to establish differentiation from competitors and ensure higher margins.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Feature your big dollar products on an eye-catching retail display&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A way to improve your retail image is to showcase well established brand products on an attractive retail display, which significantly improves the first impression of visitors. This is the most determining aspect for shoppers to associate the overall quality of your store environment. In other words if you present recognizable quality brands on a featured retail display at a dominant location, this impression will automatically spill over to your store's image.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brand awareness can be supported or enhanced by integrating graphics and signage to demonstrate special product information that decides whether or not customers accept to spend a higher amount for the featured merchandise. Communicate advantages or lifestyle values that makes this item special and coveted.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you fail to promote your heavy dollar product on a high class retail display and provide a quality focused shopping experience, unavoidably your store will be associated with a budget mart with cheap no-name merchandise. You miss the opportunity to sell high margin products to prospective shoppers who choose to make brand purchase from your competitor with a higher rated store image.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Invest in a custom design solution to target your customer base&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Custom retail displays are the most effective investment to make when you aim at highlighting brand products and achieving higher margins. Attractive retail display design is crucial for every successful retail location as the overall impression of your store environment are heavily influenced -- not only by what you sell -- but also by the way your products are presented. Additionally custom tailored retail display can draw attention from a targeted customer base by serving their design preferences and stand out from the competition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are numerous options available now for displaying your advertising media. Many are geared for permanent or long term display but more and more short term, quick change options are being developed. The retail world is a battlefield with everyone striving to gain an advantage with their special offers so choosing the right media is increasingly important. Here are a few options.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The eye catching  &quot;SwingRite&quot; is the more traditional forecourt sign with a newly acquired stability.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Based onto tubular steel legs and pivoting from the middle, this sign is excellent for use in areas where gusts of wind can cause ordinary signs to topple over.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &quot;GripTite&quot; frame is bottom weighted which keeps your display the right way up at all times. There is nothing worse than an good offer that no one can read because it's upside down.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;PaveRite&quot;, the more permanent Pavement or Forecourt sign is mounted by rigid steel legs onto a concrete base making it a stable double sided display frame.  It's rugged construction makes it difficult for anyone to damage or remove.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The space saving base, makes this sign ideal for advertising in locations where space is limited.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &quot;GripTite&quot; front opening system adds to the signs easy use and makes changing the posters held within the display unit a doddle.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The frames are ideal for weekly or monthly campaigns as well as for more permanent adverts. These are just a selection of what is available.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcGVlZHByb2Nhcm9saW5hcy5jb20vZ3JlZW5zYm9yby9wYWdlcy9TZXJ2aWNlcy9jYXQvMQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;retail displays and store fixtures&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>