<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="28dc4f079a2919c7f1e3134cfca85ee9">			Ma heart s lke a singin bird whose nest s in a water'd shoot; ma heart s like an apple tree whose boughs are bent wth thick set fruits; ma heart s like a rainbow shell dat paddles in a halcyon sea; ma hearth s gladder dan al dis; becuz ma love s come 2 Me. I love U		</conversation>		<conversation id="b3745e5bf474a5c9e0ccfb89b465889c">			1. TEXT HIM A LOVE MESSAGE :    Send him a romantic text message on his cell. Make sure it's sweet but spicy!
&lt;br /&gt;;2. DO ONE OF HIS CHORES FOR HIM:   Pick a chore that he dreads, such as mowing thelawn, and do it for him. Watch him as he sighs with relief. 
&lt;br /&gt;;3. START A HOBBY TOGETHER:   Sharing a hobby together such as horse back riding,completing a home improvement project, or selling on eBay can help keep you close.
&lt;br /&gt;;4.
&lt;br /&gt;;PLAY A GAME TOGETHER:  Have fun doing things together such as playing board games, riding bumper boats, or playing miniature golf. Just remember, if he should get the best of you, don't tackle him unless you're laughing!
&lt;br /&gt;;5.
&lt;br /&gt;;SHOW APPRECIATION:  When your husband works hard, or does something for you, let him know you appreciate him.
&lt;br /&gt;;6.
&lt;br /&gt;;MAKE YOUR HOME HIS REFUGE:  Let your home be a haven were your husband can retreat from the stresses of life. Do your best to make it a pleasant environment.
&lt;br /&gt;;7.
&lt;br /&gt;;LAUGH AT HIS ANTICS:  Don't let the little things that your husband does get on your nerves. If you think about it, some of these things may have been what attracted you to him! He just wouldn't be the same if he didn't do these things.
&lt;br /&gt;;8.
&lt;br /&gt;;PRAY FOR HIM:   Ask God to give him that extra boost to make everything OK. Let your husband hear you pray too. This will let him know that when you can't make it right, you'll ask someone who can.
&lt;br /&gt;;9.
&lt;br /&gt;;CHECK BEFORE THROWING THINGS AWAY:  If your husband has some things that seem useless to you, don't trash them until you've made sure he doesn't need them.
&lt;br /&gt;;10.
&lt;br /&gt;;CHECK BEFORE REARRANGING:   Ask your husband if it's OK before you move or straighten things on his desk or work area. If he has things where it's easy to find, it might make it chaotic if it's moved.
&lt;br /&gt;;11.
&lt;br /&gt;;TAKE A WALK OR A HIKE TOGETHER:   Let nature set the mood for romance! Talk, listen, and hold hands.
&lt;br /&gt;;12.
&lt;br /&gt;;DON'T EXPECT HIM TO READ YOUR MIND:  If there is something you want your husband to know about you, tell him. Don't expect him to just know what you're thinking or what you need.
&lt;br /&gt;;13.
&lt;br /&gt;;LAUGH TOGETHER:  Forget your adults forawhile, and just act silly together. Also, if something should go awry, try to find some humor in it somewhere. This will also reduce the stress of the situation.
&lt;br /&gt;;14.
&lt;br /&gt;;RESIST THE URGE TO SNOOP:   Don't sneak around and check up on your husband, if you want to know something, ask him to his face.
&lt;br /&gt;;15.
&lt;br /&gt;;GIVE HIM A ROMANTIC CARD: Don't wait for a special occasion to give him a card. Find the most romantic card you can findand leave it in his car. Don't forget to addyour own personal message! Maybe you'll even make him nervous, wondering if he forgot an anniversary!
&lt;br /&gt;;16.
&lt;br /&gt;;PACK HIS FAVORITE TREAT:   Buy his favorite candy bar or other treat, and pack it in his lunch with a love note.
&lt;br /&gt;;17.
&lt;br /&gt;;TAKE A BUBBLE BATH TOGETHER:  This is self-explanatory.
&lt;br /&gt;;18.
&lt;br /&gt;;E-MAIL HIM AN INVITATION FOR ROMANCE:   Invite him on a rendezvous with you! Build his anticipation, then tell him to RSVP!
&lt;br /&gt;;19.
&lt;br /&gt;;TAKE HIM TO TEST DRIVE HIS DREAM CAR:  Drive him to a car lot some Saturday, andlet him test drive the car of his dreams - even though you probably won't buy it.
&lt;br /&gt;;20.
&lt;br /&gt;;LET HIM BUY THAT TOY:   Permit him to buy that toy he's been wanting so badly. Better yet, put some of your own things off, save the money and buy it for him yourself!
&lt;br /&gt;;21.
&lt;br /&gt;;TALK ABOUT THE FUTURE:   The future isn't as far away as it seems sometimes. Talk about where you'd like to be when you're married 50 years, and work on making those dreams happen.
&lt;br /&gt;;22.
&lt;br /&gt;;GIVE HIM THE BENEFIT OF THE DOUBT:   Don't jump to conclusions if your husband has said or done something questionable. Give him the chance to explain before you pass judgement.
&lt;br /&gt;;23.
&lt;br /&gt;;LET HIM BE THE MAN OF THE HOUSE:   Although this is growing increasingly unpopular, it does still work. Just because your husband is in charge of the household doesn't mean that you can't share your opinions, it just means he's captain of the team.
&lt;br /&gt;;24.
&lt;br /&gt;;SAY, &quot;I'M SORRY&quot;:  Although you may notwant to admit it, there will be times when you're in the wrong. Maybe you've said something hurtful or done something insensitive. Never have too much pride to tell him you're sorry.
&lt;br /&gt;;25.
&lt;br /&gt;;KEEP YOUR PROMISES:  If you told your husband you'd do something, make surethat you follow through.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>