<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="3fbb4eaa87ff8c3686e50bc327c09efc">			About 4 billion years ago, before the earth consisted of an oxygen-based atmosphere, the first forms of life on earth nourished on just two nutrients: sugar and protein. Stored inside the DNA of every living organism today exists the memory of this biological fact. The very first living cells did not contain a nucleus (prokaryotic cells) and fed anaerobically on sugars and proteins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later, after  the development of an oxygen-based atmosphere, higher organisms developed from cells with a nucleus (eukaryotic cells) and the use of fat became a nutrient source for the first time. These aerobic-feeding cells utilize fatty acids and ketones for energy, just as most mammalian and human cells do today. Because fat is an aerobic nutrient, it forms the basis of aerobic metabolism in our human bodies. This is the distinction between aerobic and anaerobic energy sources.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Nobel  Prize in Medicine was granted to Dr. Otto H. Warburg in 1931 for his research on the relationship of oxygen to the pH of cancer cells. His research demonstrated that cancer cells were anaerobic and as a result maintained more acidic pH levels. Because of the high CO2 and lactic acid production, the pH could be as low as 6.0 in a cancerous environment. Dr. Warburg demonstrated that there was a direct relationship between oxygen, blood Ph levels, and growing cancer cells.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a current theory that is becoming popularized by alternative doctors and holistic wellness providers. It involves how cancer cells mature in the body. The theory proposes that cancer grows in a fermentative, acidic, sugar-rich, anaerobic environment which reflects our earliest primordial environment, reversing some cells to their prokaryotic, nucleus-less, state. This theory further posits  that cancerous tumors are masses of these identical cells that represent a weak protein matrix which feeds wholly on sugars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancer cells grow  sporadically in the body from birth. A healthy immune system will prevent the proliferation of them. But when the body becomes so burdened with toxins -- such as from the air we breathe, the EMF radiation we're exposed to, the chlorine we drink and bathe in from our water, the toxic vaccines we inject into our children, and the carcinogens, GMOs, and the dumpster-full of sugar that we consume in a lifetime -- these life-giving, oxygen-feeding, eukaryotic cells are not able to properly perform their immune system responsibilities. And this results in the growing of harmful cancer tumors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only cure for cancer is prevention. By adhering to a diet that is sugar-free, we prevent sugar from creating an acidic environment that’s ideal for cancer. This will help to produce a slightly alkaline pH level of 7.35 to 7.45, assuring that cancer cells won't be able to form in the first place -- and if by some slight risk that they do -- the cancer cells would be dissolved by a healthy immune system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Lincoln Jeffers is a [url=]Spiritual Counselor[/url],  [url=]Personal Life Coach[/url], [url=]Spiritual Life Coach[/url], holistic [url=]Wellness Coach[/url], and [url=]Health Coach[/url]  who founded Sunlighten and also co-founded Sunlight Day Spa; two holistic wellness companies devoted to infrared heat therapy, sound therapy, and massage therapy. His particular [url=]Wellness Coaching[/url] and [url=]Health Coaching[/url] practice incorporates infrared sauna purification, upper cervical care, and adhering to an alkaline-forming, antioxidant-rich, sugar-free diet. You can learn more about his work here: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qYXNvbmxpbmNvbG5qZWZmZXJzLmNvbS93ZWxsbmVzc2NvYWNoaW5nLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;health coach&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="51fd4f87b305d467c9e98dad87c3a3ea">			Approximately 4 billion years ago, before the earth contained an oxygen-based atmosphere, the principal forms of life on earth nourished on only two nutrients: sugar and protein. Stored inside the DNA of every living organism today lies the memory of this biological fact. The very first living cells didn’t contain a nucleus (prokaryotic cells) and fed anaerobically on sugars and proteins.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Later, after  the development of an oxygen-based atmosphere, higher organisms advanced from cells with a nucleus (eukaryotic cells) and the use of fat became a nutrient source for the first time. These aerobic-feeding cells utilize fatty acids and ketones for fuel, just as most mammalian and human cells do currently. Since fat is an aerobic nutrient, it forms the basis of aerobic metabolism in our human bodies. This is the distinction between aerobic and anaerobic energy sources.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Nobel  Prize in Medicine was awarded to Dr. Otto H. Warburg in 1931 for his research on the relationship of oxygen to the pH of cancer cells. His research proved that cancer cells were anaerobic and as a result maintained more acidic pH levels. Because of the high CO2 and lactic acid production, the pH could be as low as 6.0 in a cancerous environment. He proved that there was a direct relationship between oxygen, blood Ph levels, and growing cancer cells.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is a current theory that is becoming popularized by alternative physicians and holistic wellness providers. It involves how cancer cells develop in the body. The theory suggests that cancer develops in a fermentative, acidic, sugar-rich, anaerobic environment which emulates our earliest primordial environment, reversing some cells to their prokaryotic, nucleus-less, state. This theory further posits  that cancerous tumors are masses of these identical cells that embody a weak protein matrix which feeds wholly on sugars.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cancer cells mature  ocassionally in the body from birth. A healthy immune system will prevent the proliferation of cancer cells. But when the body becomes so laden with toxins -- such as from the air we breathe, the EMF radiation we're exposed to, the fluoride we drink and bathe in from our water, the toxic vaccines we inoculate into our children, and the carcinogens, GMOs, and the dumpster-full of sugar that we consume in a lifetime -- these life-giving, healthy aerobic, eukaryotic cells are not able to properly undertake their immune system responsibilities. And this results in the forming of harmful cancerous tumors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The only cure for cancer is prevention. By adhering to a diet that is sugar-free, we prevent sugar from creating a toxic environment that’s ideal for cancer. This will help to create a slightly alkaline pH level of 7.35 to 7.45, ensuring that cancer cells won't be able to develop in the first place -- and if by some slight chance that they do -- the cancer cells would be dissolved by a healthy immune system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jason Lincoln Jeffers is a [url=]Spiritual Counselor[/url],  [url=]Personal Life Coach[/url], [url=]Spiritual Life Coach[/url], alternative [url=]Wellness Coach[/url], and [url=]Health Coach[/url]  who founded Sunlighten as well as co-founded Sunlight Day Spa; two holistic wellness companies focused on far-infrared heat therapy, sound therapy, and massage therapy. His [url=]Wellness Coaching[/url] and [url=]Health Coaching[/url] program embraces infrared sauna purification, upper cervical care, and adhering to an alkaline-forming, antioxidant-rich, sugar-free diet. You can learn more about his work here: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qYXNvbmxpbmNvbG5qZWZmZXJzLmNvbS93ZWxsbmVzc2NvYWNoaW5nLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;wellness coaching&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>