<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ff77a5a58e951853e1925fb3cb11ff84">			&lt;p&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.surviving-hairloss.com%2Fimages%2Fshaved_head_thumb.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.surviving-hairloss.com/images/shaved_head_thumb.jpg&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Shaving a bald head can be done quite briskly, if you get it down and possess patience, you can profit from it. Because a bald head is in vogue today, you might benefit from it if you begin with a good shave. Nevertheless this was not  always fashionable, as a bald head was merely accepted in grieving for a loved one, and it was thought of a symbol of unhappiness, tremendous loss. Nevertheless time has changed.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Also bald heads are very popular for a reason, since countless women love the look and feeling of a shaved head. This is particularly trendy with those  losing their hair, since it can camouflage  thinning hair, while it is not rare  , for those with full heads of hair, and simply want to participate in the trend  . So permit us start with some quick aproaches to correctly shave your head bald.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Fisrtly, cut your hair close with a pair of clippers, and adjust the gauge so to provide you with as close  as achievable. That is not as hard as you may  think, although if you are experiencing difficulty with the clippers, it might be best if you go to the barber's  for the first attempt  , until you can get it down.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Second a speedy method for shaving  is having a shower to wet and fully moisturize your head and rub on  shaving cream or gel to your  whole scalp  . Remember to massage your head for a minute or two  , thus you can fully loosen all the hair follicles and make them more elastic. This gives you a completely close shave.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Lastly, a quick technique is to shave exactly as you shave your face, shaving with the grain, and attempt to stroke over each area only one time. In addition for the bald head shaving,  apply  even strokes without applying much pressure and that frequently stops nicks and cuts. Learn the bumps, grooves, and other peculiarities of your head, and head shaving will be easy and fluid.When  finished, rinse out good. You may want to use your usual after shave lotion  to your scalp too. Massage your scalp once more and enjoy the new feel. Then merely leave your new bald head alone, and don't, touch your shaved head with dirty hands. This is the surest way to start getting bumps on your head.So do take  care of your fresh shaved head. You'll want a hat and possibly  sunscreen. Your scalp may sunburn in minutes otherwise.When you feel your shaved bald head beginning to itch , that is always a sign that new hair is growing, and so with clean hands, go ahead and feel your head to see if it is time for shaving your head. Remember  the entire scalp is an erogeneous zone after shaving, and so the opposite sex is naturally drawn to it.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p style=&quot;margin: 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px 0.0px; font: 12.0px Helvetica;&quot;&gt;;&lt;span style=&quot;letter-spacing: 0.0px;&quot;&gt;; You can check out my latest website on &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frazorshaversblades.com%2Fbraun-series-7-790cc-pulsonic-electric-shaver%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BBraun"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://razorshaversblades.com/braun-series-7-790cc-pulsonic-electric-shaver/&quot;&gt;;Braun&lt;/a&gt;; Electric Shaver&lt;/a&gt;; and&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frazorshaversblades.com%2Fbraun-razor-shaver-series-7-replacement-parts%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BBraun"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://razorshaversblades.com/braun-razor-shaver-series-7-replacement-parts/&quot;&gt;;Braun&lt;/a&gt;; Razor Replacement Parts&lt;/a&gt;; which reviews and lists the best shaving options to help you look your best.&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>