<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="24">		<conversation id="f1409cb0f8b10cab746764fd6a5ab2b5">			http://www.indicatorwarehouse.com/93608/20-off-weekend-blowout-sale-indicator-warehouse-ninja-trader-indicators/Two incredibly high value deals for you today, both time sensitive. 20% Off This Weekend at Indicator Warehouse, click for coupon code.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2cccd187f1a095fbcb5d94654f542aa4">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/104402691Two incredibly high value deals for you today, both time sensitive. 20% Off This Weekend at Indicator Warehouse, click for coupon code.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8e44037188ba6e96b3225d4f72fa3483">			http://www.supportandresistance.com/Big-Weekend-Edition-123-Tops-and-Bottoms-9-30-12.htmlThe Big Weekend Edition is online including the Learn Trading series 123 Tops and Bottoms video tutorial, a support and resistance chart formation.		</conversation>		<conversation id="aae986e1a2d0191cc992067ce7a625c3">			http://realityfuturestrading.com/learn-to-day-trade-reality-room-is-coming-soon-lock-and-load/Live Trading Room will have live calls, money management, day trading questions answered, instruments - NQ, TF, YM, CL, etc. I'm honored so many people are interested - thank you!		</conversation>		<conversation id="1fd65e3ebd3eb169db6f5730a9ba1fbb">			http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Hp7B4L4j9w8&amp;;The Eagle Trend Trader is a signal generator for the Ninja Trader day trading platform, available at Indicator Warehouse built to detect longer trend moves for day trading futures, forex and stocks.		</conversation>		<conversation id="1ef4b1fb117479609df4fe95917486f">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/104881122The Eagle Trend Trader is a signal generator for the Ninja Trader day trading platform, available at Indicator Warehouse built to detect longer trend moves for day trading futures, forex and stocks.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e1e2d67aeac24483daf429405401af0d">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/104882654How to handle common online trading software security issues for your home office, whether you use day trading software or any other online trading systems.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d58543b62b027907a247c20ae5d17ce0">			http://www.indicatorwarehouse.org/showthread.php?22-Profit-Run-Trading-Pool-Best-GuessWhat a fantastic day in the markets! If you've never seen what trading is supposed to look like check out the video of todays session. If you've ever wondered about the efficiency of trading three systems at once, watch today's video.		</conversation>		<conversation id="24b774bbbaa29d833349f21204dac5ae">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/104916165Learn to Day Trade - many day traders will abandon their day trading indicators and day trading system after only as little as THREE losing trades.		</conversation>		<conversation id="82adeaf9edcaf9708602ead2d9bf9081">			http://www.supportandresistance.com/learn-trading-how-to-avoid-whipsaw-trades/“Whipsaw” is a word that strikes fear into the heart of every futures trader, from experienced veterans to those still trying to learn trading. The smaller your account the more afraid of being whipsawed you are likely to be.		</conversation>		<conversation id="76b0f72337b5e368084773f6ab09c9e9">			http://www.logicalsignals.com/shiny-new-day-trading-tools/I've been busy figuring out new day trading tools. I like simplicity in my life from food to trading. I am not a gadget girl, having used the same broker, charting service and news service forever.		</conversation>		<conversation id="28f778659a90989882c9e7686fced2d1">			http://realityfuturestrading.com/learn-to-day-trade-day-trading-us-bank-holidays/When we first learn to day trade we want to trade all the time; but is it wise to trade on bank holidays such as Columbus Day?		</conversation>		<conversation id="b363fd1dfd5cc7caaaca6a2162240fd8">			http://www.indicatorwarehouse.com/reviews/We just received another positive review for the Diversified Trading System and its Falcon Swing Trader.		</conversation>		<conversation id="3eb49ba2757aab76472c4a4351b67ab5">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/106520015See How Our Indicators Work - Our Live Demonstrations are the best way for you to learn about our day trading software before you buy. Join us to ask questions and interact with our IW Experts.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9570ddee0eca63ea93debb482615aea2">			http://www.indicatorwarehouse.com/affiliate-program/affiliates/Our affiliate program is Very Generous, with as much as $1498.50 payout on just a single sale of The Diversified Trading System (30% of the retail sale). http://www.indicatorwarehouse.com/affiliate-program/affiliates/		</conversation>		<conversation id="64fa03cd9aedda2aff250873e98f12b6">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/107169682If you are going to learn to day trade you must learn how to lose - don't average in. Take your “lump”, move on, next trade!		</conversation>		<conversation id="9ac6fc7e7f4fc00ffa9edaf9a9e6e37a">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/107367247Today's cool deal is Alert on Trendline Hit and comes with the stellar customer service that has made Indicator Warehouse the #1 source for high quality NinjaTrader indicators and day trading systems.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e37f172ed54a3ac9cd0965e5f48a466">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/107389579I had a perfectly good Day Trading Systems signal, entered the trade, and ...stopped out! If you are going to learn to day trade, you need to know that NOT every trade is going to be a winner and revenge trading can lead to disaster.		</conversation>		<conversation id="901119a18c5501f01d74b7471176c7be">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/107610319To learn day trading often requires proven day trading software. Evaluating your day trading system is measured through profits and losses.		</conversation>		<conversation id="3f7ea3d749a8606bbb62ff2c0110ec2f">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/107695376Volume Pressure Plots the Buying and Selling Pressure of Each Bar. This Day Trading Software comes with our usual stellar support!		</conversation>		<conversation id="636366983069dbfdb552fe13ddd8b876">			http://www.onlywire.com/r/108017498Today's Deal of the Day is Trending Volume - Day Trading Indicator determines the Strength of Trends and Warns of Reversals.		</conversation>		<conversation id="5dc0d605a12365070f3d4a3905bc8df0">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.onlywire.com%2Fr%2F108034089"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.onlywire.com/r/108034089&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brokers doing it all for you is a thing of the past, technological advances in day trading software make doing it yourself possible for the average trader.		</conversation>		<conversation id="65ac8d6ad513c2f644b9d593309f806e">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.onlywire.com%2Fr%2F108068011"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.onlywire.com/r/108068011&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What’s the difference between a Weatherman and a Trader? Understanding that difference can make, or cost you, a lot of money.		</conversation>		<conversation id="1ddab336f27404f997f5f2826d395de2">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.onlywire.com%2Fr%2F108069091"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.onlywire.com/r/108069091&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you are day trading with limited funds an easy way to diversify is by using ETFs - a basket of securities that can be bought and sold like a single stock.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>