<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="6dabd37b6bb03273fce5286691a89fc3">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWFscGVubnlzdG9ja3MuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Top Penny Stocks&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Investing in penny stocks is a great way to make money for some sort of speculative investor, but the hard question to answer is: Where can you detect penny stocks to buy today? The problem with penny stocks is that the best ones are often small, under the radar type companies that aren't planning to be featured on CNBC or in the Wall Street Journal. How to find the best penny stocks to purchase takes dedicated work, and also involves looking in areas where others haven't.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So if you're just beginning trying to find penny stocks to buy today, a good place to start is with MSN's commodity screening tool. Technically speaking, a penny stock is any stock under $1, but it can also be used synonymously with ultra-small and also microcap stocks. However, if you use a search filter and discover all the publicly traded stocks under $1, you'll be off to an excellent start.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My guess is, pc other filters you use your search, that you're going to create 100's, if not 1000's of results from searching for stocks under $1. How do you sift through these selections to uncover the best penny stocks to own right now? Unfortunately, that is a more &quot; heavy-duty &quot; question to answer and requires that you utilize a distinct set of criteria which will assist you to determine what stocks is going to be most likely to go up in price.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One word of cautionary to those who don't have learned to choose one penny share from another: be thorough! While some penny stocks are in fact those diamonds in the rough that investor dreams about locating, the majority of low-priced stocks are priced this way for a reason. Not to be able to discern one from the other is a recipe for failure in penny commodity investing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are certainly not totally confident in your ability to pick a winning penny stock from a losing one, my friend Jason Kelly comes with just started up an everyday newsletter in which your dog helps show investors how to consistently find the best penny stocks [http: //www. stock-university. com] to purchase. If you're interested in learning more about how Kelly finds these stocks and see how you can try his newsletter risk-free, then check out [http: //www. stock-university. com].		</conversation>	</conversations></author>