<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="92ace1ef90410d515a15aea9f1ef7534">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oYXJkd2hpc3BlcnMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;Hard Whispers&lt;/a&gt; by Pamela Martin Duarte is a gripping saga of covert government action, global intrigue and modern espionage. It is packed up with full of intensity and suspense, but based on the reality.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The theme of Hard Whispers is incredibly appealing. The story is very fast paced and the scene changes are seamless. The novel starts with the unseen dark side of politics, but gradually takes the readers on an unexpected journey with a brilliant hero who explores global conspiracy theories and modern espionage in a masterful landscape. Every place the protagonist visits is vividly described.  The readers travel the different places across Russia to Italy and on to Spain before coming back to the United States, while experiencing the various social issues and plots of government.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hard Whispers is a thought-provoking fiction plotted around intriguing stories and characters. Pamela &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BhbWVsYW1hcnRpbmR1YXJ0ZS5wb3N0ZXJvdXMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;Martin Duarte&lt;/a&gt;has focused on various social issues, level of conspiracy, government action and global intrigue in Hard Whispers. It is a conspiracy thriller chock full of political intrigue and global espionage.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Pamela Martin has spent many years traveling abroad where she has obtained a multitude of wide range of colleagues and friends. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BpbnRlcmVzdC5jb20vcGFtZWxhbWFydGluZGUv" target="_blank"&gt;Pamela Martin Duarte&lt;/a&gt; has mentioned her experience and espionage about varied aspects during her stint in Europe and Spain in Hard Whispers.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hard Whispers is published by the Greenleaf Book Group in 2011. Pamela Martin is currently working on finishing the Hard Whispers sequel, which will be available globally this summer.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>