<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="6433c006c731beb7a59ba435224e35a8">			There are no secrets to success. It is the consequence of preparation, hard work studying from failure. Examinations could be the method of monitoring and checking the academic performance of students. But the irony is that the word exams create a panic contained in the students.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is normally found that a student answers the questions very confidently in the normal classes but when they are created to appear for some test or exam, and they'll likely get nervous. Sometimes we wonder precisely what is there in the phrase exam that creates so much of fear in a child. Is it a good fear or bad fear? Exam fear can end up proved good if it creates a confident feeling about studies and it's also a bad fear as soon as it creates tension.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Everything in this world has pros and cons so similarly this examinations also do have. Sometimes it is thought that there should not be any exams as they're just very stressful. Moreover it's not necessarily good to rate the performance of the students with the dirt or grades. It is unfair to measure a student only on such basis as what he /she writes in the exams. Some people think that it's very important to have a competition but it's very important that the competition should be in right spirit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Exam should be held inside school but the child really burden with it. Conducting exams makes the teacher teach better because they know just what to educate &amp; when to teach. It also makes the child read and update the lessons which help the students to learn all lessons in a timely manner. This also develops competitive spirit within a student and creates an awareness of responsibility. But it is very important that the students must plan the exams in the interests of learning and performing to your best of their capability. Initially they should not bother for the marks because if they think correctly, they would come pressurized.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read more about Online Entrances Exams of MBA and Banks here,&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2d1aWxsZXJtb2JveTEwMjguZG11c2ljLm5ldC9qb3VybmFsLzE2ODA3MA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Tips for Online Entrance Exams&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2d1aWxsZXJtb2JveTEwMjguZG11c2ljLm5ldC9qb3VybmFsLzE2ODA4Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;;Tips for Online Entrance Exams&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This quality should be instilled inside them at the early stage to obtain flawless results. It has been proved through research that children if provided with tools and strategies, then which will build both emotional abilities and healthy physical habits when preparing for a test and may also help them get over test anxiety. Exam phobia is a self-damaging factor which adversely affects the kids and their performances.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The student is unable to give the maximum yields and weaken their amount power. Parents can also play a superb role in helping children clear away this exam fear. Simply forcing them to read day and night, parents should give their children free time so that they can feel relaxed at enough time of their exams because relaxation is needed at that stage. Moreover, sharing a good time along with the children before their exam helps them clear away this fear and feel at ease. Itâ??s true that brain needs a whole lot of energy to focus on the test for several hours. Eating a hearty and healthy breakfast, including complex carbohydrates and protein to produce their energy last as long as possible also helps them overcome their exam fears.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For similar articles do Visit  [url=] MBA Admissions[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>