<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="fe20f4903f711ccd5df79d6f8f68b6ac">			Every single day is an opportunity to become better than I was yesterday. To look deeply within my self and take a personal inventory without judgement, but with REASON... For all things within and outside of me Desire perfection.. So that is What I will seek in my analysis.. How may I perfect this Body,Mind, Heart and soul. What makes a human Epic? What makes them a legend? How does one Rise to the Top? Let us seek our limits only to find our hidden potentials and fully awakened to this Opportunity.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2ec873af142a0514b079260cdfc4374f">			 &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunities.earthportal.org%2FExist%2Ftopics%2Fview%2F75625%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://communities.earthportal.org/Exist/topics/view/75625/&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;GTVC OVERVIEW
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Introduction:
&lt;br /&gt;;Right now this project has three basic components and a two dimensional fourth. The first three consist of The GaiaTech EcoVillage Collaborative, The Alternative Energy Exchange, and The Game. The Fourth two dimensional aspect is the group which meets every Tuesday. On the microcosmic side is the individuality of each member starting with their individual participation and contribution to the overall effort. This then leads to the first trust and the evolving 8 formula of trusts or master blueprint for the understanding of the eights. Obviously this microcosmic attribute becomes macrocosmic with the first partnership  of an individual holding a first trust and apostille to another of the same.  The eight will be complete when a gateway is opened via trust to the overall project is and will be further enhanced by the GAIA Thinkank component. The following pages outline these projects and any sub projects associated with them.  It will also highlight outside interests or connections associated with the project or subproject being addressed. The third feature will be a listing of potential thinktanks which could be birthed from this discussion and or further integration amongst all participants. This document will thus be ever evolving and a tool for reference.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;GaiaTech EcoVillage Collaborative (GTVC)
&lt;br /&gt;;The GTVC was created to unite efforts across the planet to usher in a new paradigm for society based on the concept of sustainable eco friendly villages and communities. The GTVC is designed to serve as a foundational structure for this effort by serving as an open source environment for exchange between existing groups and efforts to build these communities. Consequently, the GTVC also serves as a central foundational structure from which to introduce other perceived components of this coming new paradigm. These other components are associated with the other projects which will be mentioned that are linked to the GTVC . The common denominator is the source of them all. The ideology is that everything is full circle and once publicly released becomes open sourced. The original source is already pursuing the next highest frequency or wave of development and thus any fault in that which was previously released will be rendered obsolete well in advance of any organized societal effort to block evolution of the species and emergence/ birthing of the new paradigm.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sub Projects
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The GTVC Document
&lt;br /&gt;;The GTVC document outlines everything that we could find available at the time of writing to educate interested parties regarding what is available publicly to build sustainable eco villages. It also provided hints and insight into other related projects. We are tentatively looking for the second or revised document in late January or early February. It is our intention that this edition of the GTVC will have the added addition of introducing actual physical efforts of the concept. Therefore, the second edition will be much larger and extensive rendering the original obsolete.
&lt;br /&gt;;Technology Team and the Wiki Effort
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Currently Brad has created three wiki sites. The first wiki is a data base for research a kind of footprint or library of material which contributed to the group’s efforts. The second wiki is for the EcoVillages and is conceptually seen as part of the collaborative. The third wiki is for the game. All efforts up to the present via direct contribution or other party observation is intended to be integrated into the game. I titled this project Technology Team because the technical aspect is a vital component to the ultimate success of this project. Currently Brad handles 98% of this himself and getting him assistance in his efforts is essential.  
&lt;br /&gt;;Tennessee Group/Farm/ Pod Project
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is a joint effort with the Tennessee group to place a prototype sustainable, eco friendly pod on Paul’s farm in SC or other location, or multiple. In association with this effort is the joint effort to organize more retreats for educational and unification purposes. A tentative date for the first retreat has been set   as February 10 in South Carolina or Florida. The building of the first pod could presumably take place during the retreat or in early spring at the chosen location.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Farm Project
&lt;br /&gt;;This is the idea of integrating Paul’s farm into a GTVC resource. It could potentially be an eco village with the acquisition of neighboring land. Paul has already started this project with plans for an aquaponic system, herb garden, pod prototype, and Pauwlonia nursery already in planning stages or under development.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other South Carolina Potentialities
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bella Haven Community which is for sale. Approximately, three acres near Spartanburg, SC it has existing buildings, storefront, meeting place in a retreat setting with room for expansion. Site could serve as an eco village working in conjunction with both the farm and Patricia’s idea.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Patricia’s  Idea
&lt;br /&gt;;Patricia is currently involved in a rent to own situation closer to Spartanburg, SC and has expressed the desire to establish an eco village on this property as well. The property is just under two acres in size. There is also an adjacent lot of similar dimensions for sale next to her property and several similar across the street. Taking into consideration the technology available for sustainable food production and other technologies available to meet other survival needs large plots of land are not absolutely necessary. Patricia is close to both the Farm and Bella Haven also.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Conference Calls
&lt;br /&gt;;We have been and will continue to host Tuesday and Wednesday night conference calls to share news, information, and experiences regarding all projects, research, and new data.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;GAIA Thinktanks
&lt;br /&gt;;This concept will be addressed in full at the end of this document
&lt;br /&gt;;Connections:
&lt;br /&gt;;Light of Life Society, Global Power Productions, Made by Kids Foundation, “Plan It,
&lt;br /&gt;;Plant It, Planet”, Worldwide Developer’s Foundation, Chocola True Organic Oasis,
&lt;br /&gt;;Health and Wellness Mastermind (Tennessee group), One Community.org, Peace Portal, Dr Lenny, Ultimate Water Inc, Turner Domes, Living Tree Homes, Eco House, Free Digital University, Green Society eco Built Systems, Bio Domes, Pacific Domes, Microorganisms, Earthstar Project, Project Agape (Ecuador), Dr Walter Urban (Costa Rica Project), Technologies of Harmony, Panama Canal Project (Melinda), Plarr House HumanHavens.com, The Thrive Movement, The Greening Evolution, The Venus Project, Humanity Healing, Prosperity Projects.org, Golden Age Investors, The Love Foundation/ The Orion Project, Green Planet Paradise, Global Wireless Internet, Oniya Ile, Paradise Organics, AES Aquarius EcoSystems Inc
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;AEE (Alternative Energy Exchange)
&lt;br /&gt;;The AEE is the idea of a versatile basket of currencies designed to free those who participate from the current enslaving system. The general underlying goal of AEE is to make others aware of the wealth, abundance, and prosperitywithin all of us. The goal is to evolve AEE in steps in conjunction with the other projects. AEE is intricately linked to each project it is all full circle. The ultimate goal is for the species to evolve making the need for currencies obsolete.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SITWALL ( Step in TIME with a Life Line)
&lt;br /&gt;;SITWALL is a global timebank and is the first phase of the AEE. Time is the only common denominator that we all share equally. SITWALL is not the cure all to the commerce/economic situation and it is not intended to be. SITWALL serves as a gateway from GTVC , AEE, and the game to the public. The simple shift in energy by participating in the timebank enhances everything else we collectively work on. It also provides a tool to reward the efforts of those who participate in this effort.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Voucher/Checques
&lt;br /&gt;;This concept has just come into our awareness; therefore, this section will be expanded upon in the future.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Paulownia Trust
&lt;br /&gt;;Aspect of AEE which serves as a gateway for alternative system based projects to interact with modern day economic systems. This is still being developed.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pauwlonia Trust   
&lt;br /&gt;;An alternative aspect of the AEE which is inclusive of a basket of currencies. Includes the seed bank concept, as well as, 8 specific funds to fund the various projects from an alternative system.
&lt;br /&gt;;Connections:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The recent launch of SITWALL has opened the door for various groups to start exploring the alternative exchange of Timebanking. The Golden Seekers group has been the most active. We should have more developments to share regarding this topic in the near future.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Game
&lt;br /&gt;;The Game is a project to create a virtual reality game which will bridge the generation gaps and unify people from all ages to usher in a new paradigm. The game will be a virtual lab and education center all inclusive of what we now experience as reality and what we can potentially realize. All data from all other projects will be integrated into the game. The game already has some very unique components to it which will be revealed as we get closer to testing it.
&lt;br /&gt;;Connections:
&lt;br /&gt;;Phoenix Voyageur
&lt;br /&gt;;Dr Lenny’s Existence
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8 Cell Trust / Blueprint
&lt;br /&gt;;This is the continued effort to take what has been learned from the eights into a formula which is balanced with Nature. This project works independently amongst the participants but also meets on Wednesdays to share progress and study Trustsfor use within the blueprint being created.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;GAIA Thinktanks
&lt;br /&gt;;The ideology behind the GAIA Thinktanks is multi faceted. First creating thinktanks to address specific ideas and issues or tests specific ideas can be beneficial to all the existing projects. Second it provides another data input source for the game involving living input. Third it provides a means of activity for people to get involved and be rewarded for their efforts through the AEE. Thinktanks can take all type of forms. They can consists of 2,4, or 8 people. There can be more than one thinktank for the same purpose. There is no preset time set for their existence in other words a thinktank could meet once and then dissolve. An example of a thinktank would be specific members from the 8 Cell/ Blueprint project could meet to address specific details regarding a particular type of trust arrangement and then bring their findings back to the main group. In forming a thinktank expectations could be established in advance for instance a written summary of the thinktank activity or even call recordings of the thinktank activities as qualifier for recognition of effort by the AEE.  As thinktanks are created they will be added to this document.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>