<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="7f4a8af5cf3c31eabeef48d8da8335fd">			I was not able to believe that anything of quality will be released and I thought that whole concept was merely takes a simple marketing trick (attaching a world famous name to a brand of earbuds to aid them sell). I have recently come to believe another. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Beats product tier by Dr. Dre has several kinds of headphones. There are any professional studio headphones - the Beats Studio. The Beats Solo is a cheaper alternative to that Solo. While the Beats Solo won't offer the same audio quality being the Beats Studio, it should match the average consumer. This article will center on the Beats Tour - the earbud alternative within the Beats by Dr. Dre production. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Beats Tour has the standard 20hz to 20, 000 khz regularity response. 20hz seems a bit high for a earbud that claims to be a &quot;good reproduction of hip bone hop&quot;. Generally the lower value more suitable the bass. From experience 14hz will be optimal value. However, the Beats Tour earbuds receive an impressive driver design. As quoted out of your Tour's feature list: &quot;Large, high-efficiency drivers can help you crank it up and enjoy loud play without sound-wrecking distortion. &quot; Driver size is probably the most important aspects to take into account when buying earbuds (especially concentrating on a good bass response). Customer happiness small size, earbuds often have mediocre drivers. The Head to earbuds claim large individuals, and based on the favorable customer response, it seems the large drivers size overcompensates for the mediocre occurrence response. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These earbuds come with &quot;The World's First Tangle-Free Cable&quot;. While this may occasionally not seem as a necessary issue at first, simply because use earbuds you see the annoyance of twisted cords. The Beats Tour earbuds have got a flat cable, thus comfortably eliminating that issue. Previously there initially were issues with the earbud wire breaking. The fact that this earbud cable breaks, outweighs the key benefits of a tangle free cable. However, this issue has been resolved and Tour earbuds purchased today, have a new and improved cord that won't break. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The biggest issue of this Beats Tour earbuds is a fit. Even if all the earbuds are great, if for example the fit is bad the particular earbuds are worthless. These earbuds come having several noise isolating earbud idea sizes and types to appeal to everyone. Still, please be aware why these earbud tips may not fit everyone. Customer feedback suggested that for many the earbuds went in &quot;too deep&quot;. However, don't allow that stop you. Whenever you can get a good fit, the Beats Tour earbuds sound phenomenal. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I would highly recommend buying the Beat Tour if you need an entry level top notch earbud. Before purchasing a set Beats Tour earbuds, keep in mind there are two types of Beats Tour earbuds: one with ControlTalk and the other without. ControlTalk allows someone to control your music (pause, next track and volume) and make telephone calls (using the built around microphone). The pair with ControlTalk is $30 in excess of the pair without, so it's your choice whether you believe beneficial ControlTalk brings are representative on the extra price. Either solution, you won't be disappointed while using the quality, sturdiness and stylistic price the Beats Tour wireless earbuds bring. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;dr.dre studio red ,  blue dr dre beats ,  blue dre beats  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thoughts.com%2Fsebastianmck1230%2Fmonster-beats-tour-an-earbud-review"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.thoughts.com/sebastianmck1230/monster-beats-tour-an-earbud-review&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="6c9c4d81ae2cdafea9c78677f0ffa15c">			However, don't permit that stop you. Provided you can get a good healthy, the Beats Tour earbuds sound phenomenal. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I would highly recommend buying the Beat Tour if you are researching for an entry level high-end earbud. Before purchasing some Beats Tour earbuds, don't forget this there are two sorts of Beats Tour earbuds: one with ControlTalk and another without. ControlTalk allows anyone to control your music (pause, next track and volume) and make phone calls (using the built throughout microphone). The pair with ControlTalk is $30 more than the pair without, so it's your responsibility whether you believe the advantages ControlTalk brings are representative for the extra price. Either method, you won't be disappointed along with the quality, sturdiness and stylistic worth the Beats Tour earbuds bring. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Everyone normally don't think of style in relation to headphones, but the Dr. Dre &quot;Monster Beats&quot; headphones allow you to think twice. But anyone tends to make something that looks excellent, right? How do many perform? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Dr. Dre Enormous Beats Headphones Low-down... &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Colossal Beats Appearance-&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not often implement headphones turn heads, although the sleek design of all the MB's does. The glossy black head band runs seamlessly towards the ear pieces, which are inlaid by having a red &quot;b&quot;. A metal support band is inlaid while in the headband, rings thinly in the ear pieces and also includes deep red accenting. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What To the Sound? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Monster Beats are manufactured through Monster Cable company, to ensure the name is reliable. The headphones contain a noise cancelling feature a growing number of people are giving excellent reviews about online on a website such as Amazon. Your Dr. Dre headphones have got a deep enveloping low last part bass and solid mid and high range sound quality additionally. Many people remark about the fact these headphones can be cranked up to real high volume nevertheless pump out crisp good. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ear cup style and design is being reported effortless to listen to music for extended time frames without discomfort. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another feature of the Monster Beats stands out as the right earphone can be tapped on the exterior and it mutes the particular sound. There's no digging in your own pocket to press mute or pause, just a timely tap. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Accessories for the List Beats- &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are numerous accessories to go combined with Dr. Dre headphones. All of these come in the contemporary black and red wrapping and style to accompany the headphones. Various adapters just for airplanes, in home sound experience, and even a cable by having a built-in microphone for stereo hand held phones, like the iPhone. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Creature Beats headphones are new releases of the Monster, which have been jointly developed by Grammy receiver Dr. Dre and Creature team of audio advisors. Artists and manufacturers have spent hours and hours on fine-tuning and blending melodies for making it precisely how these people hope their followers to learn it. But many of headsets can't unquestionably duplicate the intricacies stated in the studio. Simply place, studios can. With precision-engineered, state-of-the-art loudspeaker produce, driven amplification, not to mention driven disturbance cancellation, you will see melodies the way today's height creative individuals and manufacturers wish you to definitely hear. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;dr dre beats pro detox ,  best earphones ,  detox beats pro  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdecorati.com%2Fforum%2Fthread%2F19685%2Fsomething-about-monster-beats-headphones"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://decorati.com/forum/thread/19685/something-about-monster-beats-headphones&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>