<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a36f1ab21955eaed27e8688f83b58972">			Hi,
&lt;br /&gt;;Every one is knowing that mother importance. all are lucky who is get or getting love of mother. Some are feeling bad luck those no mother. I would like saying that every one is with mother. some are with more mother some are with less mother, but no one, no mother, because if you give love to any one as a son then you will get reply as a mother from every one.so first you do love then hope to love you any one.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;U K Pandey		</conversation>		<conversation id="1b02e5e8618293c8022fb9bc4f8c6f5a">			Hope all are knowing that all are authorized to think and write, what his thinking about any subject. So I am writing our thinking about reservation on promotion of service and on Job. I think this is not good practice of our government. Need to stop this facilities immediately, because due to this facilities peoples are going to handicap. they are depending on reservation and not trying to do fight.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Competition is must for growth, either self, organization or country. Our country not equivalent in USA till now due to reservation system. If reservation not applied by government in earlier then should be our position look different, too much better today.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can be justify with government vs private organization. maximum private organization are growing, but government organizations are in loss every time, because there is no competition, no punishment, you can be do work with your responsibility or not, you should be promote, get increment on time, because you are government employee, and if you are under reservation person then....................................??????  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I think it is necessary to help by government in education and medical to all who is not capable to give better education &amp; medical to his child, without cost filter criteria. And competition should be qualify to join any job, then country can be growth.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;U.K.Pandey		</conversation>	</conversations></author>