<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="dd4d55a96abdacf9e0e1c78094019597">			The observe is drinking water-resistant up to a hundred sixty five ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One more of his more reasonably priced watches is the glamorous Quartz Chronograph Crystal Accent Observe with a distinct acetate bracelet. The clear bracelet and silver-tone bezel also serve as the best backdrop for the double rows of crystals about the bezel. The spherical chronograph dial complements the bling of the bezel with silver-tone accents. The dial has 3 subdials and a date window. The bracelet is 6 inches prolonged. The observe is h2o-resistant to 330 ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Want some coloration all around your wrist? Try the Divertissement Quartz Chronograph Watch in pink. The stainless steel case is held solidly in location by a versatile, long lasting pink rubber strap. Completing the pink look is a pink dial with 3 subdials, a day window and silver-accented fingers and hour markers. The 6-inch rubber strap is secured with a buckle clasp. The view is drinking water-resistant to 165 ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a darker, handsome appear, consider the Quartz Chronograph Bracelet Observe in black resin. The black stainless metal circumstance matches the black resin bracelet. Trying to keep with the coloration scheme, the black bezel encircles a black, spherical chronograph dial established off with silver-tone accents, a few subdials and a date window. The six-inch bracelet has a deployant clasp. The observe is drinking water-resistant to a hundred sixty five toes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will uncover the Traditional Quartz Chronograph Observe with crystal detail has a slightly increased price tag point than the preceding watches. This shimmering splendor features tons of crystal specifics on the white colored strap and the champagne dial. The spherical gold-tone stainless steel circumstance is surrounded by crystals. The dial functions 3 subdials, a day window and gold-tone Arabic numerals and markers. The six-inch white colored plastic strap attributes crystals working its length. The observe is drinking water-resistant to 330 toes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a different look, examine out the Quartz Chronograph White colored Dial View. What sets it apart is the linking ceramic strap - more like a allure bracelet backlink than the bracelets on other Kors' watches. Created in all white, the white dial has 3 subdials and a day window. The ceramic bracelet steps 6 inches. The view is water-resistant to one hundred sixty five ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Include a touch of color to a white watch with the Quartz Chronograph Watch with rose gold-tone crystal accents. The eyes jump from the white colored ceramic bracelet and circumstance to the rose gold-tone bezel encrusted with crystals. The round chronograph dial retains to the coloration scheme with rose-gold-tone accents alongside with its three subdials and date window. The ceramic bracelet measures 6 inches. The observe is drinking water-resistant to a hundred sixty five ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Michael Kors did not forget about male customers. He has also designed watches for men:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The sophisticated Quartz Chronograph Two-tone Stainless Steel Watch is a elegance. It will definitely exceed your expectations in that it appears like it value a good deal a lot more than it does.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51c2FtaWNoYWVsa29yc291dGxldHMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;michael kors watches&lt;/a&gt;;When it comes to fashionable watches, the Michael Kors line for ladies boasts some beautiful designs ranging from common to contemporary.		</conversation>		<conversation id="671dea277dc744427de8ed06aaa0e1b7">			It adds an component of design to any event the wearer chooses and will absolutely garner several compliments for individuals who are appreciating it on the wrist.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Michael Kors is a leader in the trend sector with his accent line offering his products to the marketplace designed with the greatest quality standards at inexpensive rates. He is aware what will catch the eye of his marketplace and what will be flattering for most women to put on. The flexibility of this observe is great it can be the 1 piece you use all summer time lengthy. When it arrives to white ceramic women's watches, Michael Kors can make some of the best in the industry. It will surely exceed your expectations in that it seems like it value a whole lot a lot more than it does.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51c2FtaWNoYWVsa29yc291dGxldHMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;michael kors outlet&lt;/a&gt;;When it will come to elegant watches, the Michael Kors line for women boasts some stunning designs ranging from basic to up to date. Best for ladies who want to adorn their wrists in functional fashion, Michael Kors watches are an important accent that will add pizzazz to any outfit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ladies who favor classically tailored variations of attire and jewellery have a vast variety of Michael Kors watches to select from that in shape this aesthetic. One these kinds of time piece is the Michael Kors Women's Classic Quartz Acetate Bracelet Observe. With a silver tone dial that includes Japanese Quartz movement, this look at stuns with a gorgeous acetate bracelet that attaches with a jewelry clasp. Easy in style, but nevertheless eye-catching, the Classic Quartz Acetate Bracelet view also has mineral crystal, a press / pull crown and is h2o resistant to fifty meters.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another timelessly sophisticated type from the Michael Kors Assortment is the Michael Kors Women's Basic Japanese Quartz Chronograph Mother-of-Pearl Dial Bracelet Watch. With a stainless metal scenario and bracelet and a gorgeous mother-of-pearl dial with chronograph subdials, this observe moyen gorgeous aesthetics with the precise timekeeping of Japanese quartz movement. The watch also has a date window among the four:00 and 5:00, mineral crystal and a drive / pull crown. H2o resistant to 100 meters, the Classic Japanese Quartz Chronograph Mother-of-Pearl Dial Bracelet Watch will complement any attire.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In retaining true to the concept of basic simplicity, Michael Kors' Women's Quartz Rectangular Situation Brown Leather Strap View is a ideal complement to casual and enterprise attire with its rectangular silver-tone stainless steel case juxtaposed by a soft brown leather-based strap. The experience of this look at is marked with Arabic numerals at 3:00, six:00, 9:00 and twelve:00, and the silver-tone dial is powered by Japanese Quartz motion. Rounding out the particulars of this timepiece, the Women's Quartz Rectangular Case Brown Leather Strap View closes with a buckle clasp and functions a mineral crystal and a thrust / pull crown. Even though soaking the gorgeous leather-based strap is not highly recommended, this watch is water resistant to 50 meters.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girls who want a very little bling extra to a classically type watch will adore the Michael Kors Women's Quartz Chronograph Crystal Accent White colored Ceramic Bracelet Look at. Stylish and glamorous, this timepiece attributes a stainless steel case and again paired with a white colored ceramic bracelet that closes with a deployment clasp. The spherical chronograph dial is studded with silver-tone accents and has 3 subdials and Arabic numerals.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>