<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f447bc58bbd59069e9a88483a8c61834">			Losing weight is only as challenging as you make it out to be. Weight loss takes sustained effort over time, but the benefits are definitely worth it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Embarrassing as it may be, take a &quot;;before&quot;; picture as you begin your weight loss program. Once you reach a goal, you can look at the old picture and see just how far you've come. This will give you motivation to continue with your healthy choices. Many people are likely to find that your photos are an excellent inspiration to start their own weight loss programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A coastal jog is a good way to shed the pounds. You'll get a better workout by running on the beach, as opposed to running on pavement or grass, because sand provides resistance to your stride.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you've started to see weight loss results, start throwing away the clothes that are now the wrong size for your new body. This can help you to realize the progress that you have made, and serve as inspiration for your future weight loss. Seeing how many sizes you have come down will make you feel great about yourself and can help keep you motivated.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don't give in to cravings for unhealthy food. It can often be hard to resist the temptations. Instead of giving into a craving, try to distract yourself or do something to keep you occupied. Brushing your teeth and gargling with mouthwash can help deter you from giving into your cravings. Clean an old drain or watch a gory film; this may suppress your appetite.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consuming whole grains is essential if you are trying to lose weight. You should talk to your dietician on which type of whole grains you should choose or you can research them on your own. Skip buying any product that includes the words refined or enriched. You will find buying whole-grain products is not difficult with a little research. When their product includes whole grains, most manufacturers are eager to advertise the fact.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You might want to begin a food diary to control the amount of calories you consume. When you write down everything you are putting into your mouth, you will quickly be able to spot any mistakes you are making. Keeping a diary will make you more aware of what you eat and help you reduce your calorie count.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reduce your intake of drinks that are high in sugar and stay away from fried foods. Fast foods should be avoided when trying to lose weight. They are usually highly processed and have a higher fat content than nearly any homemade food. You should lower or eliminate sugary sodas from your diet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By letting your child be obese, this increases their risk of being overweight throughout the rest of their life as well. This is not something any parent wants to encourage. The best time to teach people about good nutrition is when they are young. Engage your child by having them read the nutrition labels on food, and explain to them what certain things mean. You can make family food choices and meal planning a cooperative effort with your children. As they grow into healthy young adults, they will appreciate your efforts and concerns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make your meat leaner for weight loss. Instead of using rich cream sauces or sweet barbecue and steak sauces, try a simple salsa or a rich chutney. This will prevent the meat from becoming too dry, and tasting bland. Chutneys are sweet and fruity and add excellent flavor to your protein.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Everybody says you should drink lots of water to help you lose weight. One good tip to note that a lot of people don't know is that drinking cold water helps boost your metabolism. WHen you drink water that cold, you are forcing your body to raise your temperature, which in turn increases your metabolism.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In weight loss, what you eat is most important. But the time of day you eat also matters. Generally, if you eat light at night you will be hungry in the morning, which then drives you to eat a bigger breakfast. Your first meal of the day should be your largest; that way it takes less to be satisfied by later meals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These methods demonstrate that weight loss can be achieved by researching. Weight loss is difficult for a lot of people, but educating yourself and working hard at it can help you shed those pounds quickly. As long as you have the commitment to get to work and use these tips, you will see positive improvements.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4zLWRheS1kaWV0cy5vcmc_" target="_blank"&gt;learn how to lose fat&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovLzMtZGF5LWRpZXRzLm9yZy9jYXRlZ29yeS9kaWV0aW5nLXRpcHMv" target="_blank"&gt;discover 3 day diets&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovLzMtZGF5LWRpZXRzLm9yZy9kaWV0aW5nLXRpcHMvZGlldC1mb29kLWZvci1wcmVnbmFudC13b21lbi8_" target="_blank"&gt;learn dieting&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5c3273e681771ec2e2c8e16798e32df9">			There are so many options and variables involved in losing weight that you can become discouraged before you begin. It is important to calmly focus on clearly delineated goals. The tips you will find below will get you started in the right direction.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Attempt to remove milk or any milk products from your diet and look for any effect that translates into your weight. Sometimes people who are lactose intolerant or have a milk allergy do not realize they have this problem. This can cause weight gain and bloating with no apparent cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are trying to lose weight, blue should become your favorite color. Blue has been known to suppress the appetite. To see the effect of this, try having blue items at your table. Warmer tones of yellow and red should be avoided in the kitchen since they can make you hungry. Studies show that visual cues are very effective in controlling what we eat. It's important to remember this advice when fixing plates or deciding on an outfit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're trying to practice healthy nutrition, plan meals in advance. With this schedule, it will keep you from being tempted to eat things you shouldn't. Be sure to stick to your meal plans. One of the most common mistakes people make is substituting fast food in favor of healthy alternatives. If you cook your own meal, you not only provide yourself with food that is healthier, but you also burn calories in the process.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be strong when cravings strike. This isn't always easy. If you can, use your will power to restrain yourself from eating snacks. Giving your teeth a quick brushing may help reduce your appetite. You can also kill your appetite by grossing yourself out and watching a horror movie.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stay away from most products that promise quick weight loss. In the unlikely event that they actually worked, it would probably only be for the first few pounds with no follow up strategy for keeping them off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Muscle is super-efficient at burning calories, while fat is really bad at doing so. When you build muscle, it helps you drop the pounds easier. Engaging in strength training exercises between two and five times each week will help you build your muscles and reduce your level of fat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Try eating a larger meals at home prior to going to parties and events when on a diet. This will keep you from overindulging in snacks, party food and cake at the event. When you are there, sip on wine, or avoid alcohol all together instead of drinking beer or sugary mixed drinks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Always talk to a professional before trying any diet pills. If you're already on medication or have chronic health problems, diet pills can have very adverse effects. Before beginning any diet pills, consult with your doctor.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You tend to eat less by using smaller plate. There have been studies done that show that people will most likely eat whatever size portion is set in front of them. Using a smaller plate is a good way to trick your body into accepting smaller portions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green tea can aid in weight loss and boost the metabolism. Try drinking it with honey or a natural sweetener to liven it up. Black tea also has healthy ingredients. The antioxidants in green tea boost the body's immune system and help flush toxins from the system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are going to a party, you should eat a big meal before leaving your home. You will be less tempted to gorge on fattening party foods if you arrive satiated. Mixed drinks or beer can be replaced with wine!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will see the best results from your weight loss plan, if you are completely comfortable with it, so be sure to do your own research. These tips are just some of the things you can do to make your weight loss program just what you want. There is no instant gratification when it comes to fitness, but the right exercise plan can keep you healthy and fit your whole life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4zLWRheS1kaWV0cy5vcmc_" target="_blank"&gt;learn how to lose fat&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovLzMtZGF5LWRpZXRzLm9yZy9jYXRlZ29yeS9kaWV0aW5nLXRpcHMv" target="_blank"&gt;learn dieting&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovLzMtZGF5LWRpZXRzLm9yZy9kaWV0aW5nLXRpcHMvZGlldC1mb29kLWZvci1wcmVnbmFudC13b21lbi8_" target="_blank"&gt;learn dieting&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>