<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2b5d779ccb5761c2fa02691f7f00d02f">			As you might have learned producing beats could be very over priced at the moment. To make real top quality tracks you need to spend a large amount of money in a professional studio and all the essential tools, otherwise the results could possibly be very poor. Nevertheless, it's very clear that not everyone can afford such things, so what exactly should most people do then?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's becoming more and more popular nowadays to use a beat making software. It is an easy application that may be downloaded from the Net to your personal computer and installed in few minutes. Some of them are overpriced (not as over priced as a studio obviously) but commonly speaking you may get very decent ones for under $40.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The issue is that many these beat maker computer programs are extremely bad quality and if you try and make your own music beats with them, you'll be amazed how terrible the audio is and it just doesn't sound appropriate. This is when things begin to get tough, because if you'd like to make rap music, but do not have the tools, then its game over?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sick beats may be made with the assist of personal computer applications, and I've proof of that. A couple of months ago I was in the same position as you're now: trying to find a decent software that will help me create some really cool beats.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The application I got addicted to considering that then is named DUBturbo, and I can guarantee that this may be your last software to get prior to you start making your own music. The feature list is pretty amazing: an octave keyboard, track sequencer, drum machine, pre-created beat kits and lots much more are included within the standard package! Basically it's a full digital sound recording workstation, installed on your laptop. Awesome!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is even better is you can check it out for sixty days following the purchase, and if you continue to do dislike it, you may get your money back, as it comes with one hundred percent moneyback guarantee. It can be an everyone wins scenario, and I really endorse Dub Turbo to any person interested in making beats on the internet, simply because it's just amazing!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're ready to start your music career right now, click below!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>