<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="e98d00f1fe4061653b81d5a356ac8b5a">			If Web 1.0 is described because the read write Web,  Web 2.0  described as the era of mashability, information sharing and social networking than it is probably safe to assume at this point that web 3.0 will be about mobile applications. If we have discovered everything from these companies that had been successful throughout Web 1.0 is that shifting to the new version is a bit like brain cancer . It’s a story listened to again and again, failing to evolve. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The transition period as proved again and again to be too hard as companies fail to adapt. Yahoo just can’t appear to get things together again. Google has a list of failures  longer than Magic Johnson’s arm. I am not likely to even talk about how extremely long the move into social networking took.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And Facebook seem to resist the whole mobile app movement area in I mean they took forever and when they finally got on board they develop something that was sort of, lame. The freelance marketplace are already showing these signs. Elance, Odesk yet others are quickly being replaced by specialized marketplaces like Weblance which are focused on mobile apps. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbS9yZWdpc3RyYXRpb24v" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire designers or developers&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbS93ZWJzaXRlX21hcmtldGluZy9nb29kLWJ5ZS15YWhvby1nb29nbGUtYW5kLWZhY2Vib29rLWhlcmUtY29tZS1tb2JpbGUtYXBwcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire designers or developers&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire web designers&lt;/a&gt;; is just about building sites will nilly but having a strategy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When we look at Moore's law, we know that technology will probably be changing faster and faster.  And whether your Yahoo, Google, Facebook the storyline seems to be the same over and over. They just continue with the strategy that was set despite the change of technologies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For me personally, I love the speed of technology. Checking up on the newest idea and the thousands of times you said to yourself, why didn’t I think of that! Every day someone is rising and someone is falling. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As technology increases pace it's becoming more and more difficult to keep up. Today, situations are quite manageable. When you’re looking forward to develop your next application, keep in mind that you must have a solid mobile strategy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not because working and even mobile lab sometime down the road, but because you're going to need it today.		</conversation>		<conversation id="bbfaa18aa82c7c398c2d5e4ea8a2b01b">			Web 1.0 was read write Web, and Web 2.0 was information sharing and social media, but Web 3.0 is actually clearly all about mobile apps.  When we look at businesses that needed to transition from Web 1.0 to Web 2 . 0.0 we often observe major deaths of the big boys.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You know the whole bit about if we don't learn from history are doomed to repeat it… I got up. Well I've got a tendency to want to use this towards the whole Web 1.0 Web 2 . 0.0 transition. I mean really, consider all of the giants that fell during that transition.  Look at how long it took Google to get involved with social media. I guess the question is could it be not enough too late? Yahoo well Yahoo just can't appear to get it together.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I look at the Facebook mobile app, it's crap! The freelance marketplace happen to be showing these signs. Elance, Odesk and others are quickly being replaced by specialized marketplaces like Weblance which are centered on mobile apps. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbS9yZWdpc3RyYXRpb24v" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire designers or developers&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire designers or developers&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbS93ZWJzaXRlX21hcmtldGluZy9nb29kLWJ5ZS15YWhvby1nb29nbGUtYW5kLWZhY2Vib29rLWhlcmUtY29tZS1tb2JpbGUtYXBwcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire web developers&lt;/a&gt;; is simply about building sites will nilly but using a strategy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When we take a look at Moore's law, we all know that technology will probably be changing faster and faster.  And whether your Yahoo, Google, Facebook the storyline seems to be the same over and over. They simply continue with the strategy that was set despite the change of technologies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the things I love about the technology space is how quickly things move, shift and change. It’s nearly the same as a soap opera.  Checking up on the newest idea and the thousands of times you said to yourself, why didn’t I think of that! Every day someone is rising and someone is falling. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As technology increases pace it's becoming more and more difficult to keep up.  Whatever application we believe about building today, it must include a mobile app strategy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not because working and even mobile lab sometime down the road, but because you're going to need it today.		</conversation>		<conversation id="616f31f3562617aaaebf49ddbf727c35">			Web 1.0 was read write Web, and Web 2 . 0.0 was information sharing and social media, however Web 3.0 is actually obviously about mobile apps. If we have discovered anything from these businesses that had been successful in Web 1.0 is the fact that shifting towards the new version is a bit like brain cancer . It’s a story heard again and again, failing to evolve. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The transition period as proved again and again to become too hard as companies fail to adapt. Yahoo just can’t appear to get things back together. Google lists failures  longer than Magic Johnson’s arm. I'm not likely to even talk about how extremely long the transfer to social networking took.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And Facebook seem to resist the entire mobile app movement area in I mean they took forever and when they finally got on board they develop something that was sort of, lame. The freelance marketplace happen to be showing these signs. Elance, Odesk and others are quickly being replaced by specialized marketplaces like Weblance which are centered on mobile apps. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbS9yZWdpc3RyYXRpb24v" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire web developers&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbS93ZWJzaXRlX21hcmtldGluZy9nb29kLWJ5ZS15YWhvby1nb29nbGUtYW5kLWZhY2Vib29rLWhlcmUtY29tZS1tb2JpbGUtYXBwcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire designers or developers&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYmxhbmNlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Hire designers or developers&lt;/a&gt;; is just about building sites will nilly but having a strategy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whenever we look at Moore's law, we know that technology is going to be changing faster and faster.  And whether your Yahoo, Google, Facebook the story seems to be the same over and over. They just continue with the strategy that was set despite the change of technologies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;love technologies just like a soap opera always shifting and changing. Checking up on the newest idea and the thousands of times you said to yourself, why didn’t I think of that! Every single day someone is rising and someone is falling. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As technology increases pace it's becoming more and more difficult to keep up. Today, situations are quite manageable. When you’re looking forward to develop your next application, keep in mind that you must have a solid mobile strategy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If we don't start on a mobile app strategy and our products and services today, it will be too late		</conversation>	</conversations></author>