<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3935481699b6a0e71433ee573cea1494">			This leaves no uncertainty that anti virus protection is crucial and cannot really be overlooked. Just a fantastic anti-virus software could achieve this function with the perfection needed. It's also imperative to notice that the latest operating-system like MS Windows 7 call for programs which are suitable for them if safeguard is to be achieved. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additionally, it is imperative to choose reliable programs that provide the most effective feasible safety. You need to pick an antivirus software very carefully. Specialists and online review forums can always provide the all-important specifics to assist in choice of best antivirus protection. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a long time now, Norton has stayed an innovator in supply of web security alternative. The 2012 edition of Norton net security is wide-ranging and has lived up to good status Norton has acquired in the past. The top Norton web security software offers cost-effective security against damaging infections including malwares and worms. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Just to reiterate, Norton is among the best antivirus protection programs within the market place for Windows 7 operating system which is the most recent in the line of MS Windows. The recent edition of Norton antivirus performs perfectly if you download music, browse the internet, play on-line games or do any kind of other computer function. The software makes routine backdrop checks as the equipment operates. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can get the license for Norton 2012 (basic edition) for just $fifty for one year and $75 for a couple of years. The standard anti-virus contains the subsequent characteristics in addition to totally free tech support:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Antivirus&lt;br /&gt;;• Antispyware&lt;br /&gt;;• Phishing protection&lt;br /&gt;;• Rootkit protection&lt;br /&gt;;• Worm protection&lt;br /&gt;;• Internet browser safety&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Norton 2012 (Net security release) can be acquired for $seventy for just one year and $one hundred fifteen for two years. This includes following attributes in addition to absolutely free technical support:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Antivirus&lt;br /&gt;;• Anti-spyware&lt;br /&gt;;• Phishing safety&lt;br /&gt;;• Rootkit safety&lt;br /&gt;;• Worm defense&lt;br /&gt;;• Antispam&lt;br /&gt;;• Network maps as well as checking&lt;br /&gt;;• Online identification defense&lt;br /&gt;;• Parental controls management&lt;br /&gt;;• Smart firewall program&lt;br /&gt;;• Social networking protection&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thirdly, the Norton 360 (All in one  protection version) can be obtained for $ eighty for a single year and $one hundred thirty five for two years. This specific release is thorough and involves following options together with totally free technical support:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Antivirus&lt;br /&gt;;• Anti-spyware&lt;br /&gt;;• Anti-rootkit&lt;br /&gt;;• Antiphishing&lt;br /&gt;;• Smart Firewall&lt;br /&gt;;• Networking Mapping &amp; Monitoring&lt;br /&gt;;• Special Norton Insight&lt;br /&gt;;• Brand new Norton company Control Center&lt;br /&gt;;• Fresh Norton company SafeWeb Social Media Protection&lt;br /&gt;;• New Proactive performance alerts&lt;br /&gt;;• New Norton Insight Software Ratings&lt;br /&gt;;• Improved Computer Tuneup&lt;br /&gt;;• Exclusive Norton Id Safe&lt;br /&gt;;• Improved Parent controls administration&lt;br /&gt;;• Improved SONAR™ 3 Behavioral Protection&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For personal customers, standard version of Norton company's  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.best-antivirus-protection.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.best-antivirus-protection.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  perform the objective. The Al in one  edition is great for firms that need detailed security of their files.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When making the ideal choice of anti-virus for utilization in MS Windows 7, is not simple because of the a lot of different choices. It's for that reason best to take some time, and make sure that only the finest program is selected. The normal brands give you a good place to get started. In addition, it is vital to see the various online reviews. They help a lot for making knowledgeable decisions. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.best-antivirus-protection.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.best-antivirus-protection.com/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>