<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="4c9ccb22fcc1b8494322f147c9893695">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;Top 10 Reasons Why YOU Should Buy mark. Products!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10. Ok, I'll say it - I am trying to win a trip from mark. But seriously, I've been selling mark. products for almost 6 years, and I wouldn't sell something I don't like! mark. is awesome! Read on, my friends...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. You can shop online through my mark store, and get your makeup delivered right to your door. So easy! Plus, most of the time, mark. offers free shipping codes online, so your order will ship for no extra cost. (ask me for details)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. If you shop online, not only can you pay with a credit card, but mark. also is setup to allow payment through PayPal! (Seriously, could this ordering thing be any easier&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. Multi-task. Weekender. Bag. Enough said. If you don't know what it is.....ask me!!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. Said bag above is only $35!!!!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. mark. carries beauty, fashion, jewelry, and accessories. It should be your first choice for affordable on-trend seasonal items, as well as core makeup!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Eyeshadows: $4.50, Powder: $8.00, hook-up Lip Gloss: $5.50, Mascara: $6.50. I could keep going with these incredible prices....
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. mark. has markgirl.com, where you can see makeup tutorials, read about reps and about becoming a rep, as well as celebrity blogs....all for FREE! (check it out - &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.markgirl.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.markgirl.com&lt;/a&gt;;)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. There are over 5,000 ways to customize a mark. hook-up. And any one hookup will cost you just $11 (plus you will get a free connector). Is that awesome or what?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. mark. truly is high quality makeup at an extremely affordable price, and I stand by it 100%.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SHOP TODAY! &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mymarkstore.com%2Ftiffanythomas2284"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.mymarkstore.com/tiffanythomas2284&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>