<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="dbc3f8982504f225856f1ea652675f65">			The actual question, of course, is the place may be the picture? The image is beautiful. My last television became a Pioneer Kuro 6020, and thus my look at the VT50 is actually an assessment of the two sets.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BhbmFzb25pY3ZpZXJhdGNwNjV2dDUwYmVzdHByaWNlLmJsb2dzcG90LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Panasonic VIERA TC-P50GT50 Best Price&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BhbmFzb25pY3ZpZXJhdGNwNTBndDUwYmVzdHByaWNlLmJsb2dzcG90LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Panasonic VIERA TC-P50GT50 Best Price&lt;/a&gt;; I cannot A/B them side-by-side because the Kuro stayed having a house I just sold (the client smartly insisted on keeping the Kuro within his full-price offer on the house, and so i couldn't say no), but, working off memory, I'm sure the VT50 compares favorably fot it most legendary of tv sets. Would it match the Kuro's picture? Honestly, I don't think I'm able to say and also. There were just something very special around the Kuro's black levels, its detail, its ability to both present a natural picture that also had &quot;pop.&quot; The VT50 comes not far from this, and i also would say it's about 95% there. The Panasonic's blacks are great, plus the colors are vibrant and natural. Echoing a previous review during this page, Certainly a bright room does present a glare challenge just for this TV, and my room unfortunately places a wall of windows facing the tv screen. I am going to maintain your VT50, however, because I mainly watch TV at night and that i just hate LED/LCD televisions (it is every bit a personal preference). I think you can believe the hype the VT50 provides greatest all around picture of 2012. The 3D picture is also very good.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The extras within the TV all seem nice, but I didn't choose the Television for the kids, therefore i haven't explored them also much. Recption menus and settings are very intuitive and easy to navigate and control. Panasonic did a very good job using this type of Television.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>