<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="ab369ed21d615b33145f5de5f9a1a56e">			Nike sure likes making Kobe basketball shoes. They continue to drop not only Kobe's signature shoe line, but drop it in record number of colorways. Every week seems to bring a new colorway of the Kobe VI. From the &amp;amp;quot;Grinch&amp;amp;quot; that started the year off, to the most recent news of a new 3D colorway(the second one this year if you are counting, and I am), it looks like there is no end in sight for the colorways to stop hitting the streets. Is this a good thing? Are you kidding me? This is a great thing. Including the NikeID option that this shoe can be done up in, there is absolutely no way there could possibly be too many colorways of the Kobe VI.Never has a basketball shoe been produced with such creativity and high performance capability. Let's start with the look. This shoe looks like it is covered in snakeskin! This shoe was made for the Black Mamba himself! The snake-textured synthetic upper is moldable and is one of the most, if not the most, ingenious uppers to ever be used. As with Kobe releases in the past, Flywire construction is used to create a durable, lightweight fit. The cushioning is very responsive due to the Zoom Air unit in the heel portion of the sole. The sockliner of the shoe conforms and molds to an individual's specific foot shape. The heel cup was constucted in a slimmer fashion than that of the Kobe V as to provide for a better fit. Kobe's shield logo appears on the tongue and outsole. All of these features create the kind of high perrfomance low-cut basketball shoe that has never been seen before. We are talking cutting edge technology people!One of the most exciting aspects of the Nike Zoom Kobe line is the manner in which all of the different colorways are being referred to. For the most part, all of these colorways are named. There is a theme here. The &amp;amp;quot;Chaos&amp;amp;quot; edition features a mixture of purple, neon green and solar red in representing the Joker from the Batman movies. Epic! The &amp;amp;quot;Grinch&amp;amp;quot; released this past Christmas was predominately bright candy apple green with yellow accents and red laces. Sweet! The &amp;amp;quot;Orange County&amp;amp;quot; consists of three different shades of orange and is meant to depict a sunset over the California ocean. Beautiful! You can even create a camoflouge look in a number of colors over at NikeID. Nice! I could keep going here, but there are too many colorways and themes to count.Wait, I said earlier I was counting. Well, I was. Until this past May when I lost track. I guess it's time to start counting again. I have until next week to get caught up. That's alright. It is a great problem to have, keeping track of all the sick Kobe kicks. There can never be too many Kobe Bryant shoes released. As long as they are released at Footlocker.com or Eastbay.com, that way I at least have a chance to get them.			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lebronjamesbasketballshoes-2011.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lebronjamesbasketballshoes-2011.com/&lt;/a&gt;; lebron james shoes
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f74ae669a4b4e24c912900d5c2e66fca">			&lt;P&gt;;Basketball is regarded to be the most popular sport in the world, next to football.&lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3Blow"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;low&lt;/a&gt;; hyperfuse basketball shoes&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; A lot of people around the world know the concept behind basketball and can definitely play this ball game. Together with its popularity would be the demand for quality shoes,&lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3B2011"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;2011&lt;/a&gt;; hyperdunk shoes&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; &lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3B2010"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;2010&lt;/a&gt;; hyperdunk,2010 hyperfuse&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; &lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3Bcheap"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;cheap&lt;/a&gt;; nike hyperdunk&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; which can be considered as an essential accessory in playing this game. If you want to get the best basketball shoes in the market, you don't have to worry for there are many to choose from.Nike, perhaps,&lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3Bnike"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;nike&lt;/a&gt;; hyperfuse 2011&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; is the biggest producer of shoes in the world. This company is known to create the best shoes for basketball in terms of design and performance. One of the most popular Nike shoes line &lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3B2011"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;2011&lt;/a&gt;; hyperdunk&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; is the Nike Hyperdunk. According to a lot of reviews, this is regarded to be the lightest basketball shoes that Nike made. Weight is important factor for basketball shoes since basketball is a highly strenuous sport that doesn't only include running but also jumping. It is important that the shoes, like the Nike Hyperdunk, are light so that it won't impede the running speed and the jumping reach of the player. Another Nike creat&lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3Blebron"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;lebron&lt;/a&gt;; hyperdunk &lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3Bkobe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;kobe&lt;/a&gt;; hyperdunk basketball shoes&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; basketball shoes&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; ion that has impressed a lot of basketball players is the Nike Air Jordan XX3. Aside from carrying the name of the legendary Michael Jordan, the best thing about these shoes is it boasts of a very intricate design that complements its performance.Other than Nike, there are also other basketball ma&lt;A href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3BB%26gt%3Bjordon"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hyperdunkshoes-mall.com/&quot;&gt;;&lt;B&gt;;jordon&lt;/a&gt;; hyperdunk basketball shoes&lt;/B&gt;;&lt;/A&gt;; kers that have created high performance and stylish shoes. These are Converse, Reebok, and Adidas. If you're not a Nike fan, then you can also try these brands out.Just remember that the brand doesn't really dictate whether a pair of shoes is great or not. It depends on what you really want and on how you can use these shoe to be a great basketball player. &lt;/P&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="3e183b2951133bd7d536af08d3637867">			&amp;lt;p&amp;gt;Really? In three whole years of the run of the Kobe Bryant signature sneaker line I can't purchase a metallic gold colorway? Sure, there is candy apple green, bright orange, several different shades of yellow, purple, grey, and the basic red, blue, green, black and white colorways to choose from. Heck, even a mauve pair has been dropped. Did I miss any? Probably. But one thing I am absolutely sure of is this, there has been zero, not one,&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3Bb%26amp%3Bgt%3Bkobe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;kobe&lt;/a&gt;; shoes sale&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;; pair of metallic gold Kobe Bryant shoes dropped in the last three years. I am fully aware of the fact that metallic gold was u&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3Bb%26amp%3Bgt%3Bnew"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;new&lt;/a&gt;; kobe shoes&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;;sed on the Kobe V &amp;quot;Big Stage&amp;quot; home and away editions. That doesn't count. And, besides, those stunning kicks were virtually impossible to score due to the limited availability. Why won't Nike make a basketball shoe using a solid metallic gold colored upper?No, I can't even use Nike iD to satisfy my craving for gold. Red, blue, black, grey, white, green, yellow, orange, and even some color they call &amp;quot;volt&amp;quot; can be used as an upper on the Kobe VI. But no metallic gold? How sweet would the snakeskin textured upper on the Kobe VI look all dressed up in metallic gold? This is the best sneaker for basketball and I can't rock it in the color I want. Maybe I am just succumbing to human nature. That is, we all want what we can't have. Perhaps if a Kobe shoe did exist in metallic gold I would just&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3Bb%26amp%3Bgt%3Bkobe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;kobe&lt;/a&gt;; iv shoes&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;; dismiss it and wish that I could get it in some other color. Like electric teal. No, no way, that definitely is a colorway I would not have a craving for.Ok, I am done venting. I really don't mean to be negative. The Kobe IV's,&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3Bb%26amp%3Bgt%3Bkobe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;kobe&lt;/a&gt;; basketball shoes&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;;V's, and VI's have dropped in some of t&amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3Bb%26amp%3Bgt%3Bcheap"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kobebasketballshoes-2011.com/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;cheap&lt;/a&gt;; kobe shoes 2011&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;
&lt;br /&gt;;he dopest colorways ever seen in the sneaker world. And I don't own all of them. So, the best thing a true sneakerhead should do is count his or her blessings and appreciate the truly unique designs and colorways that Nike has dropped on us. The &amp;quot;Dark Knight&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Chaos&amp;quot; are truly masterpieces. The &amp;quot;Bruce Lee&amp;quot; is unparalleled in colorway and theme. The four Kobe VI's that made up the All-Star pack at last year's festivities are works of art. I could go on and on. I am a huge fan of the colorways of the Kobe Bryant shoes.I just want gold. If and when Kobe wins his 6th NBA championship, maybe Nike will make my dreams come true and drop a metallic gold Kobe colorway. I just hope I have plane fare and someone in Los Angeles to put me up for a few nights. Because if that happens, it's gonna be a limited release. That's alright, I am preparing for that right now. I just hope it happens.			&amp;lt;/p&amp;gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>