<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2fc946eea60db1b90bfbd530b343aea1">			White Sewing Machines have been a favorite among sewing enthusiasts because of their durability and ease of use. It's so easy to create beautiful quilts, home decorations, clothing and accessories with these machines making your sewing experience fun and enjoyable all the time. If you have basic sewing needs, the White Model 2200 Multi-tasker is exactly what you need.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It has over 35 stitch functions that you can use with ease which makes it great for beginners. Basic features include 35 Stitch functions for all sewing tasks, 12 Built-in stitches, built-in buttonhole, one motion easy threading system, easy dial tension adjustment, fully adjustable stitch length and width to customize stitches, retractable feed dogs for mending or embroidery, presser foot pressure adjustment to regulate pressure for various fabrics, instant reverse to tie off stitches at the touch of a lever, electronic foot controller for constant power and built-in light.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is truly one of the most sough-after &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwhitesewingmachineinfo.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://whitesewingmachineinfo.com/&lt;/a&gt;; for beginners and professionals alike. If you want a computerized machine that is user-friendly but is loaded with features then you might consider the Style Maker from the Blue Ribbon Series. Both beginners and experts will love this wonderful machine. Great features include 200 stitch functions that can be accomplished from 50 built-in stitches plus 3 alphabet styles, help window for ultimate control of all sewing functions, 12 accessory feet plus walking foot, electronic needle up/down, stop/start, single stitch, speed control, mirror image, stitch elongation function, 7 styles buttonholes, memory where you can store stitch combinations and free-arm.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can create the simplest home decorations to the most intricate details that you can ever imagine. The possibilities are endless with the Style Maker.  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwhitesewingmachineinfo.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://whitesewingmachineinfo.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  is truly one-of-a-kind. They are durable, easy to use but they allow us to feed our creative instincts and passion. White perfectly understands the needs of beginners and expert sewers alike. No matter what your expertise level is, you have the right machine waiting for you.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>