<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="c4019b337ed5a5f1fe8db19640a7cac6">			Warm weather will get rid with huge maintenance bills, but you face the unbearable temperatures. To enjoy pleasant days as the best answer is to buy you an air conditioner, which today has become a necessary convenience that ensure your property. The role of an air conditioner is to decrease the room temperature and reduce humidity. Well, on our website, TopAerConditionat. ro apart from our wide range of affordable products, we help you choose the best air conditioning because we want all our customers are kept informed before purchasing a product and are satisfied with products they purchase from our store.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This coming year, TopAerConditionat. ro reaches eight years and therefore meets the people who want to buy the air conditioner with lots of promotional offers. In all these years, our company has gained rich experience in the installation, I managed to install over 10, 000 ac throughout the country. If you purchased such a device with our site and want to install in your home quickly, there's no problem, and help you in this regard. For people living in Bucharest together with Ilfov county, and installation company providing emergency equipment within 48 hours.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are not the only reasons to choose us: TopAerConditionat. ro give installation, warranty and post warranty maintenance of ac and without paying any money you get secured support from us when trouble air conditioning purchased from our store by our specialists who are available.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Air conditioners split&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you prefer to purchase an air conditioner for a large area, you should opt for a split unit ac units (mono-split, double split, multi-split) that enables mounting at least two units in your home, connected to an air conditioning unit outside the house. The most important advantages you can enjoy if you want to opt for an air conditioning split category include: noise is quite low, the indoor unit can be mounted easily, lower energy consumption and appliance efficiency remains the same, does not disturb air jets, the machines include filters that help purify the air inside room and, not least, the low prices which you could purchase an air conditioning split type.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whirlpool Air conditioners&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Among the most popular and efficient air conditioners are produced by Whirlpool with modern design suitable for any room. These machines I control four intelligent systems: duzumidificare, cooling, heating and ventilation. Air conditioners produced by Whirlpool have some effective functions:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Sixth sense function (unit detects everyone in the room temperature and decide which is the perfect combination to feel comfortable);&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- The sleep mode (provides peace and comfort during sleep);&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Stream function (automatic temperature set cost of 18 ° C.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An air conditioning Whirlpool product can be purchased from our store TopAerConditionat. ro at prices between £ 1149 and a maximum of £ 2599.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more information about air conditioners we sell, but about how you can order products we offer are waiting on our website TopAerConditionat. ro.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FlcmUtY29uZGl0aW9uYXRlLmNvbS5yby8_" target="_blank"&gt;;oferte aer conditionat&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d3edadf5ff350b6523ec66500e91b48f">			Because fuel hikes lately and economic dilemma, overall, there are many voices in people opinion and media that support limiting usage of air conditioning installation in cars. In basic fact, there are many recommendations for overall power economy and an outbuilding like air conditioning is amongst the first attacked, it is recommended the use of traditional ventilation, which is made of background air ventilation entering the windows. Sure, this version is not really something for anyone, especially in winter, in the event the window open flame may be triggering a flu for many weeks. However, to consider the next most common among advantages and drawbacks related to the use of air fitness in the car and can you find the right solution for you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why not use ac in the car?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's true. Use air conditioning in the car can increase consumption overall by 10% of vehicle, especially in packed cities. This rate is not the unaware, especially if you have a budget for fuel each week or month. Studies have shown that the typical or lower speed of 70 kilometers each hour, cars can be more efficient in terms of consumption and comfort by keeping car windows when aired down. So, for many current different types of roads (driving through the city, left for the mall, visiting family), the easiest may be to aeristesti car with ambient air-course, as long as being the environment and temperature will not make you sense uncomfortable or will not affect the proper functioning of your car. So, from spring to autumn, you may keep the car windows open when heat permits, and the consumer's car and he will remain at a lower level, more profitable to suit your needs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it useful to use air health and fitness?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you exceed the speed of 70-80 kilometers each hour, as is normal to happen in highway driving conditions, it is better to keep windows closed and use ac system of the car. The cars have higher fuel consumption by around 20%, if windows are open. Current slows the vehicle and do even more unstable, not to say even more awkward to handle. It is more prone to get sick if you drive with that windows down at high speed, so it's completely appropriate to make use of the air conditioning when driving at high speed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Besides air conditioning, there are other solutions that you can ventilate the car and keep comfort in the car. First, the main fan of your car, if joined within, can ventilate the car quite nicely and can decrease the temperature of the car. Then, it can change the smell of the car, namely to get rid of &quot;flavors&quot; of fuel and air alleyways. It's best to use this setting to maximum, but you can decide on less intensive options if desired. Another quite simple method is to park the car within a parking lot or cool, if not possible, even in the shade. Car doors available and vent out again before the city if it's hot, you will benefit in terms of comfort, and fuel consumption will be reduced.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FlcmUtY29uZGl0aW9uYXRlLmNvbS5yby8_" target="_blank"&gt;;oferte aer conditionat&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>