<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b139b2c46e5fc4a45269f301c2c68e1b">			Some of the main attractions that there are actually in Ealing are this Boston Manor House, Musical technology Museum, the Kew Bridge Steam Museum and many such attractions. Some in the major towns in Ealing are generally Kew Bridge, Kew Natural and Greenford. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Boston Manor House&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; The Manor House is a Jacobean manor house which was built in the 12 months 1623. It is located in parkland and contains a beautiful lake along with ancient cedar trees. This house was invested in in 1670 by Clitherow family who stayed in your house till it became an area council property in 1924. Presently, this magnificent 17th century house can be visited and enjoyed by general public for free. There are the state rooms over the first floor and living area and library on the ground floor. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One can find some excellent decorated plaster ceilings with the past era and there are more than 80 painting collections relating to the wall. This includes old views of Chiswick, Isleworth and Brentford. Some parts on the town can be hired for functions and wedding receptions too. The opening timings, admission charges and directions to visit the house are also specified on the site, wherein the information is usually provided. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Musical technology museum&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; One can encounter some fascinating world involving automatic musical instruments during his stop by at the musical museum. You can find non-stop demonstrations wherein the instruments are properly explained and played. One can get to hear the sounds from the past like the lovely tone musical box, your concert pianist subtle looks, the grandeur of pipe organ and many more. Whether such instruments were manufactured for any exclusive wealthy homes or for more humble dwellings, their whole background is described to the one who can see and hear them play automatically. Thus, it takes around 90 minutes of journey such museum. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Kew Bridge museum&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; The Kew Bridge museum carries a wonderful collection of mineral water pumping machines. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A lot of engines are on view and &quot;steamed-up&quot; each day includeing the Grand Junction 90 which has pumped water to west London to get a century. This is the biggest working beam engine on the globe and houses a wonderful 19th century pumping station. There are over several original Cornish Engines with unique range of modern diesel and steam pumping machinery. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Osterley Woodland&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Osterley Park is a spectacular 18th century property. The interior of the Osterley Park house is one of the Britain's most complete designs of Robert Adam's succeed. There is also this Royal Botanic Garden at Kew that provides its visitors lots with interesting sights. There are displays of welcome spring and coil flowers, tints of autumn together with colourful summer borders in the arboretum. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One may also visit the natural history museum with the science museum wherein usually there are some great wonders of the ancient, industrial and technological age exhibits. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;The ballet Giselle is among the most most performed and most favored ballets still danced now. Giselle evolved from that Romantic era, which only lasted for about twenty years from 1830. The characters that were created during the Romantic era were always ethereal magical beings. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ballet Giselle was initially produced in Paris in 1841. The first ballerina that played the part of Giselle was Carlotta Grisi. com  &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jbGl2ZXN3YW4uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;wedding pianist london&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>