<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a0df4de29cfb509befb455d215540638">			The best outdoor shelter is the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/&lt;/a&gt;;. The canopy is like that of a tent that allows a group of people to stay under it to be saved from one thing and one thing only: the sun. The rays of the sun, no matter how refreshing it can be, can also be destructive. According to studies most skin cancers are due to prolonged exposure to the sun. The sun rays transmit alpha and beta rays (a type of radiation) that when one experiences prolonged exposure, it can result to the production of mutated melanin cells which is the definitive sign of skin cancer. Aside from illness, over exposure to sunlight causes sunburn because of the tremendous heat that the sun radiates. People are exposed to these risks because it is imperative for them to go out from the comforts of their abode. The reason varies. Some go out to work or find a living, some go out to socialize, while some go out just for the sake of going out to have a breath of fresh air. These are the reasons why the canopy was invented. To allow people to enjoy the outdoor minus the discomfort and the health risks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are different types of canopies one can choose from. There are caravan canopies, patio canopies, camping canopies, etc. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2Fcamping-canopy%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/camping-canopy/&lt;/a&gt;; is almost the same as that of the standard canopy. The only feature that sets it apart from other canopies is its screened wall shadings. This feature gives protection to the user from all sides. The colored wall shadings also provide privacy to the user making it a comfortable and livable place to loiter or sleep at outdoors. The camping canopy is widely used in training camps. One can also use it if he or she is about to venture out in the woods or in the mountains with a group of people. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The use of the canopy is not limited for the use of camping. It can also be used for marketing, social gatherings, entertainment, events, and the like. If you are looking for the right canopy that will suit your needs, you should look at Coleman Canopy. The brand Coleman is one of the leading manufacturers of outdoor products. It boasts durability and usability for its products. One of the best product they offer is the Coleman Canopy. There are different kinds of Coleman Canopy you can choose from: They have the lighted canopy which uses LED. Best for outdoor night events. They also have different sizes of canopies to better accommodate the number of people attending the event you organized. From the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2F10x10-canopy-and-10x20-canopy%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/10x10-canopy-and-10x20-canopy/&lt;/a&gt;; to the 16 x  8, Coleman has it all. If mosquitoes are a factor to be considered, you can get screened canopies. Like the other types of canopy, the screened canopy  also comes in various sizes to better suit your needs. Specially created  canopies are also offered by Coleman. They have the beach-shade canopy, the road trip canopy, and the camping canopy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Though Coleman may be one of the leading canopy-manufacturers out there, Coleman canopy prices can be a little bit expensive for those who has a small budget. One cannot blame them. With all that is happening in the economy, it’s just practical for one to tighten their budget and cut unnecessary expenses as much as possible. With that being said, you can look for cheap &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2Fcanopy-prices%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/canopy-prices/&lt;/a&gt;; in the market. You can look for it in printed materials like newspapers or magazines. I’m sure canopy prices will be included so use it as a reference. You can also type “cheap canopy prices” in any search engines online and it will route you to websites that will offer you great finds! You just have to be patient. If you are not, then now is the time to be one.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2c312302f810377c869894558cb12e26">			They say that the street is the best marketplace there is. I couldn’t agree more to that. Hundreds if not thousands of people get out from the comforts of their home and walk through streets to get to their destination. When that happens, they inevitably gets exposed to their surrounding seeing all that there is on the street. This idea concludes that the street is the best marketplace because of the opportunity it provides entrepreneurs to flaunt their products to passers-by.  The same principle applies to commercials seen on television. The higher the visibility, the higher the chances of selling products or services. Because of the high chances of profit while selling on the streets, entrepreneurs must have a place to display their products and services. This is where Canopy comes in.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com&lt;/a&gt;; is like a tent. It provides shelter to anyone who’s below it. It gives shade from the radiating heat from the sun to anyone or anything that needs is. It has different shapes and sizes that adapts to the place where its use is needed. For market sellers, they tend to use caravan canopies and patio canopies. Caravan canopies are the most used canopies in the streets. This type of canopy gives high visibility with its aerial feel while effectively shielding the sun’s ray. This canopy is of medium built and has different kinds of designs to suit the user’s taste in design. For entrepreneurs who sell in the streets, you can have your canopy personalized to have the canopy coincide with your products’ look. If you have your own shop but decides to bring your products outside your shop, then patio canopies are suited for you. Commonly seen in night markets, patio canopies allows any merchant to bring out their valued goods to give passers-by the chance to have a closer look to the products that are up for sale. It can be regarded as a type of canopy that is easy to set up since some of it can be attached to your shop’s wall thus lessening the need of setting up columns of composite steel/plastic to serve as support for the roof. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the multi use of canopies, whether it is &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2Fcaravan-canopies%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/caravan-canopies/&lt;/a&gt;; or &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2Fpatio-canopies%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/patio-canopies/&lt;/a&gt;;, it is inevitable for the canopy to be exposed from harsh environment that will result for its wear and tear. With that being said, one should consider the quality of the canopy before they buy one. Based on reviews, the Quik Shade Canopy offers high-quality canopies that can be widely used depending on the buyer’s needs. The Quik Shade Canopy boast that they are one of the leaders in the industry of canopy-making that offers quick and easy usability canopies that are durable and long-lasting. They offer a vast array of canopies: they have what they call “Summit Canopy” that has 300 denier and boasts of its vented top. They have the “Commercial Canopy” that is professionally designed to be tough yet easy to install. They also offer the “Weekender Canopy” that is strong but lightweight because of its aluminum-made columns. If you really want the lightest version of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.canopybase.com%2Fquik-shade-canopy%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.canopybase.com/quik-shade-canopy/&lt;/a&gt;;, the  you should get the “Go Canopy” which is so light that you can easily carry them placed in your backpack. There are a lot of version of canopies that has different features and capabilities. If you wish to have one, assess what features you need then thoroughly look for them in all markets available. Go to the store or search the internet its up to you. Just be patient in looking to get the desired type of canopy you are looking for.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>