<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f7a5470788a8db50ccc3bb80d3285076">			At first glance how to make use of Twitter can seem a bit meaningless and a jumble of information. If you've ever looked at the Twitter website and especially if you're following a lot of people it's very difficult to make any sense of a message with only 140 characters inside. Yet Twitter can be a very successful marketing tool. Here's 7 tips on how to use Twitter and get off for a flying start.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;[url=]How To Make Money With Twitter[/url]&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It might sound obvious but ensure you have a few tweets already on your Twitter account before you try and attract followers. If there's nothing there, people won't follow people. You need to have a compelling background on your Twitter profile. There are some default layouts for sale in Twitter, however there are also many websites which you could add your own background. Search for Twitter backgrounds on Google and you will get a large list. The whole idea is to make people see that you're serious about using Twitter, and that if you have gone to the effort of putting together your background then you'll also probably be giving out a great deal of information.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A great tip on how to use Twitter effectively and what a lot of people don't do, is to put your website address on the background. It won't be clickable but it surely does give people the opportunity to learn more about you. Fill in your bio and a few information about yourself. Make this information align with what you use your profile background. This will again allow you to be seem like a serious customer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Follow people who you think seem to be your target audience. For example if you do online marketing find the Twitter accounts for some of the big marketers. You can these start following them and their own followers. It's very likely that their own followers are highly targeted so you want to start following them. You can also use Twitter search and enter your keywords. You need to verify they're targeted. For instance if you happen to type in internet marketing, you'll get 1000s of results, but if you type in internet marketing tricks and tips you'll get a lot fewer but they are going to more highly targeted.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don't forget when you're learning ways to use Twitter, there are tools that can automate the approach of adding followers back. One of my favourites is usually Tweetadder. This allows you to automate adding followers and following some others. You can even load all the followers for a person like an internet marketer in our example above and then follow them automatically over a period of time. Always check before you use any automated software that you are still within Twitters terms together with conditions.&lt;br /&gt;;Twitter to me is like a stock market ticker tape. If you're following a lot of people like I do then you've got constant messages streaming by on the timeline.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>