<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="df6a0e0402b875ebdf39e364353dc8ad">			People think of sun protection as skin protection, seldom have eye protection in mind. Actually, some studies suggest that UV rays are really harmful to eyes and may cause keratitis, cataracts, retinal damage and so on. Thus, delicate eyes need our special care in heat summer days. 
&lt;br /&gt;Never direct view sun, especially when it is strong. Eyes are very fragile. Direct view to sun for a while may lead to temporary giddiness.Long-term direct view to sunlight will cause pain, tears, inflammation and blurred vision and even hurt retina. 
&lt;br /&gt;As is well known, eye is a delicate tissue that is sensitive to UV rays. It can absorb UV rays with various wavelengths. The 280-nm wavelength UV ray does the greatest injury to the cornea. It is likely to cause conjunctivitis.The 290-400nm wavelength UV ray can cause biggest damage to the lens, which is also the reason for cataract. Studies suggest one is more likely to get cataract if he/she roasts in the sun more. So then what shall we do in daily life?
&lt;br /&gt;You can check out their new arrivals and view the products like Swarovski crystal beads, crystal pendants, crystal pearls and more and buy whatever you are interested in. Place the order now and receive the same in your doorstep without any hassle. It is worth notice that only quality swarovski beads are good to your eyes and effective in protection. Sunglasses of poor quality can't help in protection but result in injury to eyes. Buy a pair of anti-ultraviolet sunglasses when summer comes so that your eyes will be safer. Medical studies have certified that lenses in grey are best as grey have little influence on the effect of vision but effective in anti-UV. If you wear contact lenses, you can choose those with anti-UV function which can block 90% ultraviolet rays.Your instructors will be Swarovski Ambassador, Val Hirata, and Eureka crystal beads own Walter Marczak! You can sign up for the session on the Innovative Beads Expo website or in person at the show.At noon, the sun is strongest and your skin and eyes are at highest risk. The best way to protect you is to keep indoors.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwfefwe.buzz-echo.com%2F2011%2F05%2F10%2Fwww-beadabc-comhot-swarovski-crystal-beads-for-charming-girls%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://wfefwe.buzz-echo.com/2011/05/10/www-beadabc-comhot-swarovski-crystal-beads-for-charming-girls/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.esymo.it%2F%3Fp%3D2960%26amp%3Bpreview%3Dtrue"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.esymo.it/?p=2960&amp;preview=true&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5f4bfd254ab33615749ddb3f788bf45a">			Remember the Bears’ 3-1 start last season? They impressed a lot of people by beating the defending Super Bowl champion Steelers in the second game. For example, you can add a beaded fringe to a dress. In fact, studies have shown that ultraviolet radiation will lead to keratitis, cataracts, retinal damage and other eye diseases. Thus, delicate eyes need our special care in heat summer days. 
&lt;br /&gt;The pendant crystals presently have got a hole drilled so it is feasible to place them over a thread unbelievably easily. 
&lt;br /&gt;Crafted and authenticated by Pugster, the Cute Ram shape European Charm Bead is available for both retail and wholesale purchase through our store. The ultraviolet radiation with 250nm wavelength does the most damage to the cornea, and it is the cause of conjunctivitis. Different materials make different beads, so beads can be given on a wide variety of forms, styles, and different beads different style. here are many different things that you can do with Swarovski crystal beads and wedding hairpieces. For example,
&lt;br /&gt;Swarovski crystal beadsYou will make crystal diamond jewelry by your do it yourself or it is feasible to obtain it presently created from the designer. it really is typically an effective basic principle to begin with better top quality materials, as many of us know the completed product is only as wonderful since the sum in the particular person parts.The most common size of swarovski beads is 3mm or 4mm but of course there are multiple sizes available. Once you find the size you need, you can gather the additional supplies.Want to bring some glitter and sparkle to your spring outfit for the royal wedding? They are admired throughout the world. They are popular for their precision-cut crystals, beads and other related products. Jewelry constructed with crystal beads will be able to shimmer and stand out as one wear this by day time or by evening.There is some doubt about the durability of any coatings, and there is no guarantee that any color can be replicated again.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f1fcd5854fd7f46e7473dbb3493730b7">			Speaking of sun protection in summer, everyone would pay attention to their skin, few remember eyes. Instead, surveys show that ultraviolet radiation is the main cause of some eye diseases, such as keratitis, cataracts, retinal damage. So, we can't ignore the eye injury caused by ultraviolet radiation.
&lt;br /&gt;Don't look directly to the sunlight in the hot sunny days.Eyes are very fragile. Direct view to sun for a while may lead to temporary giddiness.One may suffer from pain, tears, inflammation and blurred vision if he/she looks up to sun for a long time. 
&lt;br /&gt;As is known to all, eyes are fragile and susceptible to ultraviolet radiation which would easily injury eyes. The ultraviolet radiation with 280nm wavelength does the most damage to the cornea, and it is the cause of conjunctivitis. The UV rays with the wavelength of 290-400nm are harmful to lens, which would result in cataract. Research indicates the risk to suffer from cataract rises by 10% if one more hour every day people expose to the sun. And now we should talk about some precautions. 
&lt;br /&gt;Swarovski crystal beadsYou will make crystal diamond jewelry by your do it yourself or it is feasible to obtain it presently created from the designer. it really is typically an effective basic principle to begin with better top quality materials, as many of us know the completed product is only as wonderful since the sum in the particular person parts.It is worth to note that the swarovski beads you buy should be good enough in quality. If your sunglasses are poor in quality, your eyes will suffer instead of benefit. It is necessary for you to have a pair of sunglasses with a special coating that locks UV light in summer. It has been shown in much medical research that sunglasses of neutral density glass with grey lenses are best in blocking UV rays. If you wear contact lenses, you can choose those with anti-UV function which can block 90% ultraviolet rays.We offer crystal beads our range of crystal jewellery beads is ready to rock and roll the market through its quality and exclusivity in designs.At noon, the sun is strongest and your skin and eyes are at highest risk. The best way to protect you is to keep indoors.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>