<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="aabba3452c87f64e888ebde1d50fa3e">			The thrilling rivalry between &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.livefootball.im%2FBarcelona-vs-RealMadrid.aspx%26quot%3B%26gt%3BReal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.livefootball.im/Barcelona-vs-RealMadrid.aspx&quot;&gt;;Real&lt;/a&gt;; Madrid and Barcelona&lt;/a&gt;; from the Spanish Football League has continued growing for over 100 years.  The two clubs have won numerous titles and still do so.  The next time the teams meet, look forward to the thrill around the league.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the last few seasons, Barcelona have been winning in this rivalry.  In 2011 they won the La Liga title and also the UEFA Champions League title, so that they  are supreme in this rivalry for another year.  Barcelona needed to beat Real Madrid to win both of these titles.  In the past 80 years Barcelona and Real Madrid have alternated in title matches with one team winning a title match then the other team winning the following year.  This has been going on since 1929 when the Spanish began playing football.  Both teams have dominated the La Liga competition.  The even have control of the Copa Del Ray, a yearly game in the Spanish League featuring the two top teams.  Forty-three  Copa Del Rey titles have been won between Barcelona and Real Madrid.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The fight between the two clubs is so unique and vigorous and this testify the victories they have made so far for many years. The preceding week matches 2011 Copa Del Rey and the 2011 Super Cup adds to the list of unforgettable matches that has been played thus far in the Soccer history. Both teams were face to face  in the semifinals of the UEFA Champions League in the previous years which is described as the most hardest trophy to be won. Barcelona took the lead at  Bernabeu, though it was a home stadium of Real Madrid, in the initial league match. The Lionel Messi of Barcelona, one of the top player in the globe, came out with the flying color by taking the both of the goals in the first leg. Also,one of most unforgettable match is 2011 Copa Del Rey, which was also played by Barcelona and Real Madrid.Here, the role of Cristiano Ronaldo, of Real Madrid's in going ahead  in the 103rd minute with a goal and winning their opponents with 1-0 was a great fare.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Real Madrid and Barcelona is 1 of the great rivalries in all sport.  Despite all their differences, these clubs will remain in the top 5 world rankings.  Pep Guardiola, Barcelona manager is a straight shooter and highly successful.  Winning is paramount and Guardiola does it well.  His eye for talent is unparalleled and the youth program is globally recognized as 1 of the best available.  Jose Mourinho, the manager of Real Madrid is considered by many for being among the most effective worldwide after winning titles with multiple teams.  Despite the controversy that surrounds his team, he'll continue to be 1 of the best around.  He relies heavily on the signing new players, utilizing the transfer market as well as developing talent through the Real Madrid youth squad.  In the sport of soccer, these 2 teams make up the fiercest rivalry around.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>