<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="cb500f2a487c62e3f790bce8adb37a56">			It is vital for attorneys to make use of an &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.attorneyreputationmanagement.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.attorneyreputationmanagement.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  method as a way to manage the online comments they get. An attorney knows how important their good reputation is in the offline world. Word of mouth is vital, and what people say about them and their firm determines their general failure or success. A lawyer's good reputation centers on the good results of their practice as well as their capability to attract new customers. On the other hand, in the computer age, the old saying that ‘bad news travels fast’ hasn't been more applicable and the effect of negative facts on the Internet more devastating to a lawyer's reputation. The easy access to information and facts on-line has evolved how individuals research goods and services and how they use that knowledge to inform their selections. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In today’s world, what individuals say about you on the internet can have an even greater impact on your firm, your business, and your bottom line. Because a lawyer's reputation is the main factor, he or she must safeguard it always. Regardless of what industry you're in, but particularly if you deal with individuals who are dealing with problems and under stress, sooner or later you'll bump into somebody who is not happy, and, if you are not pro-active about your business reputation and your proper name, whatever your enemies have to say is what people will see if they look you up. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whenever someone seeks legal representation, unfavorable information and facts posted online somewhere can show up in a natural search results even if they’re looking for it or not and have a powerful effect on an attorney's reputation. Most Internet users will not contemplate on whether the claims are spurious or factual, they will just search somewhere else. But the damage would have been done and attempts to remedy the situation by means of legal channels can be costly and draw resources from growing a legal practice. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The internet has made service reviews common. With this, malicious and false information has also become common. With so many new ways for customers to complain and vent frustrations online, attorneys are finding themselves on the wrong end of a unfavorable online article. If you look at Avvo.com or RipoffReport.com, you will see plenty of upset clients, real and imaginary, ranting about poor legal representation or terrible services rendered. As an attorney, you are already aware that there is little or nothing you can do to have these postings taken off these websites. The Communications Decency Act safeguards the information their sites contain, which makes it impossible to get rid of despite having a court order. But there is something that can be done. The detrimental testimonials can be pushed down, or substituted with new &amp; positive web content. It could be as easy as maintaining a personal blog and some social accounts to make sure that you control the rankings for your proper name. Obviously, the same methods can also help your rankings on competitive searches for what you do where you do it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So if you are an attorney, be sure to consider using &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.attorneyreputationmanagement.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.attorneyreputationmanagement.com/&lt;/a&gt;; , because if you do not manage your reputation, someone else will, and it may not be friends.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>