<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7d65478653c822745bb2104a6e4307aa">			The man slowly looked up. This was a woman clearly accustomed to the finer things of life. Her coat was new. She looked like she had never missed a meal in her life. His first thought was that she wanted to make fun of him, like so many others had done before.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Leave me alone,&quot;; he growled... To his amazement, the woman continued standing. She was smiling -- her even white teeth displayed in dazzling rows.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Are you hungry?&quot;; she asked.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;No,&quot;; he answered sarcastically. &quot;;I've just come from dining with the president.. Now go away.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The woman's smile became even broader.
&lt;br /&gt;;Suddenly the man felt a gentle hand under his arm. &quot;;What are you doing, lady?&quot;; the man asked angrily. &quot;;I said to leave me alone.
&lt;br /&gt;;Just then a policeman came up.. &quot;;Is there any problem, ma'am?&quot;; he asked..
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;No problem here, officer,&quot;; the woman answered. &quot;;I'm just trying to get this man to his feet. Will you help me?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The officer scratched his head. &quot;;That's old Jack. He's been a fixture around here for a couple of years. What do you want with him?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;See that cafeteria over there?&quot;; she asked. &quot;;I'm going to get him something to eat and get him out of the cold for awhile.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Are you crazy, lady?&quot;; the homeless man resisted. &quot;;I don't want to go in there!&quot;; Then he felt strong hands grab his other arm and lift him up.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Let me go, officer. I didn't do anything..&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;This is a good deal for you, Jack,&quot;; the officer answered. &quot;;Don't blow it.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Finally, and with some difficulty, the woman and the police officer got Jack into the cafeteria and sat him at a table in a remote corner. It was the middle of the morning, so most of the breakfast crowd had already left and the lunch bunch had not yet arrived.
&lt;br /&gt;;The manager strode across the cafeteria and stood by his table. &quot;;What's going on here, officer?&quot;; he asked.&quot;;What is all this, is this man in trouble?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;This lady brought this man in here to be fed,&quot;; the policeman answered.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Not in here!&quot;; the manager replied angrily. &quot;;Having a person like that here is bad for business.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Old Jack smiled a toothless grin. &quot;;See, lady. I told you so. Now if you'll let me go. I didn't want to come here in the first place..&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The woman turned to the cafeteria manager and smiled. &quot;;Sir, are you familiar with Eddy and Associates, the banking firm down the street?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Of course I am,&quot;; the manager answered impatiently. &quot;;They hold their weekly meetings in one of my banquet rooms.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;And do you make a goodly amount of money providing food at these weekly meetings?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;What business is that of yours?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;I, sir, am Penelope Eddy, president and CEO of the company.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Oh..&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The woman smiled again.. &quot;;I thought that might make a difference.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;She glanced at the cop who was busy stifling a laugh. &quot;;Would you like to join us in a cup of coffee and a meal, officer?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;No thanks, ma'am,&quot;; the officer replied. &quot;;I'm on duty.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Then, perhaps, a cup of coffee to go?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Yes, ma'am. That would be very nice.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The cafeteria manager turned on his heel. &quot;;I'll get your coffee for you right away, officer.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The officer watched him walk away... &quot;;You certainly put him in his place,&quot;; he said.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;That was not my intent... Believe it or not, I have a reason for all this.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;She sat down at the table across from her amazed dinner guest. She stared at him intently.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Jack, do you remember me?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Old Jack searched her face with his old, rheumy eyes. &quot;;I think so -- I mean you do look familiar.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;I'm a little older perhaps,&quot;; she said. &quot;;Maybe I've even filled out more than in my younger days when you worked here, and I came through that very door, cold and hungry.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Ma'am?&quot;; the officer said questioningly. He couldn't believe that such a magnificently turned out woman could ever have been hungry..
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;I was just out of college,&quot;; the woman began. &quot;;I had come to the city looking for a job, but I couldn't find anything. Finally I was down to my last few cents and had been kicked out of my apartment.. I walked the streets for days. It was February and I was cold and nearly starving. I saw this place and walked in on the off chance that I could get something to eat.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Jack lit up with a smile. &quot;;Now I remember,&quot;; he said. &quot;;I was behind the serving counter. You came up and asked me if you could work for something to eat. I said that it was against company policy.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;I know,&quot;; the woman continued. &quot;;Then you made me the biggest roast beef sandwich that I had ever seen, gave me a cup of coffee, and told me to go over to a corner table and enjoy it. I was afraid that you would get into trouble. Then, when I looked over and saw you put the price of my 
&lt;br /&gt;;food in the cash register, I knew then that everything would be all right...&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;So you started your own business?&quot;; Old Jack said.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;I got a job that very afternoon. I worked my way up. Eventually I started my own business that, with the help of God, prospered..&quot;; She opened her purse and pulled out a business card. &quot;;When you are finished here, I want you to pay a visit to a Mr. Lyons. He's the personnel director of my company. I'll go talk to him now and I'm certain he'll find something for you to do around the office.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;She smiled. &quot;;I think he might even find the funds to give you a little advance so that you can buy some clothes and get a place to live until you get on your feet. If you ever need anything, my door is always open to you.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;There were tears in the old man's eyes. &quot;;How can I ever thank you?&quot;; he asked.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;Don't thank me,&quot;; the woman answered. &quot;;To God goes the glory. He led me to you.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Outside the cafeteria, the officer and the woman paused at the entrance before going their separate ways.. &quot;;Thank you for your help officer,&quot;; she said.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;On the contrary, Ms. Eddy,&quot;; he answered. &quot;;Thank you. I saw a miracle today, something that I will never forget, And thank you for the coffee.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Have a Wonderful Day. May God Bless You always and don't forget that when you &quot;;cast your bread upon the waters,&quot;; you never know how it will be returned to you. God is so big He can cover the whole world with his 
&lt;br /&gt;;Love and so small He can curl up inside your heart.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When God leads you to the edge of the cliff, trust Him fully and let go.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Only 1 of 2 things will happen, either He'll catch you when you fall, or He'll teach you how to fly!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The power of one sentence! God is going to shift things around for you today and let things work in your favor.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;God closes doors no man can open &amp; God opens doors no man can close..
&lt;br /&gt;;If you need God to open some doors for you...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Have a blessed day and remember to be a blessing...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;;The Task Ahead of Me is Never as Great as the Power Behind Me!!&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;God bless you
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;JD		</conversation>	</conversations></author>