<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="700296010aca7432122ee8209c08a65b">			Strong memory depend on your vitality and  health. Are you a student studying for final examinations, the working professional interested in doing everything possible to stay mentally sharp, or senior to maintain and strengthen its position as you age gray matter, there are many things you may do to improve your mental abilities and memory. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Memory Enhancement by sleeping 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While you  sleep deprived, your brain can not function at full capacity. Creativity, problem-solving skills, critical thinking skills at risk. Did you study, work, or trying to juggle the many demands of life, lack of sleep is a recipe for disaster. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sleeping is very important in learning and memory . Research show that sleep is necessary for memory consolidation, the main memory-making activities take place during the deepest stages of sleep. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take time for friends and fun for memory enhancement 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are thinking about ways to improve memory, do you think of &quot;serious&quot; activities, such as wrestling. If you are like most of us, it is possible first. However, numerous studies have shown that the life, friends and fun come to the knowledge advantage. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Healthy relationship: 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;People are very social animals. We will not prosper, let alone thrive in isolation. Relations to promote our brains are actually interact with others, can be the best type of brain exercise. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Research shows that meaningful relationships and a strong support system is very important, not only emotional, but also to brain health. A recent study from the Harvard School of Public Health, for example, researchers found that people are the most active social life was the slowest rate of memory decline. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many ways to start using the brain and memory improvement benefits of communication. Volunteer, join the club, this time with friends more often, or by telephone. And if you are not comfortable, do not forget the animals, especially dogs a high social value. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Laughter is good for Memory Enhancement
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You've probably heard that laughter is the best medicine, and it refers to the brain and body. Unlike the emotional response that is only in certain areas in the brain, laughing the whole brain in several regions throughout. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Keep stress in check for  memory enhancement
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Stress is one of the worst enemies of the brain. Over time, if left unchecked, chronic stress destroys brain cells and damage to the hippocampus, involved in forming memories.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Eat more vegetables and fruits. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Colorful fruits and vegetables are good sources of antioxidant superfood. Try green leafy vegetables such as spinach, romaine lettuce, broccoli, Swiss chard and arugula, and fruits such as , mangoes, watermelons and apricotsmelons.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Welcome to the home-remedies-world.com. Easy &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWUtcmVtZWRpZXMtd29ybGQuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;home remedies&lt;/a&gt;; that can be found in your kitchen. If you are thinking about ways to improve memory, do you think of &quot;serious&quot; activities, such as wrestling. Learn &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWUtcmVtZWRpZXMtd29ybGQuY29tL2RpdnlhLW1lZGhhLXZhdGkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;memory enhancement&lt;/a&gt;; techniques and discover how to improve your memory and concentration. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWUtcmVtZWRpZXMtd29ybGQuY29tL0RpdnlhLUJhZGFtLVBhay5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Brain Tonic&lt;/a&gt;; is taken internally to support brain and nervous system efficiency by promoting equilibrium at a cellular level.		</conversation>		<conversation id="21e8f290e1ac869c0a18dd2504bcc270">			Almost 1 / 3 of people of high blood pressure patients, do not know they have high blood pressure, High Blood Pressure or Hypertension is a quiet disease. People may have high blood pressure for many years without experiencing symptoms or knowing that they have it. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;High blood pressure (hypertension) is defined as a systolic blood pressure - the top number - an average of 140 mm Hg or higher and / or diastolic blood pressure - the bottom number - an average of 90 mm Hg or higher. Systolic blood pressure is the pressure, the heart contracts. Diastolic blood pressure between heartbeats when the heart relaxes blood pressure. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Causes of high blood pressure 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In many cases, high blood pressure, the American Heart Association says there is no one to determine the cause. This type of high blood pressure is called essential hypertension or primary hypertension. Typically, this combination of factors, such as:-
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Operating level. Lack of physical activity tends to Thurs palpitations; which forces your heart to work with each contraction. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Weight. Increased body weight, more pressure is put on the walls of the arteries. This is because more blood is produced Thurs supply oxygen and nutrients to tissues in the body Thurs 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Tobacco- Substance in tobacco and cigarettes may damage artery walls. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Potassium intake- Low potassium levels may lead to increased sodium cells, both balance each other. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Stress- Stress raises blood pressure. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. Alcohol consumption- Excessive drinking may over time increase the risk of heart disease. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. Sodium intake- Excessive sodium diet can cause fluid retention and high blood pressure, especially for people sensitive to sodium Thurs 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. Family history- High blood pressure often affects their families. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. Age- High blood pressure risk increases as you get older. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Natural Medicines For Hypertension 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One very effective lifestyle changes for those who are over weight and suffering from hypertension in life is to lose a few pounds. Losing weight with a small evangelical tool may have a dramatic effect, reducing blood pressure. Many pharmaceutical experts appointed by the weight loss programs to treat high blood pressure. The best and safest way to keep your blood pressure, eat well. Normal blood pressure is 120/80 and 140/90, shall not exceed remain in force and without stroke and myocardial infarction. Foods such as garlic, vegetables, fruits are an essential role in maintaining blood pressure. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vegetables and Fruits:-  Vegetables and Fruits are natural medicines for hypertension, the effect of blood pressure. Research studies show that the transition to a vegetarian diet lowers blood pressure. Concentrated fruit contains potassium, vitamin C and loads of soluble fiber, all of the which Contribute to lowers blood pressure. In addition, fruits are low in sodium, which promote blood pressure. People who eat little or no fruit is prone to high blood pressure Thurs Fruit is the best source of natural vitamin C. Make sure to eat fruit every day to get your daily dose of vitamin C. Although the synthetic vitamin pills helps to some extent in lower blood pressure.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Welcome to the home-remedies-world.com. Easy &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWUtcmVtZWRpZXMtd29ybGQuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;home remedies&lt;/a&gt;; that can be found in your kitchen. In today's world, hypertension or high blood pressure has become a common illness that a person, whether an old or young. This herbal medicine is prepared by mixing various herbs that makes it a powerful Ayurvedic medicine to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWUtcmVtZWRpZXMtd29ybGQuY29tL2RpdnlhLW11a3RhLXZhdGkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;natural cure for high blood pressure&lt;/a&gt;;. If you are suffering from hypertension you can take &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvbWUtcmVtZWRpZXMtd29ybGQuY29tL3BhY2thZ2UtaGlnaC1ibG9vZC1wcmVzc3VyZS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;natural medicines for hypertension&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>