<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a5eebd874fd0825c45b5902000b3eeb5">			Now a days it's difficult to determine what creates a designer watch as opposed to a normal one. Designer watches were born straight from the fashion industry with well-known designer brands like Armani, Cartier, D&amp;G, Sesky, DKNY and Guess launching their own ranges of watches. The design of these is incredibly fashion orientated and often in line with the latest fads and couture stages. These designer brands offer a number of particularly when buying watches for women.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They also offer jewellery &amp; bracelet watches many of which go well with their jewellery accessories. If you are buying for a fashion orientated person then you will need to have a specific look or clothe themselves with mind that the designer watch goes with. You can then accessories with earrings, neckwear or wrist wear jewellery either in the same fashion designer or anyone you like.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;However we cannot your investment traditional luxury watch makers whom possess a history in making classic time pieces for men. This then developed to help wrist watches for people. Now they are additionally attuned with fashion designs of the modern day and put a lot of thought into watch pattern. This has resulted in multi-functional watches made out of precision engineering that are also very fashionable in pattern. So it is unsurprising that famous watch creators like Tissot, Hamilton, Breitling &amp; Timex are making designer watches additionally.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are thinking to buy watches for men then consider whether they are gadgets lovers or would prefer a classic and thoroughly clean looking watch design. Tissot does the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Rpc3NvdHNwb3J0d2F0Y2hlcy5jb20vdGlzc290LXQtc3BvcnQtcHJjMjAwLWNocm9ub2dyYXBoLW1lbnMtd2F0Y2gtcmV2aWV3Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Tissot Sport Watches women&lt;/a&gt;; suitable for both women and men. It is made of Titanium, comes with compass, altimeter, thermometer, barometer and is water resistant to thirty meters. This, one of many designer watches manufactured by Tissot, comes with a two year warranty.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are also watch designs based on themes like sporting events, famous celebrities or whatever is a latest fashionable fad. If the man you will be buying a watch for is a petrol head or some sort of sports fan then you'll discover a number of watch designs themed on famous sporting events like the Moto DOCTOR or the Olympics. There are a huge number of sports watches on offer that also look enjoy designer watches.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a vintage clean look go for chronograph watches from Armani, Oris, Hamilton and also &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Rpc3NvdHNwb3J0d2F0Y2hlcy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;Tissot Sport Watches women&lt;/a&gt;;. For the ladies then Armani, D&amp;G, Rotary &amp; Hamilton ladies watches are a must. These are designer watches yet maintain a vintage clean look.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Price these watches depends on supplies, functionality, craftsmanship and watch brand. The more expensive designer brands can increase in worth over time particularly if the watch is part of a limited edition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two of the more popular designer wrist watches are Tag Heuer &amp; Rollex. Antique watches from Rollex are worth a great deal of money and so buying a Rollex today constitutes a investment. That is not saying that any of this designer watches won't become highly valued in the future so make sure people always by from a great authorised dealer with manufacturer's assurance.		</conversation>		<conversation id="20ec8c140be3b7738ce5f34d31b86981">			Now a days it is difficult to determine what creates a designer watch instead of a normal one. Designer watches were born out of your fashion industry with famous designer brands like Armani, Cartier, D&amp;G, Sesky, DKNY and Guess launching their own ranges of watches. The design of these is very fashion orientated and often good latest fads and couture ranges. These designer brands offer a wide range particularly when buying watches for women.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They also offer jewellery &amp; bracelet watches many of which match their jewellery accessories. If you are buying to get a fashion orientated person then you will need to have a specific look or dress in mind that the designer watch will go with. You can after that accessories with earrings, neckwear or wrist wear jewellery either in the same fashion designer or any one you like.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;However we cannot forget the traditional luxury watch makers whom possess a history in making classic time pieces for men. This then developed to help wrist watches for women and men. Now they are additionally attuned with fashion designs of the modern day and put a lot of thought into watch design. This has resulted in multi-functional watches made with precision engineering that are very fashionable in pattern. So it is unsurprising that famous watch machines like Tissot, Hamilton, Breitling &amp; Timex are making designer watches to boot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are looking to buy watches for men then consider whether they are gadgets lovers or would prefer a classic and clean looking watch design. Tissot does the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NsaW50b25kdWtlODIxLnBvc3Rlcm91cy5jb20vYnV5aW5nLWRlc2lnbmVyLXdhdGNoZXMtZm9yLWxhZGllcy1tZW4_" target="_blank"&gt;;Buying Designer Watches For Ladies &amp; Men&lt;/a&gt;; suitable for both women and men. It is made associated with Titanium, comes with compass, altimeter, thermometer, barometer and it is water resistant to 26 meters. This, one of numerous designer watches manufactured by Tissot, comes with a two year warranty.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are watch designs based on themes like sporting events, famous celebrities or whatever is a latest fashionable fad. If the man you are buying a watch for can be a petrol head or a sports fan then you'll discover a number of see designs themed on famous sporting events like the Moto GP or the Olympics. Quite a huge number of sports watches on offer that also look enjoy designer watches.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a classic clean look go with regard to chronograph watches from Armani, Oris, Hamilton or even &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50YWdnZWQuY29tL3Rpc3NvdHNwb3J0d2F0Y2hlczMx" target="_blank"&gt;;Buying Designer Watches For Ladies &amp; Men&lt;/a&gt;;. For the women then Armani, D&amp;G, Rotary &amp; Hamilton ladies watches really are a must. These are designer watches yet maintain a classic clean look.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Price of these watches depends on materials, functionality, craftsmanship and watch brand. The more expensive custom brands can increase in worth over time particularly if the watch is part of a limited edition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two in the more popular designer watches are Tag Heuer &amp; Rollex. Antique watches from Rollex are worth a substantial amount of money and so investing in Rollex today is a good investment. That is not to say that any of that designer watches won't become highly valued when you need it so make sure you always by from a great authorised dealer with manufacturer's assurance.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>