<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b4eb8c4aade2f83984d066317d9f4d59">			Being injured in an automobile accident is a trying experience. Your car sustains damage, your body sustains damage, and your life becomes hassled with having to deal with both. If the accident was not your fault, you have the right to instigate a personal injury case to reimburse your costs of auto damage, bodily damage care, and pain and suffering. The costs of medical treatment such as with a pain center would need to be reimbursed as well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes it is prudent to retain the services of an attorney after an auto accident turns into a personal injury case (&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hemFjY2lkZW50LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Arizona Accident Attorney&lt;/a&gt;;).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the insurance company is not returning your calls, the question is why?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the insurance company is not agreeing to accept responsibility on behalf of their insured, is offering a low reimbursement amount for your medical care, is not offering any amount of payment for pain and suffering, is valuing your vehicle too low, etc. When it becomes clear that the insurance company is not going to work with you in a fair and reasonable manner, it is time to retain the services of a specialist who can fight your battle for you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;u&gt;;How do I know how to choose a good attorney?&lt;/u&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One thing you can do is choose a pain management center with an experienced legal person on staff. Or they may deal with personal injury cases regularly and know attorneys in the area. For instance, the pain center may deal with lots of personal injury attorneys and be able to provide a list for you along with setting up interviews. If the pain center has been working with attorneys in the area on many cases, they will know who are the highly chosen experts in the personal injury field.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Important considerations are a track record of calling back clients (existing or potential), working with you to obtain the best possible medical care, and working with you at the end of the case to make sure your settlement is appropriate. Having an attorney who limits your settlement to boost his practice's bottom line on the case is simply not fair.		</conversation>		<conversation id="aaaac7f2d15be0b5dc87f4cfe41d0848">			Not many people know that, after an accident, it is often possible to get around some of these roadblocks to fair compensation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once you know the basic process involved in accident claims, with a bit of organization and some patience, your can save yourself the cost of a lawyer and handle your own injury insurance claim.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Actually it is even possible that you will be able to get more compensation for your injury by handling it yourself instead of hiring a lawyer and paying attorney fees.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many reasons why this works. Here are a few of them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. It is cheaper for insurance company to settle your claim directly&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For insurance company, it is often cheaper to settle a claim than go through a trial. An insurance company's willingness to settle your claim quickly is in their best interest to save money in the long run. It is simply cheaper to pay you than to prolong the fight.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. The claims process is pretty simple&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In contrary to what insurance companies and lawyers would like you to believe, settling an injury claim is usually quite simple.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most personal injury claims involve no more than a few short letters and phone calls with an insurance adjuster who has no legal training. It is even not necessary to know the technical language or complex legal rules. Your right to be compensated usually depends on nothing more than commonsense ideas of who was careful and who was careless.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. The compensation system is structured&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The amount of fair compensation is easy to figure out basing on a number of simple factors: type of accident, injuries, medical cost, etc. Then you can easily find out how many any claim is &quot;worth&quot;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The amount an insurance company is willing to pay falls into a narrow range, no matter a personal injury attorney handles your claim or you handle it by yourself.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An insurance adjuster who learns that you are organized and that you understand the claims process will usually settle the claim with you right away.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Save money on legal fees&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A personal injury lawyer will charge you up to 40% of your recovery. Yet, except in serious or complicated cases, a lawyer can usually gain for you, if anything, only an extra 5% to 20% above what you can get for yourself once your understand the process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Review Other Posts:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2tlbnRzY2hyb2VkZTYxNC5vdmVyLWJsb2cuY29tL3BhZ2VzL2FyaXpvbmEtYWNjaWRlbnQtYXR0b3JuZXktNjkwMjQ4OC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Arizona Accident Attorney&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N5a3RhZWxya3NyZW5lc25hLmppZ3N5LmNvbS9lbnRyaWVzL2dlbmVyYWwvQXJpem9uYS1BY2NpZGVudC1BdHRvcm5leQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Arizona Accident Attorney&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>