<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="7d2cf8b5236a9feed801da0070cf6ae6">			When I think of productivity tools for the modern business professional, one of the first that comes to mind is Outlook, Microsoft's insanely useful personal management program. Outlook began life as an email client, and it's still a great one; but in the past decade, it's grown into so much more. These days, Outlook is also one of the chief ways that savvy business professionals manage their time and maximize their accessibility, from scheduling their meetings to keeping track of their personal contacts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This past year we were blessed with a new version, the inventively-named Microsoft &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.outlook2010s.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.outlook2010s.com/&lt;/a&gt;;. It's chockfull of interesting and practical features-some of them completely new, and others refinements of features introduced in earlier versions. In this article, I'll show you how to best take advantage of a few.&lt;br /&gt;;In &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.outlook2010s.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.outlook2010s.com/&lt;/a&gt;;, Microsoft introduced the Ribbon Interface on some Outlook windows, primarily those associated with message views. Now it's all over the place, including the Inbox itself. As part of the Microsoft Office Fluent User Interface, it's designed to help you quickly find the commands you need.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As with Word and other Office programs (into which the Ribbon has been integrated long since), related tasks are grouped under tabs; with minor exceptions, menus are history. And here's something exciting: you can also add customized tabs to your ribbons to enhance your personal work style and thus maximize your productivity.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is a marvelous little feature located in the Mail view on the Home tab. With Quick Steps, you can set up one-click commands for the functions you use most often. This is especially handy for automating repetitive tasks. In addition to the custom options, there are several default Quick Steps with self-evident names, including Move to:, Forward: FYI (which uses FYI instead of FW when forwarding messages), To Manager, Team Email, Done, and Reply and Delete. All you have to do is configure them, and you're good to go.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sadly, a default Quick Step they left out is Get Me a Cup of Coffee, but I'm sure an enterprising manager could set this up as a custom command in about five minutes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not only can you now see more of your messages at once, thanks to the new Conversation View, it's easier than ever to organize them. Conversations are automatically grouped by date and subject, and you can expand or collapse those views with one click. And here's the kicker: you can quickly reduce the noise in your inbox by using two new features, Ignore Conversation and Clean Up Conversations.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're getting a lot of Forwards, FYIs or other stuff that you don't care to, instead of wading through and deleting the useless threads, just click the Ignore command in the Delete group on the Message tab. Up will pop a dialog box; click Ignore Conversation, and presto, the whole conversation is sent to Deleted Items purgatory. If you decide later that ignoring the conversation was a mistake, you can go back and click Ignore again. If the conversation is still in the Deleted Items folder, you can select Stop Ignoring Conversation, and it will reappear in your Conversation View.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Clean Up Conversations is just as useful. By default, Outlook saves the original message a sender is replying to at the bottom of their message. After a while, this can make for some long, space-wasting messages. You can use Clean Up to sweep any conversation or folder clean of all redundant messages, leaving only the most recent email that contains the entire conversation. Goodbye, clutter-hello productivity! As with the Ignore function, the cleaned-up messages go into the Deleted Items folder by default, where they can be recovered as long as the folder hasn't been emptied. You can configure the feature to send them elsewhere, if you like, and there are several other options to let you specify exactly what gets cleaned up when you click the button.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In addition to the big changes outlined above, there are a number of small but significant changes to the message interface. Now you can configure Outlook to automatically close a message after you reply, and even better, there's extended capacity to resend or recall messages.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.outlook2010s.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.outlook2010s.com/&lt;/a&gt;; is good.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In previous Outlook versions, these functions were possible, but only if you and your recipient were both using a Microsoft Exchange server. Now the only restriction is that your recipient is also using Outlook, and their settings are configured properly (this varies from version to version). The recall/resend may not succeed if their settings aren't right, but as one reviewer pointed out, it's worth a try.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ability to manage calendars has always been one of Outlook's most useful features. The calendaring function hasn't changed too much in this version, but it's been tweaked to be more streamlined, and the ability to share schedules and manage multiple calendars has improved noticeably.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The new Calendar Groups feature is amazingly helpful, for example, because it lets you see the calendars of the people you work with frequently. Once you've configured the feature, you can view all their calendars with ease, and you can even determine which meeting rooms or other resources are available for use. One new feature that you team leaders will appreciate is the ability to add your team members' schedules to your new and improved Schedule View, which makes it simple to schedule meetings by laying out resource, Individual, and Group calendars on a horizontal line so that you can more easily identify the best time to meet.		</conversation>		<conversation id="919b808d11024753266746d66cb5290f">			When I think of productivity tools for the modern business professional, one of the first that comes to mind is Outlook, Microsoft's insanely useful personal management program. Outlook began life as an email client, and it's still a great one; but in the past decade, it's grown into so much more. These days, Outlook is also one of the chief ways that savvy business professionals manage their time and maximize their accessibility, from scheduling their meetings to keeping track of their personal contacts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This past year we were blessed with a new version, the inventively-named Microsoft &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.outlook2010s.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.outlook2010s.com/&lt;/a&gt;;. It's chockfull of interesting and practical features-some of them completely new, and others refinements of features introduced in earlier versions. In this article, I'll show you how to best take advantage of a few.&lt;br /&gt;;In &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.outlook2010s.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.outlook2010s.com/&lt;/a&gt;;, Microsoft introduced the Ribbon Interface on some Outlook windows, primarily those associated with message views. Now it's all over the place, including the Inbox itself. As part of the Microsoft Office Fluent User Interface, it's designed to help you quickly find the commands you need.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As with Word and other Office programs (into which the Ribbon has been integrated long since), related tasks are grouped under tabs; with minor exceptions, menus are history. And here's something exciting: you can also add customized tabs to your ribbons to enhance your personal work style and thus maximize your productivity.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is a marvelous little feature located in the Mail view on the Home tab. With Quick Steps, you can set up one-click commands for the functions you use most often. This is especially handy for automating repetitive tasks. In addition to the custom options, there are several default Quick Steps with self-evident names, including Move to:, Forward: FYI (which uses FYI instead of FW when forwarding messages), To Manager, Team Email, Done, and Reply and Delete. All you have to do is configure them, and you're good to go.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sadly, a default Quick Step they left out is Get Me a Cup of Coffee, but I'm sure an enterprising manager could set this up as a custom command in about five minutes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not only can you now see more of your messages at once, thanks to the new Conversation View, it's easier than ever to organize them. Conversations are automatically grouped by date and subject, and you can expand or collapse those views with one click. And here's the kicker: you can quickly reduce the noise in your inbox by using two new features, Ignore Conversation and Clean Up Conversations.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're getting a lot of Forwards, FYIs or other stuff that you don't care to, instead of wading through and deleting the useless threads, just click the Ignore command in the Delete group on the Message tab. Up will pop a dialog box; click Ignore Conversation, and presto, the whole conversation is sent to Deleted Items purgatory. If you decide later that ignoring the conversation was a mistake, you can go back and click Ignore again. If the conversation is still in the Deleted Items folder, you can select Stop Ignoring Conversation, and it will reappear in your Conversation View.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Clean Up Conversations is just as useful. By default, Outlook saves the original message a sender is replying to at the bottom of their message. After a while, this can make for some long, space-wasting messages. You can use Clean Up to sweep any conversation or folder clean of all redundant messages, leaving only the most recent email that contains the entire conversation. Goodbye, clutter-hello productivity! As with the Ignore function, the cleaned-up messages go into the Deleted Items folder by default, where they can be recovered as long as the folder hasn't been emptied. You can configure the feature to send them elsewhere, if you like, and there are several other options to let you specify exactly what gets cleaned up when you click the button.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In addition to the big changes outlined above, there are a number of small but significant changes to the message interface. Now you can configure Outlook to automatically close a message after you reply, and even better, there's extended capacity to resend or recall messages.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.outlook2010s.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.outlook2010s.com/&lt;/a&gt;; is good.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In previous Outlook versions, these functions were possible, but only if you and your recipient were both using a Microsoft Exchange server. Now the only restriction is that your recipient is also using Outlook, and their settings are configured properly (this varies from version to version). The recall/resend may not succeed if their settings aren't right, but as one reviewer pointed out, it's worth a try.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ability to manage calendars has always been one of Outlook's most useful features. The calendaring function hasn't changed too much in this version, but it's been tweaked to be more streamlined, and the ability to share schedules and manage multiple calendars has improved noticeably.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The new Calendar Groups feature is amazingly helpful, for example, because it lets you see the calendars of the people you work with frequently. Once you've configured the feature, you can view all their calendars with ease, and you can even determine which meeting rooms or other resources are available for use. One new feature that you team leaders will appreciate is the ability to add your team members' schedules to your new and improved Schedule View, which makes it simple to schedule meetings by laying out resource, Individual, and Group calendars on a horizontal line so that you can more easily identify the best time to meet.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>