<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="93edfdece848d11b5673c30f1ce5e42f">			Nowadays, almost every single person in the world owns a mobile phone which has a lot of uses. One of their uses is mainly for communication - to reach friends, family members and colleagues. Relationships are improved and well maintained because of the help of    phones, wherever these people are, they can still talk or text.  Today, mobile phones are no longer used for its communication purposes alone; they are now used to browse the net because of mobile optimized web which enable us to use our mobile phones to search something. Since we are now able to browse using our mobile phones,    on android apps have likewise become common.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given this, different android apps are being introduced to us through mobile optimized web. Advertising on android apps using the mobile optimized web is deemed effective in the market since mobile phones, rather than personal computers, are now used mainly to browse something because it is more handy and can be used anywhere. There are a lot of advertised android apps that are available, which can really be useful like those which allow us to make our own music, fast calculators, games and a lot more.  Due to the fact that the popularity of mobile optimized web is undeniable, advertising on android apps is used to be noticed more easily and it is way cheaper than to advertise using other methods like tv commercials and billboards. Less money and efforts are used in advertising on android apps since advertisers do not necessarily pay their advertisements per minute or spend a lot of money in huge billboards just to be noticed by people.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Advertising on android apps are commonly done nowadays since a lot of high technology mobile phones are available in the market, with mobile optimized web that enables us to download android apps and browse, thus we can see easily if there are advertisements in it. With all the advantages brought to us by advertising on android apps, some disadvantages may also be apparent. One of the disadvantages is the lack of monitoring committee to see if the  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsummitstrategicvisions.com%2Fservices%2Fmobile-marketing"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://summitstrategicvisions.com/services/mobile-marketing&lt;/a&gt;  being posted in android apps meet the proper criteria of posting advertisements and if it is safe to be viewed by minors since today, even an eight year old kid have a mobile phone. Another disadvantage is that there could be advertisements that are not really reliable, we can’t be sure if the advertised products or services really offer high quality standards that will really benefit its users.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Also, there are advertisements present in android apps that can easily be purchased right away which could be not suitable for young ones, but because of the mobile optimized web, it can easily be done without parents’ consent or guidance. Advertisers on android apps should be more responsible and think of the welfare of the people who can see their advertisements to ensure that no harm can result because of their advertisements. They should be really honest with what they are advertising so the one that will buy their products will be satisfied and good qualities are ensured. Let us enjoy what the modern world brings us that help us to make life easier and satisfying.		</conversation>		<conversation id="fed5fd95b9831787f29b6f47df0a95bb">			We know for a fact that google is considered to be the leading search engine as well as an effective marketing tool for most advertisers today. Given this, many people believe that google has the potential to become successful in almost every endeavor that it sets its foot on. And when google ads android began to surge, many people think that this is google’s ultimate step to dominating the mobile market. But then again, for you to truly determine the value of android to google, you must first be able to identify the type of mobile market that they intend to dominate. Try to take a look at google’s history on the past projects that they were in and this will surely give you a brighter view on whether  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.facebook.com%2Fssvmobilemarketing"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.facebook.com/ssvmobilemarketing&lt;/a&gt;  is truly centered on encompassing the mobile market.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We all know that google had always been a lover of new applications and software. The company has tested its hands on many endeavors that use open source codes such as the google chrome. Projects such as these, in addition to google ads android, have so much significance to the company because of its aim to provide its users with the widest source of information. Primarily, google depends on its various applications, like that of google ads android in making a fortune for the company. The people who make use of these applications are the ones who bring the company millions of dollars every month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google ads android is one smart move for google to make sure that the people continue to make use of their products, even when mobile devices seem to be taking control of today’s technology. So is this google’s ultimate step into dominating the  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ssvmobilemarketing.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.ssvmobilemarketing.com&lt;/a&gt; ? Well, we could put it that way but it seems like google ads android is focused more on ensuring that internet users continue to patronize google products despite the mobile trend of today. And this is also one way to make sure that google continues to earn the revenue that it targets every month. You will find a lot of google applications that support ads such as google mail. Google ads android is a good way for them to ensure that even people who are using mobile devices in surfing the net can preview and make use of these different ads and applications.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Google dominated the advertising market as well as the search marketing since day one and google ads android is just a way for them to continue being the top search engine that they are today. Google aims to continue to be on top despite the threat that the changes in computing brought to them. Google ads android is the company’s first step, not necessarily to dominate the mobile market yet, but to make sure that they continue to enjoy the supremacy and the revenue that they are enjoying at present. But if google does just fine with google ads android, as they always did in their past projects, then definitely, google ads android is going to be their very first leap to dominating the mobile market.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>