<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="41bf4f3defac05030df5c9c9164984ce">			What on earth is the magic of the traditional British tea time facinating the British's appetite. Even if you have never enjoyed the English afternoon tea, after the waiter places the three-layer dessert on the table, you would feel the elaboration and European aristocrat breath of the tea immediately. After you taste desserts layer-by-layer, you can furtherly understand what delicious flavor make them keep eating.What's Most Sizzling now?: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52b2d1ZXNob3dzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;fashion clothing&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Usually the first layer is sorts of salt sandwiches like ham, cheese flavor and so on. Basic Knowledge about your Great &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52b2d1ZXNob3dzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;fashion clothing&lt;/a&gt;; But these sandwiches are not made by the chief but other sandwich cooks. The Latest Collections of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52b2d1ZXNob3dzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;fashion shoes&lt;/a&gt;; are Said to be the Most Dandy One Desserts are on the next two layers. On the second layer, there is usually the strawberry tart which is essential to the tea time. Besides this, there may be lotus, cookies or chocolates depending on the chef. There is no special requirement about the third layer’s setting. Instead, the chef selects suitable desserts for it, usually cakes and fruit tarts.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No matter how various the desserts are, the afternoon tea can't exist without the word of &quot;tea&quot;,which can be absolutely seen that &quot;tea&quot; is the hero. Special Afternoon tea can be divided into Darjeeling, Earl Grey Tea and Mint Tea. It is common that people brew the tea directly, using tea strainer to keep the leaves, and then pour the tea into cups for drinking. When the hot water is poured down from transparent glass teapot, the tea tip floating slowly in the water can be seen. The most beautiful is rose tea. When watching little rose petals dancing in the water, your mood also follows flying. The combination of black tea and milk is like a elegant noble encountering a distinguished gentleman. No matter a sip or a quaffing is comfortable and fantastic. In cold winter, a cup of hot milk tea is undoubtedly a recipe for warmth. Transiently slipping from tongue to stomach, a long time past a touch of sweet is still persisting in mouth, which makes people yearning. Teamilk can be matched with afternoon desserts as you like, no matter strong cheese flavor cakes, sweet choclate muffins or ramdon thick toasts and pineapple buns.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The bright afternoon sun is shining on the slightly closed eyes, put a peron in trance, and just like travelling in River Thames, unwilling to wake up.		</conversation>		<conversation id="99afad2b5b071500f2a2ae828a1ce668">			The charity auction of having lunch with the investment guru Warren Buffett auction for the history record of 2.11 million U.S. dollars which is surprised the world's richest man. Buffett has said recently,the lunch time with him would not be extended because of the high bid. However, the man who offered a higher price to get the opportunity before didn’t think it is wasteful. People who had spent 650,000 U.S. dollars buying the meal last year said that every cent they spent to talk with the investment guru was worth the &quot;value&quot;. This amount is three times of last year’s dining opportunities prices while hit eBay’s highest price of the charity auction event’s record.What is Most Attractive Gifts for Actresses? &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52b2d1ZXNob3dzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;fashion jewelry&lt;/a&gt;; !
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lunch price is rising year after year, but the time for dialogue is not long, why can this opportunity attract more and more people? Guy Spier, the U.S. Aquamarine Capital Management CEO, competed and got the opportunity last year to have lunch with Buffett as his wish. Afterwards, he explained with his own experience that it's worthy of money to hear the investment guru's view in such short distance.The Right time to Look Great With, The Best &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52b2d1ZXNob3dzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;fashion shoes&lt;/a&gt;; to Enjoy
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the process of the conversation, for every specific question Spier raised, Buffet invariably inspired him with simple but philosophic ideas. During lunch, Buffet often talked about his life and his principles on doing things. For example, his father taught him to rely on his own judgment instead of relying on others to judge when he was young. &quot;It is very important to live one’s own life according to his standard of inner heart,” Spier quoted Buffett’s saying. If you wanted to know whether you do things by following this principle, you only need to ask yourself a simple question that is whether you would like to be regarded as the best lover for the world and the worst for yourself, or whether you would like to be regarded as the best lover for yourself and the worst for the world? When those above ideas are applied to the investment, Buffett is doing extremely well: Completely trust in himselef, invest in “his own ability scope”, and cooperate with the people who has same values with him.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;During the late 1990s, cybereconomy had developed rapidly. Baffet was widely challenged as he was unwilling to invest in that field all the way, but he didn't in the least change his mind. When the bubble burst, people who calmed down from the investment fever began to understand Baffet. &quot;What a better model can you pursue?&quot; Spier said in the &quot;Time&quot; magazine, “two days later after we had lunch, the price for lunch of next year came out on eBay, 210 million. The fact is that: Our price, 65million is definitely a cheaper price. &quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On the day that he expressed his own opinion on the charity lunch, Buffet also visited the D&amp;Q, a food brand that owned by Berkshire Hathaway Cooperation, one of his companies and talked with 6 girl scouts there when he tried the latest ice cream. Buffett told these girls at middle school or college,&quot; before entering into the investment field, they 'd better do more reading.&quot; He also added, &quot;it will be much better if you have some thinking and research on investment.&quot; When Children asked the richest man, how could they arrange the finance in the university. Buffet answered, if you can, try to use less credit card, because of the high interest rate currently, students are easy to get involved into the credit debt. “If I borrow money when I was 18 or 20, I may very likely had broken.” he said.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inspired by the deceased wife Susan, since 2000, Buffett who have the &quot;stock god&quot; reputation auctions the opportunity to have lunch with him, and donated the money to the San Francisco Glide Foundation which can help relieve poverty, hunger and homeless people. The auction was held in Sanfranciso and had transfered to ebay since 2003.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>