<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="59fe603115e23941b6274709d898d4b3">			Raising your own herbs is simple to do and can be very gratifying as many herbs can be added to culinary dishes to enhance the flavor of our food. There is certainly only the requirement for small patches of garden or simple growing pots to grow a variety of herbs and most of what you need to get started can be found at your local garden center or nursery. So herbs have many uses and benefits - let's explore  that in some detail. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Almost certainly the most well-known use of herbs is in cooking, primarily to add taste but sometimes also color. Herbs are associated with cooking, and they are used even in the most basic and humble dishes like soups and salads. There may be something thrilling about using ingredients cultivated and harvested by yourself, and perhaps that helps to explain the lift they bring to the taste of many meat dishes. Quality recipes can be adjusted to bring new culinary satisfaction to meals that were becoming a little mundane and everyday.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Over the ages a variety of illnesses and ailments have been successfully treated with herbs, many of which are credited with curative powers.  You will uncover a wide range of remedies based around herbs if you conduct some research. Both dried and fresh herbs are being used, either by imbibing them in the form of teas or tinctures, or perhaps by applying them right to the affected area in the form of creams or poulltices. Peppermint tea is the perfect example of a therapy for an upset stomach and chamomile tea is renowned for its soothing effect and can help to calm you when taken before bedtime to help you gain a restful sleep.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pick or cut your excess herbs, which usually promotes further growth, and then dry them for keeping. Dehydrated herbs can once more be used in teas and added to cooking for additional flavor. They might also be stored when dry and used as adornment, such as adding to potpourri. The aromatic smell of dried herbs can easily calm and please at the same time. A bunch of dried lavender connected with twine and hung from a kitchen ceiling offers an attractive countryside feel and provides the lovely lavender color and scent.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A small garden or just a little space is sufficient to fruitfully grow herbs at home. In fact most herbs grow very well in pots and mint is a good example of this. Other plants grown near mint usually are not a good idea, since its active and lusty spreading habit will soon suffocate them. If grown within a pot, however, this tendency is well controlled. Do remember to water your potted herbs regularly, as with any other plant.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's easy to get children to participate in growing herbs at home, thereby introducing them to the rewards and fun of gardening. This may also get your children thinking about cooking by adding the herbs they have grown to dishes and helping them to explore different flavors. As a possible introduction, allow your children to sow some cress seeds inside of a pot on a windowsill - observing the growth process will fascinate them. Apart from the easiness with which it grows, cress also offers the fun and tasty benefit that it can be cut and added to their food.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Growing your own herbs will reward you in lots of ways so don't delay getting started.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a782381919059b9cb46108bef7dcb26">			Every individual I know has or had at one point, an iPod, no matter what model. Some folks may have more than one much like me, I have got both the iPod classic as well as the touch. Some men and women prefer the touch due to the look and features, the classic is able to store 160 GB of video or music which explains why this is my iPod of choice. In this article I am going to be going over a few things this unit presents to its owners.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Almost certainly you can imagine exactly what my favorite characteristic of this unit is. This particular unit has 160 GB of storage which makes this perfect for people who require loads of storage for their music or perhaps videos. Should you look at my iPod classic you would find out that there are over 50 films and even more than 10,000 songs on it. This leaves over 80 GB of storage left on this unit but if all that data ended up being on my iPod touch I wouldn't have any space left. Which again, makes this the clear choice when it comes to a device that can provide lots of storage.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For anyone who just want to store movies on their iPod, you can save around 200 hours of video with the use of this unit. I've got a sibling that ordered one of these just to have something to kill time while he is traveling for his job. I was genuinely surprised when he explained to me that he has more than 125 movies on his iPod. He does obviously, remove as well as add new movies on a regular basis.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is simply not used just for movies though, since you can easily also store a large amount of music also. There is one individual I know which uses a couple of these types of iPods to D.J. with. I was actually surprised myself to learn that just one of these iPods can store about 40,000 songs. If every single song is about 3 minutes long, that works out to be 2,000 hours of music. And when you do a bit more math you will realize that you will be able to listen to your tunes for 12 hours each and every day, for a grand total of 166 days and you would not need to hear the same song again. This is definitely what I call a lot of storage.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Photos are one more thing you can make use of this iPod for. Should you be a photographer and you solely store pictures on the device you can in fact keep up to 25,000 photos. Another thing you can do using this product is to use it to show slide shows of your photographs on your TV. One more thing individuals like is the fact that iTunes permits you to create image transitions and add music to slide shows you produce.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I am certain you can realize why this is my personal favorite unit. If you opt to acquire one of these, I would suggest purchasing it through Amazon as you can save some money off the retail price. Amazon is now marketing this unit for $229, and also supplying free shipping for your purchase. This unit is really one of the better devices and if your thinking of getting your first iPod, I would certainly highly recommend this one. This product is really cheaper than the iPod touch but it is more  costly  than some  of  the  more  basic  iPods.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>