<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="111ca221901c02e9f728597ff4b12918">			India is an astounding country with varied culture and traditions, sects and religion, language and dialects. Every part of India being different on its behavior in terms of its traditional and folk values somehow tends to connect with each other. People here are physically different but their heart connects with each other. Everything is unique about this great democratic country. Its people, monuments, places, language, dialects, music, dance, food, and climate everything is wonderful about this great nation. It is amazing from great Himalayas to Thar Desert, from Kashmir to Kanyakumari. The two extreme K’s of India Kashmir and Kanyakumari tells a story about how vivid is the country. Whether it is the climatic condition or from the cultural perspective India is beautiful in every aspect.
&lt;br /&gt;;India has wide range of places to be visited when it comes to tourism both national and international. Whether it is historical place, sanctuaries, national parks, lakes, tea gardens, backwaters of Kerala or beautiful hill stations. Most popular tourist places during your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;India trip&lt;/a&gt;; include Kerala, Tamil Nadu, Delhi, Agra, Jaipur, Goa, Mysore, Udaipur, Nainital, Pondicherry etc. Visiting these places will make the travelers understand different culture of different states. It will give the travelers the true taste of India. One will understand the actual India and will find him/her dwelling with an Indian heart in Indian soil. Travelers will come across different colors of incredible India. India also known as ‘Bharat’ in Hindi language is a perfect delight for international travelers. This country is a perfect blend of unity in diversity, this is why it is known as incredible India. Tourists who visit India for the first time fall in love with this wonderful nation. India is a country which is known for its relation building makes tourists delighted with its charming characteristics.
&lt;br /&gt;;One experiences the vibrant India when one lands in its capital. Delhi also known as ‘Dilli’ is commonly called as ‘Dilwaalon ki Dilli’ which in English means Delhi belongs to people of heart. Delhi is countries capital and one of the best tourist destinations of India. It houses important buildings like Supreme Court, Rashtrapati Bhavan, and Parliament House. There are various places which depicts the history and glory of the capital and the country, whether monumental structures, food joints, shopping places etc. Places which must be visited by international tourists are Lotus Temple, Birla Mandir, India Gate, Akshardham Temple, Jantar Mantar, Jama Masjid, Humayun’s Tomb, Red Fort, National Museum and many other monumental structures with great history. There are amazing shopping places like Lajpat Nagar, Sarojni Nagar, Karol Bagh, Pahar Ganj, Dilli Haat, these places are very popular among the masses and are perfect spots for the tourist to shop.
&lt;br /&gt;;There are other places which are miraculously beautiful in India, Jaipur and Agra is among them. This trip is famous among the travelers it is the complete blend of North-Indian flavor. Jaipur is the known as the pink city and is the capital of the royal state of India that is Rajasthan. Jaipur is known for its beautifully build palaces and templAgra which houses the living example of love Taj Mahal is a delight among tourists.
&lt;br /&gt;;All these places win the heart of international travelers in their first visit itself and are perfect for international traveler.
&lt;br /&gt;;Sara Hasan is a travel writer, has traveled almost the entire India. Currently she is writing informative articles on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;Trip to India&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;India Trip&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;India Tours and Packages&lt;/a&gt;;. For more information explore &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.divinevoyages.in"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.divinevoyages.in&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="1f5dd1f145c9c8b45aa25c38647faff8">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;India Trip&lt;/a&gt;; are always exciting especially when it is with your loved ones. Culture and tradition plays a dominant role in building ones opinion about a place one is visiting. If you are looking for a place with strong cultural values and amazing colorful traditions India is the right choice for you.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;India is the land of amazing cultures, majestic monuments, arts-crafts, Ayurveda and delicious cuisine. India is blessed with beautiful places whether hill stations, monuments, religious places etc. India has a great history. It is a vivacious country of colorful people with different traditional and cultural background. Each and every state of the country has different dialects; language, tradition, culture and regional festivals, there are festivals which are common to all, to which the entire nation celebrates together. The main festivals of the country are Deepawali, Holi, Eid and Christmas. India has a great history and culture that is why it attracts travelers from all around the globe. India is a country of wonders whether it comes to its people their religion, food or tradition they follow. It is the perfect destination to explore among travelers. There are places right from Kashmir to Kanyakumari and east to west which have diverse and miraculous monumental history as well surprising folk cultures. The folk culture of India cannot be expressed in words; it is so beautiful and amazing that one can only feel its warmth when one visits the heart of India.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are several places to be visited by tourists from the cultural aspect, to name few places- Delhi, the capital of the country. It is situated on the banks of Yamuna river. It beholds great history and culture. Prime locations of the place include Red Fort, India Gate, Akshardham Temple, Birla Temple, Jantar Mantar, National Museum, Humayun’s Tomb, Jama Masjid etc. Agra is another place which must be visited by every traveler as it houses the great monument of love and dedication of Emperor Shah Jahan towards her wife Mumtaj Mahal in the form of one of the seven wonders of the world ‘Taj Mahal’. Other attractions include Red Fort and Fatehpur Sikri. Jaipur is among the best places which has beautiful palaces. It is also known as the pink city. Hawa Mahal, Birla Temple, Sheesh Mahal, Nahargarh Fort, Jal Mahal etc. are few amazing sites to be visited by tourists as it shows the culture and tradition of different places. These are among the best destination to be visited by travelers in North India. Apart from such wonderful places in northern India the Southern part of India also has many beautiful and lovely places. Kerala which is also known as ‘God’s own country’ is among the best destination in India. It is considered to be the paradise of southern India. It is situated among the lush green trees which make it an amazing place, its hill stations, majestic backwaters, forts are very attractive. Kerala is also famous among honeymooners and is a perfect trip for an individual or a family. Other places in India like Ooty, Pondicherry, Madurai, Kanyakumari, Mysore, Orissa, Gujarat, Rajasthan, Kolkatta, Nanital, Vrindavan, Mathura are worth visiting.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;India is the right destination for culture lovers as it has different cultures of different regions which blend beautifully with each other. Thus, travelers must visit India for a cultural twist.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sara Hasan is a travel writer, has travelled almost the entire India. Currently she is writing informative articles on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;Trip to India&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;India Trip&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZpbmV2b3lhZ2VzLmlu" target="_blank"&gt;;India Tours and Packages&lt;/a&gt;;. For more information explore &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.divinevoyages.in"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.divinevoyages.in&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>