<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d39a224d4d858a4347585c71299c6a10">			Pampering in the City of Light doesn't get a total great deal better than this.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Villa La Cupola Suite - Westin Excelsior, Rome&lt;/u&gt; - The Everlasting City gives up its very own reasonable share of opulence and extravagance for people who want to go after it, and few areas do so a lot more elegantly than the Villa La Cupola Suite at the Westin Excelsior. At about ??twenty,000 for every evening, the greatest suite in Italy - along with its 12-metre-large domed dwelling area ceiling - is out of this world.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Presidential Suite - Hotel Cala di Volpe, Costa Smerelda, Sardinia&lt;/u&gt; - If you'd like to invest a night in the split-level, a few bedroom Presidential Suite at Sardinia's Lodge Cala di Volpe, you'd greater have ??22,000 helpful. Its best function? A personal, outdoor saltwater pool in which you can soak absent all of your anxieties.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Ty Warner Penthouse - 4 Seasons, New York City&lt;/u&gt; - A one evening stay in the extravagant Ty Warner Penthouse suite in New York's Four Seasons Resort will operate you nearly ??23,000. With flooring-to-ceiling glass windows, eight-metre-large cathedral ceilings and glass balconies, this I.M. Pei-created suite is unforgettable.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;u&gt;The Royal Penthouse Suite - President Wilson Lodge, Geneva&lt;/u&gt; - With a price tag tag of more than ??42,000 for every night, the Royal Penthouse Suite at the President Wilson Hotel in Geneva won't be a best pick amongst last moment rooms. The suite, which occupies the complete top rated flooring of the lodge and offers bulletproof glass, is a favorite of diplomats. If you are looking for the grandest final moment resorts, this one particular ought to do nicely.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The spot of Gatlinburg delivers so numerous vacationer sights such as amusement parks and a bountiful normal elegance that draws in a good deal of visitors from neighborhood to foreign nations. The location is ample with natural and man- created points of interest which can be liked by vacationers. For the adventurous folks, Gatlinburg provides a lot of hiking trails and induce its vacationers the eye- catching elegance of the mountains and waterfalls close to the place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A selection of resorts are offered alongside the region that gives great services and features for the ease and comfort of their guests. Rooms have shared or personal baths and in-place displays point out availability of the shared baths. The shared loos characteristic rainfall shower heads, drinking water jets built into the sides, and streaming songs. Non-public loos also have rainfall shower heads (no jets), alongside with sleek stainless-steel sinks. The Pod also gives suites with normal TVs, personal bogs, and dwelling regions with couch beds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resort 31 NYC - Midtown East&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reflecting the eclectic, cosmopolitan individuality of New York Metropolis by itself, each and every of the 60 rooms in the eight-story Lodge 31 have their own unique ornamental design and style. Trendy, comfy, and quite affordably priced, Hotel 31 offers lodging for the discerning traveler on a spending budget.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Vanderbilt YMCA - Midtown East&lt;/strong&gt; (close to the UN)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Giving lodges for price range vacationers from each and every continent, seven YMCAs in New York Metropolis provide great price for website visitors who want to experience NYC's multifaceted neighborhoods as effectively as its fabled internet sites and amusement venues. This makes them the best washing devices for cleaning commercial kitchen areas in hotels and dining places.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhdGhob3RlbGRlYWxzLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;cheap bath hotel&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>