<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="12cc8e0651e0f0830dc0dc0bb1c44358">			Key facts about getting an FHA Mortgage in Denver &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RlbnZlcm1vcnRnYWdlLnBybw__" target="_blank"&gt;Denver FHA Mortgage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you live in Denver and are considering purchasing your first home, you owe it to yourself to learn about the FHA program. &lt;br /&gt;FHA Loans 101 &lt;br /&gt;FHA stands for the Federal Housing Administration.  FHA has several programs in place which are primarily tasked with encouragin home ownership. The FHA allows participants to get loans for homes while providing less of a down payment when compared to a conventional mortgage. This is permitted by banks because each FHA loan is backed by the FHA itself. So, if the borrower ends up not paying back the loan, the FHA guarantees they will pay the loan off so banks never have to worry about writing off a defaulted loan.  &lt;br /&gt;Who Qualifies For An FHA Mortgage? &lt;br /&gt;The FHA program is set up to let the majority of people qualify.  Conventional mortgage typically have income requirements, FHA does not really consider income.  FHA does require a credit score of 640+.  Conventional loans can require a downpayment of up to 20%, FHA loans require only 3.5% down. Of course, to prevent putting people in a position to fail, FHA does also look at an applicants debt to income ratio.  Chances are, if you cannot qualify for a FHA loan you will likely not qualify for a conventional mortgage.  If you don't qualify for an FHA loan, don't despair.  If you work with your loan officer and correct your shortcomings, you will be in your new house before you know it.  &lt;br /&gt;What Else Can FHA Do For You? &lt;br /&gt;As well as a lower down payment and lower required credit score, there are other advantages that come with having a Denver FHA mortgage such as: &lt;br /&gt;Elimination of prepayment penalty.  (This can be especially good for subprime loan recipients).&lt;br /&gt;Another part of the FHA program is FHA 203k funding.  This program will fund certain types of home improvements to protect the homeowner from heavy intial repair costs.&lt;br /&gt;FHA is much more willing to accept money you get as a gift to make your downpayment or cover closing costs.&lt;br /&gt;•	“Assumable” in certain circumstances, which means it can be taken over by someone else. &lt;br /&gt;So, Why Would You Not Choose An FHA Loan? &lt;br /&gt;The most significant restriction to the FHA loan program is the maximum loan amount. The maximum loan amount is set based on the county, with $406,250 being the current limit for Denver. On 4/9/2012 FHA began requiring private mortgage insurance or PMI.  Currently PMI is 1.75% of loan amount at closing and 1.15% per year, paid monthly for the first five years of the loan. This insurance has to be carried for a minimum of five years regardless of how much money you put down. &lt;br /&gt;PMI may not be required for conventional mortgages.  PMI protects the FHA from defaulted loan debt. It is PMI that allows the FHA to accept applicants who might otherwise be perceived as too risky.  &lt;br /&gt;FHA Loans Are The Fastrack To The American Dream Of Home Ownership &lt;br /&gt;The FHA was created to help those who could not otherwise qualify for a mortgage.  After all, not everyone has a 5, 10, or 20% downpayment saved up.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>