<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="90040e45b17c1a9f8bb87ffc11a891fb">			Having a healthy and successful relationship with money is a difficult prospect for many people. That is why it is important that you are able to manage your personal finances. If you keep reading, you will learn a lot of great advice on how to deal with your finances for the rest of your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I've read so many books about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4xc291cmNlNHN0b2Nrcy5jb20vc3RvY2tfbWFya2V0X2Jhc2ljcy90eXBlc19vZl9zdG9ja190cmFkaW5nLmFzcA__" target="_blank"&gt;types of stock trading&lt;/a&gt;, yet, the best way to stay ahead financially is to watch how you handle your money.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use your earnings and your expenditures together to determine your budget. First, figure out how much money you make in a month, after taxes. Don't forget any secondary sources of income. You should never spend more in a month than you make.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To build a good budget, the next step is to understand your cash flow. List all of your expenditures, including recurring expenses like regular monthly bills and groceries, as well as less regular expenses, like money spent on dining out, or the occasional coffee at work. Also, include other people's expenses, such as your spouse. Don't forget to account for bills that are paid quarterly, semi-annually or annually. Make sure your list is accurate and all-inclusive so that you have complete look at where your money is going.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should be able to establish a budget now so that you know exactly how much income you can generate. Make sure you list any recurring expenses and eliminate anything unnecessary. For example, many people find that they can save money by bringing a sack lunch to work rather than buying something on the go. Look for other ways you can reduce the money you spend.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Making repairs or updating your electrical and plumbing systems can lower your utility bills. When you invest on weatherizing your home, you can save money on utilities. Tankless water heaters heat the water as its being used and help save on energy. If you notice abnormally high water usage, the culprit might be pipes that leak. Hire a plumber to check for and seal up pipes and fixtures that leak water. Only run your dishwasher when you fill it up.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have older appliances, replace them with newer models which are much more energy-efficient. It's true that these may be more expensive, but the savings will add up along the way. Unplug the appliances you do not need. You will start to see a difference in your energy use over time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quick References&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Check your insulation and roof to make sure that damages are not tempering with the efficiency of your heating and cooling systems. These upgrades are a sure-fire way to significantly lower your utility bills.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These ideas will help you balance your income and your expenses. These will help you embark on the journey to saving money. Try to change your older appliances out for newer ones that are more energy efficient. Using these methods will help you better control your finances.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d47b153423aeb8a46dc2ea95912a737e">			Making slipups is an element of trading. The trick is to be certain that the mistakes you will make are small - they do not cost you as much capital! For example - one of the biggest mistakes most people make is putting off investing. If you're in your 20's, time is on your side - as is the magic of compound interest.  Most people put off investing until they are in their 40's or even later. This means you need to put more money away, just to catch up. Your cash can begin working for you. Start small, say, with $30 a week -- you may be astonished at how fast it grows. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Surprisingly, not investing, or putting it off until later in life is not the biggest mistake you can make.  The number one mistake is to start investing before your personal finances are in order. Don't start investing until your current financial situation is straightened out. If you are investing in the hopes of making money to pay off credit cards, you'll find emotion will be the deciding factor in your investment decisions. Get your credit cleaned up, pay off high interest loans and credit cards, and put at least three months of living expenses in savings. Now you are ready to start making your money work for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Don’t invest to get rich quick. That is the riskiest type of investing that there is, and you will more than likely lose. If were so easy to make money with those high risk investments, don't you think everyone would be doing it?  Trading &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4xc291cmNlNHN0b2Nrcy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;penny stocks&lt;/a&gt; can be done in a succesful method.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Instead, invest for the long term, and have the patience to weather the storms and allow your money to grow. On the other hand, if your focus is short term, then look at low risk investments. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You've heard the cliche &quot;;don't put your eggs into one basket&quot;;. There is a reason why it seems so true. Spread your money around different types of investments. You'll find this will lower the risk, and even provide better, more consistent returns. Another smart thing is to avoid moving your money around. Active investors do not do as well as those who let their money work for them. Let it ride. Pick your investments carefully, invest your money, and allow it to grow - don’t panic if the stock drops a few dollars. The markets move up and down. Follow your plan - if your stop gets hit, or your market timer says to change direction, then follow it. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When your nest egg has grown to a significant amount, then look at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4xc291cmNlNHN0b2Nrcy5jb20vZnV0dXJlcy9pbmRleC5hc3A_" target="_blank"&gt;investing in futures&lt;/a&gt; or trading options.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Due to antique road shows, everybody thinks that their collectors items are worth lots of money. Odds are, they aren't. It may be worth a lot of money to you, but odds are, its not worth as much as you think. Your retirement account won't be paid for by selling your comic book collection unless you get really lucky. Do you want to plan your retirement around luck? Count on investments made with cold hard cash instead. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By avoiding these simple mistakes, you can in fact build a nest egg that will pay for youre retirement. You can make more money by putting away small amounts when you are in your 20's, than larger amounts (know anyone in their 40's with large amounts of money&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /&gt; when you are 40. If you're no longer in your 20's, its not too late. It just means you'll have to put away larger amounts of money. The important thing is to start now. What are you waiting for?		</conversation>	</conversations></author>