<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7edc41e4578282a12bb04783e3ebfc1">			Preventing a cough write by &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWRpYS1hbGF0a2VzZWhhdGFuLmNvbS90ZW5zaW1ldGVy" target="_blank"&gt;;tensimeter digital&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There really is lost which way to prevent coughing but there are plenty of things you're able to do to reduce the associated risk of cough.&lt;br /&gt;;* Rinse hands frequently, especially any time coughing &amp; flu season.&lt;br /&gt;;* Avoid contact with those people who are experiencing fever and influenza.&lt;br /&gt;;* Don't smoke / use cigarettes products.&lt;br /&gt;;* Avoid contact with smoke smoker / secondary secondhand both in your house and at work.&lt;br /&gt;;* Drink water to avoid dehydration elbow.&lt;br /&gt;;* For older children, make sure they have all appropriate primary immunization schedule.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The most common cause of cough is an infection / inflammation of the respiratory tract due to microorganisms virus / germs. Coughing is usually with a runny nose, and sinus congestion. Cough which permitted to drag on without a verifiable actions lead to complications. Complications of cough is composed of three kinds, namely the sudden attack which may cause syncope (fainting / lack of consciousness while), coughing good or intense can cause rupture in the alveoli in the lung, together with fractured ribs. To that end prior to the cough becomes more dangerous require for prevention efforts and initiatives to overcome them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Below are a few tips / ways to counteract and treat a cough productive advisors:&lt;br /&gt;;1. Drink water at least 8 glasses a day to thin the mucus.&lt;br /&gt;;two. Bath of warm water can certainly help thin phlegm / mucus making it easier on batukkan.&lt;br /&gt;;3. Avoid usage of alcohol / caffeine may increase the frequency of urination to boost the discharge&lt;br /&gt;;body. Body fluids is necessary to keep the phlegm / mucus remains weak.&lt;br /&gt;;several. Quitting smoking, avoiding contact with dust, the environment is actually too dry or way too cold.&lt;br /&gt;;5. Keep your system warm and resting knee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Handling of cough in children&lt;br /&gt;;Try to calm your youngster. Crying causes breathing becomes tougher. Try to distract them with reading books / invite to play.&lt;br /&gt;;If available, try turning on tk humidifier moisturizes air and let the air in the humidifier on my face your youngster.&lt;br /&gt;;If not help, try the bathroom and turn on the hot shower water to provide steam. Close the bathroom door and allow child inhale steam a few minutes. Remember not to children exposed to the water is as well hot &amp; not leave children alone inside bathroom.&lt;br /&gt;;If not allow, try to take children out to breathe the night air.&lt;br /&gt;;Do not give coughing medicine pd children with 2 years unless many experts have examined by a health practitioner before. If the doctor recommends taking your youngster, follow the instructions using correct.&lt;br /&gt;;Never give children antibiotics right after they cough before getting instructions out of your doctor. Although sometimes the curability cough without medical science, but on certain circumstances verifiable severe cough &amp; really disturbing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Productive cough&lt;br /&gt;;Called each time a productive cough when cough is associated with the discharge of phlegm jg. Sputum which could have emerge from the nose and sinuses can jg of the esophagus and lungs. Productive cough truly suppressed because the actual function is to cleanse the respiratory tract of phlegm.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Non Successful cough&lt;br /&gt;;Its non-productive cough is usually dry and remove phlegm so often called a dry coughing. Dry cough usually appears on the end of flu symptoms / irritation as a result of dust and cigarette smoke.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>