<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="1350c588d501c1c3d792121b8952e631">			Winter is almost here and love is in the air yes autumn is here, you see people going outside once again and sitting down the park holding hands and whispering softly to one another expressing their love and affection from their deepest heart, and eating &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ralphlaurenpoloscheap.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bralph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ralphlaurenpoloscheap.com&quot;&gt;;ralph&lt;/a&gt;; lauren jackets&lt;/a&gt;; picnic lunches. Winter is almost here and love is in the air yes autumn is here, you&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren jackets&lt;/a&gt;; see people going outside once again and sitting down the park holding hands and whispering softly to one another expressingtheir love and affection from their deepest heart, and eating picnic lunches.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even the little birds and squirrels are roaming around and starting to make their nests. So, the pleasing Ralph Lauren perfume and cologne make your autumn wedding perfect with its fragrances. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2h0dHA6Ly93d3cucmFscGhsYXVyZW5wb2xvc2NoZWFwLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren clothes&lt;/a&gt;;was born in 1939 at Bronx New York and he discovers a grand fragrance of Ralph Lauren Cool Women launched in 2004. It has a special character fragrance that captured the interest of the public around the world. Many perfumers produce different Perfume and cologne on the market now a day ?all attempting to produce something special fragrances that will attract the people all over the modern world. However few have been successful in attracting the heart of people with its wonderful soft and sweet fragrance. One of among them is Ralph Lauren perfume and cologne that was enjoyed by the young boys and girls in the romantic fashion generation. It's Some of the most demanded fragrances are Ralph rock, Glamorous Daylight, Polo spot, Ralph Lauren Blue, Love Women, Polo Explorer, Romance men etc. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ralph Lauren Perfume fragrances give us cool, fresh, relaxed, and active, that stimulates our brain.?Creating its first plunder into fragrances in 1978, Ralph Lauren Perfume innovate Polo for men and Lauren for women to the fashion Men Hoodies market. Later on he introduced one after another of different perfume and cologne according to Men Jackets &amp; Outerwear the requirement of public in modern world. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2h0dHA6Ly93d3cucmFscGhsYXVyZW5wb2xvc2NoZWFwLmNvbS9tZW4tc2hvcnRzLWMtOC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren shorts&lt;/a&gt;; comes in different product like body lotion, body cream, body spray, deodorant etc. The products were embraced by each and every consumer because it fulfills the need and requirement for all type of body chemistry. Due to special flavor Ralph Lauren Perfume makes us handsome, beautiful and charming. The glamorous perfume of Ralph Lauren love women is one of the top lists in demand. Ralph Lauren perfume and cologne for men and women fragrances are attractive, eye-catching that makes you more gorgeous since the smell is long lasting and can be wear any time. Ralph Lauren Perfume Men Shorts can be obtained from the internet easily with reasonable prices.Place your order now and get Men Shirts your favorite Perfume and enjoy it.		</conversation>		<conversation id="31b1d9be9e5433179629288e763049b8">			Ralph Lauren revolutionized American&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9cmFscGgrbGF1cmVuK2hvb2RpZXMmYW1wO3g9MTImYW1wO3k9MA__" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren hoodies&lt;/a&gt;; and the Bronx, New York native's take on what he thought was &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren boots&lt;/a&gt;; appropriate clothing should be affected men of all walks of life. His 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL21lbi1zaG9ydHMtYy04Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren shorts&lt;/a&gt;; brand was embraced by hip hop and gang culture in a big way using bold iconography, graphics and color. While the pony logo &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9cmFscGglMjBsYXVyZW4lMjBqYWNrZXRzJmFtcDtpbmNfc3ViY2F0PTAmYW1wO3NvcnQ9MjBhJmFtcDtwYWdlPTQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren jackets&lt;/a&gt;; will always remain hot sellers, the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9cmFscGglMjBsYXVyZW4lMjBzd2VhdGVycyZhbXA7aW5jX3N1YmNhdD0wJmFtcDtzb3J0PTIwYSZhbXA7cGFnZT00" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren sweaters&lt;/a&gt;; Rugby brand brought a whole new twist on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren polo for cheap&lt;/a&gt;; and casual collared shirts. Influenced by &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Ralph Lauren Outlet&lt;/a&gt;; numbering, these bold takes on the polo helped with the resurgence of collegiate style among men of all ages. Lacoste's take on the classic tennis and golf &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9cmFscGgrbGF1cmVuK3BvbG8rc2hpcnRzJmFtcDt4PTExJmFtcDt5PTEz" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren polo shirts&lt;/a&gt;; has brought levity to the style that is sometimes deemed too stuffy and sale &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9Y2hlYXArcmFscGgrbGF1cmVuK3BvbG8rc2hpcnRzJmFtcDt4PTEyJmFtcDt5PTk_" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap ralph lauren polo shirts&lt;/a&gt;; for most men. The brand's signature bright and unexpected shades for men like hot pink, clementine orange and pale aqua, make taking a risk with color easier thanks to the clean silhouette. Much like &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9cmFscGgrbGF1cmVuK3BvbG8rdCtzaGlydHMmYW1wO3g9MTImYW1wO3k9Nw__" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren polo t shirts&lt;/a&gt;; line, Lacoste also relies on their signature alligator to sell &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren clothes&lt;/a&gt;; thanks to key branding. They've toyed with the use of over-sized gators on the chest pocket and remixed it with &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9tYWluX3BhZ2U9YWR2YW5jZWRfc2VhcmNoX3Jlc3VsdCZhbXA7c2VhcmNoX2luX2Rlc2NyaXB0aW9uPTEmYW1wO2tleXdvcmQ9cmFscGgrbGF1cmVuK3NoaXJ0cyZhbXA7eD0xMSZhbXA7eT0xMQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap ralph lauren shirts&lt;/a&gt;; touches like embroidered numbers for a fresh take on the 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap ralph lauren polo&lt;/a&gt;;.The most recent interpretation of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap ralph lauren clothes&lt;/a&gt;; is the use of mixed materials to inject a different kind of color pop.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ee12f7418704d5291a5a97fd0698e836">			Lord &amp; Taylor was the first high-end American department store, founded in 1826. It has always featured the best clothing and products that money can buy, and continues to do so on its website as well as in its stores. MyReviewsNow is excited to bring you online shopping for upscale mens fashion at Lord &amp; Taylor, featuring brands such as &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap ralph lauren polo shirts&lt;/a&gt;;, Sperry, Cole Haan, and Lord &amp; T'aylor's own brand, Black Brown 1826.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This summer it is simple to look your fashionable best by following their online shopping guide, plus another provided by &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren jackets&lt;/a&gt;;. Here you will find all the key looks available in every style, color, and size. The look is nonchalant and comfortable. Bermuda shorts are hot this year, in many colors and fabrics, from khaki to madras plaid. These shorts are topped by the indispensable polo shirt in every conceivable color and pattern, from bright solids to stripes, and even to florals. There are tees for a more casual appearance, some sporting various &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren clothes&lt;/a&gt;;o marine graphics; they are ideal for showing off a trim midriff and toned biceps. Plaid shirts are also popular, from fitted work shirts to loose-cut gingham camp shirts, great for layering over tees. The Ralph Lauren look takes classics like military-style and safari shirts, making them extra sharp and appealing for everyday wear.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The key to this summer's look is layering, which adds a relaxed quality to elements that would look too reserved or understated on their own. You can mix and match these wardrobe basics to your heart's content, and be confident that they all work together in a stylish way. Layer a polo shirt over a tee, wear them over a pair of plaid Bermuda shorts, and toss a cotton crewneck sweater around your shoulders. Strap on a rugged retro sports watch, slip on a pair of classic Sperry Topsiders, and you're good to go.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lord &amp; Taylor's featured brands, besides &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yYWxwaGxhdXJlbnBvbG9zY2hlYXAuY29tL21lbi1zaG9ydHMtYy04Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren shorts&lt;/a&gt;; include Perry Ellis, Marc New York, Calvin Klein, Buffalo Jeans, Alex Cannon, CK Jeans, Diesel, Hugo, Indigo Palms, Lucky, Nautica, Seven for All Mankind, and classic Levis. There are items by Hart Schaffner Marx, and Joseph Abboud. Incidentally, MyReviewsNow would like to point out that Abboud is the creative director of mens fashion at L &amp; T, providing the entire collection with the advantage of a designer's perspective.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Online shopping for mens fashion accessories is simplified at Lord &amp; Taylor, where you can find sunglasses by Ray-Ban, Armani Exchange, Carrera, Guess, Kenneth Cole Reaction, Polo, and Mali Jim. Look sharp in a Bailey straw fedora, or wear the best linen baseball cap by Kangol. If those don't suit, try Stetson's bucket hats or driver's caps in linen or chambray. There are elegant and comfortable slippers by Ugg Australia and L. B. Evans, and belts by Perry Ellis and Cole Haan.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Watches of every kind are available, from intriguing Victorinox Swiss sports watches to brightly-colored specimens from Swatch and Rumba Time. There are also selections from Citizen, Armani, Seiko, Movado, Burberry, Bulova, Kenneth Cole New York, Skagen Denmark, Timex, Michael Kors, G-Shock Baby G, and Fossil. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Lord &amp; Tayolr website offers a full range of mens grooming products and fragrances from Gucci, Dior, Jean Paul Gaultier, Thierry Mugler, Armani, Marc Jacobs, Burberry, Prada, Clinique, Calvin Klein, Dolce &amp; Gabbana, Givenchy, Boucheron, and many more.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>