<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="3ec1a6941fc48993be303e685de84bda">			&lt;strong&gt;;February 2, 2011 – Paris, France&lt;/strong&gt;; – the online directory of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxidWRnZXRwYXJpc2hvdGVscy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;budget hotels in Paris&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; that offers low hotel rates and great deals from budget to luxury accommodations &lt;strong&gt;;– All Budget Paris Hotels –&lt;/strong&gt;; has been listing affordable, popular hotels in the “City of Light.”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;All Budget Paris Hotels&lt;/strong&gt;; has a list of budget Paris hotels where tourists from all over the world can have a memorable stay. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As they stop for a sojourn in one of the world’s most expensive cities, tourists will find their pockets not dwindling that much when they choose to book with budget hotels in Paris. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Paris budget hotels on &lt;strong&gt;;All Budget Paris Hotels&lt;/strong&gt;; list are located in different parts of the city but just a stone’s throw away from the city’s notable landmarks such as the world-renowned Eiffel Tower, popular bars and restaurants, shopping malls, theaters and shops.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These popular budget hotels in Paris offer room amenities that are as nice as those of luxury hotels such as air conditioning, direct dial phone, safe, satellite TV, mini bar, comfortable beds, baby cots and more. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Plus, tourists will get to enjoy staying in these Paris budget hotels because of fine facilities such as restaurants, luggage rooms, lift/elevator, wireless Internet connection, tourist information desk and many more. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Budget hotels in Paris employs courteous, multilingual staff always ready to serve their guests. Tourists’ needs will be taken cared of with a minimum of language trouble. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Accommodation in budget Paris hotels only costs between €30 and €350 for a single night’s stay. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whether in a honeymoon, business trip or a family vacation, tourists will find their stay in Paris budget hotels with all its pleasant ambiance, nice facilities and courteous staff an unforgettable experience! 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Book budget Paris hotels now at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxidWRnZXRwYXJpc2hvdGVscy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.allbudgetparishotels.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.allbudgetparishotels.com/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="2639c56a69b19cc95aca0d9a3e95e24a">			&lt;strong&gt;;February 03, 2011 – Paris, France –&lt;/strong&gt;; the online budget Paris hotels search site &lt;strong&gt;;– All Budget Paris Hotels –&lt;/strong&gt;; has been featuring &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxidWRnZXRwYXJpc2hvdGVscy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Paris budget hotels&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; near top tourist destinations of the city.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These Paris budget hotels are located just steps away from the city’s top tourist destinations like the Eiffel tower, the Louvre, Notre Dame Cathedral, Champs Elysées and the Pantheon. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First on budget hotels in Paris list is the L'hotel Duquesne Eiffel which is located near the Eiffel Tower and Champs de Mars. With a quiet and discreet atmosphere, Hotel Duquesne Eiffel is a good place for rest and relaxation. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Located less than 500 meters from the Louvre and Jardin des Tuileries, Hotel Louvre Richelieu is one of the budget Hotels in Paris that offer a short-distance walk to many of the city’s best shopping areas and many of Paris’ main attractions. One station of the Pyramides, the city’s mass transport system, is just a stone’s throw away from the hotel too!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hotel Castex is a fully-airconditioned hotel located in the historical Marais district of Central Paris, close to the Bastille and is within walking distance of the Notre Dame.  It is one of the budget hotels in Paris that boasts of 17th century style furnishings, spacious and comfortable rooms. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whether for business or pleasure trip, Hotel Madeleine Plaza is an ideal place to stay in Paris with modern facilities, excellent service and elegant ambiance. Madeleine Plaza is near the Opera, Place de la Concorde, Champs Elysées and Paris’ famous department stores. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the heart of the Latin Quarter, Au Royal-Cardinal Hotel is a walking distance from the Pantheon and the Sorbonne. This simple yet elegant hotel is near to two underground stations and is surrounded by bars and restaurants.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A night stay in one of these budget Paris hotels only costs at  prices ranging from 75€ to 125€. Thus, these Paris budget hotels offer affordable and enjoyable stay while providing easy access when touring the City of Light. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Book now to one of these budget Paris hotels at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxidWRnZXRwYXJpc2hvdGVscy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.allbudgetparishotels.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.allbudgetparishotels.com/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="666baa9a4de211d170f24d724ae11ff5">			&lt;strong&gt;;February 28, 2011 – Paris, France –&lt;/strong&gt;; the online search and reservation site of Paris budget hotels – &lt;strong&gt;;All Budget Paris Hotels&lt;/strong&gt;; – has been featuring 4 star &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxidWRnZXRwYXJpc2hvdGVscy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;budget Paris hotels&lt;/a&gt;;. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These budget Paris hotels offer tourists as well as businessmen elegant and comfortable accommodations while staying at one of the world’s most elegant cities. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These budget Paris hotels which embodies a quiet, discreet and contemporary atmosphere include the Hotel Villa Alessandra, Best Western Premier Hotel Opera Opal, Hotel Villa Eugenie, Hotel Clarion Collection Opera Pavillon and Hotel Horset Washington. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A one-night stay in one of these 4 star Paris budget hotels only costs €100.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hotel Villa Alexandra is a charming 4 star hotel located in Paris, close to the the beautiful Parc Monceau and not far from prestigious Champs Elysées and majestic Arc de Triomphe. Like other budget hotels in Paris, Villa Alexandra offers Wi-Fi access and quality room services. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Housed in a hausmannian building in the 8th arrondissement, Best Western Premier Hotel Opal offers classic and superior soundproof double rooms. Its hotel facilities include a lounge bar and free Wi-Fi services in the whole building. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hotel Villa Eugenie, on the other hand, is situated in a prominent place in the center of Paris. It houses a lounge bar which is the ideal place to escape reality with its moiré fabric walls and marble topped, with the latest songs from New York, London and Paris emanating through the air. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hotel Clarion Collection Opera Pavillon is one of the budget hotels in Paris which combines classic design and high technology into a perfectly comfortable setting. Guests will enjoy the quality room service with a selection of Japanese, Chinese, and French cuisine. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hotel Horset Washington is a 4 star budget hotel whose quiet atmosphere proves relaxing. It is situated in One Place de l'Étoile, one of the most prominent Places of the city. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These 4 star Paris budget hotels offers elegance and comfort for travelers, families and tourists at prices lower than expected – a perfect and easy-on-the-pocket stay in Paris. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Book a 4 star Paris budget hotels by logging on to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGxidWRnZXRwYXJpc2hvdGVscy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.allbudgetparishotels.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.allbudgetparishotels.com/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>