<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e5e7f45257206b4d3f5aa27c9193c30e">			One of the printer’s parts that take its main function and main use is the printer cartridge. Due to this printer cartridge highly demand existence, it really did comes along with an extensive price tag. With its high costs and a high profit that an entrepreneur could get in getting into printer cartridge business, a lot of business industries had come up into different strategies in order to get a cut out of its extreme earnings that is why, they got into developing and introducing their very own versions of printer cartridges. Some of the versions of printer cartridge that came out in the market are the remanufactured printer cartridges that are packed with helpful benefits to the consumers and the society and the cloned printer cartridges that are packed with some dreadful issues.&lt;br /&gt;;Original equipments are the best known to give the best results of creations in any terms. These original equipments are said to have the highest point when it comes to the quality of the products and are said to produce the finest features compared to the ones that are being imitated like on the printer cartridges that has now become a great part of our daily consumption. Original versions of printer cartridges are said to generate an excellent quality of outputs but on the other hand, other versions of printer cartridge were introduced like the remanufactured cartridges. Remanufactured printer cartridges on the other hand are not really an original version of printer cartridges but these types of printer cartridges were introduced in the market to produce the same quality as the original versions of printer cartridges. Remanufactured printer cartridges were taken from the original version of printer cartridges. These are the broken original version printer cartridges that are being recycled and repair in order to use it again and in order to minimize the huge trash of printer cartridges most especially in the US and UK.  &lt;br /&gt;;Another type of printer cartridges that are being introduced in the market is the cloned printer cartridges. Cloned printer cartridges are not remanufactured or recycled printer cartridges nor came from the original manufacturers of printer cartridges. Cloned printer cartridges are brand-new printer cartridges but are imitations from Southeast Asia particularly in China and Taiwan. This type of printer cartridge is now alarming the market of remanufactured printer cartridges as well as the printer manufacturers. Manufacturers of remanufactured printer cartridges are alarmed with these cloned printer cartridges not only because of their losing profit but as well as losing their aim on helping Mother Nature to become greener. Cloned printer cartridges are being sold in the market with a much cheaper cost than the remanufactured printer cartridges that cost a lot more cheaply than the OEM printer cartridges.&lt;br /&gt;;According to the analysis of the members of ETIRA, cloned printer cartridges will never be a big help to their market as well as to their goal in minimizing the printer cartridge trash along with landfills for the reason that they could not continually support their manufacturing works due to their low earnings or landfills will be filled with mountains of cloned printer cartridges because cloned printer cartridges are unrecyclable. Once cloned printer cartridges are being used and damaged, you will never have any other choice but to throw it away. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2VvbmVwbHVzLmNvLnVrL2hwLWNiNTQwYS1yZW1hbnVmYWN0dXJlZC1tdWlsdHBhY2suaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;cb540a&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Jsb2doZWFkcy5vcmcvP3A9MTM_" target="_blank"&gt;;hp toner&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2VvbmVwbHVzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;cb540a&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="1743aff44fc1e0a5c461bee15315eac7">			HOW DOES REMANUFACTURED PRINTER CARTRIDGES AFFECT THE BUSINESS INDUSTRY AS WELL AS THE CONSUMERS&lt;br /&gt;;The originally manufactured printer cartridges that had been broken and are being thrown away to the landfills are being recycled by some certain manufacturers in order to up with the so-called remanufactured printer cartridges to pursue a cheaper cost of printer cartridges and as well to protect Mother Nature. Recovering these broken printer cartridges has gone into several processes like examining the whole part in order to locate the main damages and to properly fix it after cleaning and washing the said cartridges. After cleaning and fixing, the recycled materials it is being tested one by one to know if it is fully repaired and are being refilled with printer ink and are being sold in the market in a price that will suit to the customer’s budget. &lt;br /&gt;;Printers are widely used in homes, offices and most especially to the business industries that are engaging into printing productions. This is one reason why manufacturers had come up into remanufacturing printer cartridge business. The sense of the remanufacturing of the printer cartridges do not only evolve on the business owners interests to earn at large accounts but as well as the consumers satisfaction of spending lower costs in buying the said product. Other than this, remanufactured printer cartridges have also a great effect on the environment in a good way. This business of remanufacturing the printer cartridges could enormously help us in reducing our wastes into landfills and make up healthier and better surroundings.   &lt;br /&gt;;With all this insights of remanufactured printer cartridges that along with its environmental friendly involvement, it could also give the consumers a high discount in buying a printer cartridge. That is why, a lot of printer cartridge consumers are now being more interested on the recycled printer cartridges than the printer cartridges that comes from the original equipment manufacturer. In such reasons, the makers of the printer devices had been alarmed because of it’s gradually losses on its cartridge selling statistics. The remanufacturers of printer cartridges and the printer makers had gone into several rivals. But because of the high relevance of these remanufactured printer cartridges towards nature and mankind, the society of manufacturers of the remanufactured printer cartridges had build up and joined forces to come up into a stronger association in the year 2003 that is known as ETIRA or European Toner and Inkjet Remanufacturers Association that is now led by Christian Wernhart as the President of the association.&lt;br /&gt;;This association had tied up a strong business promotion that remanufactured printer cartridges do not only give credits to the consumers and the environment but also it works in the most innovative way just like the OEM version of printer cartridges. The European Toner and Inkjet Remanufacturers Association are fully guaranteeing the consumer that their remanufactured products will undoubtedly give the printing sectors high qualified productions.&lt;br /&gt;;Printer cartridge consumers started to adapt and choose remanufactured printer cartridges due to its exceptional benefits and while the manufacturers of these remanufactured printer cartridges felt such simultaneous profit, the OEM of printer cartridges are slowly losing their sales on cartridges. And because OEM is facing a highly anticipated competition with ETIRA, some of the printer makers had come up into solution of setting up a microchip that will enable the printer’s system to identify and resist such remanufactured printer cartridges. On the other hand, there are printer makers that do not setup their printers with the said microchip and that give the consumers a big credit. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Jsb2doZWFkcy5vcmcvP3A9MTM_" target="_blank"&gt;;hp toner&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2VvbmVwbHVzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;hp cb540a&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2VvbmVwbHVzLmNvLnVrL2hwLWNiNTQwYS1yZW1hbnVmYWN0dXJlZC1tdWlsdHBhY2suaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;hp cb540a&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>