<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="5b1452c0d45d7116688be2eb027e0982">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fplasma-tv-vs-led-tv-14.tumblr.com%2Fpost%2F9741989937%2Fplasma-vs-lcd-vs-led-tvs-differences-explained"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://plasma-tv-vs-led-tv-14.tumblr.com/post/9741989937/plasma-vs-lcd-vs-led-tvs-differences-explained&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fplasmatvvsledtwww..wikispaces.com%2FSamsung%2BLCD%2Btv"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://plasmatvvsledtwww..wikispaces.com/Samsung+LCD+tv&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/artserrano/blog/blogid=4664542In" target="_blank"&gt;;http://en.pan.netcom/artserrano/blog/blogid=466...&lt;/a&gt;; the last 10 years, TV technology has advanced to a great extent and has brought in state of art technologies in providing the finest flat-screen TVs. They came around at about the same time as LCD TV, but they were much cheaper for their size, which is why they were more popular upon introduction. Plasma screens use a gas, which turns into a plasma when an electrical current is passed through them, emitting light.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plasma pros:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Cheaper compared with other flat-screens for the same size.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Generally better, more realistic colour than LCD TVs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Deeper blacks and higher contract ratio than LCD TVs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Do not suffer from motion blur. Plasma screens have fast refresh rates, so moving objects appear less blurred.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Wider viewing angle than LCD TVs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plasma cons:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Less lifespan than other flat-screens. Plasmas are predicted to last 10-15 years, whereas LCD TVs will last twice that or more.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Plasma uses much more power to run.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Do not come in all sizes (they do not come in small sizes, and only come in a few set sizes, e.g. 42 inch, 50 inch, 60 inch.).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Usually a little thicker, and much heavier than the others.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Is more susceptible to reflection glare in bright rooms.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LCD TV&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LCD panels first came to existence in the form of computer monitors. The technology itself has been around for many years. It is the same basic technology as the screen on a pocket calculator. LCD TV generally refers to a florescent backlit LCD TV. This is not to be confused with the newer LED TV, which is technically still an LCD TV except with LED backlit technology.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Advantages:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Better lifespan than plasma screens. Predicted lifespan of 30+ years is possible.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- LCD screens use less power than plasma, but more than LED TV.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Comes in many sizes, from computer screens to 60+ inch displays.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Lighter than a plasma, hence easier to mount on the wall.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- While prices for LCD TV have been higher than plasma, it is falling quickly with increased production.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Disadvantages:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Worst panel in terms of performance: lowest contrast level and slow (motion blur possible).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Narrower viewing angle, with slight colour shifting possible for any particular viewer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LED TV&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LED TV is technically actually LCD, but backlit with LEDs rather than fluorescent light source/s. This technology is the next generation in LCD screens.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Differences between LED backlit and current LCD technology:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- LED backlit produces much greater dynamic contrast owing to its direct backlighting.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- LED TVs can be made extremely thin, down to around an inch thick.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- LED TVs consume the least power out of all three screen types.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- LED TVs currently cost much more than LCD, but the prices are expected to fall dramatically as production increases.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- LED TVs are considered to be the most reliable out of all current flat-screen systems.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I hope this makes your search for a suitable TV an easier experience!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The debate of LCD TV vs Plasma TV is as old as TV itself. Ever since Plasma and LCD were created one of the most popular discussions in the TV industry is Plasma vs LCD. New members have joined the television family, as well as Plasma and LCD. We now have LED back light TV. The industry is calling these back lit led TVs as just simply LED TVs.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>