<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="810ed9eb0f24222d7aabaffcaaf2f251">			Cashew nuts come with a small, evergreen tree using a short irregular shaped shoe. The fruit is oval of form resulting from a cashew flower; the fruit is referred for the reason that cashew apple containing a single seed called cashew fanatic. The nut is surrounded by a double shell containing a great allergic resin, an acid that happens to be irritating to the skin color.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtaXZvbWFya2V0LmNvbS9rYWNhbmctbWVudGUtZW5hay1rdWFsaXRhcy1leHBvcnQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;mente super enak&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cashew nuts have several uses in accordance with the field where they are utilized. First of all these include food and they are utilized to improve diet. They are excellent source of healthy proteins and fiber. They likewise have fat which protects the guts; in that they process shock thus protecting the heart besides supporting healthy levels of low good cholesterol. Cashew nuts contain magnesium which is a healthy mineral which defends against high blood stress, muscle spasm, migraine pain, tension, soreness and weakness. They also contain potassium, vitamins and useful amounts of magnesium and phosphorus. They are salted which is sodium and it increases blood pressure.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another field where cashew nuts are utilized is medicine. The cashew nutshell liquid has acids which were used to treat dental abscesses. They are also active against a wide array of other gram-positive bacteria. Beside that nut are ground to powder in order the cure snake bites, it acts as antivenom. Nut oil also acts for an antifungal for healing nullified heels and ringworm. They are also used to control many other diseases like gall pebbles and reducing risks involving diabetes. The use of controlled fat in the cashew nut is vital optimal health thus ultimately causing management of weight.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtaXZvbWFya2V0LmNvbS9rYWNhbmctbWVudGUtZW5hay1rdWFsaXRhcy1leHBvcnQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;jual kacang mente&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another area where these nuts are used is in alcohol preparation. In India; the cashew apple which produces the nut is actually mashed to extract that juice and kept for fermentation for three days. The fermented juice next undergoes double distillation resulting to the beverage. In Tanzania, cashew apple company is dried and held for sometime. Later blended with water and fermented, distillation is performed to make very strong liquor. The same procedures are also applicable to other Africa countries like Mozambique.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These nuts are also used in the preparation of snacks. They are rich in flavor and may be eaten on its own or be salted or even sugared. They are covered in chocolate to make a very tasty snack. These nuts are used in cooking to make Thai, Chinese and American indian dishes. They are ground into sauces and as well used as garnish mostly along with the Indians to make desserts and desserts. With this features that makes cashew nut a very popular nut.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>