<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="4d90436f0655ab84ebb2870a62001129">			Collagen is the most effective arthritis treatment for osteoarthritis, back pain relief and joint pain relief whether from old age or injury. The reason lies in the structural make up of all your connective tissue, which is mostly collagen. Technology has finally found a way to stabilize collagen, in capsular form, so we can ingest it as an arthritis treatment for osteoarthritis and back pain relief instead of having it injected into our bodies. Good news for the 60 million people who suffer with arthritis pain, backache or joint pain. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.arthritispainreliefnow.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.arthritispainreliefnow.org&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you have a vitamin deficiency, the solution is simple, take vitamins. If you are dehydrated and thirsty, drink water. But if you have joint pain, arthritis pain, osteoarthritis, back pain or are looking for an effective and inexpensive arthritis treatment for back pain relief or joint pain relief, the solution again is simple, take collagen to rebuild, heal, stabilize and strengthen your bones, tendons, ligaments, cartilage, muscles, hair, skin and nails, because all of your connective tissue is 85% collagen.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We make collagen everyday to replace and repair our bodies from the natural aging process, breakdown from injury or repetitive stress and invasive surgeries.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The more we make the stronger we are and the slower we age. But the older we get the less collagen we make, the slower we heal, and we start feeling the aches and joint pain associated with arthritis or osteoarthritis and the faster we age.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wouldn't it be nice to have a supplement that would supply us with all the collagen we would need to repair and heal our aching backs, arthritis, osteoarthritis and joint pain as if we were 30 years old again?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To delay, stop, or even reverse arthritis, osteoarthritis, back pain or joint pain and to gain more mobility, strength, and experience the aging process more gracefully, add collagen daily to feel and see the difference. Most people report this arthritis treatment has given them noticeable arthritis pain relief and back pain relief within three weeks. For most, the results are life changing with far less arthritis pain or joint pain and more youthful vigor and looks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;75% of protein in the body is collagen. According to the FDA, Collagen is all natural and safe for everyone, including dogs and cats, and has awarded it the highest possible safety status. Without collagen, 40% of our organs, 70% of our joints, 80% of our skin, or a total of 30% of our bodies would simply fall apart. Collagen is the structure and glue that holds us together to makes us feel strong and looking young.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Collagen is a protein comprising only of amino acids, water and minerals and contains no fat, carbohydrates or preservatives. Collagen has no undesired side effects nor does it react with drugs or other food/food ingredients.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In conclusion, Collagen is the most effective arthritis treatment for osteoarthritis, back pain relief and joint pain relief whether from old age or injury. Collagen can now be taken in a capsule for arthritis treatment, osteoarthritis and for back pain relief instead of having it injected into our bodies. Collagen is safe, effective and inexpensive with no side affects or drug and food interactions. To heal faster from surgeries, old age or injuries, collagen will supply the building blocks to delay, stop or even reverse arthritis, osteoarthritis, back pain or joint pain within three weeks for most people. Staying strong, looking younger and living pain free has never been easier. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.arthritispainreliefnow.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.arthritispainreliefnow.org&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>