<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3598dfe4d0d4273f23db1a21dad47211">			My brother and I visited Ireland again with a handful of our friends for a trip to many of the craft production  factories that they have there. It is true that the craft skills  have been in the country for hundreds of years and  have been passed down from generation to generation  over time. Large scale manufacturing  of these skills has led to the creation of firms like  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWxsZWVrLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;Belleek China&lt;/a&gt;, Tyrone Crystal and Waterford Crystal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After touring much of the country area  subsequent to our arrival, and having taken in a few of the bars, restaurants  and cafes our visit got seriously  started after some 5 days when we went to view the Waterford  Crystal facility. It was a really wonderful  experience visiting the factory to see the glass being made, after all it is a well known name throughout the globe. You can  stand near to the large furnaces where the product is fired and see the glass blowers turn the glass into some of the  varieties they require. It's fair to say this is done mostly for the tourists but it a is great sight to witness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They have a tremendous visitor's centre where you start the tour and have the  familiar history available for you to look at in the form of movies, photographs and  articles from long ago.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Collectors  would appreciate this tour and we purchased a few of the  pieces before we departed. We were able to get in  OK when we got there but had not booked the trip in advance but got in without  bother. Planning in advance for a large  group may be necessary but the seven of us got in OK.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;object width=&quot;;560&quot;; height=&quot;;315]&lt;param  name=&quot;;movie&quot;; value=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fv%2FLq4JQuab4FI%3Fversion%3D3%26amp%3Bamp%3Bhl%3Den_GB"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/v/Lq4JQuab4FI?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param  name=&quot;;allowFullScreen&quot;; value=&quot;;true]&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name=&quot;;allowscriptaccess&quot;; value=&quot;;always]&lt;/param&gt;&lt;embed  src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fv%2FLq4JQuab4FI%3Fversion%3D3%26amp%3Bamp%3Bhl%3Den_GB%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.youtube.com/v/Lq4JQuab4FI?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_GB&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; type=&quot;;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot;;  width=&quot;;560&quot;; height=&quot;;315&quot;; allowscriptaccess=&quot;;always&quot;; allowfullscreen=&quot;;true]&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We stayed in Ballyshannon for a rock music festival following a few more days heading north and continued into Northern Ireland to the pottery in the village of Belleek where they manufacture parian china.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Moving into Belleek took us across the  border from one region to another but the border itself is not obvious and our  passports were not required. Although it has been there for a a considerable period the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWxsZWVrLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;Belleek&lt;/a&gt;  establishment appears to be in a good state of repair.  At the time it was  most likely well built &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There is the familiar museum feel to the  attraction which start from their visitor's centre.  There are films about the Belleek pottery and how it was came to be and a small tour of the factory where you can view a variety of items being made. I had great interest in the creation of the Belleek bowls which are really quite amazing when you see  how delicately they are produced. We bought a  couple of trinkets on this visit instead of the Belleek bowls as those  are rather expensive.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We headed a bit further northerly then for a few days  touring the rural areas before we had to travel back for our flights in Dublin. Things had gone quite smoothly on our trip and the weather had been  fairly good despite our expectations for the rain from previous visits. It will be at least a few years we suspect before we return here again but we would recommend it to anyone for a trip.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>