<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="25158dd3e532d7de5ee3630d561837c6">			Golf is considered a great game by many people. Golf is enjoyed by people of all age ranges. Some even consider it a great family outing and get child sized clubs for their kids. Even people who think the game is boring can grow to love the game.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But it can take awhile to get good at it. Working on improving your golf swing is one of the keys to becoming a better golfer. The more you practice your swing, the better your game will be. To improve your golf swing, use the following tips. Other related posts and information: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3R5cGVzb2Znb2xmc2hvdHMwNDY3LnFhcGFjaXR5LmNvbS9teS1ibG9nLzQ2NzkyOC90aXBzLWZvci1pbXByb3ZpbmcteW91ci1nb2xmLXN3aW5nLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Golf Swing Methods That Really Work&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2luZGVwZW5kZW50LmFjYWRlbWlhLmVkdS9Eb25hbGRUeXNvbi9CbG9nLzIwMjk0Ny9JbXByb3ZpbmctR29sZi1Td2luZ3MtV2l0aC1KdXN0LTMtRWFzeS1IaW50cw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Proven Methods For Improving Your Golf Swing&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most people automatically assume that one has to hit the ball harder when going into the wind, and that is a falsehood. One result of hitting hard into the wind is you'll cause spin and the ball will lift higher. When elevation and spin occurs, then you're looking at reduced accuracy and control - bad golfer. Right, so then the right hitting stance is to move so the ball is closer to you, your stance, by about two inches or so. Make sure to keep your hands forward. Lastly, select a club that has a longer length than that which is normally called for by you. After doing this, swing easy or like you normally would. By all means practice this technique, and you will begin to experience more control and accuracy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Swinging the club at just the ball is a common misconception of beginners. But you will learn that to improve your swing, you need to swing through the ball. Your follow through is as important as the rest of the swing. To practice this skill, try these tips.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You'll want to put your ball on the first of two tees. After setting up the first tee, place the second one about eight inches in front of it. Practice hitting the ball and the second tee. By practicing, you will learn to hit the ball and make it over the second tee with a single swing. Look at these resources on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N0YWNrLWFuZC10aWx0LWdvbGYtc3dpbmcud2lraWRvdC5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;stack and tilt golf&lt;/a&gt;; here...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The power for your swing will emanate from your legs and body trunk. It's not about arm muscles, or power, but rather other parts of your body. This is a very common &quot;rookie&quot; mistake. Truthfully, attempting to gain power with only the use of your arms and wrists can be a terribly bad idea because you can produce an injury. The expert use of body mechanics and movement will give you strength from your body trunk and your legs. You'll be better able to keep the proper stance. Your arms and wrists will have protection against injuries. So just work on that technique, and hopefully in a short time you'll see real improvement in your accuracy and power. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Golf is a global hobby and past-time, and huge numbers of men and women love playing it. If you love golf, then just realize that getting better will only come with learning, practice, and then time. No worries because you are capable of a great golf swing; it will just take some time and practice to get there. Also, work on your mental game and just get to a place where you have hope and belief in an improved golf swing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other similar content articles and information:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZhbGVudGlubG9wZTI0LmppZ3N5LmNvbS9lbnRyaWVzL2dlbmVyYWwvaW1wcm92aW5nLWdvbGYtc3dpbmdzLXdpdGgtanVzdC0zLWVhc3ktaGludHM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Do You Know These Strategies for Improving Your Golf Swings?&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NjaWVuY2VzdGFnZS5jb20vZ3JvdXBfaG9tZS5waHA/Z2lkPTQ0NDc5OTk_" target="_blank"&gt;;The Best Methods for Improving Your Golf Swing&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2luZGVwZW5kZW50LmFjYWRlbWlhLmVkdS9Mb3BlelYvQmxvZy8yMDMyNzMvSW1wcm92aW5nLUdvbGYtU3dpbmdzLS0tSG93LUl0LUlzLURvbmU_" target="_blank"&gt;;Tips for Improving Your Golf Swing&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="a08780e684d9e13750f26ffbf02c0949">			So you want to improve your golf swing. Well... believe it or not, but this article can help you out with that matter. We'll be discussing some excellent tips for improving your golf swing, and you can go out right away and put it to the test. As you know, one of the not so secret secrets is practice, practice, practice. You simply must practice because one thing you will be doing is creating strong muscle memories. Golfing has its own special rewards reserved for those who are willing to put some devotion into improving. Other similar threads and advice: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2luZGVwZW5kZW50LmFjYWRlbWlhLmVkdS9Eb25hbGRUeXNvbi9CbG9nLzIwMjk0Ny9JbXByb3ZpbmctR29sZi1Td2luZ3MtV2l0aC1KdXN0LTMtRWFzeS1IaW50cw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Methods For Improving That Horrid Golf Swing&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NjaWVuY2VzdGFnZS5jb20vZ3JvdXBfaG9tZS5waHA/Z2lkPTQ0NDc0ODY_" target="_blank"&gt;;Improve Your Golf Swing with these 3 Tips&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A good golf swing, believe it or not, will feel like music. The success of both hinge on a good tempo, steady rhythm, and balance. You can't have a good piece of music without a solid foundation. Your stance is the foundation that you build your entire golf swing on.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Practice hitting golf balls with your feet spread at varying distances to find the best stance. Depending on your balance you may be more comfortable with a wider stance but try narrower ones as well to be sure. Feet shoulder width apart is the usually stance, but you will find your core stance after some practice. In order to be able to stride right into your stance when you're on the golf course, you'll want to practice it. The best approach to hitting the ball is called 'down and through.' The lift of the club will do the work of getting the ball aloft. The ball will not rise because you somehow tried to do an upswing motion on the club. That is a mistaken approach to hitting and always avoid doing it. There are a range of effects including hitting the ball just a little distance with too much height - head's up! You're more likely to send the ball straight up and then straight back down again! Find out more about these tips on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VuLndpa2lwZWRpYS5vcmcvd2lraS9Hb2xm" target="_blank"&gt;;golfing&lt;/a&gt;; here...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ok, wind again... just swing easier, ok? If you don't do that, then you will lose trajectory plus accuracy... plus control, etc. Here's a little mnemonic device created by Mr. Greg Norman; always &quot;swing easy into the breezy.&quot; It absolutely seems to make good sense that one needs to hit harder into the wind. Remember: not everything can be solved with force. Plus, you will have increased control when you swing easier. So don't let the wind trick you into ruining your game! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Getting your golf swing under control really isn't any worse than practicing core balance techniques including posture. Believe it or not these stances and posture tips help make sure you are getting the maximum effect on the ball when your club come into contact with it. Doing this helps ensure accuracy and efficiency with your balls distance too. Too many people think that improving your golf swing is too difficult. This however is a misconception it really only takes alot of practice. Keep trying you will soon see the benefits of your efforts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Similar blog posts and suggestions:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NjaWVuY2VzdGFnZS5jb20vZ3JvdXBfaG9tZS5waHA/Z2lkPTQ0NDc5OTk_" target="_blank"&gt;;3 Easy Ways to Improve Your Golf Swing&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS92YWxlbnRpbmxvcGUyNC9wb3N0cy8xMTU2MzYwL1RoZStCZXN0K01ldGhvZHMrZm9yK0ltcHJvdmluZytZb3VyK0dvbGYrU3dpbmc_" target="_blank"&gt;;Do You Know These Strategies for Improving Your Golf Swings?&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS92YWxlbnRpbmxvcGUyNC9ibG9nLzIwMTIvMDQvMTgvMy1kcml2ZS1ob21lLXRpcHMtdG8taW1wcm92ZS15b3VyLWdvbGYtc3dpbmdzP2ZpcnN0cG9zdD1Z" target="_blank"&gt;;Proven Methods For Improving Your Golf Swing&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>