<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fc0563d1f740662a091461aaddc29adb">			1 – Create a title that attracts buyers.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In all honesty, this is probably the most vital selling tip of them all, and yet it's repeatedly the most neglected one.  It's incredible how many eBay users don't comprehend the significance of generating a good title for their listing or how to produce a listing which truly gets the interest of buyers. Just remember, even if you have the finest product imaginable, and you're selling it for less than anyone else, you'll still not clock up your profits if people can't locate your listings in the first place. Bear in mind that shoppers enter particular keywords into eBay's search box whilst they're searching for a specific product, and if you've not included such keywords in your title and item description, they're not going to see your product.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Because eBay has limitations on the number of characters you can have in your title, you should make absolutely sure every character counts. Put yourself in the shoes of your prospective buyers and picture what key words you'd use to locate your item. You can rest assured, no potential buyer types in a string of cash signs, or any other pointless characters or words, so you never incorporate such things in your title.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once you feel you know which key words are likely to work the best, keep the following pointers in mind:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Leave a space between each keyword.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Never use punctuation in your title unless you really must.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Avoid special characters (like *, $, &amp;, %, and so on), since these can be interpreted as Boolean search operators by eBay's internal search engine and could keep your listing from showing up in searches. Also, as has already been mentioned, potential buyers will never use such characters when searching for something on eBay.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Write your title in title case; this means that the first letter of every word should be capitalized.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Search for other items similar to the one you're selling. If most of their titles appear in lower case, or if the majority of them are capitalized, try writing yours using only capital letters, since this will help your listing to stand out.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2 – Looks Matter
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to eBay, looks really do count. Naturally, an attractive price, reasonable shipping costs and a well written, attractive title are important factors. A well written item description is likewise incredibly important, since this is actually what you'll depend on for sealing the deal. When you have scores of sellers selling a similar product to yours, it will be your item description which will allow your listing stand out.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always remember that every eBay listing is essentially an advert. If your description is dull, lacks flare, or perhaps fails to describe your item accurately, the chance of make a sale will be minimal.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3 – Make Sure You Stand Out
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While some of the free extras on eBay, such as the listing themes for example, might look nice, but because every second seller already uses them, you're better off leaving them alone.  In truth, these tools won't make your listings stand out, and in fact, they'll almost certainly have the exact opposite affect. There are a lot of other ways to customize your listings and they're just as easy to use.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are trying to find genuine wholesale suppliers for your eBay small business, &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wholesalesourcereviews.com%2Fsalehoo-review%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSaleHoo%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.wholesalesourcereviews.com/salehoo-review/&quot;&gt;;SaleHoo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;; provide and excellent list of pre-screened dropshippers and volume wholesalers. You can discover more by reading this thorough &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.wholesalesourcereviews.com%2Fsalehoo-review%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSaleHoo"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.wholesalesourcereviews.com/salehoo-review/&quot;&gt;;SaleHoo&lt;/a&gt;; review.&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>