<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="38dba8eecd817b82db538a6952c3cffb">			Here is a step-by-step approach that will lead you from barely being able to do one pullup, to doing one arm pullups with ease! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; But First, BE PATIENT! &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rome was not built daily! This sequence is based on the fact that the body will change gradually in response to help increased stimulus. That means that you will GRADUALLY get stronger. Wait until it is possible to do the required repetitions and sets of each one exercise before moving to the next, more difficult, variation. This will insure you don't push too hard, too fast, and injure yourself. With that said... &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Intro &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will first need to have an object to complete pullups from. Use a standard pullup bar for those who have access to one. In the event you don't, get creative. Try a towel draped over a branch or beam, or maybe a retail or homemade suspension coach. Do several easy sets every day, each time stopping 2 reps short of failure. Doing several daily sets leaving a couple reps &quot;left in the tank&quot; will allow your body to steadily get stronger as yourself physically and nerves get accustomed to efficiently performing this exercising. Every couple weeks, take a day to test yourself. See how many pullups you can do in two sets with around a 5 minute break between sets. Require a day or two to recuperate after each testing morning. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Step 1: Standard Pullups &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Normal pull ups or chin ups are the initial step. Move on to phase 2 once you can EASILY do pullups/chin ups for 2 sets of 10 distributors. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Step 2: Close Grip Pullups &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Following, work on close golf grip pullups, gripping the bar with your hands touching. Try overhand (palms away from you) and underhand (hands facing you) grips to find which one feels more comfortable. Again, doing several easy sets daily (with rest days once or twice a week as vital), work up to doing 2 sets of 10 reps of nearby grip pullups. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Step: Uneven Pullups &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now try uneven pullups. Get hold of the bar with an individual hand, and grab that wrist with your other hand. Since you will be supporting your entire bodyweight with just one hand, these will construct some serious grip power, which is needed for the one arm pull up. Work up to 2 sets of 9 distributors. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Step 4: Half Repetitions &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hang on to the bar with one side. Try to do half repetitions of one armed pullups, using a towel draped in the bar for assistance since needed. Work up to help doing 2 sets associated with 6 repetitions. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Action 5: Negative Repetitions &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now try a controlled descent from the superior portion of the an individual arm pullup. If this is certainly too difficult by itself, try using your some other arm for assistance by hanging on to a towel draped on the bar. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Step 6: The One Tricep / bicep Pull Up! &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those who have steadily progressed through the prior stages, you should be capable to crank out a one armed pullup! Again, feel free to hang on to a towel with your other hand for slight assistance as necessary. Don't forget, take it slow, but be consistent, and you will succeed. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3V0dWJlLmNvbS93YXRjaD92PVktSk1aVVpQRWFB" target="_blank"&gt;;one arm chinup&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbWF6b24uY29tL09uZS1Bcm0tUHVsbC1Cb2R5d2VpZ2h0LWVib29rL2RwL0IwMDdCSk1YSzg_" target="_blank"&gt;;one arm chinup&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbWF6b24uY29tL09uZS1Bcm0tUHVsbC1VcC1Cb2R5d2VpZ2h0L2RwLzE0NzAxMDgyMzI_" target="_blank"&gt;;one arm pullup&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>