<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="96e9dc55db8327016fa94d2099fe814b">			It's certainly possible to achieve personal goals for improvement in a reasonably short amount of time using NLP, or Neuro Linguistic Programming. Very often, if not usually, NLP techniques can be learned easily and fast, and then they can be put to work, immediately. Naturally, you have to use the techniques, but doing so only produces even more positive results. The balance of this article will concern several NLP benefits that you will be able to take advantage of if you choose. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Related content pieces and tips: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2plcmVteWNhc2V5NzE3LmJyYXZlam91cm5hbC5jb20vZW50cnkvODA5Mzg_" target="_blank"&gt;Suggestions for Using NLP to Make Practical Changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2plcmVteWNhc2V5NzE3LnJvbGxyLmNvbS9wb3N0cy9zdWdnZXN0aW9ucy1mb3ItdXNpbmctbmxwLXRvLW1ha2UtcHJhY3RpY2FsLWNoYW5nZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;3 NLP Benefits that Can Change Your Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One practical part of neuro linguistic programming is their use of a tool called anchoring. Anchoring simply means mentally connecting a certain state of mind with some kind of &quot;;anchor,&quot;; which may be a word, symbol, object, song or any sensory stimulus. Normally people have each optimistic and pessimistic &quot;;anchors&quot;; which allow them to link one thing with another over time. NLP makes this method cognizant to us so that it can be advantageous to us. As an example, when you find yourself in a positive or resourceful (another common term) state you can create an anchor, such as touching yourself on the knuckle of your right thumb. Once you have an anchor, you can then apply it to return to the state of mind you want. This is a technique for you to acclimatize yourself and to deal with your feelings and feel the way you desire to. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If better communication skills is desirable, then you can employ the famous NLP strategy called, mirroring. This extremely effective technique involves mimicking or mirroring what they other person does when you're talking to them. You have to listen to the words people use and watch their body language for clues. Mirroring has an unconscious effect on people, and it has the potential to produce feelings of identification with you as a person plus a higher level of comfort. But do not mirror every movement they make, so be careful and tactful about how you do it. You can use it very unobtrusively to build up a rapport with strangers, or with those you normally don't speak with on a frequent basis. Visit these strategies on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NlbGZpbXByb3ZlbWVudHRpcHMud2lraWRvdC5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;self improve&lt;/a&gt; here...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You know you have images and pictures in your mind's eye, and Neuro Linguistic Programming works well with changing them for a desired result. One area this can help in, out of very many, is in the case of your job requiring you to give talks, yet you really are nervous to get up in front of others and speak. You now have an image in your mind of this uncomfortable situation. What you do then is create a new image that is different; you are doing the same thing yet you are totally confident and relaxed, and the people are listening intently and interested. Take the old and new images; then place the new one inside the old one - make the new one very small that fits inside the old image. Ok, next... the new confident image grows at a slow rate in size until it fills up the old picture. These NLP techniques will work, but it's your responsibility to do it, to practice them until you see good stuff happening. Neuro linguistic programming is a process that has been successfully used by many thousands of people for more than thirty years. Due to it being based on approaches and outcomes, new styles are continually being determined. The techniques for putting NLP to use that we have gone over in here are just a few of the advantages you can gain by learning more about this incredibly helpful personal growth system.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relevant columns and advice:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZpdG9yb2FjaDQxMC53ZWJzaXRld2l6YXJkLmNvbS91c2luZy1uZXVyby1saW5ndWlzdGljLXByb2dyYW1taW5nLXRvLXJlY3RpZnkteW91ci1saWZlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;Putting Neuro Linguistic Programming to Use to Make Your Life Better&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FybmVsZW52aWVtb3J5bGxveS5mcmVld2ViLm1lL2luZGV4LnBocD9uZXdzJmFtcDtuaWQ9Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;Advice for Using NLP to Make Beneficial Changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BsZXJiLmNvbS92aXRvcm9hY2g0MTA_" target="_blank"&gt;How Neuro Linguistic Programming Can Help You Overcome False Beliefs&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="ec10bc81d13e79374613573efa2c9d16">			Neuro linguistic programming, or NLP, can be applied to a variety of issues and problems. While you can spend years researching this method, you can get many advantages from it by getting to know a few easy exercises. NLP works by making changes in the way you talk to yourself or others, and the way you picture events and memories in your mind. This article will give you some basic ideas on how NLP can help you, no matter what your particular goals may be. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other similar blogposts and specifics: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9qZXJlbXljYXNleTcxNy9yZWFkLzMwOTA3MTgvMy1wcm92ZW4tbmV1cm8tbGluZ3Vpc3RpYy1wcm9ncmFtbWluZy1hcHByb2FjaGVzLXRoYXQtd29yaw__" target="_blank"&gt;3 Powerful NLP Benefits You Need To Know About&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2plcmVteWNhc2V5NzE3LnNvdXAuaW8vcG9zdC8yMzQ0NTM0ODMvMy1Qcm92ZW4tTWV0aG9kcy1OZXVyby1MaW5ndWlzdGljLVByb2dyYW1taW5nLUNhbg__" target="_blank"&gt;Hints for Using NLP to Make Productive Changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the basic ideas behind neuro linguistic programming is that we can never know the way things really are.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The things we believe in, or think, or even see is based on perception. It's relatively simple in that if you make a decision to change how you perceive a thing (in your world or mind), then other ways of thinking about it would change. We do have control in our lives to the extent that we can control how we view things. That is an important foundation in NLP, and there are many approaches that are based on how you choose to look at things in your life. You do have the ability to create your life, or re-create it, once you truly realize that you have the power to do so. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots of people want to see better results with their communications skills, and you can achieve that through the use of &quot;;mirroring.&quot;; The way it works is to simply mirror what the other person is doing in terms of movements and even voice mannerisms - within reason of course. You have to listen to the words people use and watch their body language for clues. Mirroring has an unconscious effect on people, and they'll tend to feel more relaxed and comfortable with you. You have to be careful, however, not to take this too far, as if you mirror someone's every movement it may become obvious and it then looks like you are mocking them! Used as a guideline, however, mirroring can be a great NLP technique to gain rapport with someone, even a stranger. Explore these tips on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xhd29mYXR0cmFjdGlvbmxvdmUud2lraWRvdC5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;law of attaction love&lt;/a&gt; here...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People very often do not realize or understand the power behind the images they hold, and NLP can positively help you change them. A lot of people are nervous to stand up and speak to small groups, but sometimes their jobs make it necessary to do that. The understandable effect is to hold that image in your mind's eye of standing there and feeling uncomfortable or nervous. Create a new image where you are speaking with confidence and everyone is listening and appreciating what you are saying. Then, make the new image a small obscure dot that is within the normal and larger &quot;;old&quot;; image. Now replace the old with the new, and you do that by slowly watching the new one get bigger and bigger until it blocks out the old image and only the new is left standing. If you practice this simple NLP exercise, you'll be able to make fast changes in how you feel about many things. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Neuro linguistic programming provides you with a large set of tools that can help you change yourself and how you look at life. NLP is not something that gives instant results, but it does seem to be able to allow people to make positive changes in a fairly shorter period of time. If NLP is something you feel may be of good use for you, then we encourage you to find out more and do have the courage to take action for your life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other related threads and advice:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dheTJib29rbWFya3MuY29tL3N0b3J5LnBocD90aXRsZT1UaXBzLWZvci1Vc2luZy1OTFAtdG8tTWFrZS1Qb3NpdGl2ZS1DaGFuZ2Vz" target="_blank"&gt;Suggestions for Using NLP to Make Practical Changes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZpdG9yb2FjaDQxMDQzMy53ZWJzLmNvbS9hcHBzL2Jsb2cvc2hvdy8xMjY4MjE1Ni1hZHZpY2UtZm9yLXVzaW5nLW5scC10by1tYWtlLWJlbmVmaWNpYWwtY2hhbmdlcw__" target="_blank"&gt;3 Powerful Neuro Linguistic Programming Methods To Improve Your Life&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZlYmFkLmNvbS9zdG9yeS5waHA/dGl0bGU9My1wcm92ZW4tYW5kLWVmZmVjdGl2ZS1ubHAtYmVuZWZpdHMtdG8tY2hhbmdlLXlvdXItbGlmZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;Using Neuro Linguistic Programming to Improve Your Life&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>