<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="cc4eb19d536b3b148220dc8e2f7a9d03">			Your teeth reflect not only your personality but also your health. You surely want to look and feel great! This article gives you ways to do this through whiter teeth. Enjoy reading about ways to brighten your smile. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2NpYWxpenIuY29tL2V2ZW50LzYwODIyMDgyOA__" target="_blank"&gt;;A awesome Emergency Dentist article&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gray teeth aren't often bettered with whitening treatments, it usually only works on yellowed natural teeth. Teeth with significant staining my need multiple sessions.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take the time after you eat or drink to rinse your mouth out with water. This will help keep residue from staining your teeth. This will stop your teeth getting badly stained.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When drinking, try to use a straw if possible. Many beverages such as coffee can discolor teeth, but drinking through a straw can eliminate the liquid coming in contact with your teeth. If these drinks don't touch your teeth, they can't stain them, and as a result you can easily maintain a whiter smile.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brush your teeth with a banana peel. This is easy and a lot of people do it! Try peeling a banana and make use of its peel to run across your teeth prior to brushing them. After doing this, brush your teeth as you normally would. You will see results right away.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a number of simple, natural tooth whitening procedures that you can do at home. An excellent method is using baking soda. Either purchase a whitening toothpaste containing baking soda, or use some from your kitchen.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To have a whiter smile, don't drink tea and coffee. Both of these products can discolor your teeth. If you are a coffee addict, make sure you rinse your teeth with water as soon as you finish drinking. Some of the bad effects these beverages will have on your teeth will be tempered this way.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Place importance on flossing and brushing at least two times daily. You want to prevent a plaque buildup because it can cause your teeth to become discolored. Take extra care to floss extremely well before you go to bed so that you do not have plaque staying on your teeth overnight.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is wise to consult your dentist prior to starting a teeth whitening program. You might decide that it's unnecessary once you've had a thorough cleaning. During your visit, make sure that you tell your dentist that you plan to whiten your teeth with over-the-counter products. Your dentist will determine whether or not your oral health is good enough to use home whitening kits. Cavities or gum disease will only become worse if you use a teeth whitening product on them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Oranges and other citrus-based fruits should be avoided if you want to keep the sparkle in your smile. Do not drink any juice from these fruits. The acids in these foods will eat away at your teeth. It is also important not to eat or drink citrus foods before bed because they can increase acid reflux, which also affects the way your smile looks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As discussed before, there are a multitude of teeth whitening methods available. As important as it is to take preventative measures, it is also important to continuously care for you teeth. Having a whiter, brighter smile will increase your confidence. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW11bml0eS5hdG9tLmNvbS9Qb3N0L0xpbWl0LVRoZS1FbWVyZ2VuY3ktRGVudGlzdC1NZXRob2RzLUFuZC1TdWdnZXN0aW9ucy1Pbi1LZWVwaW5nLVlvdXItVGVldGgtSW4tR29vZC1IZWFsdGgtQW5kLVNoaW55LzAzRUZCRkZGRjAyNTgzQ0Y5MDAwODAxODQ0OTdG" target="_blank"&gt;;Go here for a Emergency Dentist article&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;More Informative Articles:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NjaWVuY2VzdGFnZS5jb20vZ3JvdXBfaG9tZS5waHA/Z2lkPTQ0NDk0NjY_" target="_blank"&gt;;Brighten Your Smile With Great Teeth Whitening Advice&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9hbHBlcmtpbnM2MTQvcG9zdHMvMTE1ODAxNi9BZHZpY2UrVGhhdCtXaWxsK0hlbHArWW91K0dldCtQZWFybHkrV2hpdGUrVGVldGg_" target="_blank"&gt;;Brighten Your Smile With Great Teeth Whitening Advice&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>