<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="bf0051d59af786815f93216b48a45394">			Because of the current downturn in the economy, millions of Americans are now burdened by mountains of high-interest &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ub3dmcmVlb2ZkZWJ0LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;credit card debt&lt;/a&gt;;. Lots of people feel that there is no way for them to pay off credit card debt without turning to bankruptcy as an option.  Since bankruptcy is such a extreme option, &amp; for most people an unthinkable option not long ago, people have been looking for other options to help them discover a way to give them credit card debt relief &amp; help them start a brand new debt free life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some people have turned to is debt consolidation. Debt consolidation is used to combine multiple bills &amp; payments in to single every month payment. This can be done in a few ways. If people are looking for debt relief through debt consolidation, they can either turn to a company that provides credit card debt management services or debt settlement solutions. It is also feasible to take matters in to your own hands &amp; try to work out a paying off debt plan for yourself through a few means.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Technique of debt consolidation is to combine all of your credit card debts from multiple cards to a single card. Lots of credit card companies will offer a low introductory APR for new accounts that are providing them with a balance transfer. This is way of obtaining some small little bit of credit card debt relief. In lieu of trying to manage several credit card debts, everything you owe will be in place so you can slowly pay off credit card debt.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not long ago, technique of doing this was through a home equity loan or refinance. Lots of people would use the equity in their homes in order to pay off credit card debts. This was great when home values were high &amp; refinances were simple to come by, but with the collapse of the housing market &amp; new rigid requirements, obtaining this sort of debt relief has become much harder to come by. There are also lots of risks involved when converting unsecured debt, such as credit card debt in to secured debt with collateral. In case you fail to make your payments, you risk losing your home.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ub3dmcmVlb2ZkZWJ0LmNvbS9kZWJ0LWVsaW1pbmF0aW9uLXByb2dyYW0v" target="_blank"&gt;;Debt elimination programs&lt;/a&gt;; that will erase debt you owe to credit card companies legally &amp; safely overnight do exist. This is the best way to truly become debt free. These debt elimination programs do not basically reduce the amount of credit card debt you have, or negotiate credit card debt settlement with credit card companies, but they honestly eliminate debt one time &amp; for all.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Both of the methods described here have worked for lots of people. But debt consolidation is basically a way of shifting debt around. While it is helpful when it comes to reducing debt, it does not eliminate debt.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you need to eliminate your debt and not simply manage it, consider debt elimination as the viable and legal choice.  Visit &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ub3dmcmVlb2ZkZWJ0LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;debt elimination&lt;/a&gt;; for more info, or call 561-282-9476 for more information.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>