<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="8c3946619cc9330991a0fa320cd79b7f">			It’s just the question to be answered by the thousands of socialites logging on…
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It’s the in thing, the fad, the peer pressure, the cult, it’s the social networking community, and you need to be part of it or else you are out of it, so you got to grab a catchy username and dump in the profile with facts and fiction, upload a weird looking or a hot looking picture with the best touch up effects and spicy tag lines and launch your presence to shout out to the million odd members.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally you’ve arrived, and now you got to find the friends to fill up your friend list. Hitting the search button, browsing profiles and joining groups, you are quickly getting connected, and finally people are adding you and you are adding them, and popularity ratings for your profile are soaring high with hundreds of friends all lined up in your friend list , with no clue or reason. And it’s a chain effect till the point of it that everyone will be connected to each other in some way or the other. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have you ever thought? Out of the hundreds or thousands of people you know, how many are contacting you and vice versa and have you or they, got a chance to speak to or meet you to know the real you, just as you don’t know the real they.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There’s too much to debate here, but cutting short the lingo, I think successful socializing is about making more quality and real friends than a big list of friends who are still strangers...
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Happy Net logging!!!		</conversation>		<conversation id="ab9adb7923b9c5a4c4a3acd74840f1f6">			Interesting as the heading seems, this discussion may turn out to be an eye opener for people searching for potential matches.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Often men come across the perfect woman, seems she is the best one with all the qualities of a perfect life partner, and though there is an initial contact and a few more exchanges things don’t seem to work out. The reasons may be justified, but generalizing to a certain extent I want to get a rating done for the Top 10 qualities a woman seeks in man, out of the 20 listed below.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So please pass by and list your Top 10 as per your personal preference. FEEL FREE TO ADD WHAT I HAVE MISSED OUT…
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1)	BUSINESS INCOME/ SALARY
&lt;br /&gt;2)	POWER or DESIGNATION
&lt;br /&gt;3)	PROPERTY
&lt;br /&gt;4)	CARS
&lt;br /&gt;5)	BANK BALANCE
&lt;br /&gt;6)	GOOD LOOKS
&lt;br /&gt;7)	PERSONALITY
&lt;br /&gt;8)	PHYSIQUE
&lt;br /&gt;9)	HEIGHT
&lt;br /&gt;10)	COMPLEXION
&lt;br /&gt;11)	HUMOUR
&lt;br /&gt;12)	CONFIDENCE
&lt;br /&gt;13)	HONESTY
&lt;br /&gt;14)	CLEANLINESS
&lt;br /&gt;15)	RESPECT
&lt;br /&gt;16)	COMMITMENT
&lt;br /&gt;17)	TRUST
&lt;br /&gt;18)	LOVING AND CARING NATURE
&lt;br /&gt;19)	RELIGIOUS BELIEFS
&lt;br /&gt;20)	PROFESSION
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thanks for your valuable input &amp; Happy Net Blogging!!!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>