<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="57aa70ce18180b50cfef5633ad0f7d92">			Education is everything: the real key to  success, satisfaction, and financial freedom. The difficulty nowadays is the exceedingly high cost associated with studying at an institution of higher learning, which often is followed by the heavy load of decades of regular monthly loan payments.  Right this moment, private colleges cost,on average, twenty seven thousand dollars per year in tuition and fees alone. Graduate/Post-Grad studies are even more steeply-priced, averaging $38,655 annually. So, to attend college and a four-year graduate school will cost you more than two hundred fifty thousand dollars in tuition by itself. When you add things like an apartment or dorm, everyday expenditures, and books the overall rate can expand to roughly five hundred thousand dollars.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those that are willing to sign up for a loan often cannot get one. This is in truth fortunate for them, since the payments on a loan of that size would run them more or less $5,000 per month.  During the life of the loan (a decade more or less) a grad would pay out over three hundred grand in interest alone. There is now, however, another solution: a new course titled University For Free. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;University For Free describes how a person can:&lt;br /&gt;;	Go to college 100% for free (free tuition or free tuition and expenses)&lt;br /&gt;;	Attend graduate school 100% for free (free tuition or free tuition and expenses)&lt;br /&gt;;	Attend college one hundred percent  free (acquire no loans, and earn your diploma with zero debt)&lt;br /&gt;;Go to graduate school 100%  free (acquire no loans, and  earn your degree with absolutely no debt)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With this course, there is at this point no longer any need for anyone at all to take out a single penny in loans to attend undergraduate or graduate school.  The course details 1000s of undergraduate and graduate programs and schools which really can be attended  free. A sampling of the numbers of programs profiled for popular subject areas:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Information Technology: 150&lt;br /&gt;;- Master of Business Administration (MBA): 38&lt;br /&gt;;- Economics: 45&lt;br /&gt;;- Chemistry/Chemical Engineering: 65&lt;br /&gt;;- Psychology: 62&lt;br /&gt;;- Nursing: 45&lt;br /&gt;;- Political Science: 38&lt;br /&gt;;- African and African American Studies: 25&lt;br /&gt;;- Environmental Sciences/Engineering: 99&lt;br /&gt;;- Architecture: 18&lt;br /&gt;;- Journalism: 12&lt;br /&gt;;- Hotel, Restaurant, and Hospitality: 12&lt;br /&gt;;- Physical Education and Sports related: 37&lt;br /&gt;;- History: 102&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The areas of study listed above are a few illustrations of the thousands of opportunities presented in the course.  Contained within are detailed profiles of all the schools, alongside with a report on the degree programs available, application requirements, and contact details. This allows a person to either look through institutions to find preferred schools or explore programs in their precise topic of study.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To be clear, this program is not a catalog of scholarships or special restricted programs, but instead are universities and programs which are applicable and open to all students. Further more, the schools vary from mainstream public universities to some of the very exclusive and respected public and private colleges in the U . S . and the world, including Ivy League colleges and universities.  The price of the course is $250, but it is currently being offered for what we feel is a very reasonable price of $99, truly a pittance  in light of the astronomic price of a college or university education.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50dWJlbGVzc3R2LmNvbS9tZW1iZXJzL2Jyb2NrbWVsZW5kZTI0" target="_blank"&gt;;Free University Secrets:An Exciting New Course provides Everyone a Pathway to a Completely Free Undergraduate or Graduate Degree&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>