<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="8eb7cfdb387ae737d0293fb95c9f8ca6">			Get some sort of one-of-a-kind vintage belt buckle &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaXBiZWx0YnVja2xlLmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yaWVzL0JvdHRsZS1PcGVuZXItQmVsdC1CdWNrbGUv" target="_blank"&gt;;bottle opener belt buckle&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2h0dHA6Ly93d3cuaGlwYmVsdGJ1Y2tsZS5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcmllcy9WaW50YWdlLUJlbHQtQnVja2xlcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;superman belt buckles&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaXBiZWx0YnVja2xlLmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yaWVzL09mZmljaWFsbHktTGljZW5zZWQvU3VwZXJtYW4tQmVsdC1CdWNrbGUv" target="_blank"&gt;;superman belt buckles&lt;/a&gt;; along with that's extra cool. You can find vintage belt buckles &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaXBiZWx0YnVja2xlLmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yaWVzL09mZmljaWFsbHktTGljZW5zZWQvU3VwZXJtYW4tQmVsdC1CdWNrbGUv" target="_blank"&gt;;vintage belt buckles&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2h0dHA6Ly93d3cuaGlwYmVsdGJ1Y2tsZS5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcmllcy9WaW50YWdlLUJlbHQtQnVja2xlcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;vintage belt buckles&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaXBiZWx0YnVja2xlLmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yaWVzL0JvdHRsZS1PcGVuZXItQmVsdC1CdWNrbGUv" target="_blank"&gt;;bottle opener belt buckle&lt;/a&gt;; that come back to the early 1900s and feature many images. Don't think you need to get this mainly for women, either. Ample men love a artistry and group of vintage type buckles. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;If you desire unique and expensive-looking corporate and business gifts for exceptional clients, try choosing customized belt buckles. Diligently and expertly handcrafted, these belt buckles really are perfect giveaways. It's possible to have them in silver to add extra decadence. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Customized belt buckles is often fashioned from any design or picture in store. This makes tailored belt buckles perfect giveaways check out page special events. To your parents' diamond anniversary including, give them each of those customized belt buckle using their wedding picture upon it. If you have got a friend with a fabulous passion for horses, customized belt which has a buckle featuring some champion stallion will be the perfect gift. Or even a daughter will love an intricately built buckle with the girl name engraved on it. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having a mental image in the belt buckle you like could help you save time and makes conversation aided by the artist less difficult and confusing. But if you do not have any strategies, you may check with their brochures as well as draw your inspiration from them. Make sure which you let the specialit render a drawing first of your specifications prior to when proceeding. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If it's a picture you need, decide what material you ought to use for typically the buckle. Vertical images with a clean background start looking best on precious metal buckles. Brass buckles are better suited to horizontal images. The artist will be needing you to put in a high-resolution photo. At the lowest, it must get 300 dpi and 1000 pixels tall. The designer probably will convert the image to monochrome. For added effect, it will be sepia-toned. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;A FABULOUS belt is one the ideal accessories to highlight your look, and a buckle tends to make or break your current total getup. An intricately constructed buckle may be all you have to transform casual wear to your cool outfit. When you are hip, you may want to wear belts by means of one-of-a-kind buckle. They are sure to grab attention and compliment your style, whether you are wearing male jeans or a plain skirt. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most vintage belt buckles day back to the start of the 1900's. They are generally made of pewter and so are engraved with photographs of gauchos about Mexico, Spanish sceneries, research bugs, butterflies and women of the South Pacific. These belt buckles hold a romantic history and wearing them will truly conjure a selected air of uniqueness which makes anyone feel specialized. Original vintage belt buckles could be too expensive to wear for a regular particular date with friends. Replicas are which means next best factor. There are many online stores to get them. They'll give a wide variety of designs-from previous Mexico flair to help you Japanese art. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaXBiZWx0YnVja2xlLmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yaWVzL09mZmljaWFsbHktTGljZW5zZWQvU3VwZXJtYW4tQmVsdC1CdWNrbGUv" target="_blank"&gt;;superman belt buckles&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaXBiZWx0YnVja2xlLmNvbS9jYXRlZ29yaWVzL0JvdHRsZS1PcGVuZXItQmVsdC1CdWNrbGUv" target="_blank"&gt;;bottle opener belt buckle&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2h0dHA6Ly93d3cuaGlwYmVsdGJ1Y2tsZS5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcmllcy9WaW50YWdlLUJlbHQtQnVja2xlcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;vintage belt buckles&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>