<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b6873dae80dc63a3722b20cda9c18cb2">			HCG dietary regime is an efficient approach to weight loss. With the help of this plan, you will reduce weight and put your body in an fantastic shape. It is also successful for keeping the preferred body weight. This regime is based on a natural hormone found in a human body, so it’s risk-free to use. Many people report great results with that dietary regime. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;About HCG: The Basics &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You need to understand that HCG is a hormone that’s naturally created in a human body. It’s sometimes referred to as a “pregnancy hormone”, because its level increases during pregnancy. This is important for the mother and the fetus. With the help of this hormone, body metabolizes fat and turns it into energy that can be used by mother and the fetus. This is one of many natural methods for switching fat into energy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The above hormone is also used to deal with numerous health conditions. It can also be used as a good way of weigt management. Because fat is burned and used as energy, the body becomes slimmer and in a greater shape. It’s essential to understand [url=]hcg diet[/url] is a natural way of weight management. Women who go through these hormonal changes during pregnancy report no major negative effects as a result of high levels of this hormone in their body. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What About HCG and Men? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It’s equally important to know this hormone is risk-free for both men and women. The hormone is naturally found in a human body, and males have it, too. The levels of said hormone are particularly high in pregnancy, but it is not specifically a pregnancy nor a female hormone. Actually, men report quicker results using this diet than women do, because of the fast metabolism. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ways to Use HCG? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It’s crucial to understand how HCG diet works. This hormone helps your body metabolize the fat, turning it into energy. This burned fat is lost, so you experience a weight loss. The specific weight reduction depends on the individual and several different parameters, such as age, weight, height, gender and also some other parameters. Nevertheless, many users achieve more than satisfying results and a considerable weight loss. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;BestBuy HCG and Dr Lipman: The Dietary Program &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bestbuyhcg.com provides an elaborate weight management regime based on natural hormone methods explained previously. BestBuy HCG and Dr Lipman present a unique weight loss program created to make people slim down in a safe and effective way. This dietary regime was designed to show highest results at a very short time, without compromising your health. Richard Lipman, M.D. is a popular internist and endocrinologist who has treated overweight people with &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2thbXJ1enphbWFuMDYuaHVicGFnZXMuY29tL2h1Yi9IQ0cwOA__" target="_blank"&gt;;hcg diet&lt;/a&gt;; and accomplished great results. His new 800 Calorie HCG Food Plan is a specifically created program aimed for getting the very best results and a risk-free weight loss.		</conversation>		<conversation id="48704143c4e11e8730d7168f9f854bbe">			HCG diet is a new and effective strategy to slim down and put your body in the optimum shape. It’s a natural method to get rid of all those extra pounds and to maintain the desired body weight. The diet is dependent on a hormone naturally found in a human body, so it’s safe to use. Increasing numbers of people report excellent results with this weight loss strategy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Basic Information About HCG&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It’s important to understand HCG is a hormone that is created in the body naturally. Some think of it as a “pregnancy hormone”, even though it’s contained in a human body even outside pregnancy. This hormone has many nutritious functions in a female body during pregnancy, namely, to permit the body to process fat. This metabolized fat is burned and functions as energy that helps the mother and fetus. It is one of the body’s natural systems to use fat as energy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This hormone is popular to deal with several medical conditions. It’s also very effective for weight loss, because it helps people burn fat and use it as energy. You will lose weight and get a more shaped body. It’s extremely important to understand [url=]hcg diet[/url] is a natural technique for losing weight. Women go through very high levels of said hormone in pregnancy without any side effects. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How About HCG and Men? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While the high levels of this hormone are achieved in pregnancy, it’s crucial to know it is not a pregnancy-only hormone. Said hormone naturally exists in a human body. Men have it, too. This is why it’s safe to use by both women and men. Chances are that men will achieve a quicker weight loss because they have a quicker metabolism.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ideal way to Use HCG &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It’s crucial to know how HCG diet works. The hormone helps your body metabolize the fat, making it into energy. This burned fat is lost, so you experience a weight loss. The specific weight loss depends on the individual and several different parameters, such as age, weight, height, gender and some other factors. However, most users achieve more than satisfying results and a significant weight loss. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;About BestBuy HCG and Dr Lipman &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bestbuyhcg.com is a superb resource for losing weight with HCG and keeping the healthy body weight. The plan is created on natural hormone weight loss techniques. The regime is made by Dr Lipman, a famous internist and endocrinologist with several years of experience in treating overweight people with this hormone. The dietary plan gives fantastic results and it’s also very safe to use. BestBuy HCG and Dr Lipman give a new 800 Calorie &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hjZ2RpZXQwNzcuZGV2aHViLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;hcg diet&lt;/a&gt;; Food Plan, which is specially designed to optimize weight reduction results in a risk-free way.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>