<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7dfe7c6c22b8b5813ea74dd509999025">			This actually works, and I didn't get around to opening it until today.
&lt;br /&gt;;        Had a money windfall on Saturday after receiving this on Tuesday.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1 Kings 8:23
&lt;br /&gt;;        A blessing is coming to you in the form of money.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do not ask questions just forward to
&lt;br /&gt;;        eight people and TRUST GOD!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prayer for Finances (it works)
&lt;br /&gt;;        I claimed it for you - now claim it for me.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;God has more than a thousand ways to provide
&lt;br /&gt;;        For us, that we know nothing about.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here is your financial blessing!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's a simple prayer, you got 30 Seconds?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don't sleep on this...Someone recently
&lt;br /&gt;;        Read this for the first time and
&lt;br /&gt;;        Received exactly enough for a $0 balance
&lt;br /&gt;;        On all credit cards.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you need a financial blessing,
&lt;br /&gt;;        Continue reading this e-mail.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Heavenly Father, most Gracious and Loving
&lt;br /&gt;;        God, I pray to you that you Abundantly bless
&lt;br /&gt;;        My family and me.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I know that you recognize, that a Family
&lt;br /&gt;;        Is more than just a mother, father, sister, brother, cousin,
&lt;br /&gt;;        Husband and wife, but all who believe and trust in You.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dear GOD, I send up a prayer request for
&lt;br /&gt;;        Financial blessing for not only the Person who
&lt;br /&gt;;        Sent this to me, but for me and all that I have
&lt;br /&gt;;        Forwarded This message to.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And that the power of joined prayer by
&lt;br /&gt;;        Those who Believe and trust in you is
&lt;br /&gt;;        More powerful than anything!
&lt;br /&gt;;        Salary Payment This actually works, and I didn't get around to opening it until today. Had a money windfall on Saturday after receiving this on Tuesday. 1 Kings 8:23 A blessing is coming to you in the form of money. Do not ask questions just forward to eight people and TRUST GOD! Prayer for Finances (it works) I claimed it for you - now claim it for me. God has more than a thousand ways to provide For us, that we know nothing about. Here is your financial blessing! It's a simple prayer, you got 30 Seconds? Don't sleep on this...Someone recently Read this for the first time and Received exactly enough for a $0 balance On all credit cards. If you need a financial blessing, Continue reading this e-mail. Heavenly Father, most Gracious and Loving God, I pray to you that you Abundantly bless My family and me. I know that you recognize, that a Family Is more than just a mother, father, sister, brother, cousin, Husband and wife, but all who believe and trust in You. Dear GOD, I send up a prayer request for Financial blessing for not only the Person who Sent this to me, but for me and all that I have Forwarded This message to. And that the power of joined prayer by Those who Believe and trust in you is More powerful than anything! I thank you in Advance for your blessings. God, deliver the person reading this right Now&amp;amp;gt;From debt and debt burdens. Release your Godly wisdom that I may be a Good steward over all that you have given me GOD, for I know how wonderful and mighty You are and how if we just obey you and walk In your word and have the faith of a Mustard Seed that you will pour out blessings. I thank you now Lord for the recent blessings I have Received and for the blessings yet to come, Because I know you are not done with me yet. In Jesus name Amen... TAKE 60 SECONDS and send this on quickly and within hours, you will have Caused a multitude of people to pray to God for each other. Then sit Back and watch the power of God work in your life for doing the thing That
&lt;br /&gt;;        Hus
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hello my lovely friend.
&lt;br /&gt;;        Have a nice day.
&lt;br /&gt;;        Thanks for your friendship.
&lt;br /&gt;;        God bless you.
&lt;br /&gt;;        Takecare.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you love this man please forward this message to all your friends....
&lt;br /&gt;;        He died for you
&lt;br /&gt;;        he died for you
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He did something for you, now do something for him. Spread his word, and you'll be rewarded. How will you be rewarded? Matthew 10:32 &amp;amp;quot;Whoever acknowledges Me before men, I will acknowledge him before My Father in heaven. But whoever disowns Me before men, I will disown him before My Father in heaven.&amp;amp;quot;PLEASE do not ignore Him.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>