<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="600f5ada162ce8018fa77338e5502f99">			As a writer in some cases responsible for reviews, I've sympathy for folks who attempt to honestly and fairly review merchandise. It is not an easy process - no less than not if you want to peel away the surface in the item you are reviewing and take a closer appear at how it functions.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Anti-virus software is particularly troublesome. It’s simple to have a look in the features and make comments regarding the interface, however the actual organization of testing the protective capabilities of anti-virus computer software is hard because you can find millions of viruses in existence and thousands of new ones hitting the internet every single month. Hence, antivirus computer software evaluations demand that the software be tested against a wide range of viruses - and that’s anything only a handful of internet websites do.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Anjtivirus Comparatives&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;center&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RvcC0xMC1hbnRpdmlydXMubmV0L2Jsb2cvd2hlcmUtY2FuLXlvdS1maW5kLWluZm9ybWF0aXZlLWFudGl2aXJ1cy1wcm9ncmFtLXJldmlld3M_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fi44.tinypic.com%2Frky0qq.png%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://i44.tinypic.com/rky0qq.png&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;good antivirus review&quot; width=&quot;220&quot; height=&quot;240&quot; align=&quot;center&quot;/&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/center&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Though most Pc users don’t understand it, the field of anti-virus protection has an academic side populated by researchers and ex-hackers who rigorously analyze pc hardware and software program on the search for security flaws that need to be addressed. This study often outcomes in some valuable information and facts for the average pc user, and also the AV-Comparatives web site is maybe the most beneficial instance.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An Austrian non-profit organization, AV-Comparatives exists solely to supply unbiased and comprehensive info regarding the effectiveness of anti-virus software. They subject the software program to a range of attacks including conventional viruses, trojans, scripting attacks and more. They also spend attention to facts for instance the rate of false positives and also the quantity of viruses a program manages to quarantine but fails to remove.		</conversation>		<conversation id="4f8ee8535f0d15247e32cf34596bae0a">			As a writer from time to time responsible for testimonials, I have sympathy for people who attempt to honestly and fairly review goods. It is not a simple job - at least not if you want to peel away the surface with the item you’re reviewing and take a closer look at how it functions.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Anti-virus computer software is particularly troublesome. It’s simple to have a appear at the features and make comments about the interface, but the actual organization of testing the protective capabilities of anti-virus computer software is hard since you will discover millions of viruses in existence and thousands of new ones hitting the net every month. Therefore, antivirus software testimonials need that the computer software be tested against a wide range of viruses - and that is some thing only a handful of web-sites do.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Anjtivirus Comparatives&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;center&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RvcC0xMC1hbnRpdmlydXMubmV0L2Jsb2cvd2hlcmUtY2FuLXlvdS1maW5kLWluZm9ybWF0aXZlLWFudGl2aXJ1cy1wcm9ncmFtLXJldmlld3M_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fi44.tinypic.com%2Frky0qq.png%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://i44.tinypic.com/rky0qq.png&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;good antivirus review&quot; width=&quot;220&quot; height=&quot;240&quot; align=&quot;center&quot;/&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/center&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although most Pc users do not realize it, the field of anti-virus protection has an academic side populated by researchers and ex-hackers who rigorously analyze pc hardware and software on the search for security flaws that have to be addressed. This research usually outcomes in some useful data for the typical computer user, as well as the AV-Comparatives website is maybe the most beneficial example.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An Austrian non-profit organization, AV-Comparatives exists solely to deliver unbiased and comprehensive information concerning the effectiveness of anti-virus software. They subject the software to many different attacks which includes standard viruses, trojans, scripting attacks and far more. They also spend attention to particulars for example the rate of false positives along with the number of viruses a system manages to quarantine but fails to get rid of. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RvcC0xMC1hbnRpdmlydXMubmV0L2Jsb2cvd2hlcmUtY2FuLXlvdS1maW5kLWluZm9ybWF0aXZlLWFudGl2aXJ1cy1wcm9ncmFtLXJldmlld3M_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;More Information&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;....		</conversation>	</conversations></author>