<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="17a0b1378a9665de5a1817cd7d26f3da">			Nearly all doctors and personal trainers claim that one of the best things to do to lose weight is regular good ol' cardio. Of course we know that cardio workouts are good for burning calories and essential for the healthy functioning of your heart and the pumping of the blood. But did you know that there are actually two types of options that you can choose from. There are low-intensity cardio workouts and the high-intensity variety. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.meratoldietpill.net%2Fthe-mayo-clinic-diet%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.meratoldietpill.net/the-mayo-clinic-diet/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;High-Intensity Cardio Workout&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the primary goal is fat loss, the high-intensity version is ideal. What is high-intensity you ask? A simple example would be running at full speed till you run out of steam, stopping to catch your breath and then running flat out again. This exercise elevates your heart rate because it needs to pump out more blood to supply it to the rest of the body. When your heart rate reaches a certain level it is said to be in the 'fat burning zone'. This means that if your primary aim is fat loss you should try to maintain your heartrate in this range throughout your workout.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another reason the higher intensity workouts are ideal is because they raise your metabolism and keep it at a higher level for a couple of hours after the workout. Other examples of high-intensity cardio workout routines would be jumping rope and using the exercise bike. The shorter distances or shorter time periods while working out with maximum intensity is ideal. However, the common issue about high intensity workouts is that sometimes, the higher the intensity, the more carbohydrates (energy) burned instead of fats.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Low-Intensity Cardio Workout&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most people prefer low-intensity cardio workouts for weight loss. Why? The main reason is that during the exercise more calories are burned in comparison to the lower intensity. Also, these workouts are gentler on the joints and the overall body. According to experts, low intensity cardio workouts routines also allow an individual to monitor his or her heart rate accordingly. Examples of low intensity workouts are walking and using a elliptical machine. These exercises do not require longer periods of time and are low-impact so they dont stress your joints but you still burn calories.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What About Using A Combination?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Yes, it is very possible. In fact, those who want to lose weight the faster way maximize the two approaches. One can include both low intensity and high intensity in a single routine. For example, starting off, one can first do some stretching to warm up before the actual exercise. Then, he or she can start walking. Then, it is now time for doing intervals. After that low intensity procedure of walking, one can shift to high intensity walking such as brisk walking. Then, after walking, one can get into jogging for the high intensity interval. Then he or she gets back to low intensity, and the cycle continues as he or she cools down with another round of low intensity exercises.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whatever the approach to be used, one is assured that doing some cardio is very effective in losing weight. They do not only burn calories but they also improve your health. High and low intensity workouts have their own benefits, and combining the two will supercharge your weight loss.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.meratoldietpill.net%2Falarming-epidemic-of-obesity"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.meratoldietpill.net/alarming-epidemic-of-obesity&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f19196d05fbafaa5f39fb4145bf2ed84">			When you read the title of this article 'Easy Gym Workouts To Lose Weight' what crosses your mind? This title creates a number of images in most people's minds. Usually involving expensive memberships, long days and nights slogging away with a personal trainer shouting at them for one more rep while being bombarded of images of people looking exactly how they want to look. What you should be picturing instead is the body image you want to achieve within the next months or years. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F712020%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dailystrength.org/people/712020/journal&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most people don't have hours and hours to spend in the gym, however there are exercises you can use to get the most out of the time you do have. Gyms are becoming more and more high tech, it is hard to go into a gym these days without walking into some equipment you have no idea how to use whatsoever.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The main thing you need to do when attending a gym is stick to workouts that target exactly what you are looking for, so always do the workouts that are designed to burn fat quickly. These workouts are called HIIT, which stands for High Intensity Interval Training, these are workouts that are designed to be intense and burn calories in as short a time frame as possible. If you focus on HIIT you will lose weight in a much shorter time period than you though was possible, helping you get the body you have wanted for so long.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Burning calories is all about increasing your metabolism, you do this with cardio. When at the gym look for the equipment that lets you do HIIT routines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The following are examples of 2 good gym workouts to lose weight:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using The Treadmill&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to doing HIIT at the gym, you will want to get to know the treadmill very well. Running is one of the most physical things you can do and can be cranked up in intensity over a small amount of time in order to achieve HIIT status.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When running you are using your lower body as well as your upper body, this allows you to effectively lose as many calories as possible. With a good treadmill you will be able to not merely increase the speed, but also the incline you are running at, this allows you to really crank up the intensity properly.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For these reasons you should really take advantage of the treadmill when at the gym, using it properly will help you get the body of your dreams much faster than you though you could.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are starting out really out of shape and over weight then you should start out with a 25 minute run on the treadmill, try and do it on an empty stomach and don't be ashamed to go slow at first until you build up your cardio ability.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using The Rowing Machine&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After the treadmill the next best thing to use at the gym when trying to lose weight is the rowing machine. In case the name didn't give it away, the rowing machine mimics... yup you guess it, a rowing machine, which are particularly physical to use. You will find that the rowing machine helps you work your complete body.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most rowing machines will allow you to alter the resistance, this way when you start to see improvements and find your regular setting to easy, you can increase the intensity of your workout.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once again you should workout on the rowing machine on an empty stomach in the morning, try and keep going for 30 minutes and the highest intensity you can manage. The reason you shouldn't eat before you workout is it forces your body to use up your fat reserves to keep going. Even when you have finished working out you will continue to burn fat throughout the day.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remember to warm up before you workout, so always spend a nice 5 minutes or so getting your body ready for what is about to come.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When using gym workouts to lose weight you really need to be smart about your choice of equipment, there is no point spending 2 hours doing something you could have accomplished on a better machine in 30 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F712020%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dailystrength.org/people/712020/journal&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>