<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="4a45e227eab620733e763708ab3121db">			&lt;b&gt;;BCOMCELL-Mobile Phones News&lt;/b&gt;;-New look &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iY29tY2VsbC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;Mobile Phones News &lt;/a&gt;;come from&lt;b&gt;; iPhones 5 &lt;/b&gt;;showing the new design with aluminum back panel to all of us once again. The pictures also confirm a smaller dock connector, a 3.5 mm headphone jack placed at the bottom, a front-facing camera above the earpiece as well as a different camera and LED flash module.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The devices go all “&lt;b&gt;;the Dark Knight Rises&lt;/b&gt;;” with an all-round black design, going as deep as the external antenna of the device. Even the&lt;b&gt;; Apple &lt;/b&gt;;logo on the back is colored black.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But here’s what we find unusual about this, assumed, iPhone 5. It’s running on iOS 5, not iOS 6, which we gather from the Maps icon. The antenna has reflective surface and doesn’t look like the steel one used on the iPhone 4S. There doesn’t appear to be a secondary microphone at the top either, but it could be the tiny slit between the camera lens and the LED flash.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The iPhone 5 should arrive in the fall so this could very well be a working developer’s device. It does back up most of the rumors about the next iPhone, save for the display, which can’t be seen very well on the photos. Still, we would recommend taking a healthy pinch of salt with all of these rumors.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bcomcell.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2Fwp-post-thumbnail%2FsZktC2.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.bcomcell.com/wp-content/uploads/wp-post-thumbnail/sZktC2.jpg&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After analysing all the rumours that have poured in over the past few months we have condensed all the rumours to show you what the new iPhone 5 will probably look like as well as some of its possible features and specs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Possible Redesign&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;It is very likely that the new iPhone is going to get a brand new design. We can't be sure of what exactly it's going to look like but past rumours have suggested that it's going to get a new &amp;quot;sleeker&amp;quot; design. It's probably going to be thinner than the current model and have more rounded edges like the new iPad. Other rumours have suggested that the new iPhone is going have 4 inch display replacing 3.5 inch displays present in the current models.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Siri Updates&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Technically Siri is still in beta and its almost guaranteed that the new iPhone along with iOS 6 is going be bringing big Siri updates. A few updates are:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Better location and directions for Canada and other countries&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Possibility of Siri integration with other iOS apps &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Ability to change settings&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Ability to write tweets&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Notification integration (read our notifications)&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Ability to read text messages and email back to us&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Add and edit contacts&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;New Nano Sim&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Apple has already from normal sims to micro sims new reports suggest that the new iPhone 5 could go even smaller and contain a nano sim&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;4G / LTE&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;It is very likely for the new iPhone to have 4G/LTE technology especially because the new iPad the was already released also contained this technology.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;10 Mega Pixel Camera&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Apple has been improving the camera on the their iPhones with each new iteration. And seeing as how there is already a very capable 8mpx camera on the iPhone 4s it should be no surprise to see atleast a 10mpx camera on the newest iPhone.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Apple A6 Quad Core Processor&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Apple already has some of the mobile computing processor's on the market in their iPhones and iPads. The Samsung Galaxy S III already has a 1.5 ghz quad core processor and Apple will no doubt be ager to match or surpass that level of power with their new Apple processor. The processor in the new iPad was called the Apple A5X and it seemed to be just a minor upgrade from the A5. After analysing various rumors I have reason to believe that the new processor will be a much more significant upgrade and will be called the Apple A6&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Other Possible Features&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Some other possible features are:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;NFC technology&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;More RAM&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Thinner design&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Jjb21jZWxsLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Mobile Phones&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>