<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="aaf598cdfab513a3f8e415de40610209">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wb3J0b2Zpbm93b3JsZC5jb20vbHV4dXJ5L3BvcnRvZmluby1ob3RlbHMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;Portofino Italy Hotels&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is indeed the best destination for family retreat offering many logging alternatives of different categories right from pet friendly hotels in order to spa and casino motels. Modeled after the whole village of Portofino in Madeira, The Portofino Bay Hotel is found on a picturesque clean where convenient water minicab service can carry you from your quiet bayside Piazza on the vibrant nightlife of Common CityWalk or the fun and excitement in the two Universal theme parks plus the other two on-site motels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The rooms of this Portofino Bay Hotel because of their luxurious Italian furnishings are generally roomy and comfortable, just what you want following a long day at your parks. The rooms however aren't the only attractive feature of the Portofino Bay Hotel. The guests have a variety of fine and casual dining options with the hotel. Whether your feasting on the delectable dishes from Florida or Tuscany at The female Della's Ristorante or enjoying a leisurely meal poolside from Splendido Pizzeria, any dining pleasure is usually fulfilled right at this hotel. But your options tend not to end there. Numerous additional eating establishments can be obtained just a short mineral water taxi ride away at CityWalk or among the other hotels.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Staying at the Portofino Bay Hotel is often a memorable experience that provides benefits that extend for the two Universal theme park system. As a guest on the hotel your room key will provide you with Universal Express ride access. This allows you to bypass the off the shelf lines and avoid this long waits that sometimes occur due to huge popularity of the attractions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As with most amusement resort hotels, the Portofino Bay Hotel has promotions which are worthy of any travelers consideration. Whether you choose to see during the value time of year or the Stay some, Play free option just about any choice you make that brings that you the Portofino Bay Hotel will be a good one.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With all the options available these days getting quality and value for your money is something that most savvy travelers seek out when making travel options. The Portofino Bay Location will meet and surpass your expectations and give you that memorable experience of any lifetime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's compare the greatest hotels near Disneyland. Some of the hotels are towards the gate at Disneyland Theme Park and some will require a short ride over a shuttle bus. Be careful of hotels with names that make them sound like they are across the street from Disneyland. For example, some hotels have the word Maingate in their name but are 2-3 long blocks from the entrance to Disneyland.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Suite Hotels Near Disneyland&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The &lt;i&gt;suite hotels&lt;/i&gt; are classified as the best of the collection, with large suite rooms many perks like free breakfast time and kids programs. Unfortunately, many of these will not be near the entrance for you to Disneyland.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anaheim Marriott Suites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anaheim Portofino Inn &amp; Suites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Desert Palms Hotel &amp; Suites&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doubletree Guest Suites Anaheim Resort&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Embassy Suites Hotel Anaheim South&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Homewood Suites by Hilton Anaheim Resort&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;La Quinta Inn &amp; Suites Anaheim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Residence Inn by Marriott Anaheim Maingate&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Residence Inn Anaheim Resort Area&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Deluxe Hotels Near Disneyland&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The next choice with regard to hotels near Disneyland are the deluxe hotels. These hotels will have room service along with restaurants and gyms. Some will also deliver free breakfast and childrens programs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Anaheim Marriott Hotel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Crowne Plaza Resort Anaheim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hilton Anaheim&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hyatt Regency Orange County&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sheraton Anaheim Hotel&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sheraton Park Hotel in the Anaheim Resort&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moderate Hotels Near Disneyland&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The moderate level hotels near Disneyland will have smaller rooms but should still offer amenities like pools and room service.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>