<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="19ab11c3dd4e3845505ec4bec983c5ae">			There are numerous reasons for sharing and distributing your PowerPoint presentation. I've discovered that in most instances, distributing your slides in PDF format has some important benefits, the two for you and your presentation's recipients&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your presentation stands on its personal statically, with out dynamic elements such as animations, transitions and media, these kinds of as video clip, then you may possibly discover the PDF resolution perfect for your demands. Some of the benefits contain:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Receipients Don't Need PowerPoint&lt;/b&gt;: Nearly everybody has Adobe Reader these days, but not everybody has PowerPoint (or PowerPoint viewer) mounted on their method. Nor do you want to fret about which model of PowerPoint your recipients have, something complex by PowerPoint 2007 which launched a new file format (.pptx)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rapidly and Effortless:&lt;/b&gt; PDF files open up in a snap and it's something that every person presently is aware of how to do.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Presentation Will Look the Way You Prepared It&lt;/b&gt;: If your recipient's computer does not have all your presentation's fonts put in on their personal computer, your presentation could seem entirely in a different way to them as Windows will substitute another font rather. Changing your presentation to PDF format &quot;;locks down&quot;; all of its components, ensuring that everybody sees specifically what you well prepared.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Safeguard Your Subject material:&lt;/b&gt; Ok, I admit it. I do not like to share. I place numerous a lot of hrs into getting ready my presentations, and if a person arms me their USB flash generate at the stop of a speak and asks me for a copy, I'm a little bit hesitant if I think they'll merely just take my slides and use them as their own. Distributing a PDF file doesn't eliminate plagiarism, but it doesn't distribute your challenging operate on a silver platter, both.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to making a PDF file of your presentation's slides, you can make handouts, speaker notes, and so forth. Even if your presentation includes video clip or other dynamic elements, and if those elements reside on the Web or company network, you can embed hyperlinks in your presentation. For example, see the last page of the PDF file which consists of a hyperlink to this internet site.Saving your presentation as a PDF is straightforward, specially if you're utilizing PowerPoint 2007. Microsoft has added &quot;;PDF or XPS&quot;; as one particular of the &quot;;Help save As...&quot;; alternatives. Even so, this attribute is not enabled right after you at first set up PowerPoint 2007. You'll require to down load the &quot;;Microsoft Preserve as PDF or XPS Include-in for 2007 Microsoft Place of work plans.&quot;;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Still utilizing an previously version of PowerPoint? No concerns. Use the freeware solution CutePDF Writer which, when put in, reveals up as another printer on your system. Just decide on CutePDF as your printer and &quot;;print&quot;; your presentation and it will be saved as a PDF file. I nevertheless use CutePDF for other programs that really don't assistance PDF.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you will give the PDF tactic a try out. It really is one particular of individuals rare remedies that positive aspects the two you and your audience.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8d86d1c245a4abb31c02177776e48f2">			There are many factors for sharing and distributing your PowerPoint presentation. I've located that in most situations, distributing your slides in PDF format has some crucial positive aspects, both for you and your presentation's recipients&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If your presentation stands on its personal statically, without having dynamic elements these kinds of as animations, transitions and media, such as video clip, then you may possibly find the PDF resolution best for your demands. Some of the advantages include:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Receipients Do not Need PowerPoint&lt;/b&gt;: Almost every person has Adobe Reader these days, but not everybody has PowerPoint (or PowerPoint viewer) put in on their system. Nor do you need to be concerned about which edition of PowerPoint your recipients have, one thing complicated by PowerPoint 2007 which released a new file format (.pptx)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Quick and Straightforward:&lt;/b&gt; PDF files open in a snap and it's one thing that absolutely everyone previously understands how to do.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Your Presentation Will Appear the Way You Prepared It&lt;/b&gt;: If your recipient's computer doesn't have all your presentation's fonts mounted on their laptop or computer, your presentation may possibly look completely in another way to them as Windows will substitute another font instead. Converting your presentation to PDF format &quot;;locks down&quot;; all of its elements, guaranteeing that everyone sees specifically what you ready.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Safeguard Your Content:&lt;/b&gt; Okay, I admit it. I don't like to share. I place several numerous hours into preparing my presentations, and if an individual fingers me their USB flash push at the conclude of a talk and asks me for a duplicate, I'm a bit hesitant if I assume they'll simply just take my slides and use them as their personal. Distributing a PDF file doesn't eliminate plagiarism, but it doesn't distribute your difficult perform on a silver platter, either.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In addition to developing a PDF file of your presentation's slides, you can make handouts, speaker notes, and many others. Even if your presentation includes video or other dynamic components, and if people aspects are living on the Internet or corporate network, you can embed hyperlinks in your presentation. For illustration, see the very last page of the PDF file which contains a link to this internet site.Preserving your presentation as a PDF is easy, specifically if you're making use of PowerPoint 2007. Microsoft has additional &quot;;PDF or XPS&quot;; as 1 of the &quot;;Save As...&quot;; options. Even so, this feature is not enabled after you at first set up PowerPoint 2007. You'll require to obtain the &quot;;Microsoft Save as PDF or XPS Add-in for 2007 Microsoft Business office applications.&quot;;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nonetheless employing an previously edition of PowerPoint? No concerns. Use the freeware merchandise CutePDF Writer which, when put in, exhibits up as another printer on your method. Simply choose CutePDF as your printer and &quot;;print&quot;; your presentation and it will be saved as a PDF file. I nevertheless use CutePDF for other applications that do not assistance PDF.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I hope you will give the PDF tactic a attempt. It is 1 of people unusual solutions that rewards both you and your viewers.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>