<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="31dcc606c97f107f9bacbe758d5ab4cd">			Reputation: 5 of 5 Stars&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Amazing Cover Letter Creator was created by Jimmy Sweeney, who is a professional copywriter and has been President and CEO of a marketing and advertising company for 23 years. He's helped many people land jobs with his Job Search System, Cover Letter Creator, and Resume Creator. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obviously, if Amazing Cover Letter Creator was made by Jimmy Sweeney, it is going to be a great product. He's helped many individuals land the jobs of their dreams. Jimmy Sweeney has a great reputation, which also gives the Amazing Cover Letter Creator an excellent reputation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Simplicity of Use &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Honestly, the Amazing Cover Letter Creator is one of the simplest applications that I have ever used. With only a few clicks of your mouse, the Amazing Cover Letter Creator will create a cover letter designed specifically for the job that you're applying for. Simply, select when you're planning to apply for the job. Next, choose how many other applicants there will be for the job you are applying for. Then, select how much experience you have in the field where the job is. Next, you will get a cover letterthat will help you land an interview! It's as easy as 1, 2, 3. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ease of Use Rating: 5 of 5 Stars&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Support &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I contacted the support team twice because I had problems with setting up the program. The first time, I didn't receive a response. A few days later, I contacted support again. This time they emailed me back within two days. Although I received an answer to my issue, it took a lot longer than I'd expected. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Support Rating: 3 of 5 Stars&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Price &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The original price on the Amazing Cover Letter Creator was $49.95. However, since I am an existing customer, I am able to give anyone that I refer a 20% discount. Which means that you can purchase the Amazing Cover Letter Creator for only $39.95. Considering I made use of this software to land a position, I think that a $39.95 investment is definitely worth the cost. I am not saying that it is going to work for everyone, however I know that it worked for me. Plus, if you don't land a job interview using the software, there's a sixty day money back guarantee. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Price Rating: 5 of 5 Stars&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Overall &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Based on the 4 above criteria, I would have to rate the Amazing Cover Letter Creator 4 out of 5 stars. The application is easy to work with and anyone will be able to figure it out. One problem that I had with this program was the support. However, if you aren't going to have any problems with the application, the support isn't likely to be an issue. Plus, my question was answered after a couple of days (even though it did require some patience). I would personally recommend this application for anybody trying to find a job. The difference between applicants for a job could just come down to the cover letter.I would definitely go withI a reliable professional like Jimmy Sweeney. You never know, the Amazing Cover Letter Creator might land you a job, exactly like it did for me!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Overall Rating: 4 of 5 Stars&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FAmazing-Cover-Letters-For-Your-Resume%2F03EFBFFFF0243797A000801588F3A%3Fref_title%3Ddwightheath11%26amp%3Bref_url%3Dhttp%253a%252f%252fcommunity.atom.com%252fprofile%252f07A7943020243797A00010243797A%252fContent%252fPost%252fMyPosts2.aspx%26amp%3Bref_ucid%3D7A7943020243797A00010243797A"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://community.atom.com/Post/Amazing-Cover-Letters-For-Your-Resume/03EFBFFFF0243797A000801588F3A?ref_title=dwightheath11&amp;ref_url=http%3a%2f%2fcommunity.atom.com%2fprofile%2f07A7943020243797A00010243797A%2fContent%2fPost%2fMyPosts2.aspx&amp;ref_ucid=7A7943020243797A00010243797A&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdwightheath11.livejournal.com%2F766.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://dwightheath11.livejournal.com/766.html&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogbud.com%2Fcgi-bin%2Findex.pl%3Fpoemnumber%3D598093%26amp%3Bsitename%3Ddwightheath1136%26amp%3Bpassword%3D310331sgf2arC7o0o98247.3103%26amp%3Bpoemoffset%3D0%26amp%3Bdisplaypoem%3Dt%26amp%3Bitem%3Dblog"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://blogbud.com/cgi-bin/index.pl?poemnumber=598093&amp;sitename=dwightheath1136&amp;password=310331sgf2arC7o0o98247.3103&amp;poemoffset=0&amp;displaypoem=t&amp;item=blog&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>