<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d2c619acf0475ca4cfb448b20dfdb3fe">			&lt;strong&gt;;August 22, 2011&lt;/strong&gt;; – &lt;strong&gt;;Australia&lt;/strong&gt;; – &lt;strong&gt;;Applied Training Solutions&lt;/strong&gt;; – has offered effective training solutions for trainers and assessors of vocational and educational training (VET) providers through a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FwcGxpZWR0cmFpbmluZ3NvbHV0aW9ucy5jb20uYXUvdGFlNDAxMTAtY2VydGlmaWNhdGUtaXYtaW4tdHJhaW5pbmctYW5kLWFzc2Vzc21lbnQv" target="_blank"&gt;;Certificate IV in Training and Assessment&lt;/a&gt;;. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A Certificate IV in Training and Assessment is a mandatory requirement so that trainers and assessors become more qualified and nationally recognised to train others per Australian National Standards. A career in training becomes a worthwhile career if he completes this qualification program. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The TAE40110 Certificate IV in Training and Assessment has been found to improve the competencies of both trainers and assessors. Their skills are honed and more developed to address the training needs of groups and individuals in various registered training organisations or RTOs. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Trainers aiming for a Certificate IV in Training and Assessment are provided with skills to confidently train groups and individuals, as well as the knowledge to develop assessment tools. They are trained on how to conduct training and assessment evaluations, lead a team, develop organisational policies and procedures, and recruit, select and induct qualified staff. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Students embarking on a career in training have received expert trainer support while studying the Certificate IV in Training and Assessment course. The trainers assist in the clarification of the course content, assessment, and time management. Assessment results for the Certificate IV in Training and Assessment are received 2 business days after submitting them. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After studying the Certificate IV in Training and Assessment, the trainer-students are given the opportunity to choose and succeed in different career paths such as Trainer and Assessor in mining or construction industry, Teacher or Lecturer in VET organisations, Off-Shore Trainer, or Human Resource Development Officer. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Upon the successful completion of the course, trainer-students have received a nationally recognised qualification to perform the role of a skilled trainer or assessor within the workplace.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Applied Training Solutions&lt;/strong&gt;; offers Certificate IV in Training and Assessment for aspiring people who want to embark on a career in training. For more information, call &lt;strong&gt;;1800 287 960&lt;/strong&gt;; or visit &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FwcGxpZWR0cmFpbmluZ3NvbHV0aW9ucy5jb20uYXUv" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fappliedtrainingsolutions.com.au%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://appliedtrainingsolutions.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;About Applied Training Solutions&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Applied Training Solutions&lt;/strong&gt;; offers the course on Certificate IV in Training and Assessment along with other qualification courses. The course is rich, vibrant, engaging and of the highest standards of excellence, making it one of the most exciting training and assessment courses available for RTOs and VET providers.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>