<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="744cb1d14cfaa030c0f2b063378720cc">			Images: He Zi / Wu Min Xia, three-meter womens doubles championship very content Sohu Sports News (Jeu cultivate Sohu documented March 25) Beijing March 25, 2011, Beijing FINA Diving Grand Prix series spherical began, the three-meter womens ambigu last, Chinas mix of what place / Wu Min Xia, to 341.10 points forward of second location 30 factors gain to win very easily, Canada and Russia mixed factors have been the blend of silver and bronze. Todays closing five video games, what placement and Wu Min Xia commence from the 1st round has been firmly occupy the top placement, despite the fact that this action on the 2nd leap 5331D problems &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , only acquired 50.forty factors, but all round as the two folks power has an absolute benefit, so it is fairly smooth win. Wu Min Xia also was very thrilled right after the recreation, &quot;I am delighted when again at the Water Cube through the attempts of the two of us won, and what my situation with a lot more than a calendar year following right after, the potential has drastically improved, but there are some specific action enough hope to make the recreation perform through far better training. &quot;In truth in addition to the second jump &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , the 3rd jump nowadays, there have been two difficulties at the same time, and Wu Min Xia, a reporter asked regardless of whether this would affect two folks in the gaming state and play, explained Wu Min Xia does not have much effect, &quot;we equally accomplished their moves are also very good, as is more normal to request simultaneously on the need to far better increase action.&quot;He Chong Zhaiyin nonetheless look comfortable on the podium with a smile and Qin Kai Sohu Jeu Information (Jeu cultivate Sohu documented March 25) Beijing March twenty five, 2011, Beijing FINA Diving Grand Prix collection round started out, the The just-concluded mens three-meter closing &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , Qin Kai in 541.79 factors to win, in the realization of two consecutive collection, although also following the Moscow right after his second victory over aged rivals He Chong, who completed 2nd in factors to 536.twenty five. He Chong in 2008 atop the three-meter, have been very number of men and women ready to shake his gain &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , as sitting on &quot;the difficulty of the king&quot; in the title, He Chong and other players in the competitors has an edge. Nevertheless, due to the fact of the Olympics following the massive scar on the knee, He Chong and often up to seven months of relaxation, which also helps make him the position decline. By comparison, Qin Kai in the winter season coaching this year &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , after bursting out of their vitality, the two defeat He Chong, gave what he rushed following the Beijing Olympics only two failures, so that at the press conference, He Chong had some exciting to get in touch with him &quot;Qin Kai Ge,&quot; whilst saying &quot;these days missing his really convinced.&quot; Indeed, in the winter training in Moscow and Beijing after two stations Sequence race, Qin Kai to perform impeccable, superior stability, and what made him red in the contest to gain the upper hand. Right now, in the fifth jump 109C this motion, he obtained a gaming-substantial score of a hundred.70 factors, a portion which is the only score above, with Qin Kais words, &quot;This is my biggest achievement these days.&quot; . Talked about his perform nowadays, in fact &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , Qin Kai, said soon after his look is still a minor nervous, particularly the action in the past constantly 109C ball dropped, but nowadays can withstand stress, or sense more content. The two beat He Chong, Qin Kai blamed the education technique, &quot;In reality, He Chong before the Russian station and todays game perform is nonetheless good, it can be mentioned either just before or now, He Chong are really robust, but I was capable to get over him, that I played a winter education result, which for me is a very good return. &quot;Qin Kai, but then explained that a single or two of successful or dropping can not explain what the issue,&quot; there must have missing the recreation is such that is extremely regular &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , 2012 I am certain their objective is clear to that gold medal, as the benefits now, who do not know how to hope through our attempts to get some of the far more stable. &quot;Xinhua Beijing March 25 sports activities news (Luyu Chen, Bo Li Wen) for the British mens three-meter service fees and the Canadian people pull ten-meter platform womens singles player of the Fischer-Tropsch, the soles of the feet are the consequence slip diving in the 25th Series semi-last defeat of the Beijing Railway Station culprit. &quot;I was working ahead when the foot board on the front stage on too, so did not management the physique,&quot; the participant as a wild card entry for pull service fees, stated. La Price in Group B semi-last second jump, the unique should be finished ahead pike somersault 50 percent twist reflexive week and a 50 percent (5353&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; motion, resulting in the consider-off foot Caikong, only to be 36.thirty factors. His still left toe injuries and therefore &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nbashoesofficial.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nbashoesofficial.com&lt;/a&gt;; , impact the subsequent 4-hop perform. The very same &quot;slip&quot; out of the finals along with the Fischer-Tropsch Canadian girl. Despite the fact that the 1st look of the fellow group B Philip Wong acquired only the 1st jump 44.eighty points, adopted by appearances, nonetheless, has the Fischer-Tropsch immediately in the very first jump out of the platform, the failure of scoreless action. As far powering, struggling to close on the heels of the Fischer-Tropsch even though it has failed to make up for sliding out of the points big difference, missed the ultimate.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>