<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fb40b0270ee66b52379e7b41946d6ae7">			There is a solution in the form of luxury log cabin holidays which provide a very special place to stay and in quite intimate surroundings for a good price and are the perfect place to celebrate in these cost conscious times.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Decide On Where You Would Like To Visit&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The luxury log cabin holidays are perfect for families and also for couples wanting to get away from it all for a special weekend. Many are located in spectacular surroundings close to mountain ranges, in woodlands, or by the coast and have lots of things to see and do within the complex and also the surrounding area. From Scotland to Cornwall the choice is huge and affordable for most budgets.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The best way to find your accommodation is to decide first on which area of the England, Scotland or Wales you would like to go to. Once you have done this then you can select a sub region in that area. You will find log cabins in all the locations throughout the UK, so choosing where to go is one of the hardest decisions you will have to make.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Take a Short Break or a Main Holiday?&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A short break that makes people feel as though they have had a rest and return refreshed is very important. Staying on one of the luxury log cabin holidays does just this thanks to the peace and tranquillity and the very special surroundings. Having a bit of luxury makes a huge difference and with facilities appealing to lots of people such as a fishing lake, a hot tub and beautiful woodland walks within a short distance what could be better. Guests can choose to stay within their luxurious surroundings or explore the surrounding area.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you have some more time available on a week long stay then you can take in many of the local sights and attractions and fill your days with fun and adventure. There are lots of places to walk or to visit a local town or attraction within a short drive.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Self Catering Can Mean Enjoying the Local Produce&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having a special meal is all part of the experience of getting away and celebrating. On luxury log cabin holidays there are excellent modern self catering facilities and even barbecue areas. Why not think about visiting a local farmers market and stock up on some ingredients to create a wonderful meal from the log cabins. Choosing from freshly caught fish or local wine is a lovely experience and makes a meal very special and enjoyable. For those who don't want to cook there are usually a wide range of pubs and restaurants within a short drive.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Relax and Enjoy the Wide Range of Facilities&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guests can do as little or as much exercise as they please on a short break. Many luxury log cabin holidays are located close to swimming pools, classic walking routes and even horse riding so there is plenty to choose from and even try for the first time like surfing. There really is something for everyone on a vacation like this and booking the best place is best done sooner rather than later as those in the know make sure they have reserved their favourite spots very early to be guaranteed a return.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5taWNoYWVscGF1bGhvbGlkYXlzLmNvLnVrL0FjY29tbW9kYXRpb24vaG9saWRheS1sb2RnZXMtbG9nLWNhYmlucy12aWxsYXMuYXNweA__" target="_blank"&gt;;luxury lodges uk&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>