<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="1cd8dd719d5184392cbd2e41974934d">			To better understand what an Ascended Master is, I will share with you my understanding of what it means to ascend. To ascend is to rise above and reach through the fear of the unknown. This, of course is just the beginning.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ascend is defined as to float or suspend the physical in the air, above the physical plane of dense material energy. It is releasing, temporarily, all that is not of love and light. It is expanding conscious awareness, reaching higher and higher levels of consciousness.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To ascend is to walk the path before you as righteously as possible, living a life from the viewpoint of unconditional love and total acceptance. It is about transcending judgment, fear and limitation through healing, forgiveness of the Self and others. It is about honoring where you are, striving to the best you possible with the understanding that there are moments where faith and trust are the only stepping stones to an even higher sense of awareness.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ascension in its simplest form means to rise above. To purify your mental, emotional, physical and Spiritual energy bodies, releasing all negative energy, thoughts and emotions. The physical body is purified through righteous actions and thoughts. It may require several lifetimes in physical form to resolve and dissolve memories of worthlessness and dis-empowerment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is also about surrendering the need for material things and sometimes other people in the physical sense, rising above the laws of gravity. The higher your energy vibrates, the higher your sense of conscious awareness.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Conscious awareness causes you to see, hear, feel and act differently because your awareness is no longer heavy with fear, doubt and confusion. It is instead laced with unconditional love, light and Spiritual understanding.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Transformation is the key to ascension in any moment. Once transformation begins, the next higher vibration is that of transmutation the actual metaphysical form of alchemy from dense physical energy matter to the vibration of golden Spiritual energy. Transcendence is the attaining of ascension in its highest form, crossing over into the Etheric Plane.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An Ascended Master is, in the esoteric Metaphysical term, a human who has resolved all past issues and memories that have been experienced healed and released through multiple incarnations into physical form, rising to inhabit the Etheric Plane. The Etheric Plane or Dimension is the space in-between the Realm of Spirit and the Earthly plane of dense physical matter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once transition from physical form to the Etheric Plane has been completed, an Ascended Master may choose to incarnate into physical form to raise the vibration and share knowledge which assists many in understanding Spiritual teachings.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There comes a point or a lifetime in which it is the last incarnation into physical form and an Ascended Master chooses to remain in the Ethereal Dimension of non-form. It is from the Ethereal Dimension that Ascended Masters communicate with many people who are in physical form.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You need only ask an Ascended Master for his or help. Having asked, be open to receiving the guidance, validation, confirmation and the messages you seek to raise your own vibration, expanding your conscious awareness to higher and higher levels of understanding.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you raise your vibration, you in turn raise the vibration of all whom cross your path and that of the world in which you live, work and play.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3V0dWJlLmNvbS93YXRjaD92PWhFWTAxN21xYmt3" target="_blank"&gt;;spiritual enlightenment&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>