<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="8460de4670c59aac7bf14b9f25220a2">			Many people are based overseas for many years and small things, like watching or listening to favorite programs from home and staying in touch, become very important. With simple set up process, there are live broadcasts with absolutely no impact on the existing internet connection.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are ways around some of the restrictions – using Foxy proxy to make iPlayer think live in the UK, and having a UK iTunes account so as to access pod casts that way. But this is breaking the rules because the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaC1iYmMtaXBsYXllci5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;BBC abroad&lt;/a&gt;;seems to treat everyone beyond the British Isles differently.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are other low cost services that offer BBC abroad. These low cost services give only 1 UK VPN connection that they oversell, you will find a lot of buffering and connection problems as many people are trying to use the same connection in peak times. Every account has free access to USA servers irrespective to unblock any USA restricted website such as Hulu TV, Fox, NBC etc.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are thousands of happy customers who renew their service on a regular basis. Full   fast customer support is offered in case of any problems. Members area has everything needed to start watching BBC abroad. As standard not only BBC abroad is obtained but also all live sport links including free live Premier League and Champions league football updated daily, easy to use software allowing to switch VPN servers enabled by BBC iplayer abroad, full instructions to setup the service to watch streaming movies and international TV channels from around the world. Members also have access to discounts on other packages. Every new member has free lifetime access to members area.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is a much more expensive route, as payment is needed to make for the TV subscription as well; however the quality of picture is just amazing. For an expat living abroad and willing to watch BBC abroad online it really is the best option, there is no other way to watch BBC for instance.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The cheapest option but not really the simplest is to connect back to BBC iplayer, what is needed is forming a simple VPN or SSH tunnel back to a computer in the UK. Proxy settings can then be modified in the browser and IP address will seem to be based in the UK. This method works very well if there is some technical knowledge available and access to a machine in the UK, one of the issues is that a good upload speed from the UK machine is needed or the connection will be extremely slow.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more information:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaC1iYmMtaXBsYXllci5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;BBCiplayer&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="15235e4fccbadcab14bfd6b9c7eeee83">			Currently BBC iPlayer TV programs are available to play in the UK only
&lt;br /&gt;;BUT it is really quite easy to get &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaC1iYmMtaXBsYXllci5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;iPlayer abroad&lt;/a&gt;; working just fine. Watching the BBC iplayer abroad is possible with few of the methods/tricks. Those who miss watching BBC iplayer abroad, proxy servers are a good option. One can watch iplayer abroad both by means of free and paid options. The procedure of availing the service and question about how to watch BBC iplayer abroad are made easy with the information provided.
&lt;br /&gt;;There is much software available to watch iplayer abroad. A software known as 'Identity Cloaker' can be used for viewing the iplayer live. It also allows the users to download the programs for viewing them later. The Identity Cloaker software provides options of UK VPN and UK proxy. Using the Identity Cloaker network, one can surf through a secure proxy. Most of the free proxy servers available on the Internet have a slow speed and they are also affected by viruses. The Identity Cloaker therefore, proves to be a better option over them.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many proxy server based in the UK which allow users to access BBC iplayer abroad. One can use servers however, but should beforehand check for the most reliable ones. Most of these proxy servers provide free service. There are few which require users to have a BBC TV license. Information about one such proxy server, the TV proxy is presented below.
&lt;br /&gt;;The TV Proxy service allows people to access the iplayer abroad, given that they own a BBC TV license. The TV Proxy service, on their behalf provides access to BBC TV license holders, who want to watch the iplayer abroad.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are companies which offer proxy servers for users based abroad. These companies charge their users for accessing the servers, however, are much faster than the free ones. The fees being charged for 1 year service by these companies. Slingbox should be the answer to queries related to watching iplayer abroad. There are lots of companies who now offer services to surf via their own private proxy servers. These work in just the same way as the free ones but are faster and more reliable.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more information:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRjaC1iYmMtaXBsYXllci5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;iplayer abroad&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>