<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a66c3b78d054ff5ac63ecca3c2d4656d">			I especially like the best way it looks. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; It has some of those handy little latches on the inside to hang my keys on. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; There are a place to get my pens. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; There are a pocket for my phone. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; No make-up bag required. They've already this covered too! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; It even has an outer pocket that matches a bottle of water perfectly. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; And pockets are endless! &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Duffel bags &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Duffel bags come in numerous colors, outrageous patterns, with wheels, without wheels, in leather or fabric. They are easy to pack, extremely lightweight and easily stored once at your destination. They are ideal for road journeys and may be thrown into the back of an trunk and squashed inside fit. Or if you're moving from destination to place, a duffel with wheels is a good choice. They also weigh almost nothing so won't tip you over the baggage limit at airports, meaning you can save money money at your destination on new clothes! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The evident downside to duffel bags is the issue of protection for your belongings. Items can easily get broken, so if you're considering souvenir shopping a tote or backpack may be a better option. Duffel bags are not necessarily the easiest bag to get and carry, so if you're opting for adventure travel a backpack might be a better option. There's nothing worse than wanting to carry a heavy duffel or tote on one shoulder whilst walking straight down an uneven surface. Most of the better quality duffel bags are made by Travelpro and Switzerland Army Victorinox. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Bags &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; The perfect choice for independent, adventure travelers who ought to keep their hands free for maps and guidebooks. Backpacks come in alot of shapes and sizes, with day packs to 20 smack packs for month longer adventures. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Designed to be comfortable to have when full, make sure the backpack you choose is easy to take on and off, is adjustable to fit your frame, has padded shoulder straps and a waist and chest strap and avoid backache. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Anyone can buy backpacks with straps that can be zipped inside to stop handles getting caught with transport and potential thieves from picking them in place easily. Another backpack tip may be to choose one that could be laid flat and zipped open to pack. Top load backpacks might be a headache - you have to take everything out and discover just one item. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Totes &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Totes could be the perfect choice for company trips, providing a classy, easy to pack option that affords a specialized image, particularly when chosen in leather. They are full of pockets and compartments, to house all your documents, files and your laptop, as well as enough space for a couple of day's worth of clothing. If you travel by air regularly, investing in a good quality tote could make your travel experience much simpler, providing you enough space and protection for some souvenirs along the way. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They may well either be shoulder maintained or wheeled, are often expandable and come in a vast variety involving styles, colors and designs. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NhbWVyb25zaGFycDUxMS53aWtpc3BhY2VzLmNvbS9Td2lzcytBcm15K0JhY2twYWNrKy0rVGhlK1JpZ2h0K0Nob2ljZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;A Review of the SwissGear SA1908 ScanSmart Backpack&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5be299501f47b318493db1369bfe2ede">			Prices &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of all the back packs that are available it's probably that the leather backpacks is going to be the most expensive, because leather is a lot more expensive material than canvas and also nylon is. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You are able to find leather back packs cheaper online than you can in a local store simply because you will have a wider selection of stores. Shopping online also will allow you to compare prices before purchasing. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Backpacks are definitely the perfect accessory choice if you like to take part in adventurous, outdoor activities as well as a simple over night sleepover. Undeniably, backpacks are most suitable for carrying around essential equipment along with a few other personal items while they are out tasking part inside your outdoor hike where ever you may be off to. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Through the years the construction and design of backpacks have been completely developed to be in the utmost optimal of packs. They are large enough to hold everything had to survive several days out on the trail and have become versatile and functional in various circumstances. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A great addition to the usual heavy and often times cumbersome backpacks is the mini backpack. These were initially designed to take the few extra items which simply would not fit into your larger backpack, but also have become the perfect load up for smaller hikers together with children. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Little ones will truly appreciate having their own backpack to carry. Besides lessening the load you will need to carry, it also makes your children feel more involved and give them a sense involving responsibility and belonging. That addition of mini backpacks to your children will enable these phones manage their own possessions without putting an unneeded burden about them. Yet on the deeper level will also promote a strong sense of independence built in. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the mini backpacks for more compact or smaller loads is most beneficial. They can be used for a change of clothes or simply snacks and meals. Stocking them with the minimal of necessities will help to teach your young ones the essentials needed if he or she venture off on some sort of hike. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Outside of hiking, these mini backpacks have also become common among students of all ages. They're just the perfect size to carry all of your current school books and materials and make accessing all that you desire very convenient. There are actually even some people, male and female, that choose to use them in their reading books to carry their belongings around in the safe manner. In many cases replacing a purse or briefcase in order to free up their hands for other activities. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lets also take into account about sleepovers. Every girl and boy likes to sleep over at their best friends house from time to time. Which has a mini backpack to carry all of their sleepover accessories is definitely perfect to emulate an adventure inside safe and warm confines on their friends home. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When buying a backpack or mini backpack you'll discover that there are several brands, designs, and features that every feature. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvdHh0dHN5eWdqZ2F5Y3J5amRicnYvY29udGVudC9jYW52YXMtcnVja3NhY2stb2xkLXNjaG9vbC1iYWNrcGFjay01MTI5MzUw" target="_blank"&gt;;The Army Backpack - An Essential Soldier Kit&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9EZWxwaGExNS9yZWFkLzUxNjE0NjQvY2FudmFzLXJ1Y2tzYWNrLW9sZC1zY2hvb2wtYmFja3BhY2s_" target="_blank"&gt;;Swiss Army Backpack - The Right Choice&lt;/a&gt;;As the character Clairee Belcher so famously said in the movie Steel Magnolias, &quot;;The only thing that separates us in the animals is our capacity accessorize.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>