<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="90f02244fc7517c5ee0123695d003cdd">			Once in a while you come across a topic, like &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXlha21vcnJpcy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;kayaking chicago&lt;/a&gt; for instance, and it will be instrumental for you to realize there are related areas that it would be very good for you to explore. The fact that there is always something more to learn may not be obvious, if you read enough you should be led to explore more. So, we hope you are getting a sense or idea that it is in your best interest to keep looking until you are positive you have all you need. Missing critical information can lead to complications, and then you are still trying to figure out what is going on. While some information can look a little intimidating at first, depending on what you bring to the table, you are of course more than capable of understanding the issues involved.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The planet has had the problem of air pollution for a very long time. Some parts are worse than others, but the effects are widespread, and long term. Most of the pollution is produced by the chemicals spewed into the air due to industrialization. The breakthroughs we have in our society is worth the health and safety danger we've created because of this. Not only do the goods and services make life less difficult and more enjoyable, but also provide employment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We do not know how to tackle the problem given that industrialization has improved our lives in one aspect but has also damaged our lives on the other. A vehicle is a good example where it's great convenience but pollutes the air so why don't they make a clean driving car. Why is it completely up to men and women to change their driving habits, by car pooling, or taking a bus, when the technology is there to have more energy-efficient cars and trucks. Everyone must do their part to not squander energy, but that means every person, including those who can afford to drive what they want, when they want, and not be concerned one iota what the cost is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Emission laws have really helped minimize the amount of pollutants that get into the air. The pollution in the United States has become somewhat better because a number of businesses moved their industrial facilities overseas. Even though the air is better in the United States, the result is loss of work opportunities and a stagnate economy. Decisions that were made to help society take quite a while to realize the outcomes. It is easy for us to blame man for all the bad that has happened but nature can do some damage as well. Forests are being destroyed by fires all the time as a result of lightning.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Trees also are destroyed by tornadoes and hurricanes. Volcanoes put a great deal of pollution into the air, and this has taken place for a lot longer than any of us have been alive. It would be good to know if natural disasters take place, simply because they happen, or if man is the trigger. If we brought on many of it, then we ought to make an effort to stop it. It must involve everyone and not those who are less privileged. There has to be a way to get the affluent to find ways to solve this problem without needing to make a profit off of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most people would love to drive an energy-efficient car. Many would love to have a home that is energy efficient.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional Resources:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYm91dHVzLm9yZy9Vc2VyOnRoYWRkZXVzZGZoYXJt" target="_blank"&gt;Air Pollution: Who Is Responsible?&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>