<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="39651d642a16117f662b6d1ca84e4329">			Look no further for tips on online reputation management. Simple steps on getting positive results and effectively managing you online reputation are shown in the following article.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Increase Your Community. This is an uncomplicated and productive way to manage your online reputation. Do you have knowledge of what community building is? You can have a place like a forum or bulletin board, which is easy to do, where customers can post their questions, concerns and feedback about your product or services. Having a company forum allows you to engage with your existing customers, so that you can listen and respond while having a direct communication with them. You can also use this for posting press releases, reports, events that are happening and company updates. It?s also a good practice to interact with your customers by asking for their feedback, asking about their problems and soliciting suggestions which enables you to learn of their experience they are having with your product or service. This platform is a wonderful way to know and understand your customers grievances and allows you to resolve them in a timely manner. Leverage Social Networking Platforms: The popularity of social networking sites on the Internet such as Facebook and Twitter grows daily as more and more people log on just to share their happiness, vent their anger or simply express their opinions. Connecting with your customers will raise to a new level once you become active on social networking websites. You will know right away what others are saying about your products and services. Create company accounts on the social sites like Facebook, Twitter and Linked in and log into them daily so you can see what customers/prospects are thinking or wanting to know about your brand. Taking part in the discussions and quickly answering customers questions makes it easier to manage your online brand.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When to Hire a PR Company: If you find you don't have the time to manage your online reputation or its becoming harder to do so, then consider hiring a PR company. Not everyone has the time it takes to be active on the social media platforms so that they can effectively manage their online reputations. This is why you hiring a professional PR company is a good idea; you'll be able to outsource your online reputation management this way and get regular reports about the results. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The information above show how to effectively manage your online reputation as well as the steps to take with your company to make sure that your brand makes a strong impact on your target audience.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getmbaonline.net%2Fmba-online-degree"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.getmbaonline.net/mba-online-degree&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>