<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d3fbe6af2545152e60dfb3f59679a1a9">			If you are on a tight budget then the Vizio plasma tv is a viable choice for you. They usually are lower priced when compared with some other major brand name opponents but the quality of the tvs isn't compromised. In fact, Vizio fairly often makes Televisions that rate a lot higher compared to several of their biggest brand (and more pricey) rivals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We decided to have a search online for testimonials and also feedback of the impressive appearing 50 inches plasma tv from Vizio. Allow me to truthfully point out that there were extremely few negative responses, and surely not one which outright criticized this specific t . v . as a piece of junk. It's far away from that: this has integrated Dolby Digital audio (the first fifty&quot; High-definition television plasma to provide this).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One more excellent benefit concerning the Vizio plasma fifty in . Tv set is the fact that it really is very easy to setup. The normal Joe can have it put in place within a really brief space of time; many other tv sets nearly need a college diploma in electronics to begin with.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And so precisely why would you choose this specific television instead of an LCD?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plasma televisions just like the Vizio have a increased viewing angle and much less visible movement blur when compared to Liquid crystal display tvs. If you're looking at the brilliant Vizio JV50P Jive Plasma Television you won't locate something better in the budget range. It features a included wire less sound system which makes it stay ahead of its competitors. One more highlight is actually a Picture in Picture solution that really adds a whole lot of versatility to this Television.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Online connectivity is managed by using a Computer input. several HDMI and 2 component video ports. Even though the actual JV50P is not a 1080p Television (undetectable on a 50&quot; Television), it can take 1080p sources. The image shown on the JV50P is definitely crisp and clean along with clear colours. The particular Vizio JV50P Plasma Tv is not going to dissatisfy even the most difficult of consumers and is also the main one to think about if your spending budget allows.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.internetreadytvx.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.internetreadytvx.com/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>