<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e6127a3ac86438bb9d0c89c9c5b35e8">			In English articles content are phrases that mix with a noun to expose the type of reference getting created by&lt;br /&gt;the noun. Ordinarily articles or web site posts specify the grammatical definiteness of the noun. Examples are &quot;;the, a,&lt;br /&gt;and an&quot;;. However that isn't going to exist in Chinese.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chinese Lesson are phrases that blend with a noun to exhibit the variety of reference remaining made by&lt;br /&gt;the noun. Generally content content articles specify the grammatical definiteness of the noun. Examples are &quot;;the, a,&lt;br /&gt;and an&quot;;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are no actual posts in Chinese Lesson, there is ? zhè, but that actually indicates this. As in ???&lt;br /&gt;zhè b?n sh? indicating this guide. ? b?n is the measureword of ? sh? guide. In English you are unable to say:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;sugar, you have to say a lump of sugar, lump acquiring the measure word, also a grain of salt, grain finding&lt;br /&gt;the measure phrase. But there are only a handful of nouns in the English language which need to have to have these varieties of a amount&lt;br /&gt;phrase. In Chinese Lesson each and just about every noun desires a measure phrase. Making use of the appropriate measure phrase displays that&lt;br /&gt;you grasp the Chinese Lesson language, offered that finding the suitable measure word is actually some endeavor.&lt;br /&gt;Chinese Lesson them selfs never alwaus know the ideal measure phrase and they use the standard quantity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;phrase ? gè. The indefinite limited write-up can be translated as??y? xi? but implies some, some sum&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGluZXNlZm9yc21hcnRraWRzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;Learn Chinese Online&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>