<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fac94f9df13d92fe36f9f0aa3e29cccc">			If you've lately moved or switched careers, your Citibank credit card application will be denied for this &lt;br&gt;;explanation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Your credit record is also quick or too undesirable -&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is the major explanation purposes are denied. If your credit score score is beneath a selected quantity (which  differs from card to card) you will be regarded as also higher of a possibility to problem a card. If you have none or as well tiny credit score, card organizations feel this is just practically as undesirable as poor credit score given that they have no basis for trusting you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;You presently have too many cards -&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Citibank, like any credit score card company, does not like to see men and women opening far too numerous accounts. It may possibly show that you aren't great with your credit (if your cards are maxed out) or that you might conclude up in boueux afterwards on (if you max out the cards and then cannot spend for them), so most lenders will end issuing you cards after a particular  amount.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;People of you with a good credit score looking for a credit score card that delivers a funds reward software ought to take a appear at the Citi Dividend Platinum Select Card, issued by Citibank.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Through Citibank's Dividend Reward course, cardholders can earn 5% money from purchases at the grocery store, and even drugstores - the crucial purchases of modern-day residing. Also they can bring in one% funds rebate on all other purchases, as nicely as income innovations and harmony transfers. The Dividend Pounds do not expire.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But that is not all. By way of the Citi Dividend Merchant Network, cardholders can generate an regular of five% income again. Of training course there is a limit to the total of income back again that can be attained in a 12 months, set at $300. Even so the amount of money back again that can be earned by way of the Citi Dividend Merchant Network is unlimited. When the volume of Dividend Bucks attained reaches $fifty, a check will be issued. That's much additional enticing than redeemable products!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The downside to the Citi Dividend Card is that the curiosity costs are considerably over normal. Then there's the minimal cap of 19.99% for hard cash improvements, so even if the Prime Price drops you'd even now have to fork out a hefty curiosity rate for the bank loan.  Having to pay interest on anything is for fools.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Just to confuse you even a lot more...here ya go...here's a little outline of how it operates&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;one) Uncover stability $1200&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2) transfer that equilibrium to Citibank Card 1 at %   (learn equilibrium =         Citibank card 1 equilibrium = 1200)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3) Cancel your mail-paper statements with citicard - will get you $5 (find out stability =   Citibank card 1 balance = 1195)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;three) Make payments above the calendar year...for instance ...say you shell out off 600  (find equilibrium =    Citibank card 1 balance = 595)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4) get Citibank card #two with a % amount - cancel your paper statements immediately - credits you $5 (Citibank card 2 harmony = -five)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5) transfer Citibank card one balance again to learn card (uncover card harmony = 595 Citibank card one harmony =  Citibank card two = -5)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6) cancel Citibank card #1&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;seven) transfer discover balance to Citibank card #2 (find out harmony =   Citibank card 2 equilibrium = 590)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NpdGljYXJkc2NvbS5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;citicards&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>