<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="cdfcdd3b1f43a45a08313505d5cebc54">			Affiliate marketer Phil Henderson is launching his new Stupidly Simple SEO. Using Phil's methods, average marketers will have a real chance to break the top ten search engine results for their low page mini-sites. Even though these sites don't have a lot of content and not many links pointing to them, they easily dominate the search engines for the right keywords, taking over other strong contending websites. What's more - you'll be able to claim a number three search results position. Phil's system has the power to let you take a brand new site and have it on the first page in less than an hour. Phil has done this with his very own sites, and the results have been overwhelming. It was designed that way, to get just about anyone very high rank, very quickly. Rest easy - nothing special needed with skills or things of that nature. This article will look at how to do this for your own money sites. Make sure you visit these strategies on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N1Ym1pdC1yc3MtZmVlZC53aWtpZG90LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;rss submitter&lt;/a&gt;; here...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Phil Henderson created the Stupidly Simple SEO system for marketers like him who don't want to compete with the big boys, but rather want to have their small profitable websites rank high with the big search engines. This special blueprint is based on his year plus experiences getting his small sites ranked highly in Google. The best part about his course is that it's easy to understand and apply. So many systems/courses on SEO are hypey, not many use easy methods that actually work. You'll find Phil's SEO approaches live up to their promises. Another very cool benefit is you won't need your own sites, he'll show you how to get high rankings using other people's free websites. And for you, if you there will be no need to pay for domain names, registration, yearly renewals, hosting, etc. Learn more about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYnRvb2xzb2Z0d2FyZXMuY29tL0RpcmVjdG9yeVN1Ym1pc3Npb25Tb2Z0d2FyZS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;submit to directories&lt;/a&gt;; here...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No one has witnessed a system like this in online marketing. It isn't painful because there's no unnecessary content to wade through. Everything that you find is pure gold and will help you get one site ranked after another fast. Phil's SEO system is taken right from the same pages of his business plan, and that gives it awesome credentials. This SEO system was created just for those who are having a tough time making anything online. This works really very well. If you just do it, you won't find any regrets at all.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Similar articles or blog posts and tips:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50YWdnZWQuY29tL2RpcmVjdG9yeXN1Ym1pc3Npb25zb2Z0d2FyZTY1MzU_" target="_blank"&gt;;The Stupidly Simple SEO System - A Peek Behind The Curtain&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bnJhcnguY29tL3ZhbmlsbGEvY29tbWVudHMucGhwP0Rpc2N1c3Npb25JRD0yNzE1Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;;An Honest Review of Phil Henderson's Stupidly Simple SEO System&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2N5cnVzY29sbGluczI1LmppZ3N5LmNvbS9lbnRyaWVzL2dlbmVyYWwvc3R1cGlkbHktc2ltcGxlLXNlby1yZXZpZXdlZC1hLWxvb2staW5zaWRlLWEtc3lzdGVtLXRvLXJhbmsteW91ci1zaXRlLWluLWxlc3MtdGhhbi0xLWhvdXI_" target="_blank"&gt;;Mr. Phil Henderson's Stupidly Simple SEO System: A Revealing Review&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>