<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="5f2963991b81a3bc85c5c68b4a561b96">			A woman stopped by, unannounced, at her son's 
&lt;br /&gt;House. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She knocked on the door then immediately 
&lt;br /&gt;Walked in. She was shocked to see her 
&lt;br /&gt;Daughter-in-law lying on the couch, totally 
&lt;br /&gt;Naked. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soft music was playing, and the aroma of 
&lt;br /&gt;Perfume filled the room. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'What are you doing?' she asked. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'I'm waiting for Justin to come home from 
&lt;br /&gt;Work.' The daughter-in-law answered. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;' But you're naked!' the mother-in-law exclaimed. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'This is my love dress,' the daughter-in-law 
&lt;br /&gt;Explained. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Love dress? But you're naked!' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Justin loves me to wear this dress,' she 
&lt;br /&gt;Explained. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Every time he sees me in this 
&lt;br /&gt;Dress, he instantly becomes romantic and ravages 
&lt;br /&gt;Me for hours.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The mother-in-law left. When she got home she 
&lt;br /&gt;Undressed, showered, put on her best perfume, 
&lt;br /&gt;Dimmed the lights, put on a romantic CD, and lay 
&lt;br /&gt;On the couch waiting for her husband to arrive. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, her husband came home. He walked in 
&lt;br /&gt;And saw her lying there so provocatively. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;' What are you doing?' he asked. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'This is my love dress,' she whispered, 
&lt;br /&gt;Sensually. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Needs ironing,' he said, 'What's for dinner?' 
&lt;br /&gt;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="47e26b2c258370370acb375fe70157e1">			The FBI had an opening for an assassin. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After all the background checks, interviews 
&lt;br /&gt;And testing were done, there were 3 finalists; 
&lt;br /&gt;Two men and a woman. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the final test, the FBI agents took one of 
&lt;br /&gt;The men to a large metal door and handed 
&lt;br /&gt;Him a gun. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'We must know that you will follow your 
&lt;br /&gt;Instructions no matter what the circumstances. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Inside the room you will find your wife sitting 
&lt;br /&gt;In a chair .. . . Kill her!!' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The man said, 'You can't be serious. I could 
&lt;br /&gt;Never shoot my wife.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The agent said, 'Then you're not the right man 
&lt;br /&gt;For this job. Take your wife and go home.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second man was given the same instructions. 
&lt;br /&gt;He took the gun and went into the room. All was 
&lt;br /&gt;Quiet for a bout 5 minutes. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The man came out with tears in his eyes, 'I tried, 
&lt;br /&gt;But I can't kill my wife.' The agent said, 'You don't 
&lt;br /&gt;Have what it takes. Take your wife and go home.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally, it was the woman's turn. She was given the 
&lt;br /&gt;Same instructions, to kill her husband. She took the 
&lt;br /&gt;Gun and went into the room. Shots were heard, one 
&lt;br /&gt;After another. They heard screaming, crashing, 
&lt;br /&gt;Banging on the walls. After a few minutes, all was 
&lt;br /&gt;Quiet. The door opened slowly and there stood the 
&lt;br /&gt;Woman, wiping the sweat from her brow. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'This gun is loaded with blanks' she said. 'I had to 
&lt;br /&gt;Beat him to death with the chair.'		</conversation>		<conversation id="f6bf141836766e839a68819de5d8a8ac">			A couple, age 67, went to the doctor's office. The doctor asked, &quot;;What can 
&lt;br /&gt;I do for you?&quot;; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The man said, &quot;;Will you watch us have sexual intercourse?&quot;; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The doctor looked puzzled, but agreed. When the couple finished, the doctor 
&lt;br /&gt;said, &quot;;There is nothing wrong with the way you have intercourse.&quot;; And he 
&lt;br /&gt;then charged them $32.00. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This happened several weeks in a row. The couple would make an appointment, 
&lt;br /&gt;have intercourse, pay the doctor and leave. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally the doctor asked, &quot;;Just what exactly are you trying to find out?&quot;; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The old man said, &quot;;We're not trying to find out anything. She is married 
&lt;br /&gt;and we can't go to her house. I am married and we can't go to my house. 
&lt;br /&gt;The Holiday Inn charges $60.00 and the Hilton charges $75.00. We do it here 
&lt;br /&gt;for $32.00, and I get back $28.00 from Medicare for a visit to the doctor's 
&lt;br /&gt;office.&quot;; 
&lt;br /&gt;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="56b9e28df5fabadce2a19590c393e6cd">			Three men - a Canadian farmer, Osama bin Laden and a 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Trash Biker are all walking together one day. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They come across a lantern and a Genie pops out of it... 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'I will give each of you one wish, which is three wishes in total', 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Says the Genie. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Canadian says, 'I am a farmer and my son will also farm. I want the land to be forever fertile in Canada ' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POOF! With the blink of the Genie's eye, the land in Canada was forever fertile for farming. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Osama was amazed, so he said, 'I want a wall around Afghanistan , Palestine , Iraq and Iran so that no infidels, Americans or Canadians 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can come into our precious land.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;POOF! Again, with the blink of the Genie's eye, there was a huge wall around those countries. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Biker says, 'I am very curious. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ctell me more about this wall.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Genie explains, 'Well, it's about 5,000 feet high, 500 feet thick and completely surrounds the country. Nothing can get in or out; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;it's virtually impenetrable.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Biker sits down on his Harley, cracks a beer, lights a cigar, 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smiles and says, 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Fill it with water.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e5d8a453be3a93a3255625e6e38c86aa">			A Husband takes his wife to play her first game of golf. Of course, the wife promptly hacked her first shot right through the window of the biggest house adjacent to the course. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The husband cringed, 'I warned you to be careful! Now we'll have to go up there, find the owner, apologize and see how much your lousy drive is going to cost us.' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the couple walked up to the house and knocked on the door. A warm voice said, 'Come on in.' 
&lt;br /&gt;When they opened the door they saw the damage that was done: glass was all over the place, and a broken antique bottle was lying on its side near the pieces of window glass. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A man reclining on the couch asked, 'Are you the people that broke my window?' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Uh...yeah! , sir. We're sure sorry about that,' the husband replied. 
&lt;br /&gt;'Oh, no apology is necessary. Actually I want to thank you. You see, I'm a genie, and I've been trapped in that bottle for a thousand years. 
&lt;br /&gt;Now that you've released me, I'm allowed to grant three wishes. I'll give you each one wish, but if you don't mind, I'll keep the last one for my self.' 
&lt;br /&gt;Wow, that's great!' the husband said. He pondered a moment and blurted out, 'I'd like a million dollars a year for the rest of my life.' 
&lt;br /&gt;'No problem,' said the genie 'You've got it, it's the least I can do. And I'll guarantee you a long, healthy life!' 
&lt;br /&gt;'And now you, young lady, what do you want?' the genie asked. 
&lt;br /&gt;'I'd like to own a gorgeous home complete with servants in every country in the world,' she said. 
&lt;br /&gt;'Consider it done,' the genie said. 'And your homes will always be safe from fire, burglary and natural disasters!' 
&lt;br /&gt;'And now,' the couple asked in unison, 'what's your wish, genie?' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Well, since I've been trapped in that bottle, and haven't been with a woman in more than a thousand years, my wish is to have sex with your wife.' 
&lt;br /&gt;The husband looked at his wife and said, 'Gee, honey, you know we both now have a fortune, and all those houses. What do you think?' 
&lt;br /&gt;She mulled it over for a few moments and said, 'You know, you're right. 
&lt;br /&gt;Considering our good fortune, I guess I wouldn't mind, but what about you, honey?' 
&lt;br /&gt;You know I love you sweetheart,' said the husband. I'd do the same for you!' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So the genie and the woman went upstairs where they spent the rest of the afternoon enjoying each other. The genie was insatiable. 
&lt;br /&gt;After about three hours of non-stop sex, the genie rolled over and looked directly into her eyes and asked, How old are you and your husband?' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;'Why, we're both 35,' she responded breathlessly. 
&lt;br /&gt;'No shit,' he said. 'Thirty-five years old and you both still believe in genies?' 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>