<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="51f90cf942786d9fda2d7d1836d66a65">			When it comes to breast implants, women have two choices: silicone breast implants and saline breast implants. Although each implant is filled with different substances, each type of implant has the potential to help the patient achieve the breast size and aesthetics that she desires, making the choice that much more difficult.
&lt;br /&gt;;The decision to have silicone breast implants rather than saline breast implants and vice versa is one that can only be made after determining how you want your breasts to ultimately look and feel, after understanding how you personally feel about silicone vs. saline, and of course, after having an honest and thorough discussion with your Boston Plastic surgeon about the similarities and differences between the two implants as well as the implications of a breast implant procedure in general.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the main differences between silicone and saline implants, of course, is that the silicone implant is filled with a silicone gel and the saline implant is filled with a sterile saline solution. (Silicone is a rubber-like, heat-resistant polymer and saline is basically saltwater.) You probably didn’t know, though, that the shells of both silicone and saline implants are composed of solid silicone, technically known as silastic, which is used in a variety of other medical devices, such as heart valves, artificial joints, and artificial lenses for the eye. You may have heard about the supposed risk of contracting an autoimmune disease in the case that a silicone implant ruptures, but fear not since this is not the case- there has yet to be a study showing that silicone is even capable of causing such diseases to develop.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The other main differences between silicone and saline implants lie in their unique aesthetic factors and their individual monetary costs. Saline implants, while less expensive than silicone implants, have been said to be too hard to the touch to feel like real breast tissue and have a higher chance to cause rippling when in comparison to the look and feel of silicone implants. However, these downsides have been remedied by inserting the saline implant behind the breast muscle and overfilling it just a little bit, creating a softer look and feel.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Saline implant procedures require a smaller incision than silicone implant procedures, and in the case of rupture, are easier to detect. Also, saline implants have the added advantage in that the size of the implant can be adjusted during the Boston Breast Augmentation procedure- silicone implants are inserted after already being formed in a preset size (hence the larger incision associated with it) while saline implants are typically inserted in a deflated form, being filled with saline only after the plastic surgeon has inserted the empty shell into the patient.		</conversation>		<conversation id="baa211379ca4605df8f0a9e662b897b2">			If you are looking for a Boston plastic surgeon, you don’t have to look very far. There are a lot of professionals out there that can help you get the best results with various procedures, no matter what you have in mind. Make sure that you give yourself the chance to explore all of the options that you have and learn about this process so that you can know what you’re getting into. Aside from that, getting any type of cosmetic surgery in Boston should be a simple task. It doesn’t matter whether you want rhinoplasty or breast augmentation in Boston, because there is something for just about everyone.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cosmetic surgery is becoming increasingly popular among people who want to improve their appearance. It doesn’t matter what the reasoning is because a Boston plastic surgeon can work with anyone to give them a great image with various procedures and surgical work. If you take the time to check out different providers, you will be able to learn which ones are the most qualified and experienced to give you the results that you deserve. It’s all about your needs and part of your needs involve reputation and quality, which is why that is so important to investigate. Getting a breast augmentation in Boston or another cosmetic procedure is going to be a lot simpler than it was in the past. Technology and new procedures have changed things and made the industry more efficient, safer, and given people a lot more to appreciate about hiring a Boston plastic surgeon. With the internet, you can learn all about this technology and the many procedures that you have to choose from so that you are prepared for your surgery, no matter what you have in mind.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remember that this is still surgery, no matter how you spin it. Any Boston plastic surgeonthat is worth their weight in experience will tell you that there are still risks and you have to be absolutely certain that this is the right thing for you. Whether you want a tummy tuck, face lift, nose job, or breast augmentation in Boston, it should be easy for you to find out everything that you need to know before you go under the knife. Ask questions, use the resources that you have, and make sure that you’re informed about your options and your procedure before you have cosmetic surgery done.		</conversation>		<conversation id="47c10e5139a5bc3ea4eee68eb4b43ec1">			Boston is the largest city in New England, and is home to more than six hundred thousand residents. With so much to see and do, from catching a Red Sox game to visiting the countless museums and historical attractions, it’s also a city that is hard not to enjoy. But it’s important to look and feel your best in order to really enjoy your time, and those who feel like their body could use improvement will likely want to consider plastic surgery. Finding a good plastic surgeon in Boston isn’t hard to do if you keep a few basic tips in mind.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To begin with you’ll want to make sure that you find a plastic surgeon who handles the procedures you’re interested in having done. Most surgeons handle all of the common surgeries, but it’s still worth double checking to make sure. If you’re looking for a face lift or breast augmentation in Boston, taking a couple of seconds to make sure the surgeon offers that procedure is an obvious step but one that some actually overlook. Once you know what you’re thinking of having done and which surgeons offer it you’ll be able to narrow down your selection to find the one that works for you.
&lt;br /&gt;;Word of mouth is the easiest way to make sure you find the best plastic surgeon. Try asking friends, family members, and co-workers who have had work done. If they can make recommendations of excellent surgeons then you’ll save a lot of time. You can also use digital word of mouth and check into online review sites. These allow you to quickly and easily read what former patients thought of their experience with a particular surgeon and are excellent for tracking down the best options. You need to make sure you’re choosing wisely since this is a decision that will impact your life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The final step is simply to schedule an appointment and go in for a visit. The consultation visit will usually consist of meeting the surgeon and talking with them about the procedure and the possibilities. Use this visit to figure out if you like the surgeon, if you feel as though you can trust them, and to ask any questions you may have. Your gut instincts will usually tell you when you’ve met the surgeon for you, so don’t be afraid to trust whatever it is that they may be telling you.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>