<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="166b144eba7de5e63a759a5d1e380fb6">			then you can take this as a guide. However, if this seems feasible, then start shopping for a log package and a builder. A local builder can give you some idea what building costs are running in the area. In the end, you will have to bring a completed blueprint to a builder and tell him exactly what you are looking for flooring, cabinets, roofing, etc. He will also have to consider your lot to see if it will require more or less work than normal to put in a foundation, septic system, driveway, etc. As a last reminder, if the building costs are in the $125 per square foot range, that does not mean that you can the put in a deluxe bathroom, teak floors, imported crystal light fittings, etc. Keep your feet on the ground when designing your home unless your do not have financial constraints. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One might hear that a completed log home costs will run 2 or 3 times the price of the log package. This is not an accurate way to judge the cost of your finished log home. For instance, one package may sell for $30, 000 and another of $60, 000, nevertheless less expensive package may well have fewer materials appointed. Thus you have a range of $90, 000 to 180, 000 for a completed home which are both the same size. Components that go into a log home (or any home for example) can vary greatly in price from the low end to your high end. Which end of the building spectrum that you plan to build will make a big difference in the final cost of the home. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try using a multiplier against the cost of the log package is like getting the price of an automobile by using a factor against the weight of the vehicle. The final, only reliable way to get a finished cost of your log home is have a builder(s) go over your prints after you have them exactly what you want in the house as to materials and components. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Finally always have a buffer in your budget of 5 to 10% to cover price boosts or unforeseen expenses. If you are on a truly tight budget, don't just throw caution to the wind turbine and say, lets build it as it will figure out. It might, but if you are wrong you may or the bank may get a not quite completed home. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I have worked with people who what their dream home which will likely be a log home with the best of everything that can be had. They cannot get a loan to cover such a project so they eventually went to a factory built convention home because it was less expensive. If they had gone to a more realistic floor plan with fewer bells and whistles, then they could have had a log home that will have fit their budget. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be realistic when setting goals to your hew log home. Don't design something that is completely away from your financial range. The belief that log homes are a very expensive way to build is just not true. What happens is that some people put in too many costly features that runs up the price of the home. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWFkb3dsYXJrbG9nLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Canada log homes&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="6170762548fb696322930c293a3a19ba">			You will have a few options available, such as choosing from the log kits and then get a builder to build it. There are many companies that offer such a kit. This includes plans and the materials you must build it. The logs will come pre cut which will make it that much easier for your builder to assembled. This kit will also include pre dried and grooved fire wood, windows and door frames, caulking and foam gaskets with regard to proper sealing, fasteners to connect your logs, steel rods, nuts, washers and couplers. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will also get a construction manual that make it that much easier for your builder. Of course that you can do this yourself, but don't forget you will have to undertake the plumbing, electrical, windows and all the other things that are involved with your home so maybe a builder would be best as they know exactly what to do. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can also have a custom designed home, which will automatically go with a builder carrying it out as this is much more intricate than a person with no experience in building can do. There are plenty of builders out there that would be more than willing to build the home of your dreams. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;The above question is asked by most people before any discussion ensues about log homes typically. The above question cannot be answered unless many questions are asked with the prospective home buyer. As an example, the above question is related to one asked, How much does a car cost? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A basic consideration of home cost is what part of the United States are you planning to build. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a great disparity in building costs between these various instances of the country. Costs may be higher in California than in Arkansas because of the fact that living costs may be higher in California as compared to in Arkansas. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In some states, there will be greater requirements of the builder and more approvals with various state and local agencies before a permit may be granted to build the home. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some states should not have building codes or stiff building code requirements or with regard to engineering and contractor licensing and thus costs will end up lower. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Building materials can also be higher in some states and in some areas of individual states as compared to in another location. Thus, where you plan to build is a major consideration when the cost of a log home is analyzed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other considerations are: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The type of log home you intend to build. Will it be a precut package, a custom hand-crafted log home or random length logs from a local sawmill. The price of these various components can vary greatly and thus this is the major variable in the cost of building a sign home. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you intend to ship logs in from another part of the country to help you get the home and the home plan that you like. Shipping can result in extra costs, but should not be prohibitive when one considers the total cost on the town. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you plan to have a comprehensive basement, maybe completely finished, or are you going to build on a slab or crawl space. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWFkb3dsYXJrbG9nLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;log cabins for sale in Montana&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>