<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="a1b2e450d363baf7497f7df97a672f9a">			There are many tour operators in India who are offering exciting range of tour packages for tourism in Rajasthan, the largest state of India. There are many interesting travel destinations and numerous fascinating tourist attractions in Rajasthan which attract the attention of tourists from all over the world. Thus Indian tour operators are also offering exciting tour packages for tourism in this vibrant and colorful Indian state so that tourists can enjoy best charm of this state in most enjoyable way. Tour packages for Rajasthan tourism are designed with some of most popular tourist destinations of the state. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Jaipur (the capital city of the state, fondly known as the Pink City of India), Udaipur (the City of Lakes &amp; Palaces), Jodhpur (the second largest city of the state, fondly known as the Blue City), Bikaner, Pushkar, Ajmer, Jaisalmer, etc are destinations which appeal Tour Operators in Rajasthan and India to make exciting packages. Majestic forts &amp; palaces, historical monuments, splendid havelis, prosperous museums, exotic national parks &amp; sanctuaries, heritage hotel stay, rippling sand dunes, beautiful temples, camel safari rides, jeep safari rides, etc are some things people often look in their packages offered by various tour operators in India or Rajasthan. These days, Indian tour operators are offering their packages online. So, tourists can easily reserve the package of choice online by just making a singly mouse click on computer. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you too want to explore the best charm of Rajasthan tourism, choose the right &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zd2FnYXR0b3Vycy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;Tour Operator India&lt;/a&gt; and reserve your package soon.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f2d3019145fd1ca1293ff9f00aad6156">			Are you planning to make your holiday trip in Rajasthan? Great! You have chosen a great state in India. You might need a right Rajasthan tours package so that you can enjoy your trip to the fullest and treasure a delightful experience of lifetime. A package for holiday trip in this state must include destinations that perfectly cater your needs, interest and preferences. Hence it is imperative that you ask your travel agency about what is included or what destinations are included in the package. If you are satisfied with the destinations then it is ok. If you do not satisfied or want to change destinations, then you should ask your travel planner to customize the package to your needs, preferences and budgets as well.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are some destinations you might love to include in the itinerary of your Rajasthan Tours Package. Udaipur – the City of Lakes, Jodhpur – the Blue City of India, Jaisalmer – the Golden City of India, Bikaner – Camel City, Pushkar – the Land of Lord Brahma, Ajmer Dargah Sharif, Ranthambore National Park, Sariska Tiger Reserve, Bharatpur Bird Sanctuary and Jaipur, the capital &amp; largest city of India. Famously known as the Pink City of India, Jaipur is also a destination of Golden Triangle Tour in India along with two other northern Indian cities like Delhi and Agra including Taj Mahal. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All the aforementioned destinations in Rajasthan are fascinating. They are visited by a number of domestic and international tourists each year. During tourism in Rajasthan you will have a golden opportunity to see some of the best monuments of India including forts, palaces, temples, havelis and museums. You will also have an opportunity to enjoy jeep safari at some of most popular wildlife parks &amp; reserves of India such as Ranthambore National Park and Tiger Reserve. So, choose a right Rajasthan Tours Package and explore the incredible charm of Rajasthan tourism to relish it for lifetime.For more information visit here &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.saffronsofindia.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.saffronsofindia.com&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="14b6c1b3a48a6b3fc8d32e02ec17b8d9">			There are large numbers of travel agents working in India around all the popular tourist spots of the country. They offer well planned and customize tour packages according to the demands of the travelers. Travel agents of the country offer exceptional facilities from start of journey till to the end. They provide budget to luxury tour packages according ti budgets of the travelers.  Most of the reputed tour and travel service providers of the country plan itenery, select destinations and accommodation places according to clients’ demands. These operators offer complete assistance at each and every destination during the whole journey and make vacations full of comfort and completely enjoying. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Travel agents of the country offer variety of tour packages according to clients’ interests. They offer hill town tour packages covering some most scenic hill station holiday spots of the country like Gulmarg, Shimla, Manali, etc.  Vacationers can choose tour according to vacations and budgets and they can also customize it according to needs. They provide specialized honeymoon packages, Kerala beach and backwater trips, Goa beach packages, golden triangle packages, Taj Mahal sightseeing trips, South India Temple tours, East India Temple tours, Adventures trips, Ayurvedic treatment and medical tour packages and much more on demands of travelers. Their representatives will pick and drop you from Railway Stations and Airports by private vehicles and also offer complete assistance during whole journey.  
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of the reputed &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zd2FnYXR0b3Vycy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Travel Agents in India&lt;/a&gt; have their well developed websites and portals where you can take detailed information about popular  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbmRpYXRvdXJzLnN3YWdhdHRvdXJzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt; India Tour Packages&lt;/a&gt; They also provide facility to book required package through internet in setting in your rooms from any where across the world. So, if you are looking for a rejuvenating vacation, select a right tour package according time and budget and embark on a memorizing journey with your whole family and close ones.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ac49f8c298143b39eb23452ad181c765">			India is a vast and diverse country. It has been one of the most sought after country for tourism in South Asia due to its unique, diverse geographical features couples with rich cultural features. It is a beautiful country where you can enjoy varied tourism options such as cultural heritage tourism, adventure tourism, wildlife tourism, monsoon tourism, nature tourism, eco tourism, beach tourism, hill station tourism, backwater tourism, etc. India has also emerged as one of the most sought after destinations for medical tourism in the world. There are many fascinating travel destinations, holiday places and attractions in this country which attract the travelers from all over the world. Goa, Kerala, Maharashtra, Uttar Pradesh, Himachal Pradesh, Delhi, Rajasthan, Jammu &amp; Kashmir, Uttarakhand, etc among most visited tourist destination in the country. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taj Mahal, Lotus Temple, Ajanta &amp; Ellora Caves, Kanchipuram Temple, Mahabalipuram Group of Monuments, Khajuraho Group of Monuments, Madurai Meenakshi Temple, Tirupati Temple, Mattancherry Dutch Palace, Golden Fort, Kumbhalgarh Fort and Golden Temple, etc are famous architectural wonders in India that attract the tourists from all over the world. India is also a great destination for wildlife tourism with many wildlife sanctuaries and national parks. Adventure sports can be also enjoyed here. Thus, it is but obvious that India offers a great tourism experience. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy best charm of India tourism by all-inclusive popular  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbmRpYXRvdXJzLnN3YWdhdHRvdXJzLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;India Tour Packages &lt;/a&gt;. There are many reputed travel agents, travel companies and Tour Operators in India who are offering all-inclusive packages for tourism in the country. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, reserve a right package for you soon, and get ready to meet the temptation of incredible India.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>