<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3dc834111160e84208f6ff56c90aa3a2">			The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25jY2hpbGRzdXBwb3J0cGFyZW50cy5vcmc_" target="_blank"&gt;;nc child support parent&lt;/a&gt;;  laws governing investing in children originate in that late 18th and early 19th centuries. During those times a father was not necessary to pay the young people they produced. Rather child support was voluntary in support of with his written choice. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the 1950's the united states started to see a shift in laws that were meant to address children however. During those times a federal law was enacted to oversee your payment of child help by divorced parents. Afterwards in 1975 the legislation governing Social Security were place in place and from those laws future laws governing Child Support later followed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The very best time for family laws to remain put into place was in 1984. At this point many amendments were enacted to establish improvements in child enforcement agencies. These agencies later oversee many of the payment processes that divorced parents have to disclose everyday. Further at this point it became a requirement for state agencies to account delinquent parents to credit scoring agencies. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is because of the evolution and adoption these laws that many children are taken care of everyday. Without this amount of enforcement many families would go without. Now whenever you may disagree with your divorce settlement you can understand the need with regard to these enforcement agencies to help oversee what the courts have deemed fair and just. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Citizens of the Us enjoy certain rights below the U. S. Constitution and State Laws. Non-citizens get access to some of the protections established in the law but not these. With regard to child support non-citizens have certain protections but are also held to certain principles. If your child is residing in the then the State the child resides in should get jurisdiction over child support. There are various factors that determine whether or not the courts of that State have jurisdiction but in general if the child has resided for the reason that State for at least six months some court in that State should have jurisdiction. If the child resides outside of the United states of america then the State court the location where the other parent resides should have jurisdiction over child help disputes. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are the non-citizen and are definitely the primary care giver for your children you should be entitled to financial assist with raise your child like periodic payments from the other parent under the laws of which ever State has legal system. If you cannot reach an agreement on an amount of child support with the other parent they you'll need to file a law suit in the appropriate court. Once you file suit you'll need to have notice of the suit served on the other parent. Notice laws are very particular. Everything must be achieved perfectly or any ruling issued by way of the court will be invalid if challenged. After serving the other party the court will have to have that you allege and prove that the other person is in fact the parent of the child. You may also be required to prove that the child can be a citizen of the country. The court will then wish to see the income of one or both of the parents but will establish the amount and types of payment of child help.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>