<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="aa07422cfb88a80a2d3bace9aacc3032">			Exactly what is &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.restaurantreputationmanagement.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.restaurantreputationmanagement.org/&lt;/a&gt; about? Although many of us utilize a search engine every day, we usually think of doing searches to find what we need versus thinking of how to use them to help our businesses “get found” online. You will see that there is a lot of articles and blog posts on the subject of internet marketing; and more particularly - search engine optimization for foodservice companies and restaurants. This post offers a few tips on how search engines work and provides a great basic overview for advertisers getting ready to embark on search engine optimization (SEO) campaigns.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your restaurant website is the second most essential piece of marketing assets you have got second only to your menu.  It must be considered as an evolving and organic component of your company rather than an abstract and static communications tool.  Consider it as your +1 and get it managed just like the unit-level is managed.  Somebody has to keep up with it and stay on top of it like the restaurant restrooms; only this restroom is on display and not just every customer but every prospective customer enters through the restroom first.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An internet site is one thing, an online presence is something completely different. Any organization that plans on becoming successful on the web will need a good online marketing strategy. Online, you will find the expertise that is needed to generate an approach that will allow you to attain the type of internet presence that is necessary to the success of your business. A simpler way to look at all this is to see yourself as a landlord and every item on your menu a tenant. Like with all property, some places are more precious than others. In a three panel menu the middle of the center panel is your “Boardwalk” (or prime, most valuable area) and the right panel bottom is your “Baltic Avenue” (or “menu Ghetto”). The restaurant menu engineering process is an analysis to help you determine who's paying their fair share and who has to pay more or be evicted.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For industry-specific websites there could easily be some industry-specific site features and ranking indicators. Where restaurants are involved, menus are almost always an essential piece of content which consumers are expecting to find, and therefore items which search engines take care of specially for purposes of rankings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the majority of proprietors of small businesses a great deal of thought goes into &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.restaurantreputationmanagement.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.restaurantreputationmanagement.org/&lt;/a&gt;.  While there is no denying that restaurant web design is important to an online advertising plan, it does not play the same vital role that search engine optimization (SEO) plays.  Despite this, several small business owners and marketing managers do not think about SEO at all.  This is a grave mistake that can cost customers.  All things considered, no one is going to care how excellent your website seems if nobody can locate it.  If the main prerogative of your restaurant site is to bring in new leads, you must choose your keywords intelligently and optimize your internet site properly.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d6b0e838e3d7dfc1f267b4c967b4d47f">			When females make use of a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.venicetaxi.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.venicetaxi.org/&lt;/a&gt;, they must remember not to board it without any friends accompanying her. Most cab drivers are respectable professionals but you might run into one or two odd ones, who might attempt to make sexual advancements, particularly in the event that you had a few drinks. For most tourism cities, cabs are easy to identify by their colors, markings, and models.  Don’t accept rides from unmarked cars unless you've booked for travel through a private vehicle service. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is more difficult for cab operators to cheat you if you know exactly where you are heading.  Having a tourist map and cell phone handy are great ideas.  Before you accept “shortcuts,” special stops, and detours, be sure you know where you are, where you came from, and where it is you ultimately would like to go.  If you’re supposed to be heading to the airport, but you discover  that you’re driving in the other direction, feel free to get out of the cab as soon as possible.  Nevertheless, you still might be expected to pay whatever fare is on the meter.  It is much safer to go ahead and pay the driver than it is to hassle one another over a few bucks. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do not use a taxi if the driver appears to be under the influence of alcohol; the taxi driver does not seem to know any local area; the automobile appears to be too outdated to be used as a cab or the vehicle is in a state of disrepair.  Be mindful of traffic behavior and local street culture. Be on the lookout for reckless driving like speeding, apparent drowsiness, inattention to driving, and blatant disregard for traffic control devices.  If the operator drives irresponsibly, get out at the first safe chance.  If you think you're at risk, say something to the driver.  Avoid riding with other passengers who seem to be inebriated or on medication, excessively tired, irrational, or distracted.  Journey only in taxi cabs with functioning seat belts in the back seat.  Avoid evening traveling, especially in country areas.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be aware of what's going on around you and don't permit yourself to be distracted by small talk, people selling things, good-looking strangers or anything else.  This also means you don't let people bump into you. Taxi cab stands are likely to be fairly crowded, so pick-pockets work at these stands at times. So be mindful, maintain a nice radius of personal space, and know what's going on around you and where everyone is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before getting inside the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.venicetaxi.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.venicetaxi.org/&lt;/a&gt;, the general appearance and condition of the car that will take you to your destination should be immaculate, both outside and inside. It may sound like a joke again, but it is certainly not advisable to board a taxi cab that looks like a rattletrap. Your life could be in serious danger, contrary to official certification, which can be the result of a corrupt government office.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>