<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="fe7d078bb1c0421c492e19d6559a4b27">			NON REMY&lt;br /&gt;;(Hair extensions Northampton hairdressers Northampton : NOT recommended)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Non-Remy hair is the most popular and also frequently obtainable hair. The particular tips/roots regarding these hairs are typicalyl mixed up in non-Remy hair; tangling is as a result a big problem.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two types:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Normal non-remy hair: generally the least expensive type of hair. The particular cuticles are present in different directions, and the hair is susceptible to tangling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tangle-free non-Remy hair: obtained simply by using chemicals to get rid of the particular cuticles in an acid bathtub. A laminate is placed on the hair. After a few washes the hair will be dry/frizzy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Synthetic hair&lt;br /&gt;;Synthetic hair comes in weave (weft) and also individual strands (bulk) like individual hair. Synthetic doesn’t last as long because it becomes quickly broken simply by heat/friction. Heating devices like straighteners and also curlers typically should never be applied to synthetic hair.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;REMY Individual hair&lt;br /&gt;;The hair shaft comprises of deceased, hard protein, called keratin, in three tiers. The inner level is called the particular medulla and may even not be current. The next level will be the cortex and the outer level will be the cuticle. The particular cortex makes up a lot of the hair shaft. The particular cuticle is formed simply by tightly packed scales in an overlapping construction just like roof shingles.&lt;br /&gt;;The particular cuticle makes up most of the strength of the hair, healthy cuticles are more than a protective level, because it regulates the water articles / healthy looking glow.&lt;br /&gt;;The best hair is with the particular cuticle facing the same way and also unchanged -Virgin REMY&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;REMY means that the particular cuticles face the same direction through which they will grew. REMY hair is the best quality individual hair and has 3 marks : A Chinese, AA Native indian, AAA European.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The word REMY is being abused in the marketplace, and generally accompanies highly processed manufactured hair., so if you observe this cheap on the web then it’s probably not what it must be and should only be purchased from a reliable supplier. The Northampton hair extensions are only the best quality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Native indian hair&lt;br /&gt;;Native indian hair has advantages, it is thin but strong, mostly coming from the shaved mind of religious people who shave due to their faith based views. Finest extension hair is Native indian REMY.&lt;br /&gt;;Care must be taken because the market is inundated together with fakes&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbWhzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;Hair extensions Northamptonshire&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f492ff86f6039a05b7537040079be2c7">			Hair extensions Northampton hairdressers Northampton&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Human hair&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The hair shaft is made up of dead, hard protein, called keratin, in three layers. The inner layer is called the medulla and may not be present. The next layer is the cortex and the outer layer is the cuticle. The cortex makes up the majority of the hair shaft. The cuticle is formed by tightly packed scales in an overlapping structure similar to roof shingles.&lt;br /&gt;;The cuticle makes up most of the strength of the hair, healthy cuticles are more than a protective layer, as it controls the water content / healthy looking shine.&lt;br /&gt;;The best hair is with the cuticle facing the same way and intact -Virgin REMY&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;REMY means that the cuticles face the direction in which they grew.REMY hair is the best quality human hair and has 3 grades - A chinese, AA Indian, AAA European. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The word REMY is being abused on the market, and generally accompanies processed packaged hair., so if you see this cheap on the web then its probably not what it should be and should only be purchased from a reputable supplier. Our northampton hair extensions are only the best quality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Indian hair&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Indian hair has advantages, its thin but strong, mostly coming from the shaved heads of religious people who shave due to their religious views. Highest quality extension hair is indian REMY.&lt;br /&gt;;Care must be taken as the market is flooded with fakes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bonding&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bonding is a great way to add volume and coloured streaks to the natural hair, tracks of hair are glued to the roots of your natural hair with a special glue. Tracks should never be left for more than a week or so to prevent damage to your natural hair.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fusion &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fusion glue stick or nail tip method has been proven to last the longest and also looks the most natural as the tips are moulded around the natural hair. &lt;br /&gt;;The hot fusion method is very time consuming and can take from 2 to 8 hrs to complete a full head.&lt;br /&gt;;Care must be taken to use a certified extensionist and not a junior, unless they are strictly supervised as this could result in hair/scalp damage.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Clip-in and clip-on hair extensions&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are the least permanent and are very effective without any problems such as traction alopecia associated with glue extensions.&lt;br /&gt;;The hair weft has toupee clips sewn in.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Micro Braiding&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A popular style if one wants a long look without having actual hair strands. The hair is separated into sections then,using a hair braiding weave, the hair is weaved around synthetic hair, making a braid. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbWhzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;Hair extensions Northamptonshire&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="2a073b3fd53593aa23212973a546a421">			NON REMY&lt;br /&gt;;(Hair extensions Northampton hairdressers Northampton : NOT recommended)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Non-Remy hair is the most popular and also frequently obtainable hair. The particular tips/roots regarding these hairs are typicalyl mixed up in non-Remy hair; tangling is as a result a big problem.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two types:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Normal non-remy hair: generally the least expensive type of hair. The particular cuticles are present in different directions, and the hair is susceptible to tangling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tangle-free non-Remy hair: obtained simply by using chemicals to get rid of the particular cuticles in an acid bathtub. A laminate is placed on the hair. After a few washes the hair will be dry/frizzy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Synthetic hair&lt;br /&gt;;Synthetic hair comes in weave (weft) and also individual strands (bulk) like individual hair. Synthetic doesn’t last as long because it becomes quickly broken simply by heat/friction. Heating devices like straighteners and also curlers typically should never be applied to synthetic hair.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;REMY Individual hair&lt;br /&gt;;The hair shaft comprises of deceased, hard protein, called keratin, in three tiers. The inner level is called the particular medulla and may even not be current. The next level will be the cortex and the outer level will be the cuticle. The particular cortex makes up a lot of the hair shaft. The particular cuticle is formed simply by tightly packed scales in an overlapping construction just like roof shingles.&lt;br /&gt;;The particular cuticle makes up most of the strength of the hair, healthy cuticles are more than a protective level, because it regulates the water articles / healthy looking glow.&lt;br /&gt;;The best hair is with the particular cuticle facing the same way and also unchanged -Virgin REMY&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;REMY means that the particular cuticles face the same direction through which they will grew. REMY hair is the best quality individual hair and has 3 marks : A Chinese, AA Native indian, AAA European.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The word REMY is being abused in the marketplace, and generally accompanies highly processed manufactured hair., so if you observe this cheap on the web then it’s probably not what it must be and should only be purchased from a reliable supplier. The Northampton hair extensions are only the best quality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Native indian hair&lt;br /&gt;;Native indian hair has advantages, it is thin but strong, mostly coming from the shaved mind of religious people who shave due to their faith based views. Finest extension hair is Native indian REMY.&lt;br /&gt;;Care must be taken because the market is inundated together with fakes&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbWhzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;Hair extensions Northamptonshire&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>