<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="387eeffa7eb23518971a15a686862d2d">			Ground Source Heat Pumps offer great benefits:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Simultaneously heat &amp; cool different parts of the same building.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Very quiet users do not know when the system is operating.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Can be set up in multiple zones, with each zone having an individual room control.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Greater freedoms in building design due to 50-80% less mechanical room space.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * No outside equipment to hide, eliminating vandalism and roof top units.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Pipes have 50-year life expectancy.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * All electric, which eliminates multiple utility services.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Expel boiler and chiller maintenance.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Ground heat exchanger is maintenance free and will last 40+ years.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;GSHPs offer great savings:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Very competitive on initial costs and lower lifecycle costs than most HVAC systems.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Savings of 25-50% on energy consumption.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Lower peak demand, lowering your operating costs.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Water heated with waste heat from air conditioning at no cost in the summer and at substantial savings in the winter.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Some utilities offer rebates or incentives to their customers who purchase GSHPs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;GSHPs are environmentally friendly:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Conserve natural resources by providing efficient climate control and thus lowering emissions.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Minimize ozone layer destruction by using sealed refrigeration systems, which seldom or never have to be recharged.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Use underground loops to transfer heat, with no external venting and no air pollution.
&lt;br /&gt;;    * Very energy efficient, with the earth providing over 70% of the energy required to heat and cool.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Source: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nZW9wcm9kZXNpZ24uY29tL2VuL1BhZ2UvYmVuZWZpdHMtb2YtZ3JvdW5kLXNvdXJjZS1oZWF0LXB1bXBz" target="_blank"&gt;;Ground Source Heat Pumps&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="39a78ec4b37cc3921d1713607e71a24d">			Renewable Heat Premium Payment Scheme is designed to help in funding of renewable technologies for your home Solar thermal panels, Heat pumps ( air source, ground source or water source) and Biomass boilers.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.geoprodesign.com%2Fblog%2Frenewable-heat-premium-payment"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.geoprodesign.com/blog/renewable-heat-premium-payment&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="3003919df4354c18fc1b3a9f4d7c81db">			For Ground Source Heat Pumps installation in Spain government is providing grants and incentives which is available through local government environment offices.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.geoprodesign.com%2Fen%2FPage%2Fknowledge-center-grants-incentives"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.geoprodesign.com/en/Page/knowledge-center-grants-incentives&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>