<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="43773e80758292f37bc40f5135f38888">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXZpcHdlYmRlc2lnbi5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;seo small business&lt;/a&gt;; The domain name that you choose should be easy for your customers to recall, and closely related to the type of merchandise that you offer. RSS feed updates are counted as new content by search engines. If you have difficulty finding RSS feeds that relate to your content, you may want to consider writing your own on relevant topics, so that you can add those feeds to your site. Ensure that you get the most out of your RSS feed by interesting other people in signing up for a subscription.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When fine-tuning your site's search engine optimization, use efficiently-worded meta tag descriptions that will attract the right viewers. Keep the tag under 30 words. Limit the size of this page to 100 KB or less.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Doing this will improve the ranking that search engines give to your site. In many search engines, the meta description appears right under the hyperlink for the website, so make it inviting for searchers to click onto your site. With the right content management system, it is possible to edit your meta description for each individual page.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you fraudulently make your site get a high return ranking, search engines will manually lower your site's ranking. It has even come to the point where the most popular search engines, such as Google and Yahoo, banned companies from appearing in search results entirely! Be advised and ethically hone your search engine optimization!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Social media sites are a valuable tool in search engine optimization. Some sites, like Facebook and Twitter, allow direct interaction with customers and potential customers. Other sites, like YouTube, are great ways to showcase products.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By becoming a member of the Chamber of Commerce or Better Business Bureau, you will improve your search engine rankings. Local searches can be made easier if you are apart of the BBB. Additionally, you will have an added benefit in that people are more likely to trust a website that is rated well by the Better Business Bureau.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Consider moving into the podcast world. Podcasts are either a video or an audio program, that are sometimes streamed live, containing timely and relevant information consumers would want to listen to or view. They are becoming more and more popular with consumers so make sure that you hop on the band wagon. You should use meta descriptions attached to your podcast posting to make sure that search engine spiders can index them properly for ranking.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Add a keyword-rich site map to your website. With all the main pages and links available on one page, it is not only great for search engine optimization, but also for the convenience of your visitors who may be looking for something on your site. Site maps are used by search engine bots to find and rank websites.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A site map can help you bring more traffic to your website. A site map is an effective way to interlink your entire website. People will see the links on the side of your website and it will boost the amount of traffic that you will get to your site.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You should know that search engines are constantly developing new techniques to rank websites. To maintain a high-ranking website you should keep current with advancements in the SEO industry.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vYmxvZy5jb20mcXVvdDsgcmVsPSZxdW90O25vZm9sbG93" target="_blank"&gt;;bravejournal&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>