<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="77045ee431dac96ca485e83a22751694">			 Sharing Benefit Info.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Have you considered buying a pocket organizer? Be prepared to enter the tech world, where salespersons frequently don't know the difference between models, retail stores only offer discontinued models, and manufacturer's web sites obscure the information you are seeking.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Pocket PC is built around Windows Pocket PC 2002 operating system. This is Microsoft's theid attempt to build an OS that is easy to use and does not lock up or lose data. They seem to have gotten it right this time. It comes with a special version of Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, Media Player, E-book Reader, Messenger for Chats, and Explorer for surfing the web. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the dozens of third party programs already written for this OS, you can also use Adobe Acrobat Reader, play dozens of games, and even put together presentations to be shown on a regular computer screen. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Note that there are two different Pocket PC OS's from Microsoft: the Professional Edition with all the programs listed above, and the Premium Edition, with everything in the Professional Edition plus Windows Media Player, Acrobat Reader, MSN Messenger, and Terminal Services Client. (There is also the Pocket PC Phone Edition, but it is only found on Smart Phones). Plus most of the different machine manufacturers include their own software on a separate compact disc (CD).
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of course, to use individual programs you will need the hardware to back it up. Microsoft Outlook for email, and Explorer web browser won't be much help if your Pocket PC can't connect to the Internet or to your local network.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Should You be Connected?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The newest (and most expensive) models offer two new ways to connect to the Internet or other devices, in addition to the ability to connect by wire to a regular computer or cellular phone.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first is the wireless protocol, called 811.11(a,b, or g) or Wi-Fi. This allows your Pocket PC to connect by radio waves to a device connected to a network or cable modem connection to the Internet. You can buy this device yourself, and use it in your home or office to connect many different computers and PDAs. Some enthusiastic user have put this type of device in their workplace without authorization. But a slowly growing list of communities, universities, and businesses have installed their own devices for users to connect with if they are within the 300 foot range. All of Starbucks stores will be Wi-Fi by the end of 2004.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The other device is Bluetooth, a protocol for wireless communication between different types of devices within a 30 foot radius. Some devices that will have this ability built in soon are cellular phones, printers, fax machines, computers, maybe even refrigerators!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Either or both of these connection methods may be built in to the newer Pocket PCs. Other newer and older units can have the capability added by expansion cards from the individual manufacturer.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Connecting to your own Computer
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As mentioned above, each Pocket PC machine has the capability to connect with a personal computer. The computer must have at least Windows 98, enough space on the hard drive, and enough RAM to run the synchronization program on the computer.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most models synchronize the Pocket PC and the personal computer through a cradle made for the particular model of the Pocket PC. The cradle also recharges the Pocket PC battery. Some manufacturer sell both a regular and a cheaper version of their Pocket PC-the cheaper version does not come with a cradle. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Power and Batteries
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most models come with an average size, rechargeable Lithium Ion battery, from 1,050 mAh on the Toshiba's, to 1,400 mAh on the Hewlett-Packards. Extra batteries are available, and may be larger or smaller then the average size. For example, the Toshiba High Capacity battery is 3,000 mAh, while the Dell AXIM X5 Advanced and Basic offers a 3400 mAh.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some models crash when a battery is removed to install another, so all information must be saved first to a memory card or in your PC. Others allow you to switch batteries and remember program information in RAM, while the newer models may have a small secondary battery that powers the ROM so information there is not lost when removing the main battery (Toshiba 750.755).
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Memory
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Unlike Palm Operating systems that only require 4, 8, or 16 Megabytes (M&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; of useable (Random Access Memory, RAM) memory, Pocket PCs need 16 Mb just to run the Windows Pocket PC 2002 program. Just as with desktop computers, the more RAM in a Pocket PC the better. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The amount of RAM is one of the things that determine the price of the unit. I would recommend a new Pocket PC have 64 MB. This is very important to verify, as earlier, discontinued models still being sold may only have 32 MB.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of course, that is too simple. There is another type of memory in Pocket PCs, ROM, also called Flash memory, Flash, CMOS, or NAND/NOR Memory. This memory is durable, cannot be changed easily, and holds the information for specific programs. (Not to be confused with Flash, the program from Macromedia that allows animation on web sites.)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I would recommend a Pocket PC have at least 32 MB of ROM. Some of the newest now have 48 MB. Note that there are two types of ROM: NAND and NOR.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;NOR allows programs to to be executed in place, that is, programs stored on this memory type can be ran from that memory, and do not require transferring the program to RAM before using. NAND is ROM that only stores the programs. To use a program stored in NAND ROM, it must first be copied to RAM, and then opened.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So NAND ROM is less desirable. If you have 64 Mb of RAM, at least 16-32 MB is needed to run programs, leaving less to store data or for the processor to use in calculations. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What if you use your Pocket PC for memory intensive tasks, like:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Taking a picture (with an add on camera), or 
&lt;br /&gt;;Recording a meeting with the built in recorder, or 
&lt;br /&gt;;Making a large Word document or Excel Spreadsheet, or 
&lt;br /&gt;;Copying information off of a web site. 
&lt;br /&gt;;How can you save these things for later use? You can put any of these into the RAM of the Pocket PC, but then you might lose it when you switch batteries or if they become completely discharged. You can synchronize it with you personal computer, but then would need to go back to your computer to use the information if it had been erased off of your Pocket PC.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Expanding Your Pocket PC: SD and CF Cards
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A third way to save information is through an add-on memory card that fits into one of three standard slots.. Information stored in this add-on RAM memory stays on the card until you erase it. Most models of Pocket PCs allow users to run programs directly from a memory card. You could think of a memory card as a very small floppy disc that has so much more storage space that it is used as hard drive. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The oldest type is the CompactFlash II (CF) card. They are close to the size of a PC card used in laptop computers. Type I cards are 3.3 mm thick, while the Type II card is 5.5. Just to be confusing, they are available in 3.3 and 5 volt operation, but are interchangeable. The largest memory available for this slot is the IBM Microdrive cards at 1 GB. They are also used in PDAs, printers, and digital cameras as extra memory.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sony has its own memory card for its' devices, called the memory stick, which also is available in different memory sizes. The largest size is 128 MB. As of late 2003, a new larger memory stick is being used in new camera and digital cameras from Sony.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Secure Digital (SD) cards are the newest. It is a small plastic card, about an inch square, much smaller then the CF card and about half the size of a Memory Stick. The most common use today for this type of card is the MultiMedia Memory Card (MMC). The largest MMC available for a SD slot is 256 MB.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many other add-op devices can use these slots, such as some brands of digital cameras, music players, camcorder, cellular phones, and global positioning systems. (SD slots must have SDIO support to use any other add-on device in this type of slot besides a memory card.) Because the slots are uniform, devices can be attached made by the manufacturer, or from other manufacturers and third parties. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For example, here is a link to a Global Positioning System using the CF slot. Cards or connections for Ethernet, Modems, Bluetooth, Wi-Fi, and using full size computer monitors are available for both types of slots. If your Pocket PC only has one of the slots, many manufacturers offer expansion paks to change it into the other type.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Displays
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a few different choices in the type of screen. Any screen is better if it is Backlit, meaning little lights that can be turned off and on in low light situations. Black and White screens are less expensive, and are not being offered on newer models. Color screens come in two varieties, reflective and transreflective: the second is better for clarity and long term use. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Almost all of the newer model offer the same resolution, 240 x320 and 16 bit. Most manufacturers give little information about the graphic controller (video card), or how much memory is available for the display. An exception is the Toshiba 750-755, which has 384 KB internal video memory used by an ATI graphics controller. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sound
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sound seems to be the same on any Pocket PC device. Not all manufacturers tell about the sound hardware, but those that do use the same: AC-97 Codec Chip; WM9705 Sound Chip, 16 bit stereo; multiple kHz Sample Rate up to 44.1. The sound quality of any unit is fair to poor when using the built-in speaker, but good to excellent with stereo headphones. MP3 is supported by most models.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Processors and Speed
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As of this writing, the most advanced processor found in Pocket PCs is the Intel PXA-255. Older processors can be found in current PDAs, such as ARM, MIPS and SH3 (To find the type of processor on a PDA, see our FAQ). Many of the higher priced models still offer the PXA-250, while the less expensive models still use much older processors: Cassiopeia E-200 has the much older StrongARM SA-1110, the Dell AXIM has a 300 and 400 Hz XScale Processor. With the PXA-250 and 255, processor speeds range also from 200 to 400 MHz, and the Pocket PC Software allows the user to choose the processor speed. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Computer Shopper says that many tests have shown the older 200 MHz processors to be faster than the 400 MHz PXA-250. The reason may be that the Pocket PC software was written for the ARM family of processors, but Intel brought out the PXA processors before a upgrade to the ARM family was available.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Merging Pocket PCs and Cellular Phones
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now you can merge your cell phone with a Pocket PC! These are Smart Phones, and allow wirless Web access, e-mail, and calling capabilities on the same handheld device with personal organizers, games, Word, Excel, and graphics management.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Just as you can choose between operating systems on handhelds, you can choose from Palm, Windows Pocket PC, and a new operating system created just for a Smart Phone. The Palm OS is offered on models from Handspring, Kyocera, and Samsung. Audiovox, T-Mobile, and Toshiba models offer Pocket PC. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The T-Mobile Sidekick offers a simple OS Smart Phone. It can't synchronize with Outlook or add third party software, but for $199 you get unlimited email and Web access.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Shopping for a Pocket PC
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Caution is needed before making a purchase. Most retail stores offer some discontinued models but won't tell you unless you ask. Manufacturers mark down discontinued models to clear the selves for newer models that have been improved. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For example, many retail stores with PDAs were selling the Toshiba e740 for $399 in early 2003, a markdown of $100 from the retail price. This model had the older reflective screen and the older PXA-250 processor. It was already replaced by the e750/755, with the newer transflective screen and power saving PXA-255 processor for $500 retail, and as low as $329 on the web.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Web Links to Hardware and Software
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many of these sites have a personal use section, a business use section, while others may also have a K-12 and / or a higher education section. The first link in each line is to the manufacturer, while the links of models are to reviews of that model.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cheapest new Pocket PC Handheld known as of 9/03:
&lt;br /&gt;;Dell Axum X5: Basic Model, 300 MHz processor, 32MB RAM, 32MB ROM: $199 from &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dell4me.com%2A"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.dell4me.com*&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most expensive: HP 7455, $700 Retail.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A little lesson in terminology... An article about wireless security basics and converting a office to wireless devices. Although it discusses the older 802.11b standard, it is still relevant to the newer 802.11g standard, which now replaces both the 802.11b and 802.11a standards.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Asus Zayo MyPal A600
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Audiovox Maestro 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brighthand A Handheld community web site with discussion groups and extensive information.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Casio Cassiopeia E-200 (wireless), and BE-300
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CNETAsia General Topic Pocket PC Downloads
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dell Axim X5, Basic and Advanced
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;HP (which now includes the former Compaq) 1910, 3950, 3955, 3970, 3975, 5455 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Intel Page on the most common processor found in Pocket PCs: PXA-250, and PXA-255.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Kyocera 7135 SmartPhone (Palm OS)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PDAsoftnet.com- Palm and Pocket PC Programs, both for small fee and freeware.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New Media Medicine-Medical software for PDAs
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ontario Pocket PC User		</conversation>	</conversations></author>