<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b481dfa65fbfef3b8223ec54826b4c12">			Caribbean island Haiti occured richter scale 7.0 earthquake at 4:53 p.m. on the January 12, 2010 (local time), and its Captital port-au-prince and most areas in the country had disasters in serious conditions. The Presidential Palace and other government buildings were damaged in the 12th earthquake, but President Rene Preval and his wife were safe and sound. Haiti's prime minister Jean-Max Bellerive said on the 13th that death toll in Haiti's strong earthquake could reach 100 thousand. By the end of January 19th, 2010, it is estimated that death toll could be over 200 thousand.Ways to Deck with 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Earthquake caused the collapse of the local buildings; some residents were buried under the rubble. The Subtlest &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51Z2dzYm9vdHNhbGUudWsuY29tL1VnZ19Cb290c19DbGFzc2ljX1RhbGw_" target="_blank"&gt;;ugg classic tall&lt;/a&gt;; in the Season of This Year: 10 Prominent Attachments The collapse of the building blocked the city roads. Some were buried under the rubble, and some had died. In the rubble, tens of casualties were seen. When the ground began to shake, residents ran hither and thither screaming &quot;God&quot;, houses began to collapsed, and the whole city fell into a chaos
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A short time later after the M7.0 earthquake event, there have taken place in Haiti magnitude 5.9 and 5.5 magnitude earthquake. The United Nations peacekeeping force in Haiti and headquarters were destroyed in the earthquake. After the earthquake, international community began to lend a helping hand to provide humanitarian assistance to Haiti and provide 10 million U.S. dollars’ emergency aid. The Secretary-General Ban Ki-moon said in a statement on the 13th, he was extremely concerned about the Haiti people and the staffs of the United Nations, closely paid attention the development of the situation. He decided to appoint the UN assisstant secretary-general who formerly was in charge of the safeguard army there to Haiti. He himself was going to visit Haiti as soon as possible.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;World Bank sends a disaster assessment team to Haiti. This team is mainly responsible for earthquake damage assessment, and assits in making post-earthquake reconstruction program. The World Bank also said, it prepared to mobilize a group of emergency aid to sent to Haiti emergently. The World Bank said that Haiti now has 38 million U.S. dollars interest-free loans of World Bank, which accounts for 4% of its total foreign debt. In view of the crisis this earthquake brought to Haiti, World Bank decided to eliminate the loans which the country had to pay back in the next five years in accordance with the terms of the repayment. And the Bank was also committed to cancel the remaining debt of Haiti.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The European Commission has also decided to provide 3 million euros for emergency aid to earthquake victims in Haiti, and will provide further follow-up assistance after the assessment of disaster in Haiti. In addition, WFP was also given out high-energy biscuits which was not require cook in earthquake-stricken areas in Haiti.At the same time, WFP is also preparing for the next six months, providing food rations to 200 million people. Obama said that America was prepared to help Haiti. He shew concern over the people who sufferred the disaster and said he would continually focus on this matter. Medicins sans Frontieres reported that at least two hospitals are still in good condition, and their doctors have began preparation for emergency surgery for 500 patients.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although the international community has lent a helping hand to Haiti, but still can not restore the life of those people who had died in the earthquake. And it was not the first time of such a disaster occurred in Haiti. Haiti is located at Hispaniola, the active seismic region, and has gone through several earthquakes in history. In 1751, an earthquake hit Haiti and at that time Hispanniola was under the colonial control of France.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>