<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="42e79a56e494cdaf899ce932dd5c63e5">			Last month, I had dinner with the Grade twelve student which is called Annie. We went to an Indian restaurant named Nakeke. It’s a restaurant located in Sanshan Street. I don’t know this restaurant before this dinner.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Annie told me that she didn’t even know where to go so she asked her classmate, and her classmate told her to bring me to this place. At about half past five, we met at the restaurant. I found that there are two more Grade ten students, but I didn’t recognize them. I thought this is such an embarrass thing…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When we sat down, the waitress gave us the menu at once. The menu looked quite beautiful and special, and I cannot stop taking photos with it. I really thought all the food looked delicious. I ordered Mix Vegetable Carrie and a pie. I was looking forward to these foods, but when I saw the real food I ordered, I felt really disappointed to those foods the food on the menu looked colorful, but the real food just had one color---- black… 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Mix Vegetable Carrie tasted really horrible, especially the Carrie, it had a quite strange smell, and I cannot bear this at all. Maybe the Indians have different style of cooking food skills, and we are not to be used to eat this kind of food.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;During this meal, I nearly didn’t eat anything. I don’t like this style of food, but I’m happy to have an experience like that.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_6037638_32651957.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_15597770_32651951.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_11451974_32651943.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_15885236_32651774.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_2217825_32651723.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_692976_32651751.jpg" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="87db6ce771e0dec6eeb58b283a2d4073">			I actually went to a Korean restaurant with my friend before, but someone’s told me that we cannot go to an Asians restaurant yesterday.  It means that I had to find a new western restaurant, so I went to search this on the Internet and found a western restaurant which is called Bella Napoli.  I didn’t even hear its name before I went there.  My parents went to the restaurant with me just on this Saturday.  Bella  Napoli is just at De Ji Square’s second floor, and I think it’s quite easy to find.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We went into the restaurant and found the environment there is really wonderful.  The waiter gave us the menu, and I ordered Minced Meat and Tomato Sauce Spaghetti and Bacon and Asparagus Roll.  By the way, I think the menu looks pretty.  The waitress first serving us some bread and said that the bread is free and I think they taste good. After a few minutes, our food came and I think they were great. I had this feeling maybe just for the reason that I was really hungry.  The Bacon and Asparagus Roll looked just amazing, and I think the taste of this was special, and this is my first time to taste this style of food. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The food there has fantastic looking, smelling and tasting, the only one disadvantage is the food there is a little bit expensive.  I want to tell more people about this restaurant, and if I have another chance, I want to go to this western restaurant again.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9f64626bbf79259574fd8bbd73d862c4">			During my Grade Ten life, I just joined into two clubs, which is Chary Club, and the Music Club.  Actually I signed some other clubs, but the other club had no activity at all.  Maybe there are some activities, but I cannot join them because I didn’t have free time when they had activities.
&lt;br /&gt;;The biggest thing I did during the Grade Ten school life was just the cleaning up after the Halloween party.  The party was amazing, but it really made a lot of rubbish during the party.  The student, which dressed the GCA building as a ghost house, moved almost all the desks and chairs outside, so we need to move them into each classroom after the party.
&lt;br /&gt;;There’s not enough boys doing the volunteer work after the party, so if you were there, you could find that there’s many girls there carried the desks and the chairs.  Some kind of the chairs were really heavy, such as the NFLS’s white chair which were in the outside all the time.  Our four girls can just take one table up, and I really felt tired after we put them all in the right place.
&lt;br /&gt;;Because of they dressed the GCA building as a ghost’s house, so it really looked in a mess all around.  We need to clean the floor in each class because all the class would keep in the normal order, and we cannot let them feel that there’s something different at all.
&lt;br /&gt;;The cleaning up was really making us felt tired, but we were all proud of what we had done.  We got three hours during the cleaning up. 
&lt;br /&gt;;We also did the stationary collection during the last term, I found a lot of my old stationary which looks new, but I don’t want to use them anymore.  I brought them to school, and gave them to Victoria.  It’s a little thing for me, but I think it make a lot of sense for the poor children.
&lt;br /&gt;;I wanted to join in the singing program during the Christmas, but I thought I didn’t have enough time to prepare it that time, so I just chose to give up that chance.
&lt;br /&gt;;We really had a lot of Charity Club meeting during this school, and Victoria gave us a lot of club time from the club meeting.  It helped us a lot for collecting the club time.  Charity club is a club make us pay more attention on donate things to poor people, and let them get better lives.  I really enjoy this club.
&lt;br /&gt;;I also joined in the Music club during the Grade Ten school life.  The leader is just Serella which is in our class.  We have about six club meetings during the school.  The meeting is just for us to discuss when we should play some instrument and sing some songs together.  I learned some music skills this years, and I think thay are interesting.
&lt;br /&gt;;The different clubs make us learn more skills, and have more chance to talk with others.  I really enjoy that there are so many clubs at GCA, but I hope there’s more club activity, and then we could have more fun during our three years school life.  If I have a sport club, Ithink it can help me to get closer with my personal fitness goal, an d make us keep exercising everyday.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/154115911_2993407_37354604.jpg" /&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>