<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="1d8318c410f1343d114221ce49094415">			  Employers or colleagues usually do not respect degrees from diploma mills so ensure that the online colleges you explore are accredited.   This ed. gov site is a wonderful resource for a summary of accrediting agencies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;If you have college units, are you able to transfer your units over? &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Most accredited online colleges will allow you to transfer any credit you've got earned at another college towards a good online degree with respect to the degree requirements.   To make certain, if there can be a specific online college you are interested, call a counselor to find out if the credits you could have earned can always be transferred.   This can shorten the number of time it requires you to complete your online degree.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Are you capable of contact a live person if you ever need help? &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;From sign up through completing some sort of class, there should continually be a live person you are able to contact should you'll want to.   Call the telephone numbers which might be listed to ensure that you can get to a live man or women.   This would also be an excellent time to consult more specific questions tailored in your situation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;What Technology needs to Take the Classes online? &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Most online educational institutions offer classes through combining web streaming, e-mail, and chat rooms.   Make sure you have the right programs on your desktop to make sure you can accommodate the technology necessary to take the online classes.   Also make sure you make sure the net college has 24/7 technological support.   Since online students have a tendency to study at various times throughout the day, online colleges ought to offer 24/7 tech support.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Is the web based Degree You Need Available? &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;The neat thing about online colleges is them to cross state is bordered by.   If an on-line college doesn't provde the exact degree you intend to pursue, then verify another online institution.   Chances tend to be, there will end up being another online college which offers the specific online degree you choose.    &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Online Colleges offer Convenience along with Flexibility&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Once you have answered the concerns above, you can start realizing the rewards that online colleges offer.   With all the convenience of on-line colleges, you will take classes day or maybe night or anytime involving.   You choose what fits your current schedule best.   Along with the flexibility of online degrees, if you miss a day time of studying, you possibly can make it up morning.   Just be guaranteed not too miss too many days or you'll end up getting weeks to comprise.   Start your seek out online colleges now!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Acquiring a degree online has rewards. The people who may possibly not have had the chance to receive a college degree from the more traditional school will quickly realize an internet structured college advantageous. For the people with families as well as full-time jobs, attending classes with a campus might be difficult or perhaps impossible to attain. Online learning makes it possible for the non-traditional student enable you to achieve the degree they seek. So open your computer or laptop and start your search for the school you want to be and learn more, gain more confidence about things and share the ability that's within anyone.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vbmxpbmVjb2xsZWdlc3BvdC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;sample cover letter&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>