<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="f024bb1918650e798228d92035e77c88">			Sweetheart is a neckline with a plunge in the front in the shape of the top of a heart.No one is exactly sure of the origins of the sweetheart neckline. There are those who claim the scalloped trip necklines of the Renaissance age in Italy were the first true sweetheart necklines. Others credit 18th century French designers with creating the attractive contours of the design. A third school of thought places the first sweetheart neckline as appearing in the court of Isabella in 15th century Spain. Whatever the origins, the design has made a powerful impact on ladies' formal wear for quite a long time.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182451649_6354679_49035726.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdWRyZXNzZm9yZm9ybWFsLmNvbS9zd2VldGhlYXJ0LWZvcm1hbC1kcmVzc2Vz" target="_blank"&gt;;The sweetheart formal dress&lt;/a&gt;; is not just limited to wedding apparel; many formal gowns utilize this neckline. In addition, stage costuming will often make good use of the sweetheart neckline. During the middle of the 20th century, it became possible to obtain blouses that were cut with a sweetheart neckline. While the place of this particular design comes and goes when it comes to street wear, the sweetheart neckline remains a perennial favorite in ladies formal wear. As an option that combines visual appeal with practical coverage, few other designs can create the same effect. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The sweetheart neckline is a great way to increase bust size. Not recommended for women because it will make much bust look bigger size especially if it is a strapless with sweetheart neckline. Comparing with v-neck, sweetheart formal gowns put a more temperate accentuation on females' sex sensation. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182451649_2474852_49035738.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;2012, designer of Lafemme provide a sweetheart &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdWRyZXNzZm9yZm9ybWFsLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;formal dress&lt;/a&gt;;, this exquiste gown will be sure to wow and demand the attention of everyone in the room, with its sleek silhouette and high slit on the right hand side of the skirt, to reveal those tanned and shiny legs. However just make sure your wearing a suitable high heal to elongate those pins.
&lt;br /&gt;;Obviously the most striking detail is glamourous sequined glitter band that elegantly decorates the shoulder strap and follows diagonally across the chest, helping to really set off the subtle sweetheart shaped neckline. The bodice has slight ruching effect ,which is also imitated on the back arch of the dress,  there you can see the larger key hole back shape, extending to the lower bottom of the back, giving it a very sexy , but elegant look. The back also provides a concealed zipper which will allow you to comfortably slip the dress on and off.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a20b6c93302f5424ef6c1fbcae247071">			2012 Jovani provides a Shimmering Mermaid Maxi &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdWRyZXNzZm9yZm9ybWFsLmNvbS9jb3JzZXQtZm9ybWFsLWdvd25z" target="_blank"&gt;;Corset Formal Dress&lt;/a&gt;; to you. This gorgeous formal style dress is made from a soft shiny taffeta fabric and is designed to create a sleek and sophisticated silhouette, the dress has a natural waistline and an A-line fitted skirt to really show off your feminine shape. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdWRyZXNzZm9yZm9ybWFsLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;formal dress&lt;/a&gt;; is really designed to suit all body shapes, so it doesn’t matter what shape or size you may be, we guarantee that this dress will ensure you look stunning on your special night.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182451649_13840104_49157994.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The bodice is ruched with a one-shoulder strap design, with that gorgeous eye-catching corsage, which as you can see has been encrusted with sparkling diamante beads. The shoulder strap follows round to the mid lower back., where there is a small corset detail, running down to the concealed zipper, which is going to help you slip in and out quickly and without messing up your  new hair do. The dress is made from a shiny luxurious Taffeta quality, which will help you shimmer and sparkle throughout the evening.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A corset is a type of undergarment that serves to support the bust and define the waistline. It is most often worn by women, but sometimes by men as well. Corsets may be worn to support the spine for medical reasons or to create a certain shape for aesthetic purposes. The corset was commonly worn by women in the Western world until the use of bras became more widespread in the 1920s and 1930s.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182451649_8067252_49158000.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Corsets vary widely in their design as well as their purpose. Most are made of fabric, leather, or another flexible material and enforced with hard strips called boning. In the Victorian period, boning was usually whalebone, although steel was also used. Today, many corsets use plastic boning for a more lightweight feel. A corset typically laces up in the back in order to adjust the fit, although some models lace in the front. Some back-laced models also feature buttons or hooks on the front.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While the practice of wearing a corset, particularly during the Victorian era, often gets a bad rap, it is not harmful or uncomfortable if done correctly. Some wearers did and do take the corset to an extreme in a practice known as tightlacing, in which the waist may be reduced to around 15 inches (38 cm), and some have had ribs removed in order to create a smaller waist. However, such extremes are not widespread, and corsets do not typically create health problems or inhibit the wearer's physical activity if worn properly. When wearing a traditional corset, it is important to have it custom fitted in order to avoid health risks.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9187fc8279882c7a405c4faf93016f33">			When we have to make our budgets smaller, we do not, however, want to lose the joy of purchasing. Smaller budget can even make purchase more exciting, because we will start to look for good things of lower prices than we previously expected. Get fed up with old evening dresses in the cabinet? Just buy a new one online. Do not worry — you can make it within budget. Presuming that most of us acknowledge the convenience of purchasing online, here are a few tips on how to get a satisfying new evening dress from an online dress store within a much smaller budget than before. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182451649_12878794_49181855.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first thing to do is obviously to find out the right store. Many people only go to brand name stores, but if we search for &quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdWRyZXNzZm9yZm9ybWFsLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;formal dresses&lt;/a&gt;;&quot; or &quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdWRyZXNzZm9yZm9ybWFsLmNvbS9ldmVuaW5nLWRyZXNzZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap evening dresses&lt;/a&gt;;&quot; in Google, we can find that there are tens of thousands of online stores selling all kinds of evening dresses at much lower prices than brand name stores. The tip is to choose those can be found on Twitter, Facebook and YouTube, as good stores are always willing to communicate with their customers through every possible social media network. Online support system and free customer service line are also important things, because that will be the major means customers can reach the stores. If you are not sure about anything, try first to get through the service number to make sure the service is always available when you are in need. If you have no idea on what to ask for the first call, you may just try to figure out how fast they can deliver the dresses. If the store has warehouse located in your country, 24-48 hours are good; and if not, one week should be reasonable. In fact, in order to compete with those brand name stores, these non-brand-name stores are always quick in responding and deliver every order as fast as they so that customers will trust them for more purchases.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since a good store is chosen, the next thing is to choose from the various exhibiting dress images. Images are always illusive, but prices are reliable. Why these non-brand-name stores claim that they sell the cheapest evening dresses? The answer is they offer dresses of different price ranges. The most expensive products are possibly in the &quot;over $500&quot; group, and the cheapest ones may be placed in the &quot;under $100&quot; range. As a result, customers can always find something they like very much yet within their budget. Even the “high-class” evening dresses are still much cheaper than similar ones being sold in brand name stores. Well, not every dress designer can get high pay and considerable fame and have their designs being sold in big stores at decent prices.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182451649_3394009_49181859.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Attention: do not get over-excited for the low prices and overlook details. You should never hesitate to bother the online service persons for everything you care about – from size to product material, from whether the dress matches your shoes to what kind of extra accessories you can get, and even whether discount is available for your next purchase or referring friends. It can be expected that all of your reasonable demands will be met as long as the store believes that they get a returning customer.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>