<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e6a11de3cfb7179ee34915db1c56c86b">			Fu Mingxia (Picture). 6, couple of generations of diving king &quot;dirty&quot; clothes, February 22, 2001, was a flourishing diving queen Fu Mingxia in Guangzhou to go to a business event, making use of a printed full &quot;SEX, FUCK  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; ...... &quot; and other foul language in Speech pants attend, and she herself hasn't already found himself put during this was actually a great harm to their image of typically the pants afterwards, Fu Mingxia made this apology. Similarly, Guo Jingjing Fu Mingxia equally repeat the mistakes, in February this 365 days wearing a printed Everyday terms &quot;Late nite lounge ming le if you&quot; re singular &quot;T Xu attended was attacked out of date, it is learned, all of these words mean, &quot; If you ever nightclub on to a single communication  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , &quot;but said it was incorrect, just a simple commercial it, anyway, anyway, is there to trouble. YangYiMin (Picture) 7, to talk about leadership, Yang Yimin also scolded, &quot; XXs, how ball defense? &quot;That what food was in April 2004, the Chinese Olympic to Tehran to take part in the Athens Olympic Mmorpgs qualifiers, Olympic suffered some blows in the Olympic Games being held in advance of the big door, four-year work in vain; for the failure with the team performance, Yang Yimin felt very disappointed once the game saying he could not help but curse this bad language, &quot;XX, which is how the ball defense  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; ? &quot;Chinas first mens little league coach Horton (profile picture) 8, a coach to imply it, Holden has boomed over 01 years inside A League, the Sichuan team connected with foreign aid Luna dissatisfied using a penalty kick, then deliberately hit the referee having a shoulder Sun Baojie search, which received a yellow-colored card. things would are already quiet, while also intending Shide free kick, but now Holden was on the bench begun to trouble them because of discontent for the penalty, he actually around the sidelines the referee cursed &quot;F ** NITED KINGDOM YOU&quot;, the fourth public asked him to silent down  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , he began in order to curse the fourth endorsed and later the helper referees reminder, Sun Baojie ran to the site the Horton made the verbal warning, this come up with Houghton honest down. lindane in addition to Ji Xinpeng altercation (Picture) 9, &quot;Super Dan&quot; off early a year ago under the tutelage associated with &quot;two Lee&quot; conflicts, to help you beat Ji Xinpeng happening, we have enough to enjoy the popular character of lindane side this past year in April, is being involved in preparing for the Olympics lindane not to mention &quot;assault division door  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; &quot; in your house. Jinjiang, Fujian is the countrywide badminton team training to your squad before the Thomas Cup competition through the occurrence of lindane in addition to Ji Xinpeng mouth, then Lin Dan facing witnesses actually punch his particular coach, Ji Xinpeng and additionally afterwards, quickly set off a firestorm about the network, but when Ji Xinpeng always want to remain silent, but Lin John said, &quot;I did never beat, can not carry out coach Ji Xinpeng. &quot;Wang Hao (picture) 10, Wang Hao beat intoxicated urinating anywhere security&quot; My group is the world champion, &quot;Wang Hao video game well, but the limited quantity of alcohol, no bottles over the high last year he was drinking on a party not under regulate  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="60897b0f1ada4dc7318938eeb706ab90">			Diving Championships yesterday, all held in Changshu National Diving Championship and Olympic trials the second match day, Guangxi ladies what situation to take part in the womens 1-meter springboard competing firms, the benefits are bigger than the second area, Entire world Championships and Asian Games champion ShiTingMao The terrific gain of practically 20 factors to win to demonstrate he is the present king Almighty Chinese womens springboard. He Zi said  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , no matter what their race, as very long as is essential to dedicate themselves to participate. 1-meter board as a non-Olympic assignments, but beginning from the upcoming Planet Championships will no for a longer time set, so this task does not in the nationwide championship in remarkable, Wu Min Xia not entered the competitiveness. What situation early in 2007 when the very first earth championships in Melbourne won the gold medal in 2009 Entire world Championships in Rome and Shanghai this 12 months due to the fact she participated in the 3-meter race and give up the race one-meter board, did not take part to Asian Game titles competitors at the stop of the project. Any place in the race yesterday  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , the greatest rival is the Globe Championships and Asian Game titles from Chongqing champion ShiTingMao, the consequence is a win in any place with a score of 312.90, 19.85 details driving in second ShiTingMao. Considering that no preliminary competing firms, more than 50 players consider turns on the board, in the center waiting for a long time, venue and reduced temperature, we must say what place to triumph over the troubles and perform a continuous, displaying a design of the worlds most effective gamers  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com%2Fair-jordan-1-nike-high-heels-c-37.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com/air-jordan-1-nike-high-heels-c-37.html&lt;/a&gt;; , but also proved She is at this time the most fantastic Chinese womens springboard all-rounder. He Zi claimed immediately after the video game, &quot;a sport is no overstatement, no issue how important this undertaking, I am equal to the addition of an workout to raise the probability I will as prolonged as they look in the game all out  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; .&quot; Newspaper Changshu Reuters correspondent Liu Yilin.Xinhua News Agency, Countrywide Diving Championship and Olympic Trials yesterday in Changshu Metropolis Swimming and Diving Hall continues. In the early morning the womens final one-meter board, what situation Shenzhen remarkable champion, beat Earth Championships Shanghai, Shenzhen Universiade champion ShiTingMao, won the championship with a somme of 312.ninety points. ShiTingMao main difference amongst the runner-up with 19.85 points, to 289.forty five factors, Hebei teenager Zhang Jun won the bronze medal. The recreation, Shanghai in 2011 and 2007 planet champion ShiTingMao Melbourne duel amongst world champion what situation is the most important point. Starting from the to begin with-round motion, new and previous world champion on the firmly occupy the top two. What place to perform with a extra stable, and always with a slight edge ShiTingMao. Fourth spherical, in any situation up to 3. degree of issue to total the anti-entire body fifty percent somersault tuck, the ideal operation to conquer the referee, received a game-high 69 points  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , a lead in a single fell swoop.(Reporter Han Chengdong) yesterday early morning, the Countrywide Diving Championship and 2011 Olympic trials ended in Changshu lady solitary one-meter board competing firms. Result, all out of Chongqing flowers 203B and 303B due to the motion ShiTingMao blunders, to 19.82-position reduction to any place, won the silver medal. The London Olympics in 5 countrywide championship is the second prevent in station trials, attracting almost all of the professional participate in the competing firms. Although yesterday the womens one-meter board is a non-Olympic jobs, but there is still up to 50 contestants, the levels of competition is particularly fierce. After the preliminary and semi-finals of the levels of competition, entire world champion of the undertaking in 2007 and 2011  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , what placement stands out world champion Shiyan Mao, normally occupy the best two positions, naturally became a major contender for the gold medal. The very first two jumps, the two carried out quite perfectly in the points practically go hand in hand, tough to contend. However, in the 3rd and fourth jump leap 203B 303B two movements, Shiyan Mao have been mistakes, only received 51.seventy five details and 57.sixty points, single-round ranking 11th and 10th. It affected her and what the details difference in between the place pulled a large, inevitably won the silver medal with 293.05 points. Any position with 312.90 points to win, Zhang Jun, ranked third with 289.45 factors. fifteen, ShiTingMao will play the 3-meter simple womens game  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nikehighheelscom.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nikehighheelscom.com&lt;/a&gt;; , once once more to the gold.(Reporter Li Yuanfei) yesterday, 361 degrees 2011 Nationwide Diving Championship and Olympic Trials in Changshu Stadium war. Initial day of competitors, because of to the absence of a hand harm Swimming Planet Championships in Beijing, Shanghai teenager Cao Yuan, Zhang Yan and spouse all in concert, defeat Shanghai swimming environment champion Huo Liang / Qiu wave back again harm following successful the initial championship. Earlier yesterday, the end of the mens 1-meter last, environment champion Li Shixin 1-meter board champion. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwallinside.com%2Fpost-270110.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://wallinside.com/post-270110.html&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogabond.com%2FCommentView.aspx%3FCommentID%3D517587"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.blogabond.com/CommentView.aspx?CommentID=517587&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fblog.php%3Faction%3Dshowdiaryentry%26amp%3Bdiary_id%3D2117361%26amp%3Bgo%3Deugenia620"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.getjealous.com/blog.php?action=showdiaryentry&amp;diary_id=2117361&amp;go=eugenia620&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ftheshenzhenuniversiadedivingcompeti.wetpaint.com%2Fpage%2Fthe%2BShenzhen%2BUniversiade%2Bdiving%2Bopposition%2Binto%2Bending%2Bthe%2Bwar%2B%252892%2529"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://theshenzhenuniversiadedivingcompeti.wetpaint.com/page/the+Shenzhen+Universiade+diving+opposition+into+ending+the+war+%2892%29&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.friendsreunited.co.uk%2Fblog%2Fread%2F719721656%2F90326"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.friendsreunited.co.uk/blog/read/719721656/90326&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>