<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="bbac193fb38799e418b4b749d1dbd73c">			For residents of Washington DC, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waWFndy5jb20vZGVudGFsLWltcGxhbnRzLXdhc2hpbmd0b24tZGMvZGVudGFsLWltcGxhbnRzLmFzcHg_" target="_blank"&gt;Dental Implants Washington DC&lt;/a&gt; are an incredible, high-tech remedy to a difficult dilemma. Additionally, it states that the dental implanted teeth are easy to clean and looks more natural. Hence, dental implants are getting to be more and more popular amongst the people. It is the first preferred treatment choice of the patients, who undergo a treatment of tooth replacement. Simply stating, dental implants, is the procedure through which artificial teeth are placed in the jaw. General dentist Washington DC is a certified professional who specialize in the care of teeth and gums. They educate patients about how to brush, floss and care for their teeth. Their job is to prevent and treat cavities, tooth sensitivity, loss of tooth enamel and gum disease. They also perform removal of wisdom teeth. They fill cavities, remove decay, repair broken teeth, perform some types of extractions, provide whitening and fluoride treatments and examine X-rays for problems with the roots of teeth or other signs of dental problems.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Extraction of wisdom teeth is relatively common. Family or general dentist will explains that wisdom teeth often do not fit correctly into the arch of the mouth, thereby growing in crooked or crowding other teeth. Wisdom teeth can also be host to an array of infections later in life. Recovery from wisdom teeth removal is unpleasant and not without side effects. The longer the wisdom teeth grow unattended, the more the extraction process presents a threat. The first week of recovery after wisdom tooth extraction usually determines the duration of the recovery time. Bleeding of the extraction sites should stop after the first day, yet saliva may still be slightly red or pink. Swelling of the jaw area is likely to continue for a few days, and there will likely be significant soreness and low mobility in the jaw area for the first week. It is possible that the surgeon may have used sutures to stitch up the extraction sites of the teeth. It is important not to disturb the extraction sites by eating hard foods, or it can slow the recovery time. Usually after a week patients will have recovered enough to resume normal activities. The main complication which can hamper recovery is a dry socket, which occurs when the blood clot in the healing extraction site comes out. This can cause pain and will slow the recovery process, as a new clot will have to form.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Complications from wisdom teeth removal are uncommon, however they do occasionally occur. Some possible complications are infections and unintentional damage to nearby gums and teeth. There could also be extreme pain in the dry tooth socket when the blood clot breaks away from the wound and exposes nerves and bone. Because the clot can no longer safeguard the wound, healing will be slowed. Jaw stiffness limiting your ability to open your mouth may occur. Numbness in the lower lip or tongue can result from general anesthesia. When you encounter some complications or infections it will be best to get in touch with your local &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waWFndy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Dentist Washington DC&lt;/a&gt; to treat the gums.		</conversation>		<conversation id="487254482abe0ecc301dd0af0b250c68">			The high success rate of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waWFndy5jb20vZGVudGFsLWltcGxhbnRzLXdhc2hpbmd0b24tZGMvZGVudGFsLWltcGxhbnRzLmFzcHg_" target="_blank"&gt;Dental Implants Washington DC&lt;/a&gt; is well documented in the world's scientific literature. So whether finding and correctly using dental hygiene products and tools have been a problem or not, it is very important to recognize that infection and disease have many causes. They not really only have many causes; they also take on many forms and development at accelerated or decelerated rates within different patient mouths. These differences also cause different degrees of loss. For example, an infection alone or combined with injury can mean the follow: weak teeth sustain a crack or chip while eating or during a fall and unmonitored crack or fracture can impact the jaw with carrying a root infection into the bone. These types of tooth decay, damage, or loss can occur anywhere within the mouth. Replacing broken and missing teeth can provide you with more than simply a pretty smile - it can enhance your standard of living. Whether you are missing teeth as a result of trauma, hereditary defect, from periodontal disease or decay, dental implants may supply a permanent and natural looking solution for missing teeth.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Whether you're in need of more advanced methods such as dental implants Washington DC, veneers, and bonding or you simply wish to correct a chipped tooth or create a whiter, brighter smile, there is a spot for you within Washington DC. Dentist Washington DC has a means to fix virtually every dental issue imaginable, and are specialized in quality service that's practical, affordable, and offers results you'll be proud to show off to everyone. A visit to the dentist Washington DC every six months is ideal for dental health. A typical visit to the dentist will consist of dental services such as an x-ray to assess the health of your teeth and bone, teeth care and cleaning, as well as polishing teeth using fluoride. In the event that your wisdom teeth start erupting through your gums and crowding all of your teeth together, then you might want to contemplate wisdom tooth extraction. Getting your wisdom teeth taken out could be a scary experience because it involves a lot of pain and sometimes problems. Yet, you could be prepared by understanding a bit regarding the process of exactly how to remove wisdom teeth beforehand.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You have definitely heard many horror testimonies regarding wisdom tooth removal and you may be hoping that wisdom tooth extraction can be avoided in your case. Although all mouths and dental health differ and wisdom tooth extraction is not at all times required, you should be anxious about wisdom tooth extraction and your dental health, and so talk with a qualified dental practitioner or somewhere else regarding what your alternatives are when it pertains to wisdom tooth removal. If wisdom teeth break through the surface of your gums, it's said that they are impacted wisdom teeth and it's time for a wisdom tooth removal. You should not be overly stressed about wisdom tooth removal since your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waWFndy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Dentist Washington DC&lt;/a&gt; will make certain that you do not feel any discomfort.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>