<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="6436ba824ffaed3602ef73495a16c04c">			A growing number of ingenious gift givers have discovered a special sort of present for new babies and their households.
&lt;br /&gt;;It's a contribution to assist them collect and shop the newborn stem cells in their baby's umbilical cord blood. Banked cord blood supplies a special opportunity to guard that youngster or another family members member's future health. It's 1 of the most beneficial gifts any individual can give.
&lt;br /&gt;;Doctors use the newborn stem cells in cord blood to treat over 75 critical illnesses, such as leukemia, sickle-cell anemia, and other serious blood and immune disorders. As medical study evolves, so will stem cell therapies, with new remedies expected for heart illness, diabetes, brain harm, cerebral palsy, stroke, and other age-connected conditions, offering households far more and much more uses for banked cord blood.
&lt;br /&gt;;At the moment, scientists think, stem cells equivalent to these discovered in cord blood can develop into replacement cells for damaged organs. Clinical trials lately revealed that stem cells can heal heart tissue damaged after a heart attack or repair damaged regions of the liver. Unlocking that remarkable possible could create new therapies for illnesses only treated with classic medical therapies in the past.
&lt;br /&gt;;Newborn stem cells derived from cord blood are a noncontroversial source of stem cells. They only come from a reside birth, have comparable characteristics to embryonic stem cells, and are at the moment emerging as a viable investigation alternative to embryonic cells.
&lt;br /&gt;;Newborn stem cells are effortless to obtain and right away obtainable if required. They are special simply because they do not have to match the recipient as closely as bone marrow, supply much less opportunity of becoming rejected, and can be utilised by siblings, the child's mother and other relatives, in numerous circumstances where bone marrow cells can't.
&lt;br /&gt;;There is, however, only 1 opportunity with each and every kid to gather and store cord blood-right right after birth. The procedure is quick, easy, painless, and fully secure for mother and child.
&lt;br /&gt;;Households that bank cord blood have peace of thoughts understanding that related stem cells are instantly accessible if ever required. So when you're thinking about what to get a loved one's most recent addition, you may possibly care to assume about giving a gift that will last a lifetime. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lZHVjYXRleW91cmJhYnkuY29tL2hlYWx0aHllYXRpbmcucGhw" target="_blank"&gt;;healthy eating habits&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>