<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d3142bddb1275f389bce98a5e3123ee0">			User Review Acer AS1430Z-4677 11.6-Inches Laptop computer&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapgoodlaptopssale.com%2Facer-awww.30z-4677-11-6-inch-laptop-diamond-black-PurchaseThe"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://cheapgoodlaptopssale.com/acer-awww.30z-4677-11-6-inch-laptop-diamond-black-PurchaseThe&lt;/a&gt; size is just slightly bigger than a netbook, but for any extra inch in length, I find a 1366x768 monitor and about full sized keyboard. The display is incredibly sharp and We've color balanced it with regard to photography which has made the item even nicer. I also like the reality that the movie adapter is going to drive a new 1600x1200 display about the VGA port and therefore the HDMI seems to be great on a wide panel TV. The keyboard is not quite while nice as some of the full sized laptops which have used, but I have gotten accustomed to it in addition to being very cozy for entering. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A short while ago, I important a notebook. I cannot wait anymore to upgrade. Mine was around years old. And almost by mistake I identified THIS! I searched by price because I calculated, if I didn't are pleased, at smallest it wasn't a thousand dollars. I saw this measurements, and was kind of thinking perhaps nice &amp; modest, but unless you hold this, you usually are not sure. IBM Thinkpads (just remember those!&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /&gt; was smaller, as well, but felt like bricks in your hand! Anyways, when it all arrived My spouse and i was PRETTY pleasantly surprized inside the size and also weight. Not as small as the minor netbooks (which have been close the figures on DVD flick case... a minimal bigger plus definitely bigger around) but not as large as a common laptop, both. This is about the figures on a piece of paper... a touch over a strong inch thicker. Very great. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is usually my primary Acer product so i was uncertain of what to hope. But after reading this Amazon reviews I thought I might chance getting this laptop. I experienced it for a 30 days and As i cannot assert enough about this. It is an excellent machine and more than fits my expectations. I get purchased several machines for my company, friends and family from a variety of companies thus i just intend this model lasts for your long haul when i generally retain my computers 5 years. .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Relate Products&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapgoodlaptopssale.com%2Facer-aspire-one-aod255-1203-10-1-inch-netbook-aquamarine-Deal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://cheapgoodlaptopssale.com/acer-aspire-one-aod255-1203-10-1-inch-netbook-aquamarine-Deal&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapgoodlaptopssale.com%2Flenovo-z570-10243zu-15-6-inch-laptop-grey-metal-Bargain"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://cheapgoodlaptopssale.com/lenovo-z570-10243zu-15-6-inch-laptop-grey-metal-Bargain&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapgoodlaptopssale.com%2Ftoshiba-satellite-l635-s3100-13-3-inch-led-laptop-grey-Sale"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://cheapgoodlaptopssale.com/toshiba-satellite-l635-s3100-13-3-inch-led-laptop-grey-Sale&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcheapgoodlaptopssale.com%2Fqosmio-x505-q8100x-18-4-inch-gaming-laptop-omega-black-Purchase"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://cheapgoodlaptopssale.com/qosmio-x505-q8100x-18-4-inch-gaming-laptop-omega-black-Purchase&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>