<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="343fdebaffbe237880e0fcd6eb37b6f3">			&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/michaelarms/photo/photoid=43883623" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/147191757_4792991_43883623.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Many people throw their mobile phones away after they become old and damaged. Every landfills and city dumps are filled with mobile phones that carry deadly hazardous materials like chromium, lead and nickel. Some cell phones and their accessories contain substances that are amongst the 10 most dangerous known to man including Cadmium, Rhodium, Palladium, Beryllium and Lead Solder. They are capable of causing serious damage to our environment and underground water. E-waste can be combined with computers and other electronic devices, but mobile phones are giving a strong competition among them. This is because they are not aware of the recycling of mobile phones.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Instead of keeping our mobile phones unused in drawer, we can give them for recycle and save the basic raw materials needed to manufacture them. The housing around the mobile phones can be used to make park decks; saxophones and so on... focus all your attention in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYWNlYnV0bGVyLmNvbS9yZWN5Y2xlLWNlbGwtcGhvbmVzLmNmbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;recycle cell phones&lt;/a&gt;; them in a charitable way. Many of the big electronic chain stores have bins out where you can simply drop in your unwanted mobile phone. What could be easier? You might also consider using a local free cycle group, many of which can be found online through freecycle.org. Make sure you remove your  SIM card before recycling.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d316a3ddc52de1c16bc60dddc2a47a0a">			&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/147191757_14801257_43886871.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s believed that there are around 80 million redundant mobile phones that have been left lying around homes with their batteries starting to deteriorate. There is little point leaving an old handset sitting in a draw where it will lose value and be no good to anyone. In addition if you simply throw a mobile into the bin it will go to landfill and the components it contains can do harm to the environment if not properly disposed of, so recycling is the cleanest, greenest and most financially sensible route to take. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Well you could sell your old phone to a company for up to £150 per mobile or you could choose to donate your mobile phone to a charity. Some phones hold their value particularly well and a used phone could still be worth hundreds of pounds after you have upgraded it for the latest model, so do not delay and recycle it today. Some companies will only offer vouchers for various online sites, which may be okay in certain circumstances. However, the most desirable arrangement will involve giving you &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYWNlYnV0bGVyLmNvbS9jZWxsLXBob25lcy1mb3ItY2FzaC5jZm0_" target="_blank"&gt;;cash for phones&lt;/a&gt;; without having any strings attached.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a number of payment methods available when you trade in phone handsets. The best recycling organizations will post you a cheque covering the value of your handset so that you can pay it into your bank as soon as possible and reap the benefits of recycling your old mobile phone.		</conversation>		<conversation id="449aac9a0c31983b7ec0f67e897774bc">			It was found that people use to thrash the old cell phones in their dust bins. They do not know the value of it. Ultimately they are throwing the cash only. People should really recycle cell phones and make the environment go green. If you’ve taken good care of your cell phone, you’ll see more than the one that is all scratched and scraped up. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even hosting a used cell phone fund raiser is much better than selling products that no one needs. In this case people can give you something they don’t want and they get to help the environment. Besides this, these used cell phones can go to a better use than just lying around in a drawer.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/147191757_2606454_43888180.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many websites will let you search by the brand and model to see what its ultimate worth is and turn you old models as cell phones for cash. By trading in your old cell phones you know now that you don't need to worry about your next purchase. There is a cure for this problem... 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Well, it's a sort of cure. Instead of having to break contract and upgrade before their eligibility, you have learned that it makes more sense to sell used cell phones for cash.  You can still pick any new phone and love it until its uncanny and unfortunate demise but at least now you are not devastated by the amount of cash you must cough up. Even when you sell a broken phone you can get money for old cell phones or store credit to use in the location you sold it.		</conversation>		<conversation id="293d7da22e2dffb37c8b5f27f194cb25">			Among the prompt and prominent cell phone recyclers Pace butler Corporation is at the forefront in America. Their user friendly website not only helps in the buyback process but also provides excellent information regarding used cell phones models and their recycling aspects.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pace butler simply provide a medium to buy some efficient cell phones that has brought the web versions to mobile, so that the users are never away from their essentials works even when they are not at their PCs or laptops, it changed the way people looked at mobiles. Mobile phones are now so essential for someone, that it is hard for a person to imagine life without it.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/147191757_182566_44085264.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Such Organizations involved in cell phone recycling also recycle all non-functioning batteries through a partnership with the Rechargeable Battery Recycling Corporation. When you donate your piece to them you can direct the profits from the sales to a charity of your choice. These companies provide you with a good prospect of &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wYWNlYnV0bGVyLmNvbS9zZWxsLWNlbGwtcGhvbmVzLWZvci1jYXNoLmNmbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;sell cell phones for cash&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;; and even if it can't be reused, it is still suitable to be recycled.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>