<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="2eb1e08815df19ffba496c75ddef63ef">			Horse Racing Tips - Flexibility is key during October&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No matter where you source your horse racing tips, a highly flexibly approach for long term profits  is required. There are certain weeks of the year when your betting funds should be very carefully  looked after. October is without a doubt one of those  times!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;During the summer months successfully printing profits betting on horse racing is often straight  forward. The breeding traits for flat racing are quite easy to read for the experienced horse racing fan. Like the start of the flat season in the spring,  October can be a highly volatile time of year to be betting.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I even know many shrewd punters will quite literally take a betting holiday during this month!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So why is October such a tough time of year to be laying on  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2percentracing.com%2Fhorse-racing-tips.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.2percentracing.com/horse-racing-tips.html&lt;/a&gt;; ?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The racing codes are changing. Most of the quality flat animals have been put away for the season. Others that have not are  coming back from injury or other problems that have kept them from the racecourse  during the summer. Whilst others might be deemed as horses that will be suited to racing more the following season. The fact is, unless you really know the plans for your  horse racing tips on the day you will start to struggle to pick consistent winners.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The next issue with making your punting pay during this time  of year is the unpredictability of those horses starting out in the jumps game! Again you almost  need to be more connected to stables and information about your horse racing tips for this time of the year more than any  other!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You have only two real options:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Take the month off&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Change how you bet&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are going to not bet during the month, then great decision made! The hardest thing  will be now about when you make your decision to start again. Mid November would be a good time, the form book is starting to  make sense again and the results become more predictable. Start 'trading' your horse racing tips on paper again and see how  you get on before parting with hard earned cash!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The obvious approach is to start spreading your bets. Dutch betting is a fantastic method  used by some of the best pro punters on the planet! In essence you learn to back more than one  horse in any race, and that is without question a golden rule. By learning which two or  three risk can be minimised by backing higher percentage of the book.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those very good at this approach to betting individual winnings are reduced on every potential  investment. However considering our points about this time of the betting  year this shrewd approach can help to keep your betting bank in order!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will be able to find much information online about how this works. Dutch betting will be easier for some than others, perseverence however is  advised as this method is golden! You can find Dutch betting calculators online to help with the stake calculation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be sure to consider your approach to  betting during the various times of the year. No one month is the same as the next, with tough times during October this  flexibility will serve you well. When you learn to Dutch trade quickly, you can simply watch for the money a couple of  minutes before a race and back those horses in your Dutch calculations. By doing this more of your  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2percentracing.com%2Fhorse-racing-tips.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.2percentracing.com/horse-racing-tips.html&lt;/a&gt;;  will  win, you might win less, but winning less is better than losing any!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;`		</conversation>		<conversation id="7073cf0269e7fb246f3f65984f996b83">			Due to the complications of seasonal changes in horse racing, betting control is required at some points during the racing  calendar..&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be warned! - Betting during October is dangerous&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Identifying the cause of this  is worth taking time to digest. Why is betting on horse racing such a tough game during this  time? We have a new season underway with  horses starting out on their national hunt season and with many of these  runners current race fitness is under question. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Unless you are very well attached with some of the stable hands and you can  gain inside knowledge regarding any horses race preparation, you will find it  tough and winning horse racing tips harder to find to uncover now  than ever!.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So what can be done to find more  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2percentracing.com%2Fhorse-racing-tips.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.2percentracing.com/horse-racing-tips.html&lt;/a&gt;;  that can win?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a few things that can be done in order to improve your win strike rate, you just need before anything else to  realise that the ice is thin, treading carefully is the solution. Apart however from taking this most drastic tactic, what should you be looking for  and what can you do to find more winning horse racing tips?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Reduce stakes - Betting successfully is all about confidence.  If you have experienced a semi-pro or even full time betting career you will know just how much your own confidence will have a say in the outcome of your betting. The more you begin to lose, the more your  confidence will be knocked. Seasoned punters however know that losses are only short term therefore they do not panic when a string of losers arrive. If you can't stand to watch bets lose you must stake accordingly at this time  of year. After a long and fruitful flat campaign, noboday wants to  hand back hard earned winnings! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reducing stakes can help you keep your sanity and keep you confidence. When your horse racing tips  a winning edge once more that might be  the time to revert a more aggressive staking total.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* If you combine this with stable performance then you may well gain  from this tough time of the year. I simply love to follow horses fancied from yards that are very much in form. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Look for trainers with a 24% of larger strike rate. Be sure to consider  the sample size that the winning percentage is from. Tim Vaughn is worth keeping an eye out for. His horses tend to be highly race ready and if fancied in the trading should be considered a live contender.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The key thing to remember is that nobody is infallable at this time of year. Be careful which  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.2percentracing.com%2Fhorse-racing-tips.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.2percentracing.com/horse-racing-tips.html&lt;/a&gt;;  you back. Ask yourself why am I so confident about this horse? Backing only your own horse racing tips (unless of course you pay for quality information),  is also shrewd advice as this way you only have yourself to blame when your horses underperform!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>