<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d15dcb0a142fcf772d0e6ba02b02c708">			 gunwale, let war text Hao to squat down in the ship's bow, similar to him Ye tight gunwale, dragon night fine betwixt depend the hands of ship's bow enough get of place, similar tight tight button up gunwale.The dragon son Yi in time the order be a deep absorb tone, coast the one rocket shoot.The dragon son&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;runescape power leveling&lt;/a&gt;  Yi shout at top of voice, the body take oneself not steady bilge son to turn over in river go to, dragon night fine with war the text Hao be surprised to shout 1 in the meantime, immediately drowned at river Shui-li, two people can't swimming, have to smolder with resentment, the hands be tight tight Ye wear gunwale.
&lt;br /&gt;    The plop is 1, the whole bilge all turned over to come over, immediately dingdong voice not unique, the innumerable rocket nail on the bilge.The bilge plank is thick solid, but too small, even inside return the Chong have half of air, also accept weight of can not stand three people and the of a short moment sank river's bottom.Dragon night fine with war text Hao felling arrive the feet all trampled the silt of river's bottom, one breath shut not to live, upwards a blunt, result the plop bump all of a sudden at boat deck up, the ear still spread dragon son the laughter of the Yi, two people this just detection boat deck and surface of still have half air, quickly thrilling of breath once, certainly the heart bottom is to don't already admire to the dragon son Yi.The dragon son Yi order is 1, three people be tight to button up gunwale, and the opposite shore which trample the silt of river's bottom to river walk.
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son Yi, dragon night fine with war the text Hao silently touched top opposite shore, the cover of color which lend a night keep off river's shore and considered some kind of after, dragon son Yi decision first go toward go up north, lend a way south sun, again arrive Xu3 Chang, then toss about return to Xu2 Zhou again say.The night of dragon is fine with war the text Hao had objection, hence three people go up north all the way and go by way of south sun, bought three good horse, three day noon already in the south the sun city the north several outside.All the way top walk, have never seen the person of 3 to make track for, in three publics also something of stabilize some.
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son Yi three people then again slow bottom step son, spend about seven geniuses to arrive to Xu3 Chang, at Xu3 Chang again rest two day, then preparation some dry ration food, start to rush through to Xu2 Zhou.This distance, three people all sped a step, also however the seventh time, three people arrived to Xu2 Zhou inshore.Step on the land of home town, ignore the dragon son Yi and dragon night fine that year how young and small, young and small arrive to all have no formation impression to the home town, they be all some concussion, hasten a horse to seem to be very nasty, but actually is slow many.The first half finally and again step into Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 after.
&lt;br /&gt;    Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 want to be much noisy than the other place.Dragon son Yi they just went into the city and then see a big brigade person's horse rush into a car brigade to go into the city.Although the person in the city be not as many as ever, also not a few, see a car brigade go into the city, in succession crowded arrive street to watch from the sidelines to hope, dragon son Yi they also back a watch from the sidelines to hope.The car brigade continue long several hundred, this if in one year ago, the person in Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 also can't such urge crowded arrive street side to hesitate, but this greater half in the last years be whole nine state of variety true a lot too big, connect Xu2 Zhou so of the city of fortress be also desolate many, so 100 come to of car brigade about one in the last years still a time see.
&lt;br /&gt;    Suddenly, once the dragon son Yi facial expression change, he impressively see 3 be sit upright in a Gao Tou2's Malaysia body, just with flank a half hundred the old discuss what.The dragon son Yi turn a head to see toward night of dragon fine with war text Hao, two people understand, hurriedly with dragon son the Yi abandon horse and pressed in to hide to get up in the crowd.Very long, 3 and that old just slowly nearby walk through from they, that old facial expression some dignified, but three solution the old way be not happy in again tiny take a point Pie for satirize mouth Cape.
&lt;br /&gt;    3 and your the old just walked through and spread a burst of comment a voice in the crowd.&quot;;That ising long is the food grass that that year be responsible for watching a hoard here of three solution way long, heel he together of that old again is who?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    &quot;;That's right and have never thought to so disappear for several years, he pour to change of rich and honored a lot of, that 100 inside of the car not know hoard how much gold and silver jewelry.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    &quot;;Ha ha, that isn't also likely to be his own, say that prohibit is the wedding present which send to the emperor.&quot;;&quot;;Ha ha, you are how can anyone know to the emperor to give presents of, might it not be you be the Huang close country Qi and does know the emperor marry a princess or do a big life?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    &quot;;Send to set up Huang Ling to the emperor.&quot;;A chilly voice ring out from the crowd and just returned at comment in succession of crowd a while peaceful come down, close behind again all slowly spread.The dragon son Yi see what to talk be a young childe, that childe grow to have delicate looks, the heroic spirit be hundred percent, the whole body Ru Shan lightly take in the shoulders and seem to be him some thin and feeble, however dress Shan straight on hanging throughout, again let him seem to be outstanding.
&lt;br /&gt;    That person seem to a felling to dragon son the vision of the Yi, turned a head to see one eye, have no what special of facial expression, lightly turn round toward city center to walk.The dragon son Yi foot is quick 2, walk to the front of there Human body, wearing a smile blocked his to the road.That person is wrinkly to knit the brows, chilly looking at dragon son Yi, not the openings ask words.
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi say with a smile:&quot;;BE descend a dragon four, don't know how childe is form of address?&quot;;That person see dragon son Yi come over to climb a relation, not only don't appreciate favors given, on the contrary cold humed 1, once rounded dragon son Yi to go forward.The dragon son Yi crossed an one step to hold up that person of go to road, say:&quot;;The childe is since not intentional to become friends with, I also the inconvenience demand, just is descend there is some questions in the in the mind, think a childe to help me answer 12.&quot;;That person examined dragon son Yi some kind of, see his noodles,such as knife, pare, eyebrow the Xuan be proud, the vision be calm and steady and take in the Jun Yi three cent arrogant, turn but a smile:&quot;;Your thinking me is you to answer a problem also not is can't, but have to ask me to drink first.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    See that person promise and the dragon son Yi also peeped out smiling face:&quot;;Good say, good say, don't say a wine, be please your ten wine also all right.&quot;;That person ha ha say with smile:&quot;;The words don't say so easy.I want to drink of the wine guest be not so simple.&quot;;The dragon son Yi see that person say interesting, smile to ask a way:&quot;;How does the childe drink?&quot;;That person was wearing a smile to stretch out three jade spring onion the finger of the sort.
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son the Yi be some surprised, but is to is the finger of that woman jade spring onion sort, that kind of soft and tender finger, the his teacher match god once owned, his oddness of is the meaning that that person stretch out three finger.Think on think, dragon son the Yi be wearing a smile to ask a way:&quot;;Is the childe the meaning which say a wine to want with 32 silvers?&quot;;That person smile shook to shake head, the dragon son Yi added 1:&quot;;302?&quot;;That person still kept shaking to shake head.Dragon son Yi some helpless, he return few so can not guess the time of other people's idea, end some embarrassed ask that person.
&lt;br /&gt;    That person see dragon son Yi seem to be true not understand his meaning, tiny on smile say:&quot;;I drink three request.&quot;;The dragon son Yi is tiny one Leng, complete thought of is so simple of matter, ha ha smile to ask which three request.The that person tiny Cu move beautiful eyebrows, deliberation some kind of, just slowly say:&quot;;The now body is at Xu2 Zhou Cheng2, I compromise some good.A condition, I want to drink of the wine be very valuable, also very rare, and want to drink of category also there are more than one.&quot;;Say, wearing a smile looking at dragon son Yi, the dragon son Yi see that person more say more interesting, wearing a smile promise.
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi nod and that talented person immediately after say:&quot;;As I see it, there is 1 kind in the native vintage wine of this Xu2 Zhou call Pei public wine, since come here, which ability don't taste 12, so this a kind of the Pei public that the wine choose a hundred years bar.&quot;;Dragon son the Yi be wrinkly to knit the brows:&quot;;A hundred years?This morals of the world ……&quot;;&quot;;have difficulty Yao?I have already once said that's asking me to drink isn't so easy.&quot;;&quot;;Have no, you immediately after say.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    In the dragon son Yi heart although keep dozen drum, don't know can really lane go to that kind of wine, first steady live that person again say, another he detection him collecting in the ghost door the boundary of soul's being crystal be be by the other people in nine states precious precious stone, be also say him now is rich Ta-f Weng, as long as there is the wine that that person say in this Xu2 Zhou Cheng2, he believe oneself all ability pay tips.
&lt;br /&gt;    That person immediately after say:&quot;;This two kinds of mulberry that the wine choose a hundred years fall bar.&quot;;The dragon son Yi cannotted help but whisper 1:&quot;;You how an openings is a hundred years Chen2 Niang4!&quot;;That person ask a way:&quot;;What do you say?&quot;;The dragon son Yi has to hurriedly compensate to smile and that person continue to say:&quot;;This three kinds of wine will wine in Hsinfeng in a hundred years good.Then still have a green bamboo, Tu2 Su Jiu3, seven Yin wines, float spring, medium mountain wine, the wine of Du Kang, the end come to a ground jade wine again, above say of these Chen2 Niang4 whom the wine also all want a hundred years, you may attain.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi light listenned to these all Leng, don't even make reference to where go to lane these wine.See the dragon son Yi difficult facial expression, that person ha ha a smile:&quot;;A condition is all hard to attain, don't even say two other condition, I still keep leave.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    Volume 29 establish wine to keep on record
&lt;br /&gt;    Fragrance of books house renewal time:2011-1-411:04:31 origin chapter word number:5391
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Say, that person will once round dragon son Yi to go forward.Dragon son Yi hurriedly and crustily the skin of head promised down, but again some helplessly say:&quot;;These wines that you say, I want to your lane come also not is impossible, but this Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 be newly arrived not familiar, you can hint once, want where go to lane these wine?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    That person thought once and say:&quot;;Tell you let it be.In this ten kinds of wine in addition to the mulberry fall wine with ground jade wine rare some, other wine you can at two place find out, 1 be wide rich building, another is a barn swallow building.&quot;;The dragon son Yi nod and that person immediately after say:&quot;;The mulberry fall wine, color ratio cool syrup You2 Nen4, joss-stick together sweet dew always joss-stick, original could not look for at Xu2 Zhou Cheng2, but just that brigade person's horse went into the city to also had.But ground jade wine origin in this Xu2 Zhou Cheng2, I can also tell you, it in the barn swallow building, however good come very difficulty.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi didn't expect that person to all stare at eyes to just go into the city of three solution old way that Human body up, in the heart some feel suspicious, also some difficult, but end still point nod.That person say again:&quot;;Since you promised a condition and I say two condition.I this person have a habit, like to listen to a person play piano, if your ability find out a the ability play to start out my heart soul of song of artificial I play piano to add to the fun and I say three condition.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    That person speak of play piano and reminded of wooden fish pretty woman in the dragon son Yi brain.That person see dragon son divert absolute being, wrinkly knit the brows:&quot;;You are just think what?&quot;;The dragon son Yi hurriedly say that who being wanting please to play piano to add to the fun of matter, that person be tiny a smile:&quot;;Three condition, that is me to drink and still have to have a secluded environment, this most secluded place of Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 in the barn swallow building.However want there original extremely difficulty, but you have to attain of not only need to let oneself be able to go in, but also have to let me go in.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son Yi not know have much difficult, all noded to promise.That person say with smile:&quot;;That good, if you satisfied my request, I then answer you all inquisitive problem.&quot;;One Zheng in the dragon son Yi heart, secretly feel that person some remarkable, aught and first satisfy his request again say, perhaps still have intention to surprisingly of results.That person and dragon son's Yi's engagement take the tenth as limit, let after he attained all request then arrive city south ten inside the station wait him.
&lt;br /&gt;    After that person walk, the dragon son Yi beginning was some to risk danger, especially want that mulberry to fall wine and make him feel difficult more.He can have with 3 can't observe a festival of intermediation.Dragon son Yi inwardly deliberation, should with how of reason go to close with three solution old way together of that half hundred the old, from the his hand inside get hold of mulberry to fall wine ratio from three solution old way there start to want easy get many.
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon the night be fine with war the text Hao walk to dragon son Yi nearby and ask clear what is the row after, also all some risk danger, hard put to start.End still dragon son the Yi smile to awaken two people, together go toward wide rich building but go to.Return to Xu2 Zhou, homeless, have to Inn, besides still have to arrive wide rich building go to lane wine.
&lt;br /&gt;    Not and in a short while, dragon son Yi they was wide rich building, Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 inside unlike outside that sort be desolate, this biggest wine shop inside the city be also very noisy, this among them of reason possibility still that 100 come to the car brigade of into lived Inn in.When dragon son Yi went to the counter to open room, the shopkeeper seem to be some difficult, say that is the host who in advance granted that car brigade, after they get into wide rich building no longer accept a guest go into live.
&lt;br /&gt;    The host of that car brigade such careful establish to defend, see come to that 100 come to car inside affirmation is an all valuable thing.The dragon son Yi smiled to smile and say:&quot;;Shopkeeper you please trust, we is ratio that car brigade forerunner city of, just at city inside go shopping, saw them go into the city and then follow to see noisy, this just come slow one step.&quot;;The shopkeeper see dragon son Yi three people stature and appearance extraordinary, again some noble qualities, also not brush-off,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;runescape accounts&lt;/a&gt; but again not disobey promise the host of that car brigade.At that time seem to be some embarrassed.
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son the Yi be tiny on smile, take out a goose egg size of the purple soul be crystal and say:&quot;;Shopkeeper, you once saw a world and is your seeing me just this trick of jewelry shop Tao inside the city really false?&quot;;Shopkeeper at the sight of the soul in the dragon son Yi hand crystal, be in the eye a bright, that color can still want than the agate pure, he press near to took a look, but didn't dare openings.Dragon son the Yi be straight-tempered to make that soul put the inside of there shopkeeper hand crystal direct.Shopkeeper palm a come in contact with that soul crystal, be one Zhan in the heart:&quot;;Good thing.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The shopkeeper always has no openings, but he that Chi fan of facial expression and crystal to soul don't want to put it away of action, all told dragon son Yi, that soul was crystal very precious in the shopkeeper eyes.Dragon son the Yi was past to make to sigh:&quot;;Seeing come to this thing originally have to see some just isn't a Yao very baby.&quot;;The shopkeeper is shivering a surprised, hurriedly say:&quot;;Childe this thing perhaps isn't a Tao in the city of!&quot;;The dragon son Yi set up for to embarrassedly smile to smile and ask a way:&quot;;He2 Chu's this speech?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The shopkeeper 1 each other heart know the belly clear shape and say:&quot;;Xu2 Zhou Cheng2 returned not this etc. kinds of goods.Presumptuous ask 1, this precious stone childe which lane come of.&quot;;Dragon son Yi ha ha on smile, big four Kua great oldses contain taste, again pair of that soul crystal of since big Kua especially Kua a burst of, end is also direct generosity of say pair of it regard as they at wide rich building of building money and rice money just.
&lt;br /&gt;    Although the old shopkeeper be not quite to believe the soul in the dragon son Yi hand crystal really be such as he speak of that sort, from unknown deep look for in the abyss of the nautical mile of, he know such the youth of the handwriting affirmation Be from not vulgar, affirmation is special big of household background, so when the dragon son Yi say take the soul be crystal be before the building and rice money, shock also mistake dragon son Yi in his heart not pleased, blame him slowly didn't give does he open room.
&lt;br /&gt;    The old shopkeeper was end to promise to let dragon son Yi them to live bottom, but don'ted accept a soul crystal Be building money and rice money.The dragon son Yi tiny smile way:&quot;;I now the body have no silver two, I see not equal to so, bother shopkeeper help seek an acquaintance, turned it to sell, that silver two be is building money good.&quot;;The shopkeeper want giving a phrase say 2, but drive the dragon son Yi arrestment:&quot;;The shopkeeper don't worry, if a cake of the precious stone be not enough, I this still has a few better, gathering together foot building money must isn't a problem, another this time we may want long stay for several days, return have me to want to beg to collect as treasure in the store for several years of the United States the wine be few altars.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The shopkeeper suddenly feel dragon son Yi of take to allow of no him objection in the tone of resolute, is also a doubt in the heart he is what princes and dukes nobility, also not much say, receive purple of the soul be crystal, dragon son Yi they settle down in the east Xiang of three best guest room lived.The shopkeeper look for person to take dragon son Yi to hand over to his precious stone to the examination later on, until about a hour, just see take a precious stone a full face of to the person of examination excitement of come back, say that precious stone quality goods at reasonable prices, value very valuable.
&lt;br /&gt;    The shopkeeper grow comfortable one breath, knew a precious stone of value, also indirect of knew dragon son the identity of the Yi noble, but he where know dragon son Yi only chance and opportunity strangely fits under got those souls crystal just, basically is not what nobility posterity.The shopkeeper is hesitant, don't really hand over to his precious stone the dragon son Yi to take to exchange a silver two become a hard nut to crack.Deliberation along while, he still let the person take a precious stone go toward city west to walk 1, because he think confirm once that precious stone of value, in order to more clear of understanding the dragon son identity of the Yi.
&lt;br /&gt;    Old shopkeeper heart the bosom be trembling of etc. the along while just see that take a precious stone to the city west of person some helplessly came back, shopkeeper heart bottom a surprised, hurriedly ask a circumstance of have the precious stone.That person took out 100,002 of silver ticket, say of injustice:&quot;;The precious stone is original to sell at the city west Jing and call price continuously ascension, result afterwards come a Taoist priest, he take emperor to resist to grant to make a card and use 100,002 silvers to be strong that precious stone to buy.&quot;;The shopkeeper heart bottom is some consternation, that precious stone unexpectedly value 100,002 not only, and buy to walk it of person unexpectedly be the old way which just lived into their store.
&lt;br /&gt;    The shopkeeper is positive with that person is in the dark Xiang discussion the business of that 100,002, hear an unauthorized biography that old Taoist priest satisfied laughter:&quot;;Joe big hero, this time you perhaps is scheme in vain of preparation so many thing, old way I with this precious stone excel what you send so many thing.&quot;;His flank is exactly that half hundred the old, the old is black face, just he also in the city west Tao treasure, just ratio old way night one step, that precious stone was give by the old way exaction go to, isn't a taste in the heart, came back all the way.Hear an old way again vaunt with irony keep both of laughter, he was cold to hum 1 in anger.
&lt;br /&gt;    At this time, the original jubilant old way was suddenly cold to drink 1:&quot;;BE you?&quot;;That half hundred the old the rise took a look, see be standing down to three young men from the east Xiang, they be positive with three solution old way confrontation, see an old way was in Dutch, happy slowly walk to in his heart a side sit, join a crowd for fun.There is also many guest in the store, they be also similar to start to see noisy.
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi see three solutions an old way heart in is also one Zheng, but immediately see be catch oneself to hand over to shopkeeper in the his hand purple the soul be crystal and turn an eye and see shopkeeper from flank come out in a dark Xiang, in the hand return Ye write the silver ticket send toward the bosom, it is thus clear that is intentionally to tell him the precious stone have already make moves.In the dragon son Yi heart a comfortable, he just also heard old way and that quarrel of the old which sit in one side, it is thus clear that he that soul be crystal big have can make use of of value.
&lt;br /&gt;    Work properly light one Shan in the dragon son Yi brain, wearing a smile and calm walked down from the stairs, direct from three solution the old way nearby walk through, arrive at that old before the body and stretch hand will a ratio three solution old way hand in of purple the soul crystal larger fire red of the soul was crystal to pass the old at present.In the wine shop the heart of owner in is all one earthquake, the old is also an air concussion, voice all some repress not to live of shiver:&quot;;Childe, you this is ……?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son the Yi be tiny on smile, direct say:&quot;;I have a friend to want a the altar a hundred years mulberry to fall wine and I would like to use this to exchange with you.&quot;;That old smell speech, once the facial expression change, moment from concussion become Yin cold, ask a way:&quot;;You where be that friend ?Can please out a see?&quot;;The dragon said him to still took a look to follow dragon son Yi to come down together night fine with war text Hao, the in the mind be just think what person would know oneself of secret?
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi know to begin to suspect in the old heart, calm on smile say:&quot;;I that friend be still not here, he not only know that you have mulberry to fall wine, but also know you to prepare those things is stem what use.However I miss him since immensely resourceful, know you of secret, if want to begin to deal with you, I needed not take a so valuable precious stone, either to traded with you.&quot;;The old was cold to hum 1, but is still to knit the brows to contemplate to get up.
&lt;br /&gt;    Three fire red which see to the dragon son Yi hand the soul be crystal than oneself hand in of purple the soul be crystal to still want big, in the heart some not Fen, strong endure wrath, ha ha say with smile:&quot;;Unexpectedly we were so quick to meet again, don't know you to have interest with do I do trade, war childe?&quot;;Three solution old way the information which obviously know some who fix's boundary, otherwise he also can't wishful of total pair of war text Hao regard as they three people of lord matter.
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi Hey Hey 1 sneer at:&quot;;Old Taoist priest, don't you ever think dozen again the idea of my precious stone.I see in the middle of the your hand that is also at the point of the bayonet rob to come of.&quot;;Three solution old way facial expression changed to change:&quot;;Rob?I if true rob, perhaps your body early what also don't remain!&quot;;The dragon son Yi Hey Hey a smile:&quot;;Last time didn't ability killed you, true some regrettable, however I don't mind again try once.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son Yi old way with three solutions give tit for tat, not the slightest timid, the slightest not concession, pour to let a side of in the old heart some shocked.He heel 3 but mutually handed over for several years, know 3 of the cruel hand be hot with cunning and deceitful, he have never thought a young unexpectedly let the old Taoist priest eat shriveled, in the heart unavoidably some thrilling, well timed connect to say:&quot;;Then it little Xia such straightforward, I Joe Ya living and then be to hand over a friend, a the altar a hundred years mulberry fall wine, the power was to send to the little Xia.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    Joe Ya living so on say, three solution old way's being a full face of be to hate, in the dragon son Yi heart one Zheng.He listenned to a night of dragon fine to once say, his father and eldest brother all dead Joe's house in Yue sun, he have never thought with dragon house perish Joe Ya that have ten thousand wisp thousand silkses' relation living station at oneself in front.Although concussion in heart, have no motion to lose control, on the contrary cool a smile:&quot;;Since Joe the big hero be such generosity, younger generation also be slightly form sincerity be.&quot;;Say the soul in the handle knob be crystal to hand over Joe Ya an unfamiliar inside.Joe Ya livings and doesn't pretend brush-off, without extra trouble connect past.
&lt;br /&gt;    Not and in a short while, someone delivered an a hundred years mulberry to fall wine for the dragon son Yi, the dragon son Yi let the shopkeeper take several altar a hundred years vintage wine according to the request again, one altar Pei public wine, one altar bamboo be green, mountain wine in one altar, one wine in altar Hsinfeng, one altar be seven Yin wines.By so doing bad Tu2 Su Jiu3, float spring, the wine of Du Kang with ground jade wine, but these wine according to that person say, in the barn swallow building ability find out.So the dragon son Yi be to worry very much.
&lt;br /&gt;    The dragon son Yi let the shopkeeper arrangement's person's help pack wine, is just want toward barn swallow building to rush through go to, was livinged block of great kindness by Joe Ya down:&quot;;Small brothers will this see that friend?&quot;;The dragon son Yi know him is to go together with oneself, thought of in advance with that person engagement, say that prohibit take person more.The dragon son Yi deliberation once, a little bit end nod, at this time, three solution the old way also walked to come over, the dragon son Yi also have no objection, he want to ask that person's question to at the right moment also relate to them, when the time comes come to there and then confrontation, see them how cent say.
&lt;br /&gt;    Not and in a short while, the dragon son Yi waited for someone to is barn swallow before the building.In broad daylight of, the inside of the barn swallow building be empty to concuss but desolate, only a few turtle Nu be sweep decoration, see dragon son Yi in broad daylight push cartful wine to come in, feel some surprised, one among those persons faced to come up:&quot;;Now still cease operation in, don't know everyone a guest an officer why is the matter since then?&quot;;Dragon son the Yi be tiny on smile, say:&quot;;We to seek your boss.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The words of dragon son Yi just said that finish, a clear and crisp voice ring out:&quot;;Everyone far way since then, it living Hui the barn swallow building Peng Bi, Nu house greet arrive late, return hope to forgive.&quot;;Say see whole body wear skirt of the young age woman walked to come in from the side door, that woman noodles was like Wen Yu4, thin sweep beautiful eyebrows, eyes be very clear, body quantity seedling Joe, whole body top and bottom deeply wear a pure spirit, leave with the ground of this smoke flower to the person of impression formation mightiness anti- bad, make the person great the feeling be shocked.
&lt;br /&gt;    Dragon son the Yi be tiny a smile:&quot;;The miss gorgeous hat is nine states, be let we again etc. top a few hour, that is also worthy of of, return say what forgive to disappear to forgive of words!&quot;;Dragon son Yi the young man say this kind of words also just, can Joe Ya of one side living with three solution old way face top some hang not to live.That woman is sweet a smile:&quot;; Childe not only living of Jun friendship romantic, even talk also all so moving, true call the Nu house move.&quot;;The person who see the side of the body all without exception knit the brows, dragon son Yi ha ha a smile:&quot;;I arrive at expensive treasure ground this time, is have a matter mutually is beg in miss!&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    The vision of that woman swept 1 time on the public face, livinged to stop over a short moment with the waist of 3 at Joe Ya, again took a look dragon son Yi, ha ha say with smile:&quot;;The childe have what order, though clear speech, as long as I made out in the middle of the barn swallow building lord of, certain attain for the childe.&quot;;The dragon son Yi say with smile:&quot;;Have the miss this sentence, I trusted.I come to barn swallow building this time, a then think several altar of article here of the United States wine, two then want seek two playing skill the superb miss as our pure ear, three then want lend expensive treasure ground of a very secluded ground, meeting a short while be a friend.Don't know convenience inconvenient?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;    That woman has already seen dragon son Yi before the body of six altar old wine, the wine which know him to want also far from any article, although this ising difficult don't pour barn swallow building.But dragon son two condition of the behind of the Yi not so easy.The dragon son Yi wait for someone although the identity seem to be some extraordinary, the barn swallow building also have the rules of barn swallow building.
&lt;br /&gt;    This barn swallow building cent the inside Chinese and Foreign 3 F.Most outside the layer be also the biggest 1 F and quarrel most of 1 F, this is to provide public seek joys to have a good time, in the center the second floor be opposite a little bit smaller, but much secluded, and the woman of this inside be all each to hold technical skill, busk not to sell the body;And this in house structure and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;runescape gold&lt;/a&gt; form design of very good, in keeping with other people discuss secret, so is also many reach officer's magnate of top up it choose.As for most inside 1 F be just a legend, first, this five people understand in where river the lake and secondly want to get into most inside the 1 F be not with money, with the position, with the judge of influence of barn swallow building back with happy, but this influence of existence is also what river lake middleman can not know.
&lt;br /&gt;    See there woman some difficult of barn swallow building of rules spoke to come out, dragon son Yi tiny one Leng:See to that person be a barn swallow building with what I engagement most an inside a layer!
&lt;br /&gt;    Volume 2 nine thorough fan bureau		</conversation>	</conversations></author>