<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b0e3f1040f8a88290b1209d214e29b55">			Rob Stringer is a retired Military Vet and a dedicated family man, with four children living all  over the United States.  Rob started out on a busy ranch in a big family and&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb2JzdHJpbmdlci5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;Rob Stringer &lt;/a&gt;really enjoys the state of Arizona and its history. Part of the history of the state  includes many different celebrities and outlaws who are known to come from Arizona or have spent  a significant amount of time in the state throughout their lives. Rob gives a little rundown of  some of his favorite famous people that are known for their ties to the state of Arizona.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb2JzdHJpbmdlci5uZXQv" target="_blank"&gt;Rob Stringer &lt;/a&gt;and his wife, Sarah, have always been fans of Ted Danson. From the time Ted arrived  on Cheers as the womanizing bar owner, Sam, Rob and his wife were drawn in. Sarah had always  thought that Ted Danson was handsome. Rob, however, was taken in by the way that Ted adapted to  his roles. One of his favorite movies with Ted is Three Men and a Baby. Then, when Ted Danson  came out with another series later in his life – Becker – Rob Stringer found himself in stitches  watching the show.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most men like silly comedy and Rob Stringer is no exception. David Spade is one of Rob’s favorite  comedians to watch in movies. Some of his favorite movies to watch were when David Spade  co-starred with Chris Farley. Unfortunately, Rob does not find David Spade’s movies as hilarious  without Chris Farley, but he remains a fan nonetheless, watching old movies with the two actors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While Sarah was alive, she really got into watching television, especially while she was going  through chemotherapy. Two of her favorite shows became Grey’s Anatomy and Private Practice, the  spinoff with Kate Walsh as Addison. Rob Stringer is drawn to Kate Walsh’s fiery persona and it  certainly doesn’t help that she resembles his late wife at a younger age.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;With such patriotism abound, it does not seem that Rob Stringer would be the type to like  outlaws, but it is true. He has read everything he can get his hands on in regards to Bonnie and  Clyde from Texas. The same is also true for Arizona’s famous outlaw – the Apache Kid. The Apache  Kid began life as an orphan on the str		</conversation>		<conversation id="567ce273d11ec4d8d94f6fc92b3d15cc">			&lt;strong&gt;The Art Institute of Chicago&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaWlnby5jb20vcnNzL3VzZXIvUm9ic3RyaW5nZXIxL1N0cmluZ2VyIA__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/177268423_5058147_47215596.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the name suggests, the Artwork Institute of Chicago is really a historical landmark which holds 1 of the world's best art collections. When you plan to spend an entire day of your take a look at this Artwork Institute, you can get yourself acquainted with various exhibits and collections from Asia, Europe, and the Middle East. Do remember to see the exhibits such as the African &amp; Amerindian collection, the Ernest R. Graham Study Center for Architectural Drawings, the European Painting collection, the European Decorative Arts collection, the holdings of the Department of Textiles and the Department of Modern and Contemporary Art. For dining facilities, you can go for the Court Cafe and the Garden Restaurant.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Besides these places, there are other fun areas to go to in Chicago. So in case you have 'loads' of time in your hand, then you need to go for the famous Sears Tower Sky deck, Incredible Chicago Funhouse Maze, Buckingham Fountain Northwestern Station, Ogilvie Transportation Center, Six Flags Fantastic America, Chicago Air &amp; Water Show, Chicago Blues Festival, Chicago Cultural Center, ESPN Zone, Frank Lloyd Wright Property and Studio and the Union Station. Read more on Chicago tourism.
&lt;br /&gt;So these were among the 'many' very best places to go to in Chicago. Be assured that the money that you could possibly spend on your visit to these places in Chicago, would be worth all the enjoyment and pleasure you can get from the trip. So, give yourself a small break and go have a blast in the 'Windy City' of America!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb2JzdHJpbmdlci5vcmcvcm9iLXN0cmluZ2VyLWZhbW91cw__" target="_blank"&gt;Rob stringer&lt;/a&gt; hasn’t stopped traveling.  He visits sites that have a rich historical background, and learns something new about his great country every single day.  While visiting friends and family all over the States, he’s had a chance to increase his ever-growing knowledge of history.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>