<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="7">		<conversation id="b74236eb904bcbeb394264c715caa220">			I am a down to earth dude!!!!!!!i am not a hater and i respect each and everyone and what they do.i wont look down on anyone.Thatz me		</conversation>		<conversation id="5f99d4fb143583f16a75be38d0276a0c">			A young couple, just married, were in their honeymoon suite on their wedding night. As they were undressing for bed, the husband -- who was a big burly man -- tossed his trousers to his bride and said, &quot;;Here, put these on.&quot;; She put them on and the waist was twice the size of her body. &quot;;I cant wear your trousers,&quot;; she said. &quot;;That's right, said the husband, &quot;;and don't you ever forget it. I'm the man who wears the pants in this family.&quot;; With that she flipped him her panties and said, &quot;;Try these on.&quot;; He tried them on and found he could only get them on as far as his kneecaps. &quot;;Hell,&quot;; he said. I cant get into your panties!&quot;; She replied, &quot;;That's right, and that's the way its going to stay until your attitude changes.''		</conversation>		<conversation id="e907138df973c35bbf09c335bb77d1a3">			There was a little boy whose mother was about to have a baby. One day the little boy walked in and saw his mother naked, he asked his mother what was the hair in between her legs? She responded, &quot;;It's my washcloth&quot;;. Weeks later after the mother had the baby, the young boy walked in on his mother again, but while she was in the hospital the doctor shaved her pubic hair, and the boy asked his mother: &quot;;What happened to your washcloth?&quot;; The mother responded, &quot;;I lost it&quot;;. The little boy trying to be helpful set out to find his mother's washcloth. A few days later the little boy went running to his mother yelling and screaming, I found your washcloth, the mother thinking that the child was just playing went along with the boy and asked, &quot;;Where did you find it?&quot;; The boy answered, &quot;;The maid has it, i saw her washing daddy's face with it.&quot;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e51185e641f774aae3d68be1aff8c2e8">			A guy stuck his head into a barbershop and asked,
&lt;br /&gt;'How long before I can get a haircut? The barber looked around the shop full of
&lt;br /&gt;customers and said, 'About 2 hours.'The guy left. A few days later, the same guy stuck his head in the
&lt;br /&gt;door and asked, 'How long before I can get a
&lt;br /&gt;haircut?' The barber looked around at the shop and said,
&lt;br /&gt;'About 3 hours.'The guy left. A week later, the same guy stuck his head in the
&lt;br /&gt;shop and asked, 'How long before I can get a
&lt;br /&gt;haircut? The barber looked around the shop and said,
&lt;br /&gt;'About an hour and a half .The guy left. The barber turned to his friend and said, 'Hey, Bob,
&lt;br /&gt;do me a favor , follow him and see where he goes.
&lt;br /&gt;He keeps asking how long he has to wait for a
&lt;br /&gt;haircut, but he never comes back.' A little while later, Bob returned to the shop,
&lt;br /&gt;laughing hysterically. The barber asked, 'So, where does he go when he
&lt;br /&gt;leaves? 'Bob looked up, wiped the tears from his eyes and
&lt;br /&gt;said,'Your house!'		</conversation>		<conversation id="38e73b684207d6a0d621cbb5a7cf88fe">			A family is at the dinner table.
&lt;br /&gt;The son asks his father, &quot;;Dad, how
&lt;br /&gt;many kinds of boobs are there?&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;The father, surprised, answers,
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Well, son, there are three kinds of
&lt;br /&gt;Boobs. In her 20's, a woman's are
&lt;br /&gt;like melons, round and firm. In her
&lt;br /&gt;30's to 40's, they are like pears,
&lt;br /&gt;still nice but hanging a bit. After
&lt;br /&gt;50, they are like onions&quot;;.
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Onions?&quot;; d son asked.
&lt;br /&gt;''Yes, you see them and they make
&lt;br /&gt;you cry.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;This infuriated his wife and
&lt;br /&gt;daughter so the daughter said,
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Mum, how many kinds of
&lt;br /&gt;'willies' are there?&quot;;.
&lt;br /&gt;The mother, smiles and answers,
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Well dear, a man goes through
&lt;br /&gt;three phases. In his 20's, his willy
&lt;br /&gt;is like an oak tree, mighty and
&lt;br /&gt;hard. In his 30's and 40's, it is like
&lt;br /&gt;a birch, flexible but reliable. After
&lt;br /&gt;his 50's, its like a Christmas Tree&quot;;.
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;A Christmas tree?&quot;; d daughter
&lt;br /&gt;asked
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Yes - the root's dead and the balls
&lt;br /&gt;are just for decoration&quot;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="75c9f6b509a4f9ccef8214b79c8baac1">			Little John greeted his mama at the door after she had bin out for a week.John sed,&quot;;mum, guess wat?. Yesterday,I was playing in d closet at ur bedroom when Daddy came into d room wid the lady from next door and they got into bed,and then daddy got on top of her and...&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stop!!,the moda yelled and sed,duh say anoda word!!,wait till ur father gets home.I want u to tell him exactly wat u've jux told me&quot;;..
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The father came home, and the wife told im dat she's leaving him.&quot;;But why?&quot;;.Croaked the husband....
&lt;br /&gt;Go ahead John,tell daddy jux wat u told me...
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Well&quot;;,sed little John,&quot;;I was playing in ur closet and daddy came upstairs wid the lady next door and they got undressed and they got into bed and Daddy got on top of her and dey did exaCtly wat mommy and Uncle Ato did wen Daddy was away last summer		</conversation>		<conversation id="d45abdba00044e7ccc1f4dbde73ebd1">			3 men were drunk,they stopped a taxi. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The taxi driver figured that they were drunk,he just switched on the engine &amp; switched it off &amp; told them,we have arrived. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 1st guy gave him money, 
&lt;br /&gt;2nd guy said thanks but the 
&lt;br /&gt;3rd guy slapped him. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The taxi driver was stunned because he was hoping that none of them must have realized that the car didn't move an inch. 
&lt;br /&gt;so he asked,what was that for? 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Guy Replied, control your speed next time Dude,you almost killed us...		</conversation>	</conversations></author>