<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="351ed2f5a656c1c9d99501acd8ba4f25">			On the many other hand, saliva is only produced when the horse is eating. Under natural grazing conditions the horse spends most of the time grazing, which ensures a continuing supply of food material and saliva to dilute the acidic stomach ingredients.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is the reason for ulcers? Although the lower the main stomach can cope with being bathed continuously in the acidic stomach contents, the upper portion can not. Anything that leaves the upper portion of the stomach in touch with the acidic fluid enhances the risk of ulcers. Sorry to say, that includes many common management practices. Stabling, concentrate feeding, intensive exercise, and transport have all been shown to increase the chance of ulcers. Essentially, what happens is that the belly starts to digest again.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The mildest cases may just have a few small ulcers. But severely affected horses can have extensive areas of heavy ulceration.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even though they will often have severe ulcers, mounts rarely show dramatic indications of illness or pain. The often subtle indications that ulcers produce allow many to travel undetected. Non-specific signs including loss of appetite, negative performance, and recurrent colic, are commonly seen in horses with gastric ulcers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gastric ulcers in most cases respond to treatment with modern medication that reduces the acid production. Many owners notice an improvement within a couple of days of starting treatment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But there is a risk that the ulcers will return once the treatment stops. So it is also important to address the underlying causes. By wanting to provide a more natural lifestyle for any horse, it may be possible to balance his needs along with the requirements for training. For instance, feed the best quality roughage so that high carbohydrate feeds may be kept to a minimum. Give several small meals every day. Allow some turnout period daily.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are concerned that your horse might have gastric ulcers speak to your veterinarian.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Equine gastric ulcer syndrome (EGUS) is a variety of horse colic ailment, commonly known as &quot;equine gastric ulcer&quot;. Scientifically, it is defined as being the erosion of the horse's abdominal lining due to excessive and prolonged exposure to acid that is manufactured by the stomach.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The horse's stomach differs from humans as their own stomachs produce acid regularly. So when a horse skips a meal or two, the plaque created by sugar produced will damage this stomach lining causing serious horse colic pain.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gastric ulcer may range between a mild inflamed stomach lining to your more severe and widespread wearing down in the stomach lining leading to help bleeding. Generally, foals tend to have a thinner cell lining and are more prone to gastric ulceration as compared to horse adults.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; 2 Different types of Gastric Ulcer: &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ol&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; Squamous Ulceration &lt;/strong&gt;; - this happens inside dorsal region of the stomach where it is covered by squamous epithelium. Ulcers happen here as a result of acid secretion. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; Glandular Ulceration &lt;/strong&gt;; - this happens in the ventral region where it is filled with glandular epithelium which serves as being the protective layer in the stomach wall. Ulceration happens in this region when the mucus layer is torn down as a result of acid. Be attentive in the dosage level and see the label carefully on horse pharmaceutical packages, as excessive dosage involving equine medications will result in more severe case of horse colic conditions.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcXVpc3VyZW5vdy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;ulcers in horses&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Byb2VhcnRoYW5pbWFsaGVhbHRoLmNvbS9lcXVpLXN1cmUv" target="_blank"&gt;;treatment of colic in horses&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5680d4b6485d8a093e62def1f4c56089">			It has also been used to treat skin color ulcers, phlebitis, leg cramping, cough, and diarrhea.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Administration&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For symptomatic treatment associated with chronic venous insufficiency: Dosage is 250 mg orally every day, up to 3 x a day. Some sources recommend using 450 to 750 mg daily to decrease symptoms, and decreasing dose to 175 to 350 mg on a daily basis&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tincture formulation: Dosage is 1 to 4 ml by mouth three times a day.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hazards&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Side effects involving horse chestnut include GI irritation (especially with immediate release products) hazardous nephropathy, calf cramps, itching, and skin cancer (topical oil skin cleansers). Use with anticoagulants may increase anticoagulant effects with increased bleeding and bruising. Increased hypoglycemic effects may well occur when horse chestnut is utilized with antidiabetics and insulin. Aescin binds to plasma proteins and will displace drugs that are proteinbound.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When used using other herbs with anticoagulant or even antiplatelet potential, such as feverfew, garlic, ginkgo, together with ginseng, horse chestnut may increase anticoagulant effects, bleeding, and bruising. Other herbs with hypoglycemic potential, which include aconite, dong quai, gotu kola, gymnema, sylvestie, and fenugreek, may cause increased hypoglycemic effects when joined with horse chestnut.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The FDA considers whole horse chestnut unsafe. Those with infectious and inflammatory Gl conditions shouldn't use horse chestnut as a result of potential for GI tract irritation. Patients with severe renal or hepatic impairment, diabetic patients, and patients taking anticoagulants ought to avoid the herb, as should pregnant or breast-feeding a lot of women.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Safety Risk Horse chestnut may cause hepatotoxicity and anaphylaxis. High doses and nonstandardized forms can be lethal.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Clinical considerations&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This nuts, seeds, twigs, plants sprouting up, and leaves of mount chestnut are poisonous. Standardized formulations remove the vast majority of toxins and standardize the quantity of aescin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Signs and symptoms of toxicity include decrease of coordination, salivation, hemolysis, pain, dilated pupils, muscle twitching, seizures, throwing up, diarrhea, depression, paralysis, respiratory and cardiac failure, together with death.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Monitor patient with regard to signs of toxicity together with discontinue horse chestnut right away if any occur.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Monitor blood sugar level in patients using antidiabetics for hypoglycemia.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Advise patient to use only a standardized get containing 16% to 21 % aescin, at recommended doses, and to bring to close use if signs associated with toxic reaction occur.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tell patient that this is only symptomatic procedure of chronic venous insufficiency not a cure.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Advise patient not to confuse horse chestnut with sweet chestnut, which is utilized as a food.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Advise patient to maintain the herb away with children. Consumption of amounts of leaves, twigs, and seeds equaling 1 % of an child's weight may end up lethal.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tell patient to advise pharmacist of any herbal or nutritional supplement that he's taking when getting a new prescription.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Advise patient to consult his doctor before using an herbal preparation web-site needs to be treatment with proven efficacy may very well be available.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Research summary&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;FDA considers whole horse chestnut to be an unsafe herb and warns that each parts of the plants with this genus are potentially harmful. However, German Commission E considers it safe. European researchers have evaluated it's effectiveness and safety. However, recent research suggests that certain components of that horse chestnut may increase venous compliance and lower edema in patients with chronic venous insufficiency.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25lc3RvcnNhbnRpYTQxMC5qaWdzeS5jb20vZW50cmllcy9nZW5lcmFsL2hvcnNlLWNvbGljLWZhY3RzLXdoYXQtaXMtZXF1aW5lLWdhc3RyaWMtdWxjZXItc3luZHJvbWU_" target="_blank"&gt;;Vitamins For Ulcer&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cueGluZy5jb20vZXZlbnRzL3NpZ2h0LW1pbmQtaGlkZGVuLXByb2JsZW1zLWhvcnNlLXN0b21hY2gtMTAzNTU3Mw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Horse Colic Facts: What Is Equine Gastric Ulcer Syndrome?&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2V2ZW50cy5lbnhvZWlkdW1hbWFla3Jrcy5wb2RvbWF0aWMuY29tL2VudHJ5LzIwMTItMDQtMDNUMDlfMTRfMDgtMDdfMDA_" target="_blank"&gt;;Vitamins For Ulcer&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS93bWFuZHJld3MzNy9wb3N0cy8xMDI1NDkyL1ZpdGFtaW5zK0ZvcitVbGNlcg__" target="_blank"&gt;;Horse Colic Facts: What Is Equine Gastric Ulcer Syndrome?&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/ZugayriimdaCox/blog/blogid=8080096" target="_blank"&gt;;Out Of Sight, Out Of Mind? The Hidden Problems In Your Horse's Stomach&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rvbm5pY2hvbHMxMy5icmF2ZWpvdXJuYWwuY29tL2VudHJ5LzkxNzMz" target="_blank"&gt;;Horse Colic Facts: What Is Equine Gastric Ulcer Syndrome?&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS93bWFuZHJld3MzNy9ibG9nLzIwMTIvMDQvMDQvaG9yc2UtY29saWMtZmFjdHMtd2hhdC1pcy1lcXVpbmUtZ2FzdHJpYy11bGNlci1zeW5kcm9tZT9maXJzdHBvc3Q9WQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Treat ulcers in your horse&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>