<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="70f28259d8c521723a9541dfb0923a7c">			 they sat to talk away several, is immediately after silent.The elder sister purple Juan they go out a burst of, haven't come back till now, and also have no the sound of physical fight.Just at the time of feel suspicious, the text be loose blunt come over, through the sword body of the silver feather white light&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS10emhhYXItZmlnaHQtY2F2ZS1jLTI5XzMyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;fire cape&lt;/a&gt;;  ability see a text loose face top the spring breeze kiss noodles, such as take the happy facial expression of peach blossom.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Export, two elder brother, three elder brother.&quot;The text is loose unthinking remark arrived an ear behind.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister purple Juan come back, that damp and black and smooth hair cover with at after death, &quot;yes&quot;, she two blunt younger brother nod.
&lt;br /&gt;;They put away thing to walk, the text was loose to rob fore head, he arrive at exit a cake of stretch out of rock up, there just enough a person stop for a rest.He station over there get down hope go to, fly move of the snowflake fall at it elegance of hair, he exhale of white spirit moment namely is blown about in the air.
&lt;br /&gt;;His habitual ground touch a waist up, there a very wet calico sack outside, there is no his thing for expect, the forked rope hang up.
&lt;br /&gt;;Elder sister they looking at a text loose, suspicious think on the face he what's wrong strength of place.&quot;How?&quot;The silver dragon ask.
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose wrinkly eyebrows, voice prolong ground say, &quot;the ? rope ? of my ? hang up&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Cloud bridge and the silver dragon together together repeated way, &quot;does the rope hang up?&quot;Suddenly realize empress smiled, think is what big not of matter, have never thought is his one of the extremely valued, the forked rope hang up.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;I forget it at under the fist precipice of flat ground top.&quot;Find out answer, he sighed in sorrow 1.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Return to take back.&quot;The elder sister see him sad and know perfectly well impossible or intentionally say.
&lt;br /&gt;;Let out ray of light in the text loose eye, &quot;return?&quot;Seem true want to return similar, immediately after shake, ego negation say, &quot;return ……&quot; he took a look the cliff of foot, return have fluffy of white snow, he say, &quot; still calculated.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Purple Juan ha ha smile, the Wu shut up not a break into laughter voice.
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose on jumping to jump to go out, Gao Da4's body dead straight whereabouts, the breeze,such as knife, blow to pare off his cheeks.He shut up the mouth, eyes Mi wear, and the jelly iron within successful hang up to all hold not to live.
&lt;br /&gt;;He fell ground up, snow there be loose soft deep, soon the place of calf.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister purple Juan walked to go out and see the text loose Yang noodles looking at here.She settled to stop and think, deep absorb one breath, is downwards jumping, but detection overhead of precipice wall top long one stub greenery the plant of the purple flower, the purple flower be partial to red, become form Sui form.
&lt;br /&gt;;That be the Wu heart which bloomed grass.This kind of plant has grass a leaf the subtle fragrance of the mud sort, legend as long as the flower blossom, ability resist demon bad work properly of harass, for wear to wear of the person bring good luck.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Wu heart grass&quot;, the elder sister point at to float to shake in the breeze of Wu heart grass, shouted it of name, &quot;take off it to come to do a perfume satchel to five younger sisters.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The silver dragon stretch forward and see top of head that stub so-called Wu heart grass above, in plant in the rock clip sew, the appearance of the Pu common.But see the reaction of elder sister, also didn't query, he draw out silver feather upward on flick, that greenery purple flower be then chopped in two from the root-stock.
&lt;br /&gt;;The silver dragon connect, and give elder sister.
&lt;br /&gt;;Underneath of the text be loose to not and trust looking at above of scene, &quot;how?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Have no matter&quot;, elder sister answer, &quot;this came down.&quot;Say that finishing purple Juan get down to jump.
&lt;br /&gt;;Cloud bridge is 3 and have a little to fear afraid, hesitant repeatedly, still keep coming down.The end is a silver dragon, his skill take sword, skill protect to have killing the calico sack of black lotus.
&lt;br /&gt;;Four people all have already come down, they slightly tidy up behind toward below the hills walking.Day the light be gradually dark, if in time they return and can stay overnight in the last time stay overnight of that cave.
&lt;br /&gt;;The damp and cold clothes didn't bring body skin the least bit temperature, but that heart that go home be hot, calculate drop into freeze of lake inside is also hot of.
&lt;br /&gt;;They found out them to hide in come down of the process of burden, take to again walk faster up the empress.Evening they really stayed overnight in the hole inside of that bottle gourd shape, a heap of firewood grain prosperously combustion, light of fire gradual melt the cold idea that their body overlay, also urge in the meantime tired their body.That night they finished eat only remain not much of stem meat, everybody still don't arrive a cake of, again ate a few snow, they then lie down.
&lt;br /&gt;;The second day they set out and make their accident of is sky unexpectedly pinned up for a red day, although the ray be thin Huang, can be also a sunlight.Saw the comfort mood of sunlight them go toward below the hills walk, there borrowed to keep their horses, that docile of somebody else, the purple Juan felt deficit them to be a lot of.
&lt;br /&gt;;But, that woman was still in every possible way and passionately a reception them, looking at them to come over, far far start shout the name of purple Juan, even the kid of home be also beckon with the hand to call.The horse keep thoroughly and even still grow fatty some.See there a few horse, imitate Fo spring city at at present.
&lt;br /&gt;;Farmer woman Ying Ying the ground smiled.Need not ask again, the light see from the facial expression of several people of elder sister's younger brother face and save have already known them to get a this trip and seek of killing black lotus.The man isn't at home, she be then come make up decision of person.&quot;Stay to stay last the first here, kid in my house still need to listen to you speak spring the story in the city.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan have a little embarrassed, keep to this kind of white of enthusiasm she be what heart save feel grateful, in the meantime nearby of little girl return tight tight pull a her hand.However, hurry up to return be her most should, is also most urgent to want something to do.
&lt;br /&gt;;See the difficult facial expression of purple Juan face, that woman also not etc. purple Juan answer, &quot;do not stay you, don't stay you, your younger sister's business be important.&quot;She walk into a house and separate a burst of come out is hand top many some fruit for dry in the sun and cook of fillet.
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan and three younger brother smile apologetically together, can't measure with the money for this family's good intentions hospitality afraid of, however purple Juan while walk possibly much cent the silver in the bag two, &quot;take to buy again a Geng cow, Peng inside of that is also too small.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Little girl jump to say to her mother, &quot;be, be, cow cow in my house be so small but want it to plow fields farmland, buy the head be big of substitute it stem to live.&quot;Then, she looking at the purple Juan that the hair silk flaunt, unwilling to part, the Shan in eye wear radiant thing, &quot; you be walk, don't walk can?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan looking at her, that tears in the kid's eyes be only warm hot, &quot;not line, I also want to return care oneself of younger sister.You are free and must come to spring.&quot;She is a kid reason reason before the sum of hair, lead long a her hand to say.
&lt;br /&gt;;That girl nod, but the voice be matchless of firmness, &quot;certain, certain.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;She has been beckon with the hand them to wave hand on departure toward the purple Juan, until can't see any further.
&lt;br /&gt;;Get to return to horse, got Hui to present, they ride the horse a burst of Yang whip to press and Ma3 Fei like run.Road of return is acquaint with, walk through several days ago at least, so ratio a time quick.All the way top seldom stop over, connect seldom ride a horse, don't make it a rule to jolt right away of the cloud bridge also silently accept, he face top complain, on the contrary have plenty of expectation of air.
&lt;br /&gt;;They stopped at the Xun river town for a night, be still that Inn, boss, room, meal already a long time such as past, but their mood is big not homology.The bed of clean warmth, the steaming hot meal make them fully satisfied and very early and then started on for two days.
&lt;br /&gt;;Flat broad visual field, the warm sun Pu shine on of the weather, they again start on.
&lt;br /&gt;;The evening setting sun twilight shine on a city wall those rock which be suffused with ashes up, have a gold sort of glorious.The front door still keeps open, but has no how much pass in and out of shadow of human figure.Purple Juan they looking at a city wall to hang high up up the Gao of wood Bian:West Dragon gate.
&lt;br /&gt;;Spring the city have been already arrived, separate the 67th, scenery here constant, but even add several cent benignity.They see mutually and immediately after walked to go into west Dragon gate.
&lt;br /&gt;;Five younger sister, we came back.Seem to be in the heart of each of them all is say the words of same.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Look for the medicine chapter 22 to counteract poison(up)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The person of street in the evening city already rarely seen, however ride a horse to walk through still someone looking at them.They also the don't care even is stranger to examine, curious about vision, have never also let them feel uncomfortable.
&lt;br /&gt;;They finally returned to oneself of abode, they are in the spring the city more than ten year, stop for a rest of point.Four people are all slow one breath, walk into yard, those leafs flutter to move one wonderful of joy voice.They pair of Ma3 Shuan is on the tree trunk, a moment also not the wish stop over ground to run to the third floor, five younger sister the place of the snow Yu lie-down.
&lt;br /&gt;;Five younger sisters still keep lying quietly so and seem matchless leisurely got into dreamland.But this sleep to would be so for several days, see close of the eyelids be also tiny curved black of long long eyelash, on the face have no rosy and blood-red color.
&lt;br /&gt;;Purple Juan past pull five younger sister the hand of snow Yu, relax before her at heart is deeply, of the mood band together all of a sudden.&quot;To the dragon Kui, all of everythings be because of him&quot;, she bite to move a tooth and the hand be also shiver.
&lt;br /&gt;;Cloud bridge come forward, the skill press the shoulder in elder sister, &quot;the elder sister don't want to worry, five younger sister would good of.That know us to have already come back toward the dragon Kui affirmation and he will seek ours.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The silver dragon beside advise Wei, &quot;miss him to can't play, either what pattern, there is black lotus snow Yu return will be like originally so, will jump will smile, old love imagination, and make track for to ask some oddness of question.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose to also come over here, he say, &quot;etc. five younger sister instauration, we in no case pass toward the dragon Kui.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan smiled, she turned head to looking at three younger brother, satisfaction location head, then turn past continue to see snow Yu, counteract the face of the hand petting snow Yu, that is a perfect face, naturally beautiful medium have several cent lovely, and pure without blemish, there is no a black birthmark, ripple on the face of brilliant smiling face, seem bloom of heavy flower.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister sobbed, misty in the eye, she is nearby strong to endure to ask Wu2 Da4 Shen3's daughter, &quot;small Lai, did everyday take a Dan medicine for snow Yu?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;That girl is bigger than snow Yu 45 years old, the person be clever and reasonable, is Wu2 Da4 Shen3 life of good assistant, her reason reason ear of hair, two jet black eyes looking at purple Juan, &quot;took for the younger sister, purple Juan elder sister.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;That good, small Lai, pain you.Now from we care be, you return, thank your mother for me.&quot;The purple Juan say.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Have no matter of, purple Juan elder sister, later have what matter remember call we be.&quot;The small Lai say that finish turned round and then walked to go out.
&lt;br /&gt;;Inside house leave their five people.Five people, like five finger of a hand.Return preceding paragraphs of remember the decade loose five fingers Nu the situation of the piece, that appearance can never forget, because of from that a moment beginning they woulded be five people, not and mutually separate of five finger.
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan withdraw oneself of hand, see come to hand five finger of jade sort of palm, the look in the eyes be a few confusing, a the tears outstanding eye socket which roll a circle, flowed down from the eye Cape.The hair that is before the sum float bottom and the noodles which covered her permit.But cloud bridge they all know elder sister at the moment of feeling, they also have same heavy mood, and expect to.
&lt;br /&gt;;They satted down, round a bedside in snow Yu, use concern and gentleness of the look in the eyes looking at her, connect the text be loose in the past the facial expression of that very happy also disappear be missing, in his heart think of is all ppearance for snow Yu to awake.
&lt;br /&gt;;The color of the sky out of the window is dark bottom to go to, connect far-away place setting sun fall in place of red the rosy sunset also become gray of.
&lt;br /&gt;;Door outside burst upon the figure of small Lai, she be blunt to come in, on the face take in a hurry of air, a words would be, &quot;someone seek you, purple Juan elder sister.Is &quot;see purple Juan combine nothing important reaction, immediately after say again, &quot; quite a few people, in the yard of.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan kiss at present hair to the back of the ear, looking at small Lai, &quot;okay, thank you small Lai.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Silver dragon the text was loose to see one eye mutually, is all 1 face of doubt, this time?Is there still a good many?To seek them?
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan start, &quot;I see&quot;, say that finishing to follow small Lai behind went out.But don't trust elder sister, the silver dragon also come out a door together.
&lt;br /&gt;;Their station look down on the wood gallery but bottom saw seven people, two among those people's face so acquainted with.Listenned to an elder sister anger hate ground to shout 1 toward the dragon Kui, the that white dress man shook to begin medium of iron, stand on 1 to wear to pay&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcvcnVuZXNjYXBlLW1pbmktZ2FtZS1iYXJiYXJpYW4tYXNzYXVsdC1jLTI5XzMzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Fighter torso&lt;/a&gt;;   attention to, rich and honored but again not extravagant of man flank, see to that man ratio another from the age acquaint with of person-Europe's sun big Xia slightly big, they be attach an ear to say words.
&lt;br /&gt;;See toward the elder sister of dragon Kui certainly for at present of the scene be shocked, so quick seek to come, afraid is go into the city it hour have already known them back.
&lt;br /&gt;;Silver longan absolute being in also have one silk worry in uncertainty, sun in Europe big Xia, that is all the way fierce to make track for until the person of fist precipice also come, return and together and after death follow the person whom four Wu3 Jia dress up toward the dragon Kui.This what kind of combination?The person called to steal things and is steal of person together, also at company quantity what.Reckon to take a killing black lotus also needless with these people come?The silver dragon in the mind keep make to whisper.
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose to hear noise to rush through with cloud bridge, cloud bridge still give°ed green Ying and silver feather they.Hold an iron to hang up in the text loose hand, be like fierce tiger similar stare at toward the dragon Kui.
&lt;br /&gt;;To dragon Kui face top hang to smile, can this time but have no that kind of icy cold, aversion of felling, contrary but is take several cent calmly with cool.He purple Juan, again with nearby of the person said a sentence words.
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan is tight to grip the Nan wood of the green Ying a handle, in the eye that white dress the man brought them a disaster, but want battle him to cure good five younger sister snow Yu, the mood be anxious and have innumerable of the dint need to be let out, but have to endure.&quot;To the dragon Kui, you say of black lotus already bring back come, according to engagement pair of snow Yu of poison solution, otherwise calculate your person much don't also want to return.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Under of to dragon Kui and nearby of man's look in the eyes be tiny to change, for had a black lotus them is a satisfaction of, but behind threat of words again let their air a tight.Wielding an iron toward the dragon Kui still keep being an uninfluenced shape, he toward purple Juan to say, &quot;you come down to talk.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan is hesitant.The silver dragon that is nearby see the other party have no how much hostility, connect once also a face of to the sun in Europe big Xia of silver dragon gnash teeth in hatred dispassion, that is quietly hide in breadth knife sheath in.Hence he give the expression of eyes that the elder sister be an affirmation.
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose also at one side low voice say, &quot;quantity they also dare not again play what pattern, we be vivid to reply be.&quot;But cloud bridge is to firmly nod, is sorry and ashamed to error his heart of last time, also think no longer evade, active face.
&lt;br /&gt;;They came downstairs and stand under the eaves of stone steps, looking at white dress man and flank that 50 top and bottom of of man, he top body is hide blue to embroider point beak Phoenix of clothes, waist a cake of the thin and blue raised carving jade wear and descend body pants green medium take purple, the skin Xue of the feet previous utter darkness.Some tiny grow fat on the face, however the ability still see the face of a knife sword sort department outline, a Gao Bi2 and a pair of deep eyes.Have a kind once acquaint with of felling.
&lt;br /&gt;;But, the purple Juan also didn't think carefully a this person identity.She say to the that white dress handsome and talented man, have to gnash teeth with hatred in the words of pain, although hand in of green Ying's being clear be his, &quot;we come down, to the dragon Kui.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The silver dragon, text are after death loose to stand and grip weapon, sharp vehemence and elder sister to compare the slightest don't reduce, connect cloud bridge that fatty and thick soil bean face's being also full be harsh countenance.They are the strong backing of the elder sister, with to dragon Kui that square confrontation.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister talk, but three people the hungry wolf be general to stare at an evening to come to visit of several individual.&quot;We give° the killing black lotus you, oh, in fact should be regarded as killing purple lotus.You can work well an antidote for several days.&quot;The elder sister say.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;How many days?&quot;Suddenly counter-question toward the dragon Kui, &quot; in fact sleep dragon blood the poison of the grass is have no the medicine is soluble.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Have no … medicine … can … solution …&quot; elder sister break continuous continuously repeated, a the wrath which soon fly off the handle in heart rise Teng but.And then square hear the text of this words loose enumerate an iron to hang up will go toward outside blunt, &quot;I want to kill you and I want to kill you.&quot;Listen to a text loose face top write whole full is to arouse an anger.
&lt;br /&gt;;The silver dragon pulled him and toward Yin is cold but firmly say again toward the dragon Kui, &quot;that you today will pay for it.&quot;The silver feather within hand starts to be unclear to go into action and respond to the silver dragon thoughts and feelings within brain.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister pulled out green Ying from the skin set, in the ray of ash white in evening send out of is light green light, &quot;that I be five younger sisters.&quot;The behind words card is in the throat, she in mind swear to want be cut to pieces toward the dragon Kui, the Cuo bone Yang ash.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;You five younger sisters have no matter.&quot;Say toward the dragon Kui that close the snake line iron in the hand.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Nothing.&quot;Purple Juan they as one man say.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Rightness, what she win not is sleep dragon blood poison, just with meticulous care make of dizzy sleep the poison of type just, but though the antidote of this kind of poison be difficult to go together with, also have the ready-made.&quot;Say toward the dragon Kui explanation.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;But also have ready-made of&quot; purple Juan repeated his words, have an antidote five younger sister the nature life have no sorrow, should be happy, but really be such?Already how many three foreign lands is cheat, be his words still authentic?
&lt;br /&gt;;Toward make to account to cheat to walk a silver dragon a text before dragon Kui see a worry in uncertainty of purple Juan, loose, poison dizzy snow Yu, also cheat say medium sleep dragon blood poison, arrive at this time but say this poison not antidote, again say medium of is another of poison.He is with meticulous care some kind of arrangement, killing the black lotus have been already take off, the words that are in the heart intend for and the dish give, can body side the adult have no openings and he be also much more embarrassed to say what.
&lt;br /&gt;;After all the adult is the decision that occupy, behind how turn into all is depend his.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Dispensation but become of poison kill people killing easy, can grow the person to sleep not but is a difficult matter.Perhaps learn several year, the purple Juan of medicine also know, but, you not what to know be in fact &quot;, he, open an iron to continue to say, &quot;, give you of the tablet be also a poison of a part, everyday 1 grain then ability maintenance next day of in coma.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Purple Juan at heart disillusion, at the beginning five younger sister poisoned, the at heart distress, the brains thinking waslike ed subjected to control, didn't once doubt lead those replace three meal food of tablet.Calculate such, to dragon Kui instant give understanding medicine, five younger sister awake, can also hard accept so of fact.&quot;Pain plan and prepare for getting a killing black lotus?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Looking at purple Juan like eyes of lake water sort toward the dragon Kui, answer a way, &quot;yes.&quot;But don't know a behind how to should connect words, so tiny shut lips and say again.
&lt;br /&gt;;That man of flank suddenly come forward, he be provided to begin, voice is strong to emolliently say, &quot;the life Niang purple Juan, not the Kui work for the woman of great capability is also brave make firm decision, don't be lose in usually man.It was descend sun Jin in Europe to once see miss.&quot;That words say manner condescension, unavoidably let the public rise to esteem highly.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Sun Jin in Europe&quot;, the elder sister be in mind surging, at present that person be take charge of of sun mansion in Europe, that Chi Mao winds and clouds several decadeseseses, smell breeze the bad guy extremely frightened, spring grant favor in the city in usually common people, held many sun Jin in Europe of strange treasure conference, such the person of legend at the moment station in her in front, be 23 Zhangs of distance, imitated Fo to separate several inside far.
&lt;br /&gt;;After death of three younger brother also feel more an accident, difficult way for recovering to steal of thing, this also was to dispatch army and involve the masses too much.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister toward sun Jin in Europe, is also an arch hand, &quot;Yu younger brother dead hour visit your family, also to take a few artifacts of your home, origin want to return to city in, have time then go the your home return to compensate offense, don't think adult to unexpectedly and personally come, thousand times sorry.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;Origin think the other party to hear oneself mention a matter of steal the thief meeting Lou face of resentment, but the other party on the contrary on smile, arch wear of the hand let go of go to, but is still clear voice to say, &quot;the purple Juan miss need not bind by formalities, you are to have no a way would commit burglary.Today come not for these thing outside the body since then.&quot;He stopped down, the sun in Europe big Xia body of behind a tight, polite politely return to looking at sun Jin in Europe.
&lt;br /&gt;;Sun Jin in Europe toward nearby of don't  be an order but is a consultation to the dragon Kui of the tone make reference to, &quot;counteract poison for five younger sisters of purple Juan first to the wise niece.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The iron owed a body to promise toward the dragon Kui, closed to wave without extra trouble touched a grain of gold the tablet of the yellow.Tablet rock, waked up with a start the purple Juan in consider still, &quot;we go upstairs to counteract poison for your five younger sisterses.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The purple Juan reaction come over, but just listenned to get a goal clear, to the wise niece, this again what happened.But, purple Juan also no longer Chi Chu, have Europe the sun Jin adult is would be to can believe.Hence they take a silver dragon to still have Europe the sun Jin to walk to the room of the third floor snow Yu.But sun in Europe big Xia together with four under charge stay and wait in the yard.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Look for the medicine chapter 22 to counteract poison(bottom)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They arrive at the inside of the building.This is 1 display simple of room, there is no attire of gold and silver jade, also not high-class and interesting and novel room, just common somebody else house in of decoration, have thin such as the aroma of clear water let the house be unlikely too depressed, and house in in addition to one Zhang Mu4 Chuang2, one Zhang Mu4 Tai2, one mouthful big box outside again have no don't of big piece artifacts, but then some daughter of the small piece domestic expenses of decorations, there are also a decorative lantern and a kite of butterfly kind.
&lt;br /&gt;;Walk on the purple Juan after death toward the dragon Kui, see snow Yu of sleep soundly the shape, his heart bottom slide past one silk apology and looking at calm and steady eyes of her black to seem is say, pain you, snow Yu.Seem his skill an arrangement to purple Juan everything do by them, can that is also have no alternative of.Fortunately with think in his heart of similar, purple Juan they took a black lotus to safely come back and have in their look in the eyes a kind of harm what it love hate an idea, but vision is also firmness of, there is secretly of strength.
&lt;br /&gt;;Purple Juan past start to hand five younger sisters, the soft body be like a silk ans stain sort to depend on elder sister's body, eyes slightly shut, small breathing quiet if have no voice.The purple Juan look in the eyes complications looking at toward the dragon Kui, there is perplexity, there is anger hate, there is also sincere one silk.
&lt;br /&gt;;Walk through toward the dragon Kui go to, didn't say a words, also didn't turn head a facial expression of see the others, he take out a grain of purple brown tablet from the bag and there is some the black marks of sesame sort in the top.He slowly send out, and is loose to come forward a text, head also don't return to ground to say, &quot;the text be loose, quick take water.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose past carry to a half bowl boiled water, but the purple Juan also open a mouth for snow Yu.The bowl put the tablet into the mouth of snow Yu toward the dragon Kui, once been alongside of to hold water, pour into snow Yu half of the piece in.
&lt;br /&gt;;Tablet with wear water be swallow by snow Yu into the stomach, slowly the snow Yu body have variety, she face of gradual instauration blood-red color, the double shoulder which hang to fall paid no attention ground to tremble two times, even eyelids also beginning loose move.
&lt;br /&gt;;The text is loose surprised pleasedly shout loudly, the slightest inattentive have outsider at, &quot;five younger sisters moved and five younger sisters lived to come over.&quot;Cloud bridge and silver dragon also took notice of snow Yu body since of variety, is also that once the eyebrows move, tiny have concussion of air.
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister purple Juan looking at snow Yu to open eyes, the eye pupil son turn to move in the eye socket and see at present of person after, that eye pupil again top turn over to stare at purple Juan to see.The elder sister Chi Chi ground, the body be motionless such as on having carve of sculpture carvings, Be just that heart but apace flutter, wrap up to warm up in the double eyes of liquid, that tears faintness her view, however can still see that double of eyes which work properly to move to have absolute being.
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Elder sister, how was this ?BE that the day want to put bright?Why have so many people?&quot;A series of question made her have a liking for to seemed to just wake up from the in a dream, but the at present white dress man make she a surprised, she backward one Suo, it is tight to stick elder sister almost.Although just wake up, the whole body was still soft to lack to have no dint, still the hard way raise a hand, point at that white dress a man, &quot;elder sister, that be the bad person.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;The elder sister is by hand light to touch the arm of snow Yu, once next clap, &quot;he be a bad person, however now had no matter.&quot;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>