<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="210d49642876ed61e804a5259c78607c">			&lt;p align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;;Post by (&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck online&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; Jun 2011&lt;/p&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The frontrunner for leader of the Scottish Conservatives has said he will disband the party if he wins the leadership election next month.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The MSP Murdo Fraser says the Conservatives carry too much baggage in Scotland and claims a new centre-right party would attract more voters. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The party would sit with the Tories in the Commons but have its own policies.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mr Fraser said David Cameron was aware and the idea had the support of several senior Conservatives at Westminster. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He told the BBC: &quot;What we have to do is get many more people elected from Scottish constituencies to support David Cameron and a future UK Conservative government and the best way to do that is to create a new progressive centre-right with a Scottish identity.&quot; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He added: &quot;I think that will be much more attractive to many people in Scotland who share our values.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Leadership pitch
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Conservatives have failed to revive their fortunes in Scotland since the 1997 general election, which saw them lose all 11 of their Westminster seats. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;At last year's election, they only managed to retain one MP, David Mundell in Dumfriesshire, Clydesdale and Tweeddale.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mr Fraser says the party has been in continual decline in Scotland since the 1960s and the best option was to create a new party.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But he can expect some opposition with the former Secretary of State for Scotland, Lord Forsyth, calling the plan a &quot;ludicrous idea&quot; which amounts to raising the white flag in the face of opposition from the SNP. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mr Fraser says his campaign slogan in the Scottish Conservatives leadership race was a &quot;new party for Scotland&quot;.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;This is the central plank of my leadership pitch,&quot; he said. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;And what I'll be saying effectively is there is a lot of interest in centre-right values amongst people in Scotland but they don't vote for the Conservative Party.&quot; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck online shop&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;Wenn Sie an &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck günstig&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; interessiert sind,bitte besuchen unsere Website: &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck online kaufen&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="c0d4fd5f0e845d3be54f5e613056d14c">			&lt;p align=&quot;right&quot;&gt;;Post by (&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck online&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; Jun 2011&lt;/p&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;We like and appreciate what NATO did for us,&quot; a smiling Belhadj said in an interview Saturday, referring to the North Atlantic Treaty Organization bombing campaign against Kadafi's forces. &quot;We now have a popular Libyan revolution that doesn't have any Islamic ideology.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Belhadj conceded that he might sue the CIA — he alleges that he was tortured while in its custody in Bangkok, Thailand — but said he didn't have any hard feelings against the United States or the West. He said his group had rejected overtures to affiliate with Al Qaeda and that Libya's new government will not be Islamist.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;We believe that Libya should have relations with all nations,&quot; Belhadj said at his heavily guarded seaside complex in Tripoli, the Libyan capital. &quot;We Muslims need to interact with all other nations, and all other religions. This is what Islam tells us.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Belhadj's saga has echoes in other shifting U.S. alliances. Washington spent billions to oust the Soviets from Afghanistan, only to see that nation become a breeding ground of Islamic extremism targeting the West. The George W. Bush administration marched on Baghdad to oust Saddam Hussein, only to see the new Iraq become a close ally of the stridently anti-American Iran.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Belhadj's emergence as a major player in Libya's post-revolutionary government has raised anew thorny questions about Islamic influences and potential anti-Western currents in the new Libyan order.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not everyone is happy with the turn of events.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Belhadj is a bad man,&quot; said one former CIA operative with long experience in the Middle East who declined to be identified. &quot;He's a capable Al Qaeda field leader.... Belhadj was a serious enough actor for us to find him, kidnap him and render him. He's somehow had a conversion to democracy? What do they base that on? It's just a pipe dream.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But the official U.S. position is a stated belief in the new Libyan leadership's professed desire for a representative and democratic state after more than four decades of Kadafi's autocratic rule.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nonetheless, many rebels who fought to oust Kadafi have Islamic militant ties — notably Belhadj, who earned his stripes as a young fighter against the Soviet Union in Afghanistan, using the nom de guerre Abdullah al Sadiq.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The CIA detained him in 2004, according to documents found by Human Rights Watch in the abandoned Tripoli office of Kadafi's former intelligence chief, including a fax seeking Libyan assistance in the agency's plan to transport him to Libya.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;We also appreciate your allowing our service direct access to Al Sadiq for debriefing purposes once he is in your country,&quot; said a March 6, 2004, fax from the CIA to Libyan authorities.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The fax provided the office and cellphone number of an apparent CIA contact, but cautioned that Al Sadiq should be treated &quot;humanely,&quot; and sought guarantees that &quot;his human rights will be respected.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A generation after Belhadj fought in Afghanistan, Libya was fertile ground for Islamists seeking to fight U.S. troops in Iraq. Some had links to Belhadj's former organization, the Libyan Islamic Fighting Group, labeled a terrorist organization by the U.S. government.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Kadafi, once a backer of terrorist groups in Europe and elsewhere, came to view Islamists and Al Qaeda as a threat to his autocratic rule. This is where Kadafi and the former Bush administration found common ground.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Kadafi's regime dispatched many Islamists or suspected Islamists to prisons, including Tripoli's notorious Abu Salim lockup, which was liberated by rebels last month. In one cell of the now-abandoned jail, graffiti display an affinity for anti-Western thinking.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck online shop&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;Wenn Sie an &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck günstig&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; interessiert sind,bitte besuchen unsere Website: &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shopschmuckonline.de%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shopschmuckonline.de/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;schmuck&quot;&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;schmuck online kaufen&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>