<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d02978c79794cbdde65fdd4ea74322ab">			In the year 2012, the planet is explained to undergo a series of destructive occasions that will render all living creatures in it extinct. The Nibiru 2012 Planet X Barack Obama Evolution is a single of the several views about the issue, and even a lot more speculations surface area as individuals attempt to cipher what the info from scientific research and the predictions of historical cultures might signify. Nonetheless, a debate relating to the issue is nevertheless unconcluded since there are several aspects to be thought to be about these forecasts. Under are some of the several views about this distinct situation:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;bull	In line with this, several men and women believe that there is in some way a correlation among the present United States president and the occurrence of the cataclysm involving Nibiru in accordance to the prognostications by Nostradamus. The said 16th century French astrologer is deemed to be 1 of individuals individuals who have considerably an correct foretelling prowess that is in by itself actual and reputable. In his predictions, he pointed out about the existence of a character named &quot;Mabus&quot;, who will signify the onset of chaos on the earth.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;bull	In this facet, &quot;Mabus&quot; is explained to be a mix of the names &quot;Obama&quot; and &quot;Bush&quot;, the two newest presidents of one particular of the most powerful countries in the globe. When the present president was elected, it produced a relatively wretched reaction from particular groups of individuals towards the predictions of Nostradamus, who have formerly mentioned about a &quot;darkish gentleman originating from slaves&quot; taking control. This coincidence may possibly or may not be true, but there is even now minor or no proof with regards to this matter at all. As these kinds of, Nibiru 2012 Planet X Barack Obama Evolution is however to be verified.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;bull	Contrary to this, other individuals say that the stated character is in fact an true gentleman, in the man or woman of a certain Ray Mabus, who performs as an adviser to the president in terms of the dealings of the US in the Center East. It is mentioned that in case an assassination of this gentleman is manufactured, it would mark the begin of a cataclysmic stage on earth, perhaps the start of Globe War III. Shockingly, Nostradamus' predictions mentioned one thing about &quot;vengeance&quot; that could be connected to this event, and the existence of &quot;a comet&quot; that is thought to be a literary representation for a nuclear bomb hitting the terrorists who would assassinate the president's adviser.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;bull	Others say that the presence of &quot;Mabus&quot; is the birth of the greatest antichrist, the features of whom is considerably in line with that of Adolf Hitler and Napoleon Bonaparte. The activities that he could trigger would be relatively devastating, and Nibiru 2012 Planet X Barack Obama Evolution might be right associated to this. Knowing that the foretold arrival of Planet X, which is the enormous heavenly body predicted to hit the earth in 2012, will result in turmoil to our planet, there is very an overflow of suggestions and views from diverse establishments and organizations. If you believe the stop is coming close to or even that widespread devastation would outcome from this sort of occasions as referred to right here, get measures to get ready by yourself via simple survival techniques and preparations.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmarynorris49.bravejournal.com%2Fentry%2F82070"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://marynorris49.bravejournal.com/entry/82070&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thoughts.com%2Fmarynorris49%2Fnibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit-1"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.thoughts.com/marynorris49/nibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit-1&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="914cd59c70c53f2b9339fe863d3ebfd4">			How could a planet from a distant location could orbit so quick in a span of 6 many years? They in no way presented any facts at all, just illustrations of the passage of the planet.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rumors spread that on Might fifteen, 2009 Planet Nibiru would be visible around the southern hemisphere. But nothing occurred nor something odd in the skies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If our planet's magnetic poles are aligning in the direction of Nibiru then what about the other planets? What about Jupiter? Saturn? The Sun? The dilemma with the doomsayers are the only thing they consider about is the Earth. They have entirely disregarded what would occur on the other planets. Why? Simply because they can not discover sufficient excuses to feed your lies. Exactly where does Nibiru suit in?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Planet Nibiru is due to pass amongst the Earth and the Sun in this timeframe triggering a gravitation pull which will quit the Earth's rotation resulting in a 90 degree positional shift or a polar shift. This in flip will make a shock wave of radiation from pole to pole.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The construct-up to the coming of Nibiru can be witnessed in the anomalies that the Earth is previously experiencing through Tsunamis, hurricanes, earthquakes of incredible scale and proportion. Specific members of the scientific group imagine that the gravitational pulls that are staying seasoned are only a precursor of what is but to arrive.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All satellites, conversation links, Tv, radio, web, GPS positioning are all due to fall short by way of the oncoming arrival of Planet X. While the Mayans feel that Nibiru signals the finish of the globe there are many other folks who feel that December 21 2012 merely indicators an stop to the world as we presently know it. How did planet Earth endure just before the net and all the incredible technological improvements that have introduced us into the 21st century? Have we come as well far far too fast and is this galactic realignment an avenue for returning us again to basic principles?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even though this matter is hotly debated on message boards, post sites, by means of scientific seminars, papers, thesis etc. there is a distinctive lack of acknowledgment from governmental agencies of any nationalities. This fuels the conspiracy theorists who believe that there is globally governmental collusion in retaining data from the masses to avoid worldwide panic. Does this also imply that this eventuality is previously accepted by our leaders, do they know a lot more than they are telling us?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the year 2012, the globe is explained to undergo a series of destructive occasions that will render all residing creatures in it extinct. The Nibiru 2012 Planet X Barack Obama Evolution is 1 of the a lot of views about the make any difference, and even far more speculations surface area as men and women try out to cipher what the data from scientific investigation and the predictions of ancient cultures may possibly signify. Nonetheless, a debate regarding the make any difference is even now unconcluded given that there are many facets to be regarded as about these forecasts. This is since even if we know that this would definitely transpire, there is virtually no possibility of surviving the catastrophe that is about to happen.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frs2commmunity.org%2FNibiru.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://rs2commmunity.org/Nibiru.html&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frs2commmunity.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://rs2commmunity.org/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>