<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="41f2a893b60c6d9ed8aff4b9b4eb641f">			Flying has become stressful in many ways, which is why it's good to know about which airlines are best in 2012.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Between rising fuel costs and heightened security, many people are thinking long and hard before choosing an airline. It is important that you choose to fly on an airline that will get you to your destination in a comfortable and enjoyable manner. With that said, let's now look at some of the best airlines in 2012. We have compiled tips and suggestions to help you make the right choice.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People don't just think highly of Cathay Pacific Airways in Asia (the airline is based in Hong Kong) people all over the world love to fly it. It's central hub is one of the busiest airports on the planet: Hong Kong International Airport. The world economy is being affected by Asia more and more and that means that destinations like Hong Kong are becoming regular stops for more and more people. Hong Kong, China and other cities and countries in Asia offer plenty of opportunities for tourists. Travelers who really want to explore both Asia's history and current developmental progress can take advantage of the recently announced Quest for Harmony tour--a tour Cathay Pacific just started offering that will take you through places like Macau, Guangdong and Hong Kong (among others). We had a lot of fun putting this article together because this subject of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oYWlyc3RyYWlnaHRlbmluZ25vdy5jb20vaGFpci1zdHJhaWdodGVuaW5nLWF0LWhvbWUtdGlwcy8_" target="_blank"&gt;hair straightening at home&lt;/a&gt; really fascinates us. If you think this is all there is, then you are in for a real treat when you see what else we have written on the matter.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is all we ask of anyone, really, to view this with a receptive mind and go farther with it. When it all begins to gel for you, then you will be able to rise above to some degree thanks to added knowledge. It is natural for us humans to want to have some degree of command over the events and situations in our lives. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the lesser-known airlines that has been gaining quite a reputation as of late is EVA Air. The second-largest airline in Taiwan, it is well known in this Asian country. In the last few years, EVA, which was founded in 1989, has become more well known worldwide. In fact, in a few key areas, Skytrax has awarded EVA a four-star ranking which indicates that its service has improved over the last few years. Star Alliance, the largest airline group in the world, has recently been joined by EVA. This makes it convenient to fly with EVA if you're getting a connecting flight from another Star Alliance airline.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a lot of things to think about when you're trying to find the best airline of 2012 and price and value are among them. Your destination and when you want to travel are also important things to think about. If you are booking a flight you need to look at the actual plane that will be flown like a 737 or a 757 because it can make all of the difference when you are considering comfort or your safety. Airlines have different policies when it comes to special needs as well, like when you want to bring a pet on board. So while you should look at which airlines are best overall, you should also keep an open mind and try to find the best airline for the particular trip you're taking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In conclusion, you can see that there are many airlines that fall into the category of the best airlines in 2012. We also recommend doing your own research. In some cases, the top rated airlines might not even fly where you have to go, which means you have to choose among the airlines that are available. Using your own past experience, as well as research that you get from Skytrax or Epinions.com, choosing an airline that you will appreciate can actually be quite easy.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>