<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fb38675b36af3fea10f09b49534f5be8">			It is bad enough when a twenty-year old exercises poor judgment and posts something potentially offensive to others. Can a business afford the negative publicity it may receive as a result of such a major gaffe as posting or tweeting profane content? No, it cannot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We all realize these are tough times with higher unemployment and reduced revenue at many businesses. Most are looking to reduce payrolls and cut corners, wherever possible. Wages are among the first areas that CEOs go looking for savings and hiring on the cheap is very often a preferred strategy to save money. For those of us who truly believe a company's success is based on the quality of its workforce, this sort of thinking is very reactionary, short-sighted and ineffective.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Today, there are far too many companies announcing profits based on cost cutting measures rather than as a result of innovation in design, production, sales and service. Attempting to save money by risking results and reputation can easily backfire when it comes to placing inexperienced people on your front lines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recently, a business owner called my office, sharing his concern that articles posted to the business Facebook page weren't about his business specifically, and that he didn't see the value in social media because it didn't seem like it was being done &quot;right.&quot; While there is still no one way to make social media marketing work for everyone, there are ways to better establish an online presence and personality that will only help your business grow its brand online and offline. Let's review some of the facts in this particular case:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The business owner said customers asked about the articles posted on Facebook&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Conversations being started at your place of business because of social media gives you a chance to chat it up with your customer and get to know them even better so you can offer even more customized service. In this case, people were curious about some of the articles posted (usually related in some remote capacity, but often about local news or other interesting events trending online), and the business owner simply didn't know how to respond. Social is about being social, and it does often extend into the business space, so staying aware of your social campaign will definitely help you engage customers on a more personal level. Be prepared to get social in the real world!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many business owners simply do not understand the purpose of social media, because it is often times still new to the individuals working at the business. In this case, it is always best to educate yourself on your investment, or for social media marketers to educate their clients on the approaches and goals of their social media campaign. This particular case was unusual because contact was a consistent challenge throughout the months of the campaign's run. From a social media marketer to business owners everywhere, my best piece of advice is this: Before you go social online, make sure you understand how it will work, establish goals, and educate yourself on the products and services you'll be paying for. They should report to you the number of posts made in a month with site names and links to the posts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2NpYWxleHBvc3VyZS5jby51aw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Social Marketing&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>