<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f5a3b75d13515e379dd18708c0bfe600">			Sexy Time Can Help Your Mental Health&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3B1cmVzYWZldHlyZXdhcmRzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Loyalty Program&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VuLndpa2lwZWRpYS5vcmcvd2lraS9Mb3lhbHR5X3Byb2dyYW0_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FLoyalty_program"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Loyalty_program&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You already know there are a number of physical benefits connected with having regular sex. Together with other things, it helps you burn a lot of calories, raises the rate of your heart, gives you a complete body workout...you get the idea. Are you aware, however, that having sex on a regular basis can also be rather beneficial to your mental health? It's the truth! Of course you already know that having regular sexual intercourse gives you a feeling of satisfaction but the honest to god truth is that regular sex is quite beneficial for your brain and the rest of your body as well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love-making is, all things considered, a workout. You produce endorphins when you work out. Endorphins are the reason for mood elevation and a general sense of wellness. It is part of the reason that you feel so on top of the world after completing an excellent workout at the health club. Intercourse releases endorphins much the same way that exercising does--they're the same hormones. This is why, along with the beneficial feelings associated with achieving orgasmic pleasure, you feel so good after you and your partner have a satisfying sexual encounter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The orgasm opens up a person both mentally and physically. This is why they are generally the &amp;quot;goal&amp;quot; most people have in mind while having sexual intercourse. Your sexual climax helps relieve the stress you might have been going through before you started making love and it can help keep it away for a while. You feel a kind of &amp;quot;high&amp;quot; after an orgasm that makes it simpler for you to resolve issues and that can help you lower your overall stress levels. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Self esteem is bolstered through love-making as the intercourse itself encourages the people having it to give in and simply enjoy pleasure for a short time. This enjoyment isn't just the result of the physical act of having sex. It arises from the increased skin on skin contact both just before and soon after. It is also acquired through feeling close to another person on an emotional level. It's the consequence of the fun and happiness you share in your companionship. All kinds of wonderful things take place while having sex. If you have sex regularly, you have these great things often. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The act of having sex really encourages both the intimacy and emotional closeness people can share. Lasting relationships have this all the more fully. The connection that happens due to the regular intercourse helps a person feel safe. You'll have a much easier time feeling great about yourself when you know that you share a solid and safe bond with another person on every emotional and physical level. That's why even if a couple doesn't achieve sexual climax every time they have intercourse, the intimacy of love making can still help improve a person's mental health.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many reasons that regular sex can help someone feel better. If you want to feel much better in a bunch of different ways, do not let yourself feel scared of this  sort  of commitment.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>