<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="24066892abd5fe8688cb4d6eff4da836">			Even today, its influence can be viewed in many aspects in the following region. It led to the creation of the term 'California Dream', which attracted thousands of immigrants. The gold-rush was the first period of boom in Ca, which was followed by others. California farmers, oil drillers, movie makers, airplane builders, and &quot;dot-com&quot; entrepreneurs have each had their boom times inside decades after the Gold-Rush. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Gold-Rush period affected just about all the industries in California and the way they flourished. Similar to the gold-rush times, whenever developments were made in any industry, people from around the world flocked to California to a lot more than situation. Let us take the example of Hollywood from this regard. As the entertainment industry in California started to grow in the 1900s, people from across America came to Hollywood looking for work. Even today, most aspiring actors, and actresses move to Hollywood being at the centre of this entertainment world. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Aerospace industry also had its share of influence in the Gold-Rush. California has been one the main aerospace centres in the world throughout history. According to a survey, 42, 000 aerospace agencies, and suppliers are located within California, and many people moved here for employment with this sector. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Similarly, the details technology boom came in earlier 2000s, which led to the development in the Silicon Valley. Millions of people have since then shifted there in quest of prosperity, and it is known as an entrepreneurial haven. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Gold-Rush was an occasion that had a lasting effect on people's attitudes. It opened up their minds to a lot possibilities and gave them hope on the better tomorrow. As people grew to be more optimistic and driven, it produced the development of all key industries of California. The traditions of taking risks, and making quick money initiated out of your Gold Rush, and still offers its roots deeply imbedded within California. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;The Kodak Theatre is located at the Hollywood &amp; Highland Centre on Hollywood Boulevard and North Highland Method in Hollywood. This live theatre created by David Rockwell is the venue with the annual Academy Awards. It was opened on November 9, 2001 which includes a seating capacity for 3, 332 people. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The theatre was built for a cost of $94 million using active sponsorship from Eastman Kodak Corporation. Some of the famous artists performed in the theatre include Celine Dion, Prince, Alicia Keys, Barry Manilow and Melissa Etheridge. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A towering portal at Hollywood Boulevard is the entrance to the Kodak Treatment room. It leads to a two-story Honours Walk where backlit glass plaques involving Best Oscar winners are displayed on several limestone portals. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some sort of grand spiral staircase surrounds that five level theatre lobby. There are actually twenty six images of famous Oscar winners which include Marlon Brando, Grace Kelly, Julia Robert together with Grace Kelly displayed on four lobby levels. There is a privileged George Eastman room where this Oscar?? statuette awarded to Kodak Corporation is displayed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The audience chamber will get cherry wood finishing and serious plum upholstery. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JnbS5tZS9yLzE0ODY2MDI_" target="_blank"&gt;;Decorating with Fabrics&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3JhZGlvanV2ZW50dXNkb25ib3Njby5jb20vMjAxMi8wNC8wMi9kZWNvcmF0aW5nLXdpdGgtY2hyaXN0bWFzLWhvbGlkYXktZGVjb3Iv" target="_blank"&gt;;Decorating With Christmas Holiday Decor&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3J1YmlubWFzc2V5MTIub2JvbG9nLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Decorating With Christmas Holiday Decor&lt;/a&gt;;So you just got to Hollywood, California because you are following your dreams of becoming an actor, director, musician, and model.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>