<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7d58d78f1e136d49f8790e36f384f772">			Sikkim is definitely a charming state of North East India, fortunate with unmatched natural splendor. This location provides you with a chance to unwind in refreshing as well as charming environment, for this it becomes a preferred location to vacationers. Additionally, it offers majestic view of the great Kanchenjunga, the 3rd greatest mountaintops on the planet. Unfasten yourself in the good thing about regal mountaintops, fast streaming rivers, wonderful valleys along with vibrant flowers, amazing wildlife and gorgeous monasteries. 'Chang', an additional attraction of Sikkim, which is a delicious beverage, produced from fermented millet. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvd3RvcmVhY2hnYW5ndG9rLnR1bWJsci5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;How to go to Sikkim&lt;/a&gt;;?
&lt;br /&gt;;You may reach there by air, railway or by road. But there is no direct air link to Sikkim. You may avail helicopter service from Bagdogra, nearest air terminal. Journey through highway is very entertaining.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;A few of the well-known points of interest of Sikkim are:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Khecheopari Lake&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Positioned in a tranquil atmosphere it's a stunning body of water. Amidst the thick woods, this water body retains pure spiritual significance and Hindus and Buddhists frequent it. This attractive lake draws in numerous visitors.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Temi Tea Garden&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pay a visit to this particular rejuvenating tea yard and get rejuvenated. It's on the slope of the Tendong Hill and generates top quality green tea. Because of high quality tealeaves, this tea garden received quality awards.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Jawaharlal Nehru Botanical Garden&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Check out this particular garden and deal with your feelings using the sights and aroma of vibrant flowers and many different flower varieties. The several types of orchids with this garden entice guests from everywhere. It’s operating by the Forest Department of the Government of Sikkim.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Wildlife&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Within this state you're going to get to find out various types of wild creatures. It's a home to about 30% inhabitants of bird varieties found in the Indian Subcontinent. Some other wildlife located here are leopard, wild ass, snow leopard, red panda, flying squirrel and Himalayan black bear.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Kanchanjunga Trekking&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Trekking is among the most popular outing pursuits in Sikkim. Continue the Kanchenjunga trekking and for certain you'll appreciate it. This particular hiking trail provides pure beauty in abundance.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Monasteries&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This specific state is marked with gorgeous monasteries and also the most renowned among them are Pemayangtse Monastery, Rumtek Monastery and Phesang Monastery.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>