<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="7e676486398a570f2c80283d6154789c">			So you think that you should be &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bmVtcGxveW1lbnQtZXh0ZW5zaW9uLm9yZy9zdGF0ZS5waHA/c3RhdGU9b3I_" target="_blank"&gt;;Oregon Unemployment&lt;/a&gt;; promoted. You are irritated also that why your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bmVtcGxveW1lbnQtZXh0ZW5zaW9uLm9yZw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Oregon Unemployment&lt;/a&gt;; is getting delayed. You are working hard and doing your work satisfactorily. Why should you not get promoted? You want to ask your boss, but do not know how to ask? Can you we find out if you deserve to be promoted? If you are sure that you deserve Oregon Unemployment, you can approach your boss with surety and put forward your case. Let us quiz your Oregon Unemployment.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Quiz your working style - are you working very satisfactorily in your present responsibility? Have you improved the efficiency? Are your colleagues happy with you? Is your immediate superior happy with your performance? Have you learnt all that any body could in your present job? Please quiz yourself about these factors.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Quiz your ability- what is your ability in different specializations that your organization may demand. You think that you deserve a Oregon Unemployment, but what about your ability for that responsibility? You are working well with the present job. Will you be able to do justice to the new responsibility or you were only equipped to do the present job? A new responsibility demands new qualities. Do you have them? Or you will make a mess of that Oregon Unemployment job? Unless you are yourself sure about your ability to handle the new posting, please do not approach your superiors for getting Oregon Unemployment. Once you are sure that you can handle the new responsibility well, go ahead. Sometimes, we invite trouble by getting Oregon Unemployment promoted. Please avoid that.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2e7d66e31c521c4a9cd6365962107e6d">			Do you dream of becoming the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bmVtcGxveW1lbnQtZXh0ZW5zaW9uLm9yZy9zdGF0ZS5waHA/c3RhdGU9b3I_" target="_blank"&gt;;OREGON UNEMPLOYMENT&lt;/a&gt;; of your organization? Even if you are at the bottom tier and your company employs more than hundred thousand employees? Do you think that you will one day become the&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bmVtcGxveW1lbnQtZXh0ZW5zaW9uLm9yZw__" target="_blank"&gt;;OREGON UNEMPLOYMENT&lt;/a&gt;; of your organization? Is it only a dream or you have the ability? Why not quiz yourself and find out now? 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you know about the responsibilities of a OREGON UNEMPLOYMENT? Let us discuss about them and quiz your knowledge about that.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. To manage the organization
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Co ordinate all the departments
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Decide the goals
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. prepare and approve the strategy for achieving the goals
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Prepare the organization for the future.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. get the best out of human resources
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. Improve efficiency. Bring down the cost and increase the profits
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. Plan for new product launches
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. Keep ready for the competition
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10. Keep shareholders happy
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;11. Manage by anticipating the problems
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;12. Follow all the legal requirements
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are some of the functions of a OREGON UNEMPLOYMENT. If you want to become the OREGON UNEMPLOYMENT of your organization in future think about all these functions and prepare yourself mentally and gain knowledge to achieve the objectives. Dreaming is good. When concrete actions that is better and only then one support the dreams can realize the dreams.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e296b953daf94ddaf11718409b52e9dc">			According to a recent survey by &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bmVtcGxveW1lbnQtZXh0ZW5zaW9uLm9yZy9zdGF0ZS5waHA/c3RhdGU9b3I_" target="_blank"&gt;;Oregon Unemployment&lt;/a&gt;;Outlook, for the third year now there is a positive increase in hiring fresh college graduates for 2006. Business owners plan on hiring more from the class of 2005-06 than they did from the 2004-05 class as well as offering higher compensation and benefits for the new hires.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the annual survey by the National Association of Colleges and Employers, nine out of ten companies describe the new &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bmVtcGxveW1lbnQtZXh0ZW5zaW9uLm9yZw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Oregon Unemployment&lt;/a&gt;; market as good, very good, and excellent. Public accounting and consulting firms narrated the brightest prospect for the future graduates, while engineering and construction firms supported the idea by saying they'll also be hiring.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is a growing demand for new graduates in the Oregon Unemployment market as a result of the also growing products and services they offer and to keep up with the retiring HR staff. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Who are in demand?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Mechanical engineering 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Electrical engineering 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Accounting 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Business administration/ management 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Economics/finance 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Computer science 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Information sciences and systems 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Marketing/marketing management 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Computer engineering 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Chemical engineering 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mechanical engineering graduates topped the list and eyeing on them are aerospace, automotive, mechanical equipment manufacturers. They also plan on hiring graduates with Ph.D.s in science and computer related courses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Banking, transportation, financial, and insurance services are seeking Economics/Finance graduates. The food and beverage processing companies, merchandisers, and financial services will need more Business Administration/Management degree holders. One-third of business owners plan on hiring associate graduates categorized into three: technology, engineering and business related degrees. Insurance and engineering/surveying companies appear the most in need of 2 year course graduates for they bear a productive kind of technical knowledge which does not require more training. They belong to the hands-on work force who developed a good work ethic which is sadly observed by employers as missing in previous amateur graduates.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;During the survey, only 23.5%, (mainly manufacturers) respondents planned on hiring international graduates in 2006. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What qualities should a new graduate possess?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Must have excellent verbal and written communication skills
&lt;br /&gt;;• Must be honest and has a high regard with integrity
&lt;br /&gt;;• Can easily relate to others
&lt;br /&gt;;• Maintain strong work ethic
&lt;br /&gt;;• Can work well with others –TEAMWORK
&lt;br /&gt;;• Analytical skills
&lt;br /&gt;;• Must be self motivated and initiative
&lt;br /&gt;;• Adaptability to change
&lt;br /&gt;;• Updated computer skills
&lt;br /&gt;;• Observant to details
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The standards of companies’ ideal candidates are often higher than the last year’s. It is important that new graduates show good G.P.A.s as full time Oregon Unemployments come with good benefits coming from good revenues. Salary, should not be the sole consideration when looking for a Oregon Unemployment, benefits are part of it.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here are some of the lists of benefits:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Life and Medical/Dental insurance
&lt;br /&gt;;• Retirement plans
&lt;br /&gt;;• Annual and semi-annual increase
&lt;br /&gt;;• Employee counseling program
&lt;br /&gt;;• Dress code
&lt;br /&gt;;• Paid trainings
&lt;br /&gt;;• Bonus and commissions
&lt;br /&gt;;• Family benefits
&lt;br /&gt;;• Flexi-time
&lt;br /&gt;;• Performance updates
&lt;br /&gt;;• Vacation and sick leaves
&lt;br /&gt;;• On-site fitness and recreational facilities
&lt;br /&gt;;• Day care center
&lt;br /&gt;;• Company car/service
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The best places to seek competitive employers can be on campus Oregon Unemployment fairs, during on-the-Oregon Unemployment-trainings, student organizations and clubs, Internet search Oregon Unemployment search engines, etc. What’s important is that you target the right employers. Don’t let an opportunity pass, get in the interview to know more about their career offers and don’t forget to research about the company. You must be able to discuss your career objectives and compose a list of relevant and creative questions you can ask yourself.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>