<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f2fc3472bc6a4800312a189425af276b">			Have you ever seen Windows 7 blue screen? I believe all Windows 7 users might have encountered this during the computer life. So, do you know what causes it? Here, we will learn both from hardware and software to see the causes and how to fix Windows 7 blue screen of death.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;The error message usually states that a problem has been detected and Windows has been shut down to prevent damage to your computer. Then it comes with hex address codes like 0x000000C1. This error message should not be taken for granted. Once you encounter this system error message, you should immediately search for a fix. You can log on to Windows website for a safer approach. But of course this is too much a hassle to fix blue screen problems. The best thing to do is to analyze the problem with all patience and then follow these options:
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;o Fix your Windows Registry
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Run registry cleaner software to scan your entire registry, and fix all the errors inside. Most of the blue screen errors are related to Windows registry problems. Blue screen of death can be caused by the invaid, corrupted and malicious registry entries. Actually, it is a effective way for fixing blue screen with registry repair tools. Moreover, over time, the registry of your windows gets cluttered with tons of information. If you experience slow down in your PC during boot up times, opening up of new folders, surfing windows, its likely your registry has a ton of information it needs to wade through. Therefore, it is the most important step you should take to fix blue screen of death error.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;o Check your hardware
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;If you have plugged and installed a hardware device, let’s say a USB device, it might not be working properly with your system and might be the one responsible for the BSOD to appear. To stop blue screen of death, uninstall and unplug that device and reboot your system.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;o Check your installed drivers
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Blue Screen Error of course would be probably occurred because of the conflicts between drivers. You need to keep your PC device drivers new in order to fix Windows 7 Blue Screen of Death Error.t.Click Here To Download Latest drivers for your PC.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;To fix Windows 7 Blue Screen of Death,You need to follow the steps below:
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Step 1:
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Download &amp; Install Perfect SpeedyPc Pro.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Step 2:
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Click the “Scan” button.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Step 3:
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Click the ‘Fix Errors’ Button to Repair Your PC!		</conversation>		<conversation id="be49ffdb6276fd661070b0949bd396e5">			Android system as an open operating system is almost the same features and the Windows on a PC, they almost have the same advantages and disadvantages, and this is the Android system fascinating ... developers when Andrews systems in development seems to imagine, as does Microsoft to build a free and open ecological environment, but also opening up even more than Windows. same time, they also noted that a variety of problems encountered by the Linux distributions too open.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;So they built efficient Linux kernel on the basis of a less efficient virtual machine to achieve the versatility of most of the software. And attracted a large number of vendors through an open and free mode to production and sales of Android devices and development applicable to Android software, which is the Android system we see today.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Android and Windows have the following characteristics:
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;A good software open: you can through various channels to install the program, and a variety of program sales does not necessarily go through the official channels. Whether it is professional software company or developer community can be for the system development process. The system provides a powerful vitality.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;(2) the openness of the various interfaces: the various procedures in the case to obtain root privileges (administrator rights) are able to direct access to modify system files, manage and use the system equipment, this is restricted in the IOS and Saipan Tom Cat, for example, you can not speak for Symbian s60 development, because any program do not have permission to access the microphone.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Various parts of the system can be replaced: for example, on Windows you can use icesword to replace the Task Manager to set up the system with software such as Super Rabbit; in the Android system, you are free to replace the desktop program (this is also possible on Windows do), or in the setup interface CM set this feature to meet the user's desire to control.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Hardware differences: a variety of hardware devices are able to run Android, either X86 or ARM, whether it is 600mhz +256 m or 4 core I7, +4 G memory to run the Android system, as either 486 or I7 are able to run Windows, like a lot of enthusiasm to the major hardware vendors, so that they compete with each other to produce better chip.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;The breadth of the user: it is due to hardware differences, making the price of Android devices have from 500-5000 pc price is to cover the $ 2,000 to tens of thousands of dollars, which makes Whether you're short The dwarfish poor or rich handsome can have it. This greatly improves the system's coverage, but also makes more software developers to develop software for it.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;These are Android and Windows have the advantage, followed by a common drawback
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;The system's inefficiency: the Android system and efficient Linux kernel, but the use of virtual machines greatly reduce its hardware utilization; Windows system is not as good as the length and complexity of the code makes its efficiency has been Linux, even the I7 processor when multi-tasking can still feel the system Caton fact, Caton, largely because of the multitasking, the contention between the various tasks on the processor time. ios- The gravestone system and user interface the process of ultra-high priority, on the face of customer service Caton of the user interface, while WP7 is to give up the WM era of multitasking and user interface beautiful to get the fluency of the system.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;System is easy to crash: from Windows95 times that the classic blue screen, winxp era &quot;;program stops responding&quot;; errors correspond to the Android crashes automatically restart and error,? In fact, the IOS program and Saipan is the same error just the IOS smart &quot;;concealed the fact that direct bomb back to the desktop without any prompts, Saipan is always Caton, pull the battery to restart until the user.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;(3) the fragmentation of the system: when most users are still using winxp Microsoft has released win8, when the majority of users still use Android2.3 Android release 4.0, and even release 5.0, and many use the old version of the device also can not be an official update to the latest version, or want the latest version, please pay. This is an open or semi-open system defects can not be avoided, can only be said to be better than the excessive fragmentation of Linux distribution. In fact, Android really need a similar PNP technology in Windows, that is integrated in the operating system the most basic drivers, this can greatly reduce the difficulty of Android system upgrades.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;4 hardware compatibility issues: prior to the earliest days of Windows DX standard does not promote the different graphics cards will bring a different picture of the game, some games can only play a brand of graphics or other graphics on the game Huaping bug, this problem until now is still not fully resolved, such as Battlefield 3 frames on the N card is much higher than the A card. GPU is also a wide variety of Android ANDREO Qualcomm, Texas Instruments and Samsung of the SGX, NV geForce the ARM own mali, these gpu support openGL texture map format are different, leading to different devices require different packet Android really need a similar standard of the DX.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;5 high power consumption of the system: Due to the open hardware system has led to an arms race in the hardware manufacturers, which greatly improves the power consumption of the device, as long as competition will lead to rising power consumption, such as Intel and AMD compete The most intense era of P4 P4 processors and Athlon processors power more than 130w, AMD's do not give force to cause the intel i7 processor with lower power consumption, the other hand, the graphics market ATI (AMD) and NVDIA been deadlocked, the top graphics cards power consumption has reached a 250w now mobile SOC market is a competitive market, the major processor manufacturers makes the power of the SOC than ARM9 times have greatly improved in order to compete, but also makes advance the multi-core processors into the market, use multiple cores than directly enhance the frequency of more energy-saving power and efficiency can not have both just like the fish and eat the same.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;The same time, we can see the the Apple IP4S A5 processor dual-core 800MHZ, but use the top GPU-SGX543MP4, this to making IP4S and Android devices, like become a day charge, which fully shows that any good system is to establish a good hardware based on, and not beautiful any interface feature-rich system can run on the hardware slag is very smooth.Click Here To Fix &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fpcerrorfixpro.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bpc"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://pcerrorfixpro.com&quot;;&gt;;pc&lt;/a&gt;; error&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>