<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="2a84a61da3cc53c52f8c005d779d598d">			You can have your thesaurus modified depending on the article project you are working on.Its a rough task making tons of articles with high-quality content, and this is the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;linkwheel service&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; reason more and more article marketers go with article spinning software. While you take into account publishing lots of profitable articles &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;;link wheel&lt;/a&gt;; for your prospective buyers to read, you also need to think of the quality of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51c3B0by5nb3Y_" target="_blank"&gt;;linkwheel&lt;/a&gt;; the articles at the same time.- Automatic download of rewritten articles on your hard disk, your online business, or &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1jcmVhdGlvbi1zZXJ2aWNlLWxpbmstd2hlZWwtc2VydmljZXMtbGluay1weXJhbWlkLXdlYi0yLjAmYW1wO2NpZD0yMjE_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;link wheel service&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; via RSS feeds. But before you pay for anything, you might need to compare the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibHVydHkuY29tL3RhbGtwb3N0LmJtbD9qb3VybmFsPXNvbmpha2FyJmFtcDtpdGVtaWQ9MTUwOQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;link wheel&lt;/a&gt;; features of these content spinning software available in the market. You have the option to choose the way to access your article spinner.- Preview. You can ask advice from consumers who have purchased their own copies of content spinners.As you spin articles, words are often changed into their other synonyms, and the structure of individual sentences is changed in such a way that it does not disrupt the original flow of the articles.These are the different software issues that you need to keep in mind if youre up to purchasing a article spinner.With article content spinning, you can send out several articles as you can all over the internet without having to concern yourself with being penalized by search engines for posting &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;;mininet&lt;/a&gt;; duplicate content.- CD copy or online membership.What is an article spinner tool? Is it just a fad? What are the pros and cons spinning the contents &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51c3B0by5nb3Y_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;linkwheel&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; of your articles?Spinning the article &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;linkwheel&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; means rearranging the words and sentences of an original article in order to produce at least 10 to 20 unique articles. Additional words, phrases, or sentences are also included to enhance the content structure.Posting as many articles as possible over the World wide web means exposing your merchandise to the target clients. Article spinners can produce rewritten content in any text file format that you want.- Video tutorials. You can purchase a hard copy online or &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;;link wheel&lt;/a&gt;; through your local store, or &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1jcmVhdGlvbi1zZXJ2aWNlLWxpbmstd2hlZWwtc2VydmljZXMtbGluay1weXJhbWlkLXdlYi0yLjAmYW1wO2NpZD0yMjE_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;link wheel service&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; you can sign-up for a paid account. A content spinning software package usually contains tutorials by which you can learn the basics of article marketing and content spinning through videos. You[img]&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dominateseo.net%2Fimages%2Fweb%2Flinkwheel-pyramid.png"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dominateseo.net/images/web/linkwheel-pyramid.png&lt;/a&gt;;[/img] have the option to edit or rearrange the spun articles if you would like further improvements. A lot of companies provide content spinning software at a low cost. In this way, you will be assured that youll get your moneys worth for purchasing their content spinning software.Other features of the article spinning software include:- Automatic upload of content found in article directories or in your own text files. Articles in online directories can be grabbed by your content spinning software and can be automatically rewritten to serve your idea. Some article spinners can generate thousands of unique rewritten articles. The majority of articles on the Web are meant for this purpose, and you &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;;mininet&lt;/a&gt;; have &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RhaGVkZW5pLmJ1c3l0aHVtYnMuY29tL2VudHJ5X2lkLzE1MDA2MzUvYWN0aW9uL3ZpZXdlbnRyeS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;link wheel&lt;/a&gt;; to be good at it if you want your online business to be prominent.- Customizable thesaurus.If you want to try a particular brand of article generator, ask the software creator if they have free trial for a specific &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;;linkwheel service&lt;/a&gt;; period of time. If not, you can inquire if they supply any product guarantee..Using Article Spinner Software To Generate More Visitors To your Online BusinessIf you’re operating a business online, the simplest way for making individuals understand it is by offering information &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mcmVlLWJsb2ctc2l0ZS5jb20vYmxvZy5waHA/dXNlcj1tYWxpc3NhbW9yYWMmYW1wO25vdGU9MTUwMDM3" target="_blank"&gt;;link wheel&lt;/a&gt;; about the product or service that you provide. Online registrations usually have monthly or yearly membership fees, but most of them allow you to access their content spinner without having to download any software on your computer. You can preview your projects as the software automatically generates rewritten articles		</conversation>		<conversation id="10178f27faa60cfe62e7035705f0b152">			my new home my new blog my new blog post 2011		</conversation>		<conversation id="73895f9f1a063d2d9d878633c163183d">			my new home my new blog my new blog post 2011		</conversation>		<conversation id="c128150f20c3044327cbe0610f8bbc39">			my new home my new blog my new blog post 2011		</conversation>		<conversation id="76a359028f7bd4197dec9ec0d3b7ca16">			my new home my new blog my new blog post 2011		</conversation>	</conversations></author>