<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="846a27bfb645a5969887397fa7324011">			The discovery of pits in Xian, China in 1974 containing a life size army of over 8000 Terracotta Warriors more than two millenniums old was hailed as the Eighth Wonder of the Ancient World. These amazing soldiers with chariots, horses, stone armor and a following of court officials and entertainers were made over a period of 37 years to form part of the First Emperor of China Qin Shi Haung's entourage that would guard him in the afterlife. Terracotta Warriors tours offer tourist the opportunity of viewing this magnificent sight at affordable prices.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tours of various duration lengths through the city itself or viewing the pits and other cultural and historical places of interest in the Province can be arranged. A guide is appointed to each tour group and people can arrange their own customized itinerary to suit their budget and the time they have at their disposal.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The city itself has been in existence for over 3000 years and has played an important role in the history of China. One of four ancient capitals it is located on the eastern section on the route of the legendary Silk Road. Since the discovery of these pits it has achieved a further elevated level of importance.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With easy and inexpensive access by air or rail from Beijing it is a must if one is visiting China. Private tours to see the famous army of one or more days for select groups can be arranged. Packages include all admission fees, a tour guide and a personal driver for an air-conditioned car or van. Tours include day and nights visits to famous sites and places of interest.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A 120 piece exhibition including 20 compete figures representing warriors, generals, court officials and entertainers was displayed in a few major centers around the world. New discoveries such as two bronze chariots and life size bronze animals were included in the exhibition. If one did not view that exhibition then they may have to visit the actual site to see these wonders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The First Emperor Qin Shi Huang was a great visionary. He created the country that is today known as China by bringing all the provinces under one ruler and was the force advocating the building of China's Great Wall. He also built what is believed to be a splendid tomb which to date has not been opened and the now famous entourage of warriors and other artifacts to accompany him into life after death.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For anyone wanting to visit this area the internet is where they should start their research. Numerous websites carry interesting and relevant data for planning private tours or looking to book into an arranged tour. When visiting foreign countries it may be advisable to book through local companies as they are aware of all regulations and requirements.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This great discovery has been declared a World Heritage Site encompassing a museum and national park. Terracotta Warriors tours have ensured that their highly trained guides have a wide spectrum of local and national history and cultural knowledge to make any tour an interesting and unforgettable experience. This is a unique site and the only one of its kind in the world and well worth a visit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54aWFudHJhdmVsaW5mby5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Terracotta Warriors Tours&lt;/a&gt;; are a once in life experience so contact us for the best &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54aWFudHJhdmVsaW5mby5jb20vIy93YXJyaW9yLXRvdXJzLzQ1Mjc0MTMyNjM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Terracotta warrior Tour&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>