<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="48b6200de5cd58043ae5bd3c68bfef8">			It is also important to note that while this breed might have its difficulties, these are traits that can be drastically settled down, but require the proper specialized knowledge to do so. Being an expert on dog training myself, I highly recommend that you acquire the right specialized knowledge of how to train you're Akita properly, or you're Akita experience might prove to be somewhat bitter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It should also be noted, that training you're Akita is actually not a hard process, even though it might seem as such, the Akita's incredible intelligence makes it a very quick and fun learner.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As a new puppy owner, one of the most important things on your 'to do' list is to find the best puppy food for your precious bundle of joy. BUT.... a trip to the local Pet superstore will soon show you just how difficult this task can be!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are so many different brands and types of puppy food available, and they all claim to be the 'best', so how can you tell which one to use? Well, it's all about the ingredients... but before you go blind (or crazy) trying to read, and then decipher, the ingredient panels of twenty different dog food bags, just read this article and you'll know exactly what (and where) you should be looking.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before we go into where and what to look for, here's where NOT to go.... the local grocery store, supermarket or dollar store! The generic, store brand puppy foods that you'll find there won't give your large breed (or any size for that matter!) puppy what he/she needs to grow and develop properly. You want to AVOID puppy and dog food that has a lot of cheap ingredients, artificial additives and preservatives, and other fillers or 'junk'.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So, where should you look? And what are you looking for? Here's a quick overview........&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some of the best puppy food brands can easily be found online. Other good places are good feed stores, and specialty pet stores or even your veterinarian's office. There are one or two excellent puppy foods that can be found at the major Pet superstores, but you need to know exactly which ones they are. (Don't worry, if you follow the link at the bottom of this article, you'll find a list of the best puppy food on the market and which one/s can be found locally)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This may sound like it's a problem, but choosing and ordering puppy and dog food online is actually quick and easy, its' even delivered right to your door. Great news when you have a large breed pup that eats a LOT of food.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now, let's take a look at the ingredients found in the best puppy food choices, so you know which foods to be ordering.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;One of the first two (or three tops) ingredients should be a good source of protein. Real meat, not meat by-products or grain.&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;All natural, human grade or organic ingredients. Your vet will usually do a blood test to check your puppy's    anti-body absorption rate and if needed, your vet will then proceed to inject    some serum from it's mother to speed up the process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb3R0d2VpbGVyLXB1cHBpZXMub3JnL2NhdC0xMTMtYW1lcmljYW5fcm90dHdlaWxlci5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;rottweiler puppies for sale&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb3R0d2VpbGVyLXB1cHBpZXMub3JnL2NhdC0xMTYtZ2VybWFuX3JvdHR3ZWlsZXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;rottweiler puppy&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb3R0d2VpbGVyLXB1cHBpZXMub3JnLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;rottweiler puppies&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="7b17bbb848a2c867950b2f2455d7ceb1">			Most veterinarians will want for you to keep track of when the symptoms first appeared, whether they are getting better or worse, and also whether the symptoms are intermittent, continuous, or increasing in frequency.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Pain&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dogs that are in pain will likely indicate that they are suffering by giving you clues as to where the area of discomfort is. For instance, a dog that has abdominal pain will continually glance toward their belly, bite or lick the area, and will not want to leave his/her bed. The dog may stand hunched over, or take the 'prayer position' which is when a dog gets down on it's forelegs with the hind legs still standing, because of the pain in her abdomen area.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dogs can not tell you that they are hurting or cry real tears but a dog may vocalize their pain in a different way. A dog that is hurt suddenly (such as being stepped on) will cry out or wimper in pain. This also happens when an external injury or internal injury (such as an organ) is touched. Whining or vocalization that is unprovoked may be caused from an internal injury as well. Some breeds of dogs (such as the American Pit Bull Terrier) have a higher pain threshold and need to be watched more closely for signs of pain. Breeds with a high pain tolerance are more likely to endure the pain without vocalization.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another clue to pain is a change in temperament. A dog that is in pain may show signs of aggression. Please take note of this before concluding that a dog has become vicious and let your veterinarian know so that the correct treatment can be administered. Also females in general (even humans!) have days when they are just in a bad mood for no obvious reason. Take note of days of times that these mood swings occur as well as any events that might have triggered them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Other signs that your dog may be sick:&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Ears: discharge, debris, odor, scratching, crusted tips, twitching or shaking.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Eyes: redness, swelling or discharge.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Nose: runny, thickened or colored discharge, crusty.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Coughing, sneezing, vomiting or gagging.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Shortness of breath, irregular breathing or prolonged/heavy panting&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Evidence of parasites in the dog's stool, strange color, blood in the stool, or lack of a bowel movement (constipation).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Loss of appetite or not drinking as much water as normally would.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Weight Loss.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Strange color of urine, small amount of urine, straining, dribbling, or not going as frequently as normal.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Bad odor coming from mouth, ears, or skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Hair loss, wounds, tumors, dander or change of the skin's color.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Biting of the skin, parasites, scratching or licking the skin frequently.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The preceding article was meant to help educate you to the signs and symptoms of probable pain or sickness in your dog. If any of these symptoms occur over a prolonged period of time, please seek the help of a veterinarian. Your vet will usually do a blood test to check your puppy's    anti-body absorption rate and if needed, your vet will then proceed to inject    some serum from it's mother to speed up the process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb3R0d2VpbGVyLXB1cHBpZXMub3JnL2NhdC0xMTMtYW1lcmljYW5fcm90dHdlaWxlci5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;rottweiler puppies for sale&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb3R0d2VpbGVyLXB1cHBpZXMub3JnL2NhdC0xMTYtZ2VybWFuX3JvdHR3ZWlsZXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;rottweiler puppy&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yb3R0d2VpbGVyLXB1cHBpZXMub3JnLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;rottweiler puppies&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>