<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="1b69d50347e0e0693eef6366d95faa95">			Despite this rampant rumors, Disney Vacation Club officials do not confirm the information. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With August 2007, Disney opened a sales center for any timeshare club in this upscale Woodfield Mall, a suburban Chicago retail center. The new mall sales center is called Disney Doorway to Dreams and carries a two bedroom model in the Animal Kingdom suites at Disney World in Holiday to orlando. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is also a more sophisticated, grownup look ahead for the Disney Vacation Club [http: //www. edisneytimeshare. com] brand name. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Look for a major shift in DVC graphics and artwork in 2008. The brand will reportedly move away from its traditional Disney dynamics based pixie dust approach toward a more grownup brand theme emphasizing the worldwide travel opportunities on the market to Club members. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The company graphics shift and repositioning is because, oddly enough, Mickey Mouse hasn't been always considered the preferred approach when it came to time share sales. Tony adamowicz &amp;shy; Diehl, the timeshare Club sales manager, reportedly says that clients cannot always make the bond &amp;shy; between the animated icon and an actual real estate sale and closing. And DVC Vice President Lisa Becket says your club logo, made up of Florida palm trees, ocean waves, mountain peeks, in addition to a Mickey head silhouette, does not tell the complete account. This is a excellent pool to enjoy at dusk. You can relax at the pool and watch the Electrical Water Pageant together with Wishes Fireworks! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are the favorite Disney World Resort pools for a next family vacation. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;If you've been as a result of Disney World in Florida, you have no doubt seen the signs in the parks and resorts, requesting if you've heard Disney's &lt;i&gt;; best kept secret &lt;/i&gt;;. Properly, it isn't much of a secret really. That's the come-on for the Disney Vacation Club, that's Disney's timeshare brand. It sounds intriguing, but there's a chance you're a little leery of attending a timeshare presentation in the Disney resorts if you have ever experienced them elsewhere. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Well, let me assure you, you may relax. Even when it comes to selling timeshares, there is a Disney difference in precisely how things are done. So if you would like to see what some of the Disney Vacation Club resorts look like, go ahead and sign up for your tour. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; What you will probably have on a Disney Vacation Club Tour? &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first thing that's different about that Disney timeshare presentation is that there is little in the way of enticement. They don't consider it wise to get visitors in the tour by offering them cash or freebies. The most you can expect is a fastpass card that can be used immediately. This allows you to jump the lines on some of the most popular attractions at the parks, consequently it's quite useful if you need to head over to Everest or Soarin' after you finish your tour. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The second big difference is that this Disney presentation isn't very time-consuming. Most timeshare presentations anywhere else will often run 1 1/2 to three hours, depending on the sales representative. Nevertheless with DVC, you may set your own speed. If you need to take a lot of time and have lots of questions, that's okay. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215ZGlzbmV5dmFjYXRpb24udXMvZGlzbmV5LXZhY2F0aW9uLWNsdWIvZGlzbmV5LXZhY2F0aW9uLWNsdWItYnV5aW5nLXRpcHMv" target="_blank"&gt;;disney vacation club&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="fba37ed8255f67525affa4f60abd02eb">			edisneytimeshare. com] brand name. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Look for a major shift in DVC graphics and artwork in 2008. The brand will reportedly move away from its traditional Disney personality based pixie dust approach toward a much more grownup brand theme emphasizing the worldwide travel opportunities available to Club members. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The brand graphics shift and repositioning is because, oddly enough, Mickey Mouse hasn't been always considered the preferred approach when it arrived at time share sales. Tony &amp;shy; Diehl, the timeshare Club sales manager, reportedly says that buyers cannot always make the connection &amp;shy; between the animated icon and an actual real estate sale together with closing. And DVC Vice Leader Lisa Becket says the club logo, made in place of Florida palm trees and shrubs, ocean waves, mountain peeks, in addition to a Mickey head silhouette, does not tell the complete story. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The full Disney Vacation Club timeshares story is apparently more large and grand than even the fantastic Mickey Mouse can converse. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;The Disney Old Key West Resort is a favorite destination for many families for a great fun getaway. Located in Lake Buena Vista, Fl, this deluxe villa resort is the perfect place to enjoy the leisure and romance in the Florida Keys. The Resort has a wide range of amenities, activities and entertainment options that are tailored to families and anyone looking for a relaxing and memorable family vacation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 2. Disney Moderate Resorts &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are looking for that once in a childhood dining experience at economical prices, then Disney Moderate Resorts should be your choice. Carribeans Beach Resort, Coronado, Spring Resort etc. belong to that class. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 3. The Disney Deluxe Major resorts &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As soon as Strategic location and super facilities rank high on your priority, the Disney Deluxe Resorts offer you just that. The best of &quot;competitive hotel hospitality&quot; is usually what this place gives you. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 4. Disney Vacation Club &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You don't take a vacation like this every alternate year and therefore want only the best that money can buy. Walt Disney has an option which can be just what you need in Disney Vacation Membership. Animal Kingdom Villas, Beach Club Villas together with Boardwalk Villas are truly a class apart we could that enchanting experience. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 5. Campgrounds &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'Disney's Fort Wilderness resort' is known as Campgrounds and stands up to now another option for you to explore. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You should now grab one of these options and get going. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Back in 1988 I went on a trip to Disney World using my parents and at some time during our vacation people got roped into going on a timeshare presentation at one of the ubiquitous timeshare resorts in the Orlando area. At plenty of time I barely noticed the hard sell and I was supremely disappointed that will my parents didn't read the wonderful potential in timeshares. They decided not to buy and my dreams were smashed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Properly, I'm a few many years older now and having been through the timeshare presentation ringer repetitions, I feel like something of an champion. So last year, on a trip to help Walt Disney World, I elected to go on a tour of considered one of their properties, Saratoga Springs Resort &amp;amp; Spa. In the morning I scheduled my tour, a Disney Vacation Club guide picked me up at Pop Millennium Resort inside WDW and took me off to help Saratoga Springs. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215ZGlzbmV5dmFjYXRpb24udXMvZGlzbmV5LXZhY2F0aW9uLWNsdWIvZGlzbmV5LXZhY2F0aW9uLWNsdWItYnV5aW5nLXRpcHMv" target="_blank"&gt;;disney vacation club&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>