<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="20f2611c614dd4c9aefb57e753df51dc">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9pcC1jYW1lcmEtNC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;IP Camera&lt;/a&gt;; were installed by the Hillsborough County Sheriff's Office a few years ago in parts of north Tampa.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A few years ago, shootings, robberies and drug deals in the north and central parts of Hillsborough County caused the area to gain notoriety as a hub for major crimes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So authorities in District 1, which includes part of Ehrlich Road in Carrollwood, held public meetings with residents to brainstorm crime prevention. Eventually, they came up with a plan modeled after the city of Chicago: Installing 20 cameras in a 2.5-mile radius to watch crimes in progress and dispatch authorities to the scene.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The $1.3 million surveillance system, which was paid for using a federal grant, uses cameras that border Fowler Avenue on the south side, Bearss Avenue on the north side, Nebraska on the western end and Bruce B. Downs on the east. The cameras can zoom into license plates after hit-and-runs or catch drug buys as they occur.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;We had a deputy manning the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9pcC1jYW1lcmEtNC90ZW52aXMvdGVudmlzLXdpcmVsZXNzLXdpZmktaXItbmlnaHQtdmlzaW9uLXNlY3VyaXR5LWlwLWNhbWVyYS1taW5pMzE5dy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Tenvis Mini319W&lt;/a&gt;; camera, and she watched a robbery in progress,&quot; said District 1 Major J.R. Burton, who hopes to install 10 more cameras by year's end. &quot;We directed deputies to the area, and broadcast a photo (of the suspect) to deputies. One deputy knew the guy and arrested him.&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Would you support the sheriff's office installing cameras in the heart of Carrollwood, or do you think it would feel like Big Brother is watching you? Is there a particular area in Carrollwood or Northdale you think &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS90ZW52aXMtaXAzOTF3LXdpcmVsZXNzLXdpZmktaXItbGVkLWlwLW5ldHdvcmstb3V0ZG9vci1jYW1lcmEtd2F0ZXJwcm9vZi1jY3R2LXdlYmNhbS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Tenvis IP391W&lt;/a&gt;; cameras should go? Tell us in the comments.		</conversation>		<conversation id="dd2e1d4d0b7fcaea9d6c44e8475284ed">			Q: Will Microsoft's (MSFT) Surface &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS83LWluY2gtYWlub2wtbm92bzctbWFycy04Z2ItdGFibGV0LXBjLWFuZHJvaWQtNC0wLXdpLWZpLTFnaHotMWdiLWRkcjMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;ainol novo 7 mars&lt;/a&gt;; tablet computer be what finally gets the stock to start moving again?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A: It's ironic that a flat computer, less than a half inch thick, is what some investors hope will be the answer to Microsoft's flat stock.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hopes are high on Microsoft's Surface, a line of ultra thin tablet computers that sport the power of a PC in the slim body of a touch-screen tablet. The computers were announced in mid June, shocking the public, which had no idea these devices were coming.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Surface line of computers will come in two variants: The Surface and Surface Pro. The Surface is a low-cost tablet that runs special touch-optimized apps ranging from e-mail to news readers. The Surface is aimed directly at Apple's iPad tablet computer. Meanwhile the Surface Pro is a full-powered Windows-based computer, which not only runs the touch optimized apps, but can run all Windows-based applications, too.
&lt;br /&gt;;The iPad is finally getting a run for its money. Companies, which have long preferred Windows-based desktop systems due to their flexibility and cost, will have a viable option when it comes to tablets. Executives, for instance, could be issued Surface Tablets giving them not just the ease-of-use interface but also access to corporate systems that run in Windows.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But as important as Surface is to Microsoft, it's just the showcase of more make-or-break trends at the company. The Surface isn't just a way for Microsoft to tap the market for tablet computers. It's also a demonstration of the company's upcoming Windows 8 operating system, which is one of the most essential products to the company's success.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Surface could &quot;set the standard&quot; for what a Windows 8 &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9zbWFsbGVzdC1hazgwMi1hbmRyb2lkLTQtMC1taW5pLXBjLTUxMm1iLTRnYi1hMTAtY29ydGV4LWE4LWdvb2dsZS10di1wbGF5ZXIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;AK802 android mini PC&lt;/a&gt;; tablet should look like and function, according to a report by Philip Winslow of Credit Suisse, who rates Microsoft stock &quot;outperform.&quot; If other makers of Windows-based systems see strong sales of the Surface, they may follow suit in building compelling devices running Windows 8, Winslow says.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So if the Surface stokes interest in Windows 8, than it could be the tablet that gets Microsoft's stock back on the swing higher, he writes. And that's saying something, given how stagnant Microsoft's stock has been for years. Shares of Microsoft have been essentially unchanged since 2001, just after the tech-stock crash. Meanwhile, Apple has made inroads especially with consumers and become the most valuable U.S. company.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But the Surface might reignite competition in the computing industry, Winslow says. &quot;We believe Windows 8 will have a more meaningful position in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9vbmRhLXZpMzAtZWxpdGUtZWRpdGlvbi1hbmRyb2lkLTQtMC10YWJsZXQtcGMtZHVhbC1jYW1lcmEtYTEwLTEtNWdoei0xZ2IuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Onda Vi30 Elite&lt;/a&gt;; tablet than the market appreciates,&quot; Winslow says. &quot;Which we expect to serve as a catalyst for the stock.&quot;		</conversation>		<conversation id="eea841520d1f8afa7b35d801e9dfa542">			Mystore365 Surveillance Pro offers many Security &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9pcC1jYW1lcmEtNC9kYi1wb3dlci5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;DB power ip camera&lt;/a&gt;; Systems in the market at the best prices. Mystore365 Security Surveillance Pro helps homeowners install Security Home Surveillance Cameras. Cameras usually remain maintenance-free for years and can be found easily by their brands. They pride themselves in offering a wide range of &quot;do it yourself&quot; Surveillance and Security products including Video Surveillance Kits, Nanny Cameras, Hidden Cameras, Video Intercom Systems and many more.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All these products enable one to address their security needs quickly and professionally, because the goal of Camera Surveillance is to help protect families and valuables. Mystore365 Surveillance Pro security design professionals will immediately contact the customer to provide assistance at any time.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The spokesperson of Mystore365 Surveillance Pro stated, “It is our goal to make it easy for you to access the products you need and also have access to thousands of other pieces of hardware that can fit any need.”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This company also provides Indoor home &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9zdXJ2ZWlsbGFuY2UtY2FtZXJhL2NjdHYtY2FtZXJhLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;CCTV cameras&lt;/a&gt;; for home or business owners. People mainly consider the outside but they forget that it is also necessary to install them on the inside as well. There indoor security cameras will help to prevent crime and help home or business owners to properly monitor their property at all times.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;About Mystore365 Surveillance Pro
&lt;br /&gt;;Mystore365 Surveillance Pro is owned by industry professionals who have years of experience in Security &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXN0b3JlMzY1LmNvbS9zdXJ2ZWlsbGFuY2UtY2FtZXJhLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Surveillance Cameras&lt;/a&gt;; Systems and now wanted to help everyone protect their property and assets. For over 20 years, the experts at Mystore365 Surveillance Pro have earned the trust and confidence of our valued customers by providing professional assistance and expert technical advice. Get help from fully trained and highly experienced expert in evaluating products, which can be found on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2FMystore365.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://Mystore365.com&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>