<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="d4432457603fbc2dd10fd4facddc459f">			TRUTH is the true and only LIGHT showing the real WAY; reflecting genuine LIFE. Any other light leading in another way, reflecting a strange life is a ruinous trap.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many great and glorious destinies were traped, wasted and buried unutillized and unfulfilled. Still many people are troping enmasse daily and being caught by same fast destructive ancient traps of human Traper.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wisdom of the wise is for his safety. Escape, turn away from false light and its ways. Turn to True LIGHT today for sure freedom and good success here on earth.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why? Because you can't stand in darkness to fight the Darkness.		</conversation>		<conversation id="591e169578887ff9850875680ab5141e">			LOVE: Another such word is LOVE. We may say that this is the key word of Scripture which is prostituted, since we read: ''God is love'' (I John 4:16). The word, agapee, expresses godly love, and in christendom today it has come to be used for a blind, senseless powerless and (essentially) destructive emotionalism.             Brotherly love - reserved in Scripture for those within the personal family and the Church family - is an emotional love based on agapee. Yet agapee itself is a love based on justice, punishment and a type of action toward another that is intelligently (often contrary to the emotions) formulated by what is best for the other person - not on what he may prefer nor on what one's own emotional involvement may cause one to wish to do.            Never forget that it is yet our God of love who is speaking in Matthew 23:1-36 and in Mark 14:18-21. and in Paul's action in Acts 13:9-11 or in Peter's action in Acts 5:1-10, the same God of love is He who sent Israel to exterminate the Canaanites, and who commanded King Saul to kill all men, women and children plus their livestock, of the Amalekites (I Sam. 15:3-33). You do not understand? It is simple. Love has its priorities, and God's priority is His holy people. Those who would destroy God's people must, themselves, be destroyed in order to protect His people (Read: Esther 3:7 to 9:19). Those who would be an example of and, perhaps, a lure into worldlines within the family of God, the Church, must be removed. God only is holy, and there is no holiness within a congregation that does not love God to such an extent that each member seeks constantly to please Him and emulate Him. [Or is this too idealistic?] Note that love is so important to God that His Holy Spirit said: ''Blessed (is) the man who endures trial because, having become approved, he will receive the crown of life which (the Lord) promised to the (ones who) love Him'' (James 1:12). NOT fear Him: NOT obey Him - just LOVE HIM.   It shocks me that, while men get teary-eyed and ga-ga over the thirteenth chapter of First Corinthians, none seems to comprehend that it is probably the most damning chapter in the entire Bible. Think about it! The chapter tells us that NOTHING - not all your goodness (of which Jesus tells us that we have none), not all your prayers, not all your tithing and charity, not all your time given for the Lord and His Church ... none of it will gain one little bit of a share in the Lord's inheritance unless the motive behind it has been love. Not the emotional type pseudo-affection, but agapee: The love that is clear-sighted, intelligent and judgmental, determining what is best for the one loved in every instance; and above all, the love for God that puts Him, His pleasure, and His honor before self or anyone or anything else within this world. In interpretation of God's word, true love must be comprehended, else honest interpretation becomes impossible. Without love, the interpretation really becomes little more than an attempt to justify the unjustifiable actions or teachings of those dear to the one doing the interpretation. And that is just another form of idolatry.		</conversation>		<conversation id="23d4f83dad29b670543f8688420fed39">			COVENANT: One of those prostituted words is Covenant. Today the word is hardly heard in the Churches, yet God works with men through Covenants. To totally emasculate the word, the common banner of christendom today is: I have nothing to do; God does it all for me. Hogwash! God works with men through covenants, legal contracts more binding than any a bank might even formulateg A covenant or contract is an instrument of mutual promise. For every promise God gives, He demands a vow! If you are a Christian, you have a Covenant which has been formed by God, presented in the blood of Jesus Christ and sealed by His resurrection. And to be valid, it must have been signed by you in the precise manner - and we reiterate: the exact, both in the physical and spiritual spheres - manner laid down by the Omnipotent God. If you have not fully satisfied His requirements in the signing and implementing of this contract, then you are still in your sins with no promise from the Lord.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b2b574c4bdf314c4324d7a9b1ea819cf">			UNITY: A third word which has been prostituted to open the door to the tolerance of sin in the Family of God is UNITY. The word unity means oneness; it indicates harmony - a singleness of purpose and action. Jesus depicted His Church as a vine with its branches - and let us not err in thinking that the branches indicated denominations. The branches are plainly shown to be individuals who, as part of Christ's body, reach out to do His work, to bear His fruit (John 15:8). And so we read: ''For as many as were baptized into Christ have put on Christ'' (Gal. 3:27). If we are all parts of Christ's body, there cannot be differences of purpose and action. If there are differences of purpose and action, there may be union; but it cannot be unity. Union is a combination, a coalition, a confederation of independent parts. Therefore, union can never satisfy the Lord's requirements for His Church; for we read that God the Father has ''subjected all (things) under His (Jesus Christ's) feet and gave Him (to be) head over all (things) to the Church'' (Eph. 1:22). Therefore, if the Church is one body with one head, that head controls every part of the body, as is so clearly seen by looking at any incarnate body. Union can be attained in any situation by negotiation and compromise. But even among men and in worldly affairs, negotiation and compromise are only operative when handled by those authorized, it is treason. Listen to what He says to those within His kingdom - and understand, while reading, that His citizens are only those born into His kingdom by His will. Therefore, all within His kingdom must ''Glorify the God and Father of the Lord Jesus Christ with one mouth, with one will'' (Rom. 15:6), for all are to be like-minded (Rom. 15:5), since all are members of one another (Rom. 12:5; Eph. 4:25). None is to be wise in his or her own conceit (Rom. 12:16); all should be compassionate, pitying, courteous, and should love one another as brothers (I Peter 5:5), esteeming other better than self (Rom. 12:10; Phil. 2:2), knowing that Christ, the Sanctifier, and His Church, the sanctified, are ALL ONE (Heb. 2:11). There can be no unity between the faithful one and the concessionaire - the one who barters a watered-down faith in the amusement park of today's society.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>