<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="27237b366dc076001dc78f9cbc97675e">			It's rather a lucrative and beneficial web promotion strategy and what best- it works with regard to both new and effective businesses. Few reasons why SEO should be considered as a major issue for business websites are: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. You can attract highly targeted visitors to a particular service or product page. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;two. Much more visibility and higher credibility. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Brand promotion and goodwill. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. Long term Return on investment and 24*7 online special offers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. An opportunity to remain ahead of customers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. Helps worldwide customers to find you easily. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;8. Brings results from nearby or international market so as to sell everywhere or anywhere world wide. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Knowing about most of the benefits the SEO services can supply, it is easy to decide that SEO is a critical aspect of internet marketing that there is no-one to afford to neglect because it indeed is a serious factor for business sites! &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;After successfully designing and hosting your internet-site, you must drive traffic into it. Failure to do so, all your efforts putting it up would be in vain. You may have designed the best website inside your niche, with the best information or the best sales copy you might ever imagine. But without driving traffic aimed at your website no one will ever know about it thus no an individual will ever visit your site and ultimately you will not ever make money with your internet-site. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your success online largely will depend on how successful you can be in driving targeted traffic to your website(s). It is very important that you use good SEO techniques that can drive targeted traffic to your website. These are some of the good search engine optimization techniques that can drive traffic to site: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Marketing with articles &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Article marketing is among the most good and free methods for driving targeted traffic aimed at your website. It involves writing an article(s) and submitting it to the top article directories. This in return brings you traffic within two ways: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When most people visit these directories that they read your article of course, if your article is relevant to what they need, they click your chek out you website, in my experience this traffic converts perfectly. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the article has a back chek out your site, the back links are one of the criteria the search engine uses to rank your websites. It is important to consider that the search engine loves unique content. Settle down ! articles must be unique and resourceful. Some of the greatest free article directories where you can submit your articles comprise: EzineArticles. com, goarticles. com, webpronews. com, articlesbase. com and many more &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Directory Submission &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Directory Submission allows you bring direct traffic aimed at your website, it also increases backlinks to your site consequently improving your ranking in the search engine. Most with the directories are free to list your site however some requires a small fee for your website to obtain listed. Some of the best free Directories include: dmoz. org, lii. org, hotfrog. com, info-listings. com plus numerous others. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt; Social bookmark creating &lt;/strong&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Social bookmark creating is fast becoming a very good SEO technique. This is because though social bookmarking you will get many free back links aimed at your website and drives free traffic aimed at your website. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Nlby1jb25zdWx0YW50LXNlcnZpY2VzLXVrLmNvLnVrLw__" target="_blank"&gt;seo consultant uk&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>