<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="583b5985516265b8a11d0ebd575a295b">			Your boring PC is a great place to watch free streaming movies. Did you know that? No i didn't either until i found out the ways, the tips and the tricks to start watching Hollywood Blockbusters online.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get watching online and remember that every day more and more streams and websites appear on the internet.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will also need a selection of media players installed on your computer. They are all free to download. You will need Adobe Flash player, Windows Media Player and Apple Quicktime for example and probably already have them installed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most movies are streamed to your computer as you watch. There is also the option of downloading first to watch at your leisure. Most are streamed though and that is why a fast connection is needed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now to get watching the streams just visit one of the hundreds of websites around that have links to the movies and tv shows. One such site is worldtvpc.com that has a big choice of free streaming movies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By looking through the many streaming TV and movie sites online you are able to view latest movies and TV shows as soon as they are released. Please look for different streams if the quality or speed are not good enough.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To find out more just visit &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2V3YXRjaGZyZWVtb3ZpZXNvbmxpbmVub3cuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;watch free movies online now&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Today it is so much easier than ever before to see free streaming movies and television shows from your computer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So is this legal? Well it is a grey area but the websites would be shut down if there was an issue and nobody has ever been jailed for watching online movies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Download now and watch unlimited movies and tv shows online for absolutely free. There are a lot of scam websites online which promise you to watch movies to your computer free of charge. The fact is that a vast majority of them don't work at all.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Others work alright but their movie and TV episodes selection is so old and of poor quality you are better off without them. The trick is in knowing how to tell the good sites from the fake and scam ones.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First things first, if you want to get quality free movie downloads all year round, you need to pay a membership fee to a good site that invests time and money keeping their website clean of viruses and updates their movie files. This is the only way you can get guaranteed highest quality best priced movie downloads online.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;From my experience most of the free movie websites are so full of harmful malware and viruses that your pc will crush in no time. I tried them and regretted dearly when I lost virtually all my important pc records and files.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even the paid membership websites are not all perfect. A majority of them have movies for download alright but the variety and categories are nothing interesting. Only a few of the top movie download sites online get it right and finding them is like finding a yellow colored needle in a haystack.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On the other hand stumbling on the scam download websites is almost guaranteed. Chances are that you can lose money fast online looking for a site. The best websites to watch free movies online will require a membership fee of about $25-$30 per year.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The good ones will ask for this payment once and you can access unlimited downloads for popular TV shows like heroes, one tree hill, prison break and others.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Look out for sites that offer you a money back guarantee in case you want to opt out.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What do you think when you hear the phrase &quot;free movies online&quot;? Is it suspicion of copyright infringement, shadowy looking download sites, or excitement over the tremendous viewing possibilities? While the checkered past of free movies online has some people cautious, let's set the record straight about the right places to watch free movies online.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some of the new players are Crackle, EPIX, Fancast, and SlashControl. Crackle is backed by Sony Pictures and has hundreds of free movies such as Ghostbusters, Godzilla, and St. Elmo's Fire. EPIX is the new movie site from Paramount, MGM, and Lionsgate, and is the perfect place to watch Ironman, Raiders of the Lost Ark, and many more popular movies. Fancast is backed by the cable giant Comcast and has hundreds more movies, such as Chaplin, Captain America, and Naked Gun 2.5.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SlashControl was started by AOL TimeWarner, and has many more movies such as Sparticus, Ronin, and the classic western Hang 'em High. Those sites join the other mainstays of free movies, including Hulu, Veoh, and Joost. Even YouTube has jumped on the bandwagon and legally hosts free movies online, such as classic Shirley Temple films like The Little Princess and Heidi.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Several TV sites also have films online, including American Movie Classics (AMC), Syfy, ABC Family, and TNT. If you have a Netflix subscription, the Watch Instantly feature comes free for the Owner account. Top films to watch online include Wall-E, Bolt, The Nightmare Before Christmas, as well as the extensive list of STARZ play. So, if you are going to watch a movie on a computer, here are a few quick tips:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Turn the screen saver and power save features to longer than the length of the movie.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;2. If watching via an inexpensive wireless router, like the ones AT&amp;amp;T U-Verse hands out for free, make certain the router is well ventilated, as extended viewing could cause some minor over-heating, causing the router to reset, thus causing the movie to take an unexpected intermission.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;3. Otherwise, sit back and enjoy.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>