<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="1c00d5e4be082653d47b4f3f37f08a06">			Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu's wife Sarah has its former maid, Lillian Peretz filed a lawsuit alleging defamation and invasion of privacy. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bralph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;ralph&lt;/a&gt;; lauren&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Sarah Netanyahu filed a suit to a court in Haifa, Israel, and claims 60 million shekels (about $ 158,000). The petition pointed out that Peretz dissemination of information on Sarah's &quot;;insulting and malicious story, Sarah verbal attacks, damage the reputation of Sarah, and Sarah had been to remain silent. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bpolo"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;polo&lt;/a&gt;; ralph lauren&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;In addition, Peretz also a violation of the confidentiality agreement signed by Netanyahu's official residence employed. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Sarah's lawyers said that Sarah has repeatedly tried to stop the dispute, but to no avail. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;h&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3BGHD%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;GHD&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Peretz had in the Netanyahu belongings maid for six years, resigned in September 2008. In January 2010, Peretz filed the lawsuit, said Sarah deduction of their salaries, but also often abused her claims $ 80,000 for this to Sarah. After the news broke, Netanyahu's office denied the statement of Amir Peretz, called pleadings full of &quot;;lies and slander&quot;;, also criticized the media malicious speculation, lack of basic journalistic ethics. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3BLisseur"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Lisseur&lt;/a&gt;; Ghd&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Sarah, aged 51, who is El Al Israel Airlines flight attendants, for Netanyahu, his third wife, now in the children's psychological. Some media reports said, Sarah Netanyahu as Israeli Prime Minister from 1996 to 1999 period will incur a lot of controversy, her high-handed policy, the servants, and set very strict standards for cleanliness of the room, but also public places boast of his children, and interfere with the husband, the conduct of public affairs. However, Sarah Netanyahu in March 2009 re-serving prime minister since kept a low profile stance. The couple has always been a high rate of public support. &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;www.lisseurghdfrance.net&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="82a47c97b0f55176f090650039c6e341">			Afghan President Hamid Karzai Hamid Karzai has publicly expressed support for the religious law allows a husband beat his wife and other restrictions on female behavior. Local human rights organizations, which represents a big step backward in women's rights in Afghanistan.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wb2xvLXJhbHBobGF1cmVucy5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;ralph lauren&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Afghan Islamic scholars (Ulema Council) of the Council recently issued by the behavior of the Act stipulates that women can not travel without a male guardian, and not in public places such as schools, markets, or in the office, contacts with strange men; men beat their wives , of course, the beaten and the Islamic law-related; In addition, the divorced woman is more restrictive.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wb2xvLXJhbHBobGF1cmVucy5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;polo ralph lauren&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;A press conference in Kabul, Karzai publicly expressed support for these decrees, saying that comply with Islamic law, and with reference to the views of women's rights organizations in Afghanistan. Karzai said: &quot;;the Council of Islamic scholars did not impose any restrictions on women, these are all Muslims and Afghans should comply with Islamic law.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wb2xvLXJhbHBobGF1cmVucy5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;British media that Karzai publicly support the fatwa of the restrictions on female behavior may be intended to curry favor with the Taliban, or simply want to get the support of the Council of Islamic scholars of the body can become the government and the rebels negotiations. middleman.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5saXNzZXVyZ2hkZnJhbmNlLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;;GHD&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;However, the feminist who said Karzai's behavior means that the existing or planned to enact the Law on the Protection of the rights of women to become the victim of the peace negotiations.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5saXNzZXVyZ2hkZnJhbmNlLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Lisseur Ghd&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Fata Na Ishaq Gailani (Fatana Ishaq Gailani), the creator of the &quot;;Afghan Women Committee, said she supports negotiations with the Taliban, but Afghan women should not be sacrificed. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5saXNzZXVyZ2hkZnJhbmNlLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.lisseurghdfrance.net&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="cf1cc61c7f54c7d776de0cefc0fdcd41">			University of Pittsburgh on the 8th, local time shooting incident, at least two people were killed and seven injured.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bralph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;ralph&lt;/a&gt;; lauren&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The shooting took place at 8 pm, located at the Institute of Psychiatry of the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center. The authorities said the shooting involving at least nine people, two of whom have been declared dead.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bpolo"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;polo&lt;/a&gt;; ralph lauren&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Pittsburgh Police Initial investigations revealed that the gunman should be one of the deceased, but their identity and motive are unknown. The injured include at least one policeman on duty at the University of Pittsburgh, gunshot wounds to his leg. The police were allegedly wounded the gunman. Police temporarily exclude the gunmen dead, there are other accomplices.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The seven injured in the shootings has been directly to the University of Pittsburgh Medical Center to receive first aid, it is unclear the status of the injured. Once rumors hostage by gunmen hijacked, thus triggered panic in the Pitt campus.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;h&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3BGHD%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;GHD&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The live video display, a number of police cars to the Institute where the building surrounded by a large number of police rushed to the scene to step up its investigation in order to ensure the safety of patients treated in the Institute of Psychiatry. In addition, Pittsburgh is also the scene of a  exploration part of the campus of the university campus is blocked, some people were evacuated under police escort to safety.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3BLisseur"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Lisseur&lt;/a&gt;; Ghd&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;University of Pittsburgh in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, is well-known U.S. universities, is currently being spring break, not many students on campus, but a lot of buildings and facilities are not closed due to holiday.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;www.lisseurghdfrance.net&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;University of Pittsburgh Medical Center has been named the nation's best psychiatric clinic, one of its medical research also top ranked in the nation.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b4081e4eb6907ccce513b427a62c9a55">			Sally France • Kaqisada,, middle-aged women in Afghanistan is a patriarchal society does not allow women alone by car or public appearances, as the only &quot;;Village&quot;;, has 18 times by the Afghan government in recognition of his actions in Afghanistan always seem to &quot;;stand out&quot;;.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bralph"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;ralph&lt;/a&gt;; lauren&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;WASHINGTON middle-aged women Sally France • Kaqisada, was just an ordinary Afghan women. Her 12-year-old married, had given birth to 15 children. But she has some extraordinary: She is Afghanistan's only a woman village head, driving tractors and motorcycles to know, Afghanistan is a not allow women to drive alone or the spotlight of the patriarchal society. She also carried a Kalashnikov rifle, and its actions in Afghanistan and everywhere seems to &quot;;stand out&quot;;.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bpolo"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;polo&lt;/a&gt;; ralph lauren&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Women to drive a motorcycle
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In Afghanistan, a rare
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since the fall of the Taliban regime, Kaqisada committed to improving the lives of villagers. She is particularly to safeguard the rights of women. Kaqisada often drove the motorcycle to go door to door to deal with things in the village. She is only one female village head in Afghanistan. Their village in northern Afghanistan Masalisha Autoliv. For many villagers, in Afghanistan, a female a motorcycle is rare. However, it is the villagers voluntarily elect Sally law for the village head.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bwww.polo-ralphlaurens.net%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;www.polo-ralphlaurens.net&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Kaqisada said: &quot;;People see me in the village access to electricity, built a mosque, always on the side with them, although I do not have any political office; because I helped them, so they elected me as the village head. &quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brave men laugh at
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Women have a very high reputation
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;h&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3BGHD%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;GHD&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Many men do not like a woman when the mayor. Sally law know how to protect themselves physically: &quot;;I just started working, and some men laughed at me, I pushed them, shut them up with force is now no one dare laugh at me and even some The man tried to kill me, thank God I'm alive. &quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3BLisseur"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Lisseur&lt;/a&gt;; Ghd&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;, Kaqisada enjoy a high reputation in the female villagers. In the village, women with men in the mosque to pray. Elsewhere in Afghanistan, women rarely entered the mosque.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt%3Bwww.lisseurghdfrance.net%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lisseurghdfrance.net&quot;;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;www.lisseurghdfrance.net&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Kaqisada said: &quot;;Because the matter of the mosque, we had a lot of trouble and we must be shifts in prayer, the men had prayed, women pull them behind a curtain to pray now, men and women can pray together.&quot;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>