<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="6">		<conversation id="e22575c56172d1993aa0469792d6f1f4">			&lt;strong&gt;;What would you do if you were me?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you fight to thy end so that everyone could see
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you believe in your self and know that your right
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you believe that man can only be defined by sight?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you hurt the people that care for you the most?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you sit back and watch the sun slowly died behind the end of the red coast?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you look in the mirror and remember who you are
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you fight knowing that it would leave a scare?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you trust your word and know it’s true?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you believe the memories of the things you’ve been through?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you listen to the stars and trust in the sight of man?
&lt;br /&gt;;Would you fight for us and leave a promise with the right hand?
&lt;br /&gt;;The answer is key but the eyes can only see
&lt;br /&gt;;So if that is so then why won’t you trust in me?
&lt;br /&gt;;So was the lesson true about this blind society?
&lt;br /&gt;;Answer because I wonder what you would do if you were me&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="748bb83bd5ac4013e571a78b9e1325fb">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;Open in to a true sight 
&lt;br /&gt;;Life it self can’t help a feeling so bright
&lt;br /&gt;;My soul was condemned because my life had been wasted
&lt;br /&gt;;But judgment hadn’t came so my struggle I had to face it
&lt;br /&gt;;But when the mind is caged and the heart can no longer bear
&lt;br /&gt;;We must fight for hope because no one else seems to care
&lt;br /&gt;;I stand upon my roof looking for love in an unmarked area
&lt;br /&gt;;I search for a true heart and maybe I’ll marry her
&lt;br /&gt;;So guide me to the land because I bear the mark
&lt;br /&gt;;And hope lies in a mans soul
&lt;br /&gt;;But purpose lies in a women’s heart		</conversation>		<conversation id="c2dd42005b32cea18902cf85fd2457cf">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;With the hands I was given I must make more of what I have
&lt;br /&gt;;But the fight continues as the devils friends laugh
&lt;br /&gt;;My judgment has been wasted upon the streets of my block
&lt;br /&gt;;I must pick up the peaces as the silence surrounds the clock
&lt;br /&gt;;I guess when I look back on everything it’s sad how many have been lost
&lt;br /&gt;;People take lives without the second thought of cost
&lt;br /&gt;;So there the skies rain pain the cause of living is gone
&lt;br /&gt;;People rage war with them selves and before night came dawn
&lt;br /&gt;;I Open my eyes to realize that all is lost and peace is broken
&lt;br /&gt;;I tell these words to many but the lost think that I’m joken
&lt;br /&gt;;So the prize is lost forever forgotten broken and kicked to the side
&lt;br /&gt;;Our youth are troubled and left lost without an older guide
&lt;br /&gt;;But trust in the true because there are more things out here
&lt;br /&gt;;There are place’s of joy we must experience but the question is do we won’t to be there?
&lt;br /&gt;;People are surprised at the sight of the dead
&lt;br /&gt;;But why be when all this was once said		</conversation>		<conversation id="8acd23711b4966225f3304117a845cc">			&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;If I could do it again I would change the things I did
&lt;br /&gt;;I would change my life around I wouldn’t take a chance on a bid
&lt;br /&gt;;If I could change today and the coming tomorrow I would bring light
&lt;br /&gt;;Lighter days that is because my people still haven’t learn to fight
&lt;br /&gt;;If I could I would but life doesn’t work that way
&lt;br /&gt;;So I fight I fight for just one more day
&lt;br /&gt;;I pray I laugh I fall I get back up
&lt;br /&gt;;But what happens when life seems it’s depending upon luck?
&lt;br /&gt;;So I search I look on for brighter days
&lt;br /&gt;;But pain continues to strike in many different ways
&lt;br /&gt;;So how does life become an endless  task?
&lt;br /&gt;;Is it the words we  have been living life to fast?
&lt;br /&gt;;I question a lot because I can’t find an answer in my mind
&lt;br /&gt;;But I still look on and hopefully in time I’ll find
&lt;br /&gt;;Some how I have fall’n because of my life of sin
&lt;br /&gt;;But some how I just wish only if I could do it all again…		</conversation>		<conversation id="addba309fe1d2412a5bdeb893562050d">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;Straight to the bottom we must fall
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s self cause that has us all
&lt;br /&gt;;I’ve forgotten about the past but own to deal with the future
&lt;br /&gt;;But now I realize that if your homeless people will kick you to the side like a piece of furniture
&lt;br /&gt;;But with that I wonder were our help is hiding
&lt;br /&gt;;But I’m done I’ve left and must keep riding
&lt;br /&gt;;To the skies I must search but still I see pain
&lt;br /&gt;;I see it at home and work oohh some body help stop the rain
&lt;br /&gt;;I turn my back only to regain my sight of true path
&lt;br /&gt;;But it’s hard when I tell people of there pain and they laugh
&lt;br /&gt;;Am I searching for a truth that isn’t really there?
&lt;br /&gt;;Maybe but maybe not or maybe it’s just no one has a care
&lt;br /&gt;;So I’m searching of a place were I can let my dreams fly
&lt;br /&gt;;But who’s going to save us is there anyone when we must cry?		</conversation>		<conversation id="3bc2134aa5c60d038e1468a1a8481411">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;Straight from the bottom I rose
&lt;br /&gt;;I planted my feet upon the ground with a story untold
&lt;br /&gt;;Through the gates I push for difference in the world I live in
&lt;br /&gt;;I push pass the fire the hate and the unforgiving to find a true friend
&lt;br /&gt;;But with a friend came an opening for trouble
&lt;br /&gt;;The pain and the rain had seem to double
&lt;br /&gt;;But the fight could not be won
&lt;br /&gt;;Because that friend felt different so the pain had just begun
&lt;br /&gt;;So through my window I had searched to find a place of hope
&lt;br /&gt;;But troubles came again and it became hard to coop
&lt;br /&gt;;So to my people I through out my arms to find relief
&lt;br /&gt;;But only to see that they had lost hope and belief
&lt;br /&gt;;So what was I to do with my lonely soul
&lt;br /&gt;;I was troubled and had lost my path of goal
&lt;br /&gt;;I had searched for power upon a thousand lands
&lt;br /&gt;;Only to remember it all lied in the power of my hands		</conversation>	</conversations></author>