<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="8414c85123fe3b9484e255ac249cc3a8">			When you were younger you probably looked at the zits and pimples that plagued you and thought &amp;quot;I will do anything to get rid of these spots!&amp;quot;. Many people will try virtually anything to make their acne go away. This would include chemical and synthetic treatments that may or may not have worked. We of course know better now. So when you treat your acne, remember that natural ingredients and acne treatments will help you out the most. Why put your face through so many chemicals and treatments when there are better ways to clear up your acne? Now let's look at a couple of the best natural acne treatments available.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drinking water every day in sufficient quantities is very important. 64 ounces of water is what most doctors recommend that you drink. Drinking plain water, or bottled, will help your skin either way. You can keep your face hydrated by drinking water, and also splashing it on your face - both methods work. Splashing water does two things for your face - it rinses your pours out and shrinks them. It's free to do this! So if you feel like your face is oily, or if you need a little refreshing, bring a spray bottle with you and spray yourself throughout the day. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your skin can benefit from tea tree oil - a natural remedy that really works. This oil has healing properties which can not only dry out existing pimples, but prevent future outbreaks from happening. So before they get started, but using this oil, you can prevent acne from showing up on your face. There is an antibacterial agent in tea tree oil that helps with this. It can really take care of your skin because of the way that it kills bacteria. People use it everyday for this very reason. You can find tea tree oil virtually anywhere. It comes in a variety of sizes and prices, giving you quite a few choices before purchasing the product.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Can you get oily skin from eating oily foods? This is a common myth that many people believe. While this isn't literally true, it is figuratively true. If you don't wash your face (after rubbing the food on your face) then this would be true. Otherwise, it's not. There is the possibility that you could accidentally clog your pores by clogging them from inside your body by eating too many greasy foods each and every day. Junk food is called &amp;quot;junk&amp;quot; food for a reason. Your skin will be healthy and pimple free if you simply healthy natural foods for every meal. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are all sorts of things that you can do to keep your skin clear and healthy. People that fall for generally anything will spend their hard-earned money on harsh chemically-based treatments that may or may not work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many remedies exist that can naturally keep your skin blemish free. For your skin to be clear and clean, natural ingredients should always be utilized. Just look around (on the Internet or at the library) and you should be overwhelmed with all the natural acne remedies that you will never have time to use.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is well known that a huge number of people are affected by &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0anVpY2VycmV2aWV3c2hxLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;Juicer Reviews&lt;/a&gt; and just about everywhere. But just avoid the thought that something is lacking in you if you were caught off guard when this arrived on your doorstep.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Probably the best defense against such situation is paying attention to your thoughts and keeping your eyes wide open. We all know the saying about an ounce of prevention, but still that holds true in very many situations. Have you not ever noticed that about people or even your self? It does seem to be very prevalent in our opinion. Be that as it may, there is never anything wrong with just being informed and taking whatever measures that are necessary or represent common sense.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>