<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a4362ae89839304a36fddf41bcbe43d8">			We do not care why you are interested in [url=]Price Comparison[/url] because regardless of the reason you will be sure to be able to find what you need to know. Truth about it is that is where it all starts with everybody - realizing there is something more to the story.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sure, there is a lot to know on the topic, and we understand if you feel that you do not have the time or confidence to take care of matters, your self. Since we are all different, what you will find are those who like to take matters into their own hands which is our approach, too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However, with that said, do read what we have to offer you here today and then make your own calls and use what you need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We wish you well in your journey of discovery, and that is really what this is in many ways.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bose SoundLink Wireless Mobile Speaker - Nylon lets you share the music you have on your cell phone. It is possible to take this to wherever you go and it can connect wirelessly to your iPhone, tablet, laptop, Android device or Blackberry. After you set up your Bluetooth device with your speakers, you can actually play your music instantly. The speaker can remember up to six different Bluetooth devices and can play music files or stream from services like Pandora or Rhapsody.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Bose Soundlink is a well designed audio speaker system but a bit weighty for portable speakers. The overall sound quality is pretty good though you need to hear it for yourself. The integrated cover both protects the speaker when it's not being used and acts as a stand when you play your tunes. When the cover is closed, the speakers automatically switch off. Feedback have been rather positive and the look of the speakers are quite trendy even though a few found the sound only to be satisfactory.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thing Bose is recognized for is the way their speakers produce bass, and this speaker is not an exception to that. These tiny speaker systems pack a great deal of sound and deep bass. Unless you compare it to other makes, you won't be able to truly tell how bad or good these audio speakers are. If you compare, you could find a brand which is better than Bose. Whether sound is clean or has too much bass is simply a personal taste and cannot be neutral.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It doesn't have a remote control, but that mustn't be a problem, as you can control everything on an iPhone, if that is what you are using. It is also possible to change the song selection, loudness as well as pausing and playing. You can't modify the tone on the speaker itself, instead you control it via your bluetooth device. The speakers also have a mini-plug cable so that you can connect an auxiliary device. In case you have a device that doesn't have bluetooth, you could use the mini-plug cable. You could expect the speaker systems to give you about 3 to 6 hours of battery life.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are searching for this sort of system, the Bose SoundLink Wireless Mobile Speaker - Nylon, could be just what you want. You absolutely should compare other similar systems for cost, and listen for the audio quality. You will probably find a more affordable brand that even sounds a lot better. You should get the system that sounds best for you, instead of somebody else.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additional Links:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2RlbWV0cml1c2RmY29sLmJsb2dzcGFjZS5mci8_" target="_blank"&gt;Take Your Music Along Using Bose SoundLink Wireless Mobile Speaker&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hYm91dHVzLm9yZy9Vc2VyOmVhcmxmZ2RlbGVvbg__" target="_blank"&gt;Bose SoundLink Wireless Mobile Speaker: Take Your Music Everywhere You Go&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VhcmxmZ2RlbGVvbi5zaXRlcnVuLmV1L2luZGV4LnBocD9wZz0xMDg4MjM_" target="_blank"&gt;The Bose SoundLink Wireless Mobile Speaker Will Take Your Music Wherever You Go&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>