<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="76b66712a1049ec7156cb6b1246dbb93">			&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/178941612_2028436_47483642.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2NpYWxzZWN1cml0eWxhd2F0dG9ybmV5LmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Filing for Social Security disability&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;; benefits is one complicated and tedious process to go through. It is true that only 30 percent of disability claimants are approved by the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;Social Security Administration&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; with regards to their claims, while the remaining 70 percent must undergo the appeals process. But this doesn’t mean you are likely to be included on that large percentage of denied applicants. The best thing that you should do is prepare for it as thoroughly as possible.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You start by telling your treating physician or doctor that you are going to file for disability benefits. If he or she is willing to help you go through the process, obtaining medical records from him or her should be easy. Also, your treating physician will be contacted by the SSA for relative information regarding your medical condition, including written statements that will support the notion that your disability deters you to perform a gainful work activity.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Speaking of medical records, it is of great importance that you collect and submit all necessary &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L2Rpc2FiaWxpdHkvcHJvZmVzc2lvbmFscy9ibHVlYm9vay9ldmlkZW50aWFyeS5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;documents&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; that you need to attach or at least provide in your claim. They must include the complete copy of medical records such as history of treatment, laboratory tests and findings, and your doctor’s statements. Also, you must include your employment information. The SSA will look at them and consider your “&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXNhYmlsaXR5c2VjcmV0cy5jb20vcGFnZTEwLTEzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;work credits&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;” to make you eligible for benefits.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once you’ve prepared your claim, you can then apply for disability benefits. You can do it &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L2FwcGx5Zm9yZGlzYWJpbGl0eS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;online&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; through their website. You can also apply over the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L3BnbS9zZXJ2aWNlcy5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;phone&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;. You can also go to the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly9zZWN1cmUuc3NhLmdvdi9hcHBzNnovRk9MTy9mbzAwMS5qc3A_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;nearest SSA office in your home state&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;. Once you’ve submitted your claim, you will be given a set of forms in which you need to fill up. Be sure that you are elaborate with your answers; not doing so may immediately result into a denial.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now that you’ve submitted your claim along with the SSA forms, you are expected to wait for their response between three to six months. After which, you’ll be receiving a letter containing the reasons for their decision.		</conversation>		<conversation id="74b6cc4215185702585968008a28b796">			&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/178941612_12019460_47778676.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You have to go through a long and tedious process when dealing with your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2NpYWxzZWN1cml0eWxhd2F0dG9ybmV5LmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;Social Security disability&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; claim. You may have allotted a lot of your time just to submit and wait for the Social Security Administration’s (SSA) decision regarding your eligibility to receive disability benefits. However, it can be a heartbreaking for if the months of waiting may result to SSA’s decision of denying you of your chance to receive your much-needed benefits.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Like you, it is true that many applicants could get a letter of denial from the SSA. In fact, 60 to 70 percent of initial claimants experience this. Note that this debunks the myth that the SSA denies all initial disability claimants. Nevertheless, you must not lose hope; instead, you must undergo the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L2FwcGVhbHMvaGVhcmluZ19wcm9jZXNzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;appeals process&lt;/a&gt;;. This involves four stages.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Reconsideration stage – In this stage, your denied claim will be submitted again for a reassessment. An SSA representative that does not have anything to do with the initial decision of denying your claim will review it. However, 85 percent of the denied claims that go through this stage will be denied anew.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Disability hearing stage – Hearing is done before an Administrative Law Judge. At this stage, you can hire a disability lawyer that will help you present medical evidence and witnesses that will support your case. The decision by the ALJ is made through a written letter, a copy of which the SSA shall send you.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Social Security Appeals Council – If you are not satisfied with the decision of the ALJ, you can bring your denied case to the Social Security Appeals Council. The role of the Appeals Council is to review the decision of the ALJ thus to see if it was made erroneously. If the ALJ was found to have done so, the Council would most likely award you benefits. They may also return your case to the ALJ for another review.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	If the Appeals Council’s decision still does not satisfy you, you can bring your claim to court by filing a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L2FwcGVhbHMvY291cnRfcHJvY2Vzcy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;federal lawsuit&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="6a02caa184a3fa414eeb8cd239ced0e1">			The whole Social Security process is long and tedious. You are considered lucky if your claim has been approved soon as you expect. However, when your claim has been denied, you have to exert more time and effort in trying to appeal for the SSA’s decision and hopefully have it reversed.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/178941612_10726162_48150721.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before you can submit a claim to your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L2xvY2F0b3I_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;local SSA office&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;, it would be essential for you to know what the Social Security process is all about in the statistical perspective.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	The percentage of disabled in the United States only accounts for 12% of the whole population. Per year, about 2.3 million applications are submitted every year. Out of this number, 69% go to the initial application stage. Only 31% are technically denied because of various reasons: missing medical records, lack of information, lack of work credits and excessive substantial gainful activity.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	The 69% of the initial applications are evaluated by the Disability Determination Services to see if they met certain requirements. Out of 1.6 million of these applications, only 38% are granted monthly benefits, including back pay. About 62%, of the applications, however are denied. Out of almost a million applications denied, only 48% of them undergo the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zc2EuZ292L2FwcGVhbHMv" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;appeals process&lt;/span&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; or 480,000 applicants.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	In the reconsideration stage of the appeals process, 90 percent are denied, while the remaining 10% get approved.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	In the 430,000 applicants (90%) who are denied in the reconsideration stage, only 18% or approximately 80,000 of them continue on with the remaining stages of the appeals process.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Once the more or less 80,000 of them reached the final stage of the appeal, which is a federal court lawsuit, 81% of them are approved, while 19% are denied.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You are most likely to undergo this long process if you do not prepare well enough. As such, one of the ways in which you can prepare for when submitting a claim is hiring the legal services of a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2NpYWxzZWN1cml0eWxhd2F0dG9ybmV5LmNvbS9jYWxpZm9ybmlhLWRpc2FiaWxpdHktYXR0b3JuZXkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;em&gt;;California disability attorney&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>