<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c092c92a0948d170beec996197d2963f">			Point-and-click what you see is what you get (WYSIWYG) programs do all the coding while the user simply indicates what type of design he or she would like.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Commercial sites require websites that are not only attractive to the eye, but easy to navigate, search, and in the case of retailers, to purchase from. Scripts that return error codes or pages that hang customers out to dry spell lost sales to the online merchant. The webmaster is responsible for ensuring every visitor can use the site with ease and find their way to what they need or want without hassle or confusion.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some large online companies like Yahoo!™ provide “virtual storefronts” to online sellers who would like a Web presence without having to hire a webmaster. A virtual storefront is a “prefabricated” storefront that a seller can “step into” and use immediately, also known as a turnkey solution. In this case Yahoo! (or the company providing the storefront) handles all site maintenance and manages the webmasters responsible for keeping the system up and running. The ability to take credit cards, PayPal and other forms of payment are built-in, as are shopping carts and search engines for checking merchant inventory.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Turnkey solutions aside, entrepreneurial webmasters are still very much in demand for those companies that require totally unique websites that ‘wow’ visitors. Major movie studios and various production companies employ webmasters with a true sense of art and magic. Investment companies, real-estate and professional employment hubs each utilize design styles reflective of their products. The mark of an excellent webmaster is that he or she designs a theme that will appeal to visitors of that particular website in both form and function. About 20% of my time is spent maintaining the existing site. New offers are going up all the time, the focus of the site is rethought, improved graphics are created which require changes to multiple parts of the site. Someone needs to have a good idea of where the site is going, and what items fit where.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Because of this, I need to have a h3 grasp, not only of HTML, but how it interacts with the major browsers that we support. I do most of my work with Netscape as my default, and this can turn around and bite me if I make a mistake in the HTML that IE4.0 doesn't like and a Director or VP uses IE4.0. Some of my co-workers are amazed at the number of browsers that I have on my PC — I have Netscape 1.0 through 4.04, IE 4.0, IE 3.0 at another computer, and Netscape 3.0 Gold on my Unix Sparc workstation. Plus, I have easy access to Netscape 3.0 and IE3.0 on a Macintosh, but I usually just ask my co-worker to check those for me.&lt;br /&gt;;Programming&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another 30-50% of my time is spent in project development. I create and maintain CGIs for the site, and so I have to know C programming. Many sites use Perl as their scripting language, but our company chose C because we felt it was more flexible in the long term.&lt;br /&gt;;Development&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My favorite activity in my job is new page/application development. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2ZvcnVtLnJvamFkaXJlY3RhLmVzL21lbWJlci5waHA/MTA1NDExNC1qYXJyZXR0Y2Fycmk5MjM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Webmasters&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53b3JkdHJhdmVscy5jb20vZm9ydW0vYWNjb3VudC5waHA/dT0xNDA2NTc_" target="_blank"&gt;;Webmasters&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>