<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="eb885977069b6ff307af0a6f4f5dbe5d">			People these days have more firearms than ever before. The fact that more crimes are being committed than in the past has caused people to by guns for personal and home protection. Especially the number of violent crimes has steadily risen in the last three decades. But just owning a weapon is not going to keep you safe. You need to know how to use is in an alarming situation.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Luckily there are courses that teach you how to control a dangerous situation with a weapon. But that is only half the story. When the gun is not being used it must be stored safely. There are many cases of children finding improperly stored weapons and accidentally shooting themselves or each other. The proper place for a weapon is a locked safe, not a shoe box in you closet. Here are some quick tips on how to choose a proper gun safe:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Size. There are many sizes of safes available on the market. They range from small boxes to large cabinets. The smallest type only holds a pistol and ammunition. It is the best size for some one who owns a weapon for personal protection. It can be easily stored beside you bed where it is readily available in case it is ever needed. The medium sized safes can also hold important documents and valuables in addition to multiple weapons and ammunition. So if you have jewelry or cash at home, then it is the best choice for your. The largest gun safes are made for larger weapons like rifles and shotguns. They are the best choices for hunter who has multiple weapons.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Lock. There are three types of lock available for safes. There are key locks, combination locks and biometric locks (fingerprint locks). Key locks are best for larger safes with rifles or shotguns. A combination lock would be impractical, because it is not very quick to open and rifle safes are often opened and closed multiple times per day. A biometric lock would just be too expensive for this type of application.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Combination lock is the best for medium sized safes. Since you don't need you valuables every day it does not matter if it takes a little longer to open. A small biometric gun safe is the best choice if you own a gun for personal protection. A fingerprint reader makes the safe easy and quick to open in case of an emergency. There is no need for memorizing a combination which can be easily forgotten in a stressful situation.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I hope this quick guide helps you choose the proper safe for your needs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Click here for more information on how to choose a biometric gun safe		</conversation>	</conversations></author>