<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="bb33653e5a72585b1922fecbba3ec373">			Ice skating has a extended history. In reality the origins of ice skating date back to the early ninth century. The objective then was far far more practical, nevertheless, than recreational. The earliest ice skates are believed to have been located in London and made of horse bone. It is believed that these skates served utilitarian purposes such as movement from place to spot in order to search or scavenge for food rather than the largely recreational purpose that most ice skates have in contemporary society.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54Y3NraXN0b3JlLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;ski equipment packages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ice skating more than the centuries has become far more of a recreational activity and provides lengthy hours of entertainment to each skaters and spectators alike. From figure skating to ice hockey all around the world there is a fondness for this certain activity that transcends time and speaks volumes about both the complexity of this activity and the simplicity of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS9kb25iZXJnMjQvYmxvZy8yMDEyLzA1LzA1L2ljZS1za2F0aW5nLXZpYS10aGUtY2VudHVyaWVzP2ZpcnN0cG9zdD1Z" target="_blank"&gt;ski equipment packages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ice skating is a sport that is both loved and hated by its practitioners. For some the whole sport is ice skating, for others the actual act of skating on ice is basically one particular aspect of a quite complicated and multifaceted activity. And others are merely content material to skate. In and of itself ice skating supplies a substantial challenge for these just understanding and becomes second nature to these who have been undertaking it for long periods of time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54Y3NraXN0b3JlLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;ski equipment packages&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The difficulty of ice skating is considerably like that of roller skating. Once you understand, you by no means really forget. You may possibly have a handful of unsteady moments in the beginning immediately after a extended absence but all in all it comes rushing back once you get out there and try once again. Whether you are an avid skater or just a breathless spectator of the sport, Im positive youve found the dichotomy between the beauty of figure skating and the brutality of ice hockey fascinating. I know I definitely have.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>