<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="73fde418c7766e53f76dc4323f3f1902">			If you search at the time, then, of course not.  In the case of much more than 300 kilometers per hour and also turn, no one looked down at table.  Moreover, all the data I require will be met by the command center directly by the radio to notify me.  Nevertheless, even so, we usually still putting on it.  Some people may be simply because the partnership of the sponsor, and also I desire the other kind of putting on a watch.  Only the RM 009-1 Tourbillon watch the world's only limited edition of 25, as well as creative movement manufactured ??of aluminum-lithium alloy plate.  At the very same time, with ALUSIC the aluminum AS7G silicon carbon made ??the case, the purpose is to create the world's lightest, also resistant to vibration, acceleration as well as deceleration and impact of the tourbillon watches.  I guess a lot of people want to know the speed of 300 km on the ground movement is what it feels like?  Many of my friends asked me this question, I can only say: can not describe.  Tense, exciting, excited, or anything else.  Control in that the speed of the car need to be very focused, so may find it hard to recognize in the end what is the state.  But one thing is sure, If you like speed, it is definitely a cool feeling.  For the F1 campaign, which thing is most important?  Abilities, experience, courage, team .  Everything!  I want to not just F1, whether you want to do what thing, there is usually a lot of circumstances to meet each other in order to achieve.  Of course, these will be in F1, you always take each and every part try to do our best, be possible to have better results, get a bit, and even won the title.  Did not you watch the interesting thing?  For example, your teammates to get it?  I am sure everyone wants it!  After all, there is a great watch with their own name, this is a excellent glory.  You can put on it every day, telling myself to be able to drive a Formula One car how lucky also hope that the following game to do much.  RM007 Massa present for his girlfriend, so far, Richard is presently the Mille only a female form.  Have you imagined about when would send someone one of Richard Mille?  I've done that!  I bought a RM007 gave it to my girlfriend.  The golden piece of the diamond, she really likes!  A racing fascinated of the watchmaking genius and a watch fond of Formula One driver, Richard Mille as well as Mr.  Felipe Massa will naturally turn very excellent friends. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3JpY2hhcmRtaWxsZTEud29yZHByZXNzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Richard Mille RM 026 Tourbillon, replica Richard Mille&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3JpY2hhcmRtaWxsZTEud29yZHByZXNzLmNvbS8yMDEyLzAzLzI5L3JpY2hhcmQtbWlsbGUtcm0tMDI2LXRvdXJiaWxsb24td2F0Y2gv" target="_blank"&gt;;Richard Mille RM 026 Tourbillon, replica Richard Mille&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3JpY2hhcmRtaWxsZTEud29yZHByZXNzLmNvbS8yMDEyLzAzLzIxL3JpY2hhcmQtbWlsbGUtcm0wMjctdG91cmJpbGxvbi8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Richard Mille RM027, Richard Mille Tourbillon&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>