<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="f7b482f646f79ad7f4653909a9cc3ab7">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmicronassociatesredsmith87.blogspot.com%2F2012%2F04%2Fmicron-associates-barcelona-spain.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://micronassociatesredsmith87.blogspot.com/2012/04/micron-associates-barcelona-spain.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sprint Nextel Corporation S +0.36% : Sprint Nextel Corporation S +0.36% and its no-contract brand Boost Mobile have recently been rated highest among full-service and non-contract providers in J.D. Power and Associates’ Wireless Purchase Experience Study, Volume 1. Sprint share prices reached US$2.52 on Thursday, with 13% up. There were 100.51 million stock shares traded, which was 2.3 times more than average volume. Do you want to know when company insiders will buy their shares? Want to add and monitor this company on an on-going basis? It can be done for free by registering below.		</conversation>		<conversation id="83817f8b481a395fe848bfc592f0dce3">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feldrigefinancialreviews.com%2Fcategory%2Fcredit-equity%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://eldrigefinancialreviews.com/category/credit-equity/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ramanathan K, CIO, ING Investment Management India talks about what will drive the market direction in the short term and sectors he is overweight on to an interview with ET.&lt;/em&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you expect the earnings delivery to be in Q4 and the commentary to be for FY13?&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One good thing about the expectations vis-a-vis the IT results is that the expectations are poor. Managements like TCS as well as Infosys have already guided for poor volume growth. We are going into the IT results season with poor expectations, which is actually positive. From an overall perspective, the budgets for FY13 or CY12 in the case of global companies are at best flat. These boards are well for a 13% to 16% earnings growth for next year. Valuations in this space, especially in the large cap are in the range of 15 to 17 times. Valuations are not expensive. If you have issues in terms of global flows because of GAAR provisions, rupee should depreciate further. If there is a selloff, that should again be positive. Overall, we are positive on the space and overweight on the sector.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What happened today with regards to PNGRB and the margins for IGL, is not an isolated case of interference. Does this sour the mood for investments? 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;Yes. The step taken by PNGRB has been very negative for the company and we have seen a significant de-rating as well as expected EPS downgrades for this stock. It is negative and we have had several such cases of orders being implemented which significantly impacts profitability. We have seen the case of ONGC, Coal India where there is no clarity on implementation in terms of how much they have to provide for, if they default on 80% FSA. We have seen the GAAR provisions which are supposed to be retroactively implemented. All these do not give a positive connotation for global investors.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What can the market do in the near term given the volatility?&lt;/strong&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The key issue which is troubling the market is GAAR provisions, its implementation and applicability. We need more clarity which is expected over the next few weeks. If FII P-note holders, private equity hedge fund long only guys are being targeted, that is not going to board well for the market. We need capital flows. We have a huge current account and fiscal deficit. You would have a significant pressure on the rupee if there are no flaws on the capital. And, it is going to be very negative in the markets. Clarification on the GAAR provisions will drive the direction of the markets in the short term.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What does one do with Coal India, BHEL, and GAIL? &lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I cannot talk on specific stocks. Vis-a-vis the oil and gas sector, we are underweight in some of the names which you mentioned. I would not like to paint all companies in the PSU space with a negative brush or a black paint. These are stock specific issues. From an overall perspective, regulatory changes are impacting stock performance as well as profitability negatively. Wherever the risks are perceived to be pretty high, we would surely look to go underweight.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9315004002bb8f4e3415f1c8aa86ed48">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Feldrigefinancialreviews.com%2Fcategory%2Fcurrencies%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://eldrigefinancialreviews.com/category/currencies/&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both Australian and New Zealand dollars fell against their U.S. opposite number and the yen as increased concern that Europe’s sovereign-debt crisis is worsening reduced demand for higher-yielding assets.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aussie undermines against the yen stocks and a commodity drooping amid concern the global economic recovery is faltering for a third day. While the borrowing costs mounted up, New Zealand’s currency f
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Head of the U.S currency sales at Mizuho Financial Group Inc. in New York, Fabian Eliasson said that Europe has been quite a bit worse and Spain has become more focus. Commodity currencies occupy itself to a big fear in the market.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yesterday in New York, Australia’s dollar fell 0.6 percent to $1.0251, a 1.6 percent dropped to 82.70 yen. The New Zealand’s currency, kiwi, destabilized 0.8 percent to 81.49 U.S cents and also dropped 1.8 percent to 65.74 yen.The Standard &amp;amp; Poor’s 500 Index (SPX) also tumbled 1.7 percent, falling for a fifth day in its longest slouch since November. The Thomson Reuters/Jefferies CRB Index (CRY) of raw materials decreased 1.4 percent.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For the 10th year of yielding, Spain climbed more than a 24 basis of points, 0.24 percentage point, to 5.99 percent, noted as the highest level in this year. Last week since the five days ended January 6, they mounted up as much as 40 basis points which confirmed as the biggest surge said by the Prime Minister Mariano Rajo, the nation is in “extreme difficulty,” he added.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Capital&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At a conference in Madrid, Governor of the Bank of Spain, Miguel Angel Fernandez Ordonez said that “Spanish banks may need an additional capital if the economy weakens more than what it was expected”, as he warned the recovery will be slow. According to a report last week, U.S employers added the fewest jobs in March in five months.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The U.S recovery is far from complete, spurring concern the global economic recovery is faltering said by the Federal Reserve Chairman Ben S. Bernake on April 9 at a conference in Stone Mountain, Georgia.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>