<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a9dcf9c0e2cb4144131e06b13058028e">			Initial, the jargon.
&lt;br /&gt;Back link: this is exactly where a web site links to your web site i.e. Site X has a link pointing to your internet site, so your website has a back link from Site X
&lt;br /&gt;One particular-way link: where only web site X links to your website, but your internet site does NOT link to internet site X
&lt;br /&gt;Reciprocal link: exactly where two web sites have swapped links so they both link to every other
&lt;br /&gt;Anchor text: the text/description that is linked with your link on the back link web site.
&lt;br /&gt;Page rank: Google's proprietary technique for assigning a value (from 1-ten where 10 is best) to the combined quantity and the top quality of back links pointing to your site. Typically abbreviated to &quot;;PR&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;Search Engine Results Page (SERP): we use the terms &quot;;SERPs&quot;; to refer to the search engine outcomes page, and the position of a site on it. So if a site has a SERP of three, it indicates for a distinct keyword search it appears on page 3 of the outcomes. Note that some folks use SERP to refer to the position on the page, so that a SERP of three might also mean the site appears at #3 on the first page.
&lt;br /&gt;Check you page rank and backlinks now! Quick and simple Page rank checking at what does it all mean?
&lt;br /&gt;In the online advertising planet, Page Rank signifies a lot. Increasing a website's PR is 1 of the key foci of on the internet marketing.
&lt;br /&gt;The objective is to get as high a PR as attainable for your website. PR is measured by a proprietary algorithm belonging to Google. What Google does is measure the quality of the website linking to your web site. How does it do this? By measuring, amongst other things, that site's PR. There is also evidence that the degree of relatedness of content material is also critical. If you internet site is an e.g. Actual estate web site, then a back link from a site dealing in scuba gear may not be worth considerably to you. But back links from internet sites that have excellent PR and are related to you (e.g. by sector or by region/location) are nicely worth pursuing. By growing the number and quality of links pointing to your web site, over time you will increase your PR.
&lt;br /&gt;Note also that numerous other engines also use back links as part of their SERP algorithm. Some may not be as sophisticated as Google, but numerous measure the number of back links in their index and use this as element of how they rank your website under a particular search.
&lt;br /&gt;You can check your back links and page rank at how do I increase my Page Rank?
&lt;br /&gt;Firstly, make positive your website has good high quality content. Make other sites and their owners want to link to you. Then get out on the web and start off making propositions to other internet site owners in related fields.
&lt;br /&gt;Ideally, you will get links from internet sites that have a larger Page Rank than yours, but this isn't always attainable. What you should appear for are internet sites that:
&lt;br /&gt;Have excellent content
&lt;br /&gt;Are relevant or connected to your website
&lt;br /&gt;Have some Page Rank currently (i.e. not brand new)
&lt;br /&gt;Also, older domains may possibly do greater than newer domains
&lt;br /&gt;Some of the do nots.
&lt;br /&gt;Be wary of FFA (Free of charge For All) sites frequently these do you no very good and can in fact do you harm as they tend to be viewed as spam internet sites by some engines.
&lt;br /&gt;Don't &quot;;spam&quot;; your anchor text make it related and do not overload it with keywords or repetitions.
&lt;br /&gt;Vary your anchor text. Use different variations or re-writes of anchor text on diverse websites.
&lt;br /&gt;Make positive the page where your link will be placed has been indexed by the search engines. If it has not been indexed (or can not be for whatever cause) then you won't get any advantage from it.
&lt;br /&gt;Make sure that the pages you place links on have limits to the quantity of links listed. Single figures are ideal, but not always feasible. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5saW5rZW1wZXJvci5jb20vaGlnaC1wci1iYWNrbGlua3M_" target="_blank"&gt;quality backlinks&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>