<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7bcfa784c79d9cf765268d59ae9e8054">			 &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;; - &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Level&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;• Fitness  level in 3 minutes
&lt;br /&gt;; • Comparison  with national Olympic team results
&lt;br /&gt;; • Includes  Target Heart Rate calculation
&lt;br /&gt;; • Personal  recommendation on fitness improvement
&lt;br /&gt;; • Designed  for beginners and well-trained athletes
&lt;br /&gt;; • Helps  optimize your fitness program for best results
&lt;br /&gt;; Using &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness test&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Prepare for the test.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness  Test&lt;/a&gt;;provides simple-to-follow instructions to get started  including visuals. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;;plug-in  USB pulse wave sensors, attach the ear-clip to your earlobe or a finger, sit  down and relax.
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;;once  you’re ready click the “Start” button for recording. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness  Test&lt;/a&gt;;device will be turned into recording state to monitor and  transmit the data to your computer.
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;;you  will be asked to sit comfortable watching beautiful landscapes and listening  relaxing music for 1 minute, than prompted to stand up and continue standing  for the next 2 minutes. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;;tool  will monitor, analyze your body's reaction on that and give you a fitness  report at the end.
&lt;br /&gt;;Your Age Fitness. This parameter reflects your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;; compared to the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness  level&lt;/a&gt;; of healthy individuals of your age group. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness  Test&lt;/a&gt;; it shows how good you are for your age.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness level&lt;/a&gt;;. This parameter reflects your current &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;; on the worldwide scale. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;; it is verbal-numeric: you get the verbal value (Depleted - Very Poor - Poor  -Fair - Good - Very Good - Excellent) as well as its numeric representation:  0.0-7.0. Given this value and result interpretations you can see how fit you  are, set up goals to achieve the excellent value. Note: to have the  correct &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness  level&lt;/a&gt;; value you must avoid having certain conditions (see program  screens for details) before monitoring. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;; -  however, if the required conditions are not met the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;; parameter can be interpreted as a level of current fitness power: higher before  the training and lower after it. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;; professional athletes use this parameter before the championship to determine  their readiness.
&lt;br /&gt;;Progress since Last Test. This parameter shows the progress you've made since the last time you've  performed the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness  Test&lt;/a&gt;;. Use this parameter to track the short-term effectiveness of your  fitness program.
&lt;br /&gt;;Last 6 months progress. This  parameter shows the progress you've made in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness  level&lt;/a&gt;; during the last 6 months. Use this parameter to track the  long-term effectiveness of your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;; program.
&lt;br /&gt;; Average &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;;. This parameter shows your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;; averaged in last 3 months.
&lt;br /&gt;;Best &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;;. This parameter shows your best &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness level&lt;/a&gt;; since the very first &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;; performed by you in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Fitness Test&lt;/a&gt;;.  You can beat your personal record at any time!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; throughout  history, different teachers have taught about the wellness of body and spirit. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; in the time of ancient Greece two  societies have fought over which one was important. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; one who believed that the body was  more important was the Spartans who lived in Sparta and the ones who believed  that the mind was more important were the Athenians who lived in Athens. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; you may be wondering why I equated  the mind and the soul together and the answer is that because Athenians looked  at the spirit as the one which controlled every thought that comes through our  minds. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; every thought we think about came  from the spirit, even our memories. Because of this difference of views they  have developed into societies which specialized in different things. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; sparta developed into a warrior  society and Athens became the center of learning and knowledge during their  time.
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; during the time of the discovery of  the existence of the difference of the Eastern and Western medicine this was  also the case. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; eastern medicine focused on the  person’s well being through the mind and spirit. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; specific culture of the east that  concentrated on spirituality are the Chinese who believed that many of their  sicknesses come from the disruption on the flow of energy of the body which they  called “ki” and the treatment of such sicknesses were natural herbs and  different other methods now described in contemporary times as “alternative  medicine. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; western medicine on the other hand  concentrated on the material element of human health. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; used science to explain and diagnose  sicknesses through the different discoveries of how things worked. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; body being an object that followed  the laws of reason therefore reason is used to know exactly what is wrong with  a person. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; treatments have changed over the  centuries, and during these contemporary times, the usual treatment is medicine  which target specific sicknesses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; for the most part of our history,  western medicine has dominated the medical scene. The eastern medicine were  labeled to be “unreasonable”, “not logical” and in some instances called by  some as “crazy” and “useless”. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; was believed by many throughout the  earth until a new trend in the physical fitness has begun. The numbers of  people who believe that western medicine is no longer the sole answer to the  problems of health are increasing dramatically. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; are beginning to believe, and with  good reason to, that there must be something deeper and indeed more important  than just our material world.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; in this age a new proposal has come  up. This proposal is starting to take the world by storm because of the effects  it has on people. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; a rising number of people testify and  agree to its validity and effectiveness that it is no longer seen as fiction. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; this proposal is the marriage  between eastern and western medicine. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; marriage of the matter and the  spirit or the view that fitness is no longer the exclusive interaction of the  body with its material environment but the interaction of the mind, body,  spirit and our environment.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; is now a belief that we as human  beings are composed of different things and these different things are also  affected differently and manifests in our bodies. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; mind affects the spirit and the  spirit affects the body. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; health of the body then affects the  workings of the mind and we come into complete circle. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; human wellness is no longer seen as  simple interaction of one part of our being but the combination of all the  things that has been said to make us human. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; in this view, an important connection  is made. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhyZXZpc2VyLmNvbS9jb250ZW50L2ZpdG5lc3MtdGVzdA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Physical fitness test&lt;/a&gt;; wellness is not just taking care of  the body but also taking care of the mind that is said to be the manifestation  of our spirit.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>