<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="17f7a95f30256bfdaf905e1dfa8614d9">			10April 2012 – SpringhillCare – SlideShare - People are relying on mortgage in order to buy their own house. Investing in a house is considered to be the biggest financial commitment one can ever make. Therefore, it will be beneficial for the consumer if you could choose your own mortgage term. Before you apply for a mortgage loan make sure that you take help of a loan mortgage calculator to calculate your monthly payment. This will help you determine the mortgage loan that you can afford to take out.
&lt;br /&gt;When a borrower chooses his own term mortgage then it will be easier for him to pay off the owed amount without a single default
&lt;br /&gt;Quicken loan offers “YOURmortgage” where the consumers will determine the length of the mortgage where you can choose the term between 8 to 30 years.
&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, if you are not keen to apply for a standard 30 or 15-year term then refinancing your mortgage into an 18-year fixed or a 24-year fixed loan can be beneficial for you. If your loan term is short then interest rate will be comparatively lower, thereby you can save considerable amount of money.
&lt;br /&gt; If you take out 15 years fixed term mortgage then the interest rate will be lower than 30 years fixed term mortgage. So you can save considerable amount of money with a shorter term as less interest will be paid over a shorter amount of time. In shorter term mortgage you pay less as the loan amortizes faster. But remember that the monthly mortgage will be higher if your loan term is shorter. So this is considered to be a drawback of this mortgage program.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reason behind choosing your own mortgage term:
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can choose your own mortgage term in accordance with your budget. This will help you avoid burning a hole in your pocket while paying back the owed amount.
&lt;br /&gt;You can set your mortgage term according to age you plan to retire. Therefore, before your retirement you’ll be able to pay back the mortgage loan and avoid default.
&lt;br /&gt;You can choose a mortgage term and then plan your budget accordingly so that you can pay off the mortgage within a stipulated time.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are not interested to reset your mortgage then choose to refinance it by choosing a term that keeps the collective term at the standard 30 years. Therefore, if your present mortgage is for seven years then refinancing can extend the term to a 23-year fixed.
&lt;br /&gt;Therefore, choosing your own term mortgage can help you determine your own payment schedule. You can make larger payment if you want to pay off your mortgage loan quickly.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b952fac24c40abe9893aea239f101125">			10April 2012 - Springhill Care Group News - view articles at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fnews.springhillcaregroup.net%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://news.springhillcaregroup.net/&lt;/a&gt; - A 7.1-magnitude quake has struck Central Chile on Sunday night, the longest and strongest one yet since an earthquake happened in the same area in 2010. Although they are reports of injured from the falling ceiling of a church, there were no major damage or casualty.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;According to the US Geological Survey, the earthquake struck at around 7.30 pm (local time) at a depth of 22 miles, lasting for a minute.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It was estimated by Springhill Care Group that the earthquake’s epicenter was in Maule, 27 kilometers NW of Talca and around 220 kilometers SW of Santiago, the nation’s capital with 17.2 million residents.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They had a total collapse of telephone and mobile lines as buildings in the country’s capital swayed. People on a 480-mile radius of Chile’s central coast are warned to evacuate to higher ground.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Residents of Constitucion were especially alarmed because their downtown region was where a terrible tsunami happened in 2010.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chile’s oceanographic and hydrographic services along with the national emergency units called off the tsunami warning to be issued for most of the coastal areas following an assessment that the earthquake is unlikely to trigger huge waves.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The alert they issued was restored for the region’s most close to the epicenter after authorities noticed the waters have retreated 130 feet from the shore in Duao and Iloca. They are well aware that a sharp out surge of surf can bring a tsunami.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lots of residents living in the coastal regions kept away from the shore as they have recalled how the government told them during the 2010 earthquake that there will be no tsunami, moments before huge waves actually struck, leaving 156 dead.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Springhill Care Group has retracted a preventive measure of evacuation order before midnight following the order to evacuate 7,000 people in the coastal areas due to fears of tsunami (although no formal tsunami alert was given).
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fortunately, there are no known fatalities except from one who died of heart attack. And according to their President, Sebastian Pinera, the nation’s infrastructures have resisted the effects of the earthquake as well.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>