<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="217b91404b50f9c6a401a173fc944211">			Don't you wish that all marriages were guaranteed to be great? I've heard many of my clients state that, &quot;If I have to work at it, then it's not the right relationship.&quot; This is not a true statement, any more than it's true that you don't have to work at good physical health through exercise, eating well, and stress reduction.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is funny, but what I have noticed in all my years of marriage counseling is that as long as both spouses are equally committed to repairing a relationship, no marriage is to far damaged.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;KNOWING THAT YOU ARE BEING DILIGENT 
&lt;br /&gt;; A successful relationship must start with you.  You are the only one that you have control over. So you must decide that you are the one who will take control of your actions and reactions in the relationship. One must realize that your spouse is not responsible for your happiness but you are responsible for your happiness and well-being.  Therefore only you can make yourself happy. One must try and learn how to accept themselves as they are.  It is the only way to accept others as they are. I have seen it over and over that a self-critical person will never be able to feel true joy even though their partner tries hard to make them happy.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;COMPASSION IS VITAL FOR A MARRIAGE
&lt;br /&gt;;Truly being able to empathize with your mate is a valuable trait. This is the essence of a truly spiritual life. We all yearn to be treated lovingly with kindness, compassion, understanding, and acceptance. Everyone must understand that this kind of acceptance must start with us accepting ourselves before we can pass it on to other people. You marriage will bloom when both spouses take the time to accept themselves and the other person. No one can make another person act a certain way, but starting the process of kindness normally brings similar reactions. If you find yourself with a frustrated, critical, and irritated spouse - you must not focus on their unkindness but rather focus on your actions and reactions and make sure that you are not adding to the problem by just adding fuel to the fire. Kindness to others does not mean sacrificing yourself. Always remember that taking responsibility for yourself rather than blaming others is the most important thing you can do.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is definitely fascinating is that most of us look at great &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;&gt;;love&lt;/a&gt;; quotes&lt;/a&gt;; and most people all believe that bond was intended for us.  But that bond we examine inside the &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;&gt;;love&lt;/a&gt;; quotes for him&lt;/a&gt;; and her is without a doubt love that's been subjected to testing by time and has remained.  So the quotes about love is a target to be attained, not necessarily merely a common reality.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LISTENING AND LETTING GO
&lt;br /&gt;;Conflict will always be a part of a relationship.  So when it occurs we have the choice of how to handle it.  We can either learn from it or we can keep on having the same argument over and over again. We've all learning many overt and subtle ways of trying to control others into behaving the way we want: anger, blame, judgment, niceness, compliance, care-taking, resistance, withdrawal of love, explaining, teaching, defending, lying, denying, and so on. All the ways we try to control create even more conflict. Remembering to learn instead of control is a vital part of improving your relationship.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The funny thing is that we keep our guards up because we think that we will be cast aside if we reveal our real selves or that we will get lost in the other person if we truly just let go. When these fears get activated, most people immediately protect themselves against these fears with their controlling behavior. One must learn to let go of their control and fears and really relax into a loving and caring relationship. So in this we must learn to learn from our fights and not get hung up in our old patterns of thinking and doing.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f7dd79813fd229fc34e5e9436647dd63">			The key to a successful marriage is hard to find. Some think that it is impossible to find. The thing to be considered is that a successful and happy relationship is not that hard to find.  It is build through the simple things in life.  But we can easily loose sight of those simple things. So come with us as we look at what it takes to make your relationship one that will endure through the ages.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Without quality time together, your relationship will not survive. Aim to devote at least half an hour a night, and at least one day a month when the two of you spend time exclusively together. Each person in the couple should feel like they are heard and listened to as you begin to engage in meaningful conversation together.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. The great thing about a married sex life is that is can remain vital thorough your long marriage. Find ways to spice up the bedroom so that it will be a source of joy and fulfillment. Many times one partner needs more sexual experiences than the other. Why not experiment with new ideas in the bedroom. Role-play, dressing up, or maybe take your sex life out of the bedroom and try new places. The introduction of marital aids into the relationship can also help to spice things up. Do not push your spouse out of their comfort zone.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Learn the fine balance of interdependence in your life. Tell your partner how much you need them, but don't get to dependent on them and cling to them all the time, as that can make your partner feel trapped. On the flip side of this, don't allow your partner to think you don't need them, by going or doing things without them. A good marriage will know the difference between imbalance and balance in these areas.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Sex and money, the two classic arguments with money topping the charts. Any good partnership will have its agreements, that is why a marriage should have a good budget in place. A spending plan allows you both to have a say in how the money will be spent. Without a budget someone normally becomes the financial dictator - with both people feeling unhappy. The budget will be that person for you. A good spending plan should take each others needs into account.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Learn to argue well. It is important to say only things that you would want repeated back to you. Just remember, the one good thing they say about arguing, is the making up afterwards. The word divorce should be stricken from the record. It should be stricken from your vocabulary.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The fact remains, that whether you're dating or married, relationships are hard. Each of you must be willing to give it your all for it to work. Yet millions of happy couples will tell you that it is more than possible for you to find happiness if you want it. But that is not to say that perfection will be yours at the drop of a hat, it does take a lot of work. And remember it's the little things that you sometimes do that can go a long way to making your relationship work.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take into account that the &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;&gt;;love&lt;/a&gt;; quotes&lt;/a&gt;; which we all browse through really should be a motivation but not an indictment.  All of us would like a love in which will last like we learn about in the &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bquotes"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;&gt;;quotes&lt;/a&gt;; about love&lt;/a&gt;;.  Yet that romance is certainly one that's obtained and not just handed down to people.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>