<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b4933bcd1110cf1c239b19a191abb83">			Often, if your comfort food is a sugary food or some other junk food, this is very true. Other times, however, comfort foods can be totally nourishing and it's good for you to consume them. There are a number of foods that, when you consume them, could better your mood. When you are feeling a little down and need an emotional boost, test out a few of these.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eggs, you might be surprised to discover, are great at combating depression. Just see to it that you don't toss out the yolk. The yolk is the part of the egg that is the most important in terms of helping you cheer up. Eggs, specifically the egg yolks, are loaded with B vitamins. B vitamins can be great for boosting your mood. This is because they help your neural transmitters--the parts of your brain that control your mood--function better. Try consuming a couple of eggs to cheer up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Put together some trail mix of nuts or seeds. Peanuts, cashews, sunflower seeds, almonds, pumpkin seeds, etc are all terrific for helping to raise your mood. This is because these nuts are rich in magnesium, which helps to boost serotonin production. Serotonin is the &quot;;feel good&quot;; natural substance that dictates to your brain how you feel day in and day out. The higher your serotonin levels, the happier you will feel. Not just that, nuts, specifically, are a fantastic source of protein.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cold water fish are wonderful for eating if you want to combat depression. Herring, trout, tuna, wild salmon, and mackerel are all high in omega-3 fatty acids and DHA. Omega-3 fatty acids and DHA are two things that improve the quality and the function of your brain's gray matter. We are offering you solid pieces of advice here, but do be aware that some are more important to understanding &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29kcmVhZHMuY29tL2V2ZW50L3Nob3cvMjA3MDY1LXNldmVub2Frcy1yZXN0YXVyYW50cy10dXJuLXRvLWZvb2QtdG8taW1wcm92ZS15b3VyLW1vb2Q_" target="_blank"&gt;Sevenoaks Restaurants - Foods That Make You Happy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Jlc3RhdXJhbnRzZXZlbm9ha3MxMS5ibG9nLmNvbS8yMDExLzEwLzIyL3NldmVub2Frcy1yZXN0YXVyYW50cy1ob3ctdG8taW1wcm92ZS15b3VyLW1vb2Qtd2l0aC1mb29kLw__" target="_blank"&gt;Sevenoaks Restaurants - Discover How to Boost Your Mood with Food&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aWtpLmNvbS9lbi9hbGktYnJlbm5hbi03KzQzNDc1NS9wb3N0L1NldmVub2Frcy1SZXN0YXVyYW50cy0tLUZvb2RzLVRoYXQtQ2FuLU1ha2UtWW91LUhhcHB5KzEzMDk1MDYy" target="_blank"&gt;Sevenoaks Restaurants - Information on How to Boost Your Mood with Food&lt;/a&gt;. But in the end you are the only individual who can correctly make that call. Of course there is rather a lot more to be learned. Yet have more big pieces of the total picture to offer to you, though. We believe you will find them highly relevant to your overall goals, plus there is even more. It's the truth: consuming tuna fish sandwiches can truly help you battle your depression.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Grains can be wonderful for fighting a bad mood. Teff, barley, millet, quinoa, etc are all excellent for helping you feel better. These foods can help you feel full for longer as well, which is a mood improver. Feeling hungry can be a real downer! These grains can improve your mood as it's not at all hard for your body to digest them. These foods are easier to digest than others which helps promote a rise in your blood glucose which in turn takes your mood to a happier place.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Green tea is really excellent for your mood. You were just waiting to read that here, weren't you? Green tea is rich in a certain amino acid called L-theanine. Research has found that this amino acid promotes the production of brain waves. This helps better your mental sharpness while having a relaxing effect on the rest of your body. You likely already knew how easy it is to be healthy when you drink green tea.		</conversation>		<conversation id="c0213dfe21b360a51976830f1307b7b2">			&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.restaurantskent.co.uk%2Fimages%2Fbanner2.gif%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.restaurantskent.co.uk/images/banner2.gif&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; alt=&quot;;Sevenoaks Restaurants&quot;; align=right width=30% height=30%&gt;Many of us think that comfort foods are bad for us and that we should stay away from them. Often, if your comfort food is basically candy or other junk foods, this can be true. Other times, however, comfort foods can be totally nourishing and it's good for you to consume them. There are some foods that really can boost your moods when you consume them. When you feel a little down and need an emotional boost, test out a few of these.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Eggs, believe it or not, are wonderful for helping you fight depression. Just be sure that you don't throw away the yolk. Whenever you wish to cheer yourself up, the yolk is the most crucial part of the egg. Eggs, the egg yolk especially, are rich in B vitamins. B vitamins can actually help you improve your mood. This is because they help in bettering the function of your neural transmitters, the parts of your brain that dictate your mood. Try eating an egg and cheer up!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Make a trail mix out of seeds and/or nuts. Almonds, cashews, peanuts, pumpkin seeds, sunflower seeds, and so on are all great for elevating your mood. This is because seeds and nuts have a lot of magnesium which raises your brain's serotonin levels. Serotonin is referred to as the &quot;;feel good&quot;; chemical substance and it tells your brain how you should be feeling day in and day out. The more serotonin you have, the happier you are going to feel. Nuts, along with raising your mood, can be a superb source of protein.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cold water fish are excellent if you are wanting to feel happier. Cold water fish including tuna, trout and wild salmon are chock full of DHA and omega-3 fats. These are two substances that boost the quality and function of the grey matter in your brain. As we have just stated, [url=]Sevenoaks Restaurants - Try Using Food to Elevate Your Mood[/url], &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FydHVyb3Q2OTc4aG9vZDExMTQud2Vicy5jb20vYXBwcy9ibG9nL3Nob3cvOTcxNDY1My1zZXZlbm9ha3MtcmVzdGF1cmFudHMtdHVybi10by1mb29kLXRvLWltcHJvdmUteW91ci1tb29k" target="_blank"&gt;Sevenoaks Restaurants - Foods That Can Make You Happy&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NhbXB1c2J1Zy5jb20vYmxvZ3Mvdmlldy5waHA/aWQ9NjE0MjM_" target="_blank"&gt;Sevenoaks Restaurants - Foods That Make You Happy&lt;/a&gt; is something that cannot be ignored - or at least should never be ignored. No one really can adequately address all the different circumstances that could arise with this particular topic. That is really a lot when you think about it, so just the briefest instant to mention something. After all we have read, this is timely and powerful information that should be considered. As usual, we typically save the very finest for last. It's true: consuming a tuna fish sandwich can seriously raise your mood.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It's not hard to overcome your bad mood when you are eating grains. Barley, millet, quinoa, etc are excellent at helping you feel better. They fill you up better and that can help improve your moods as well. Feeling starved can be awful! The reason these grains are so good for your mood is that they are easy for your stomach to digest. You digest them more quickly than other things which can help promote your blood sugar levels, which, in turn, helps make you feel happier, mood wise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your mood can actually be helped by green tea. You just knew it had to be mentioned in this article, right? Green tea has a lot of an amino acid known as L-theanine. Studies have found that this amino acid basically induces brain waves.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>