<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ee9d389abedab1936c3de23a337b87cf">			For those ninety years perhaps, Citizen has led the way in which with their traditional and innovative watches. Citizen watches simply symbolize high quality and precision and affordability for typical people. But beyond that, the Citizen See Company has generally set their goals and objectives to stay prior to the curve with their groundbreaking technologies as well as their &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcitizenecodrive.org%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://citizenecodrive.org/&lt;/a&gt;; worldwide recognized brand.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Founded on 1918, the name Citizen was born from the founder's idea that whichever country or where someone got their start in, it would resonate while in the heart of all persons. From there, the corporate name of Person Watch Company was basically formed and the revolutionary and technologically advanced Citizen running watches began the triumphant journey we've seen for almost a hundred years.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Speaking of engineering, beyond expanding around the world and positioning itself as being the largest watch manufacturer on this planet every year to your past 25 a long time, Citizens is typically the king of &quot;;firsts&quot;; with the watchmaking industry. Citizens first possibly pocket watch was created and sold in 1924. A Japanese Homeowner manufacturer developed the 1st shock resistant watch in 1956. And even in 1959, Japan's first water-resistant watch was given birth to.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Citizen also created the thinnest LCD watch the planet had seen, the first voice recognition view, and the 1st professional diving enjoy which even had and electronic sensor to gauge water height. And then Resident went green in the world. The Eco-Drive Person watch collection leads the world with &quot;;ecologically responsible&quot;; timepieces that can be simply powered from light. They are usually literally continuously charged up again by both man-made light and all natural sunlight, so create need to switch the custom lithium-ion power supply. Innovation is the business and his or her history.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Signature Bunch of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democratandchronicle.com%2Fapps%2Fpbcs.dll%2Fsection%3Fcategory%3DPluckPersona%26amp%3BU%3D2d2bf515a93c4a4898a4bb4a44126ca8%26amp%3BplckPersonaPage%3DBlogViewPost%26amp%3BplckUserId%3D2d2bf515a93c4a4898a4bb4a44126ca8%26amp%3BplckPostId%3DBlog%253a2d2bf515a93c4a4898a4bb4a44126ca8Post%253a3ddd8d9d-75bf-49b2-8d7e-9a31fe63b473%26amp%3BplckBlogItemsPerPage%3D5"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.democratandchronicle.com/apps/pbcs.dll/section?category=PluckPersona&amp;U=2d2bf515a93c4a4898a4bb4a44126ca8&amp;plckPersonaPage=BlogViewPost&amp;plckUserId=2d2bf515a93c4a4898a4bb4a44126ca8&amp;plckPostId=Blog%3a2d2bf515a93c4a4898a4bb4a44126ca8Post%3a3ddd8d9d-75bf-49b2-8d7e-9a31fe63b473&amp;plckBlogItemsPerPage=5&lt;/a&gt;; are consists of many different models for both men and women. There are 5 the latest models of of the Lavish Complication watches, 9 types of the Flyback Chronograph and even 9 models in the Perpetual Calendar set, all of which can be watches for adult men. As far as watches for ladies, the Octavia Gemstone Series has 4 models as well as Quattro Diamond Selection is represented clearly with 9 different types. None of typically the Octavia Diamond Line watches are water-resistant, but all the rest of the Signature Collection is water-resistant as many as 100 meters, with the exception of 5 of the actual Perpetual Calendar products, which resist fluids in depths about 300 meters.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And precisely what is so amazing, being the largest  watchmaker globally for the over quarter century is right now only approximately 40 p . c of Citizens total business worldwide. Clocks and jewelry commonly are not a stretch for many people to believe, they also dabble in healthcare products and picture frames for eyeglasses. The simplest way is that pertaining to diversity? I believe they will work with any adventure they choose.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>