<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="6">		<conversation id="d66ffc357b5b6a13f7a4019a9150433b">			Most times pple tend to misinterpret situations,flirting as being in love and of course online dating,dz it ever work?Lets not be misled,ladies especially cz we fall 4 these things everyday only to b hurt sooner than anticipated.		</conversation>		<conversation id="c1f11cd9a5f30e745d5bb55916d47c76">			Dear heart,
&lt;br /&gt;;Stop hoping,he doesn't love you.		</conversation>		<conversation id="afda0820ec631489f2b4afb302d68b5">			Real love or True love cn b found it all depends on where u looked.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2706cc78fe3a30dc079c84f1ce851c7e">			A MUST READ TO ALL THE SINGLES
&lt;br /&gt;;My precious single friends i want to give you a 'love checklist' to help u to avoid pouring your heart out into the wrong relationship.Trust me-it is better to be single and satisfied than heartbroken.....so here is the list
&lt;br /&gt;;1.Look at the way a man loves his mother because it is the way he will eventually love his wife.
&lt;br /&gt;;2.Pay attention to the way he reacts when there is a conflict or stress.
&lt;br /&gt;;3.Meet his friends and keep in mind that the people he hangs with are a reflection of his heart.
&lt;br /&gt;;4.Pay attention to what your good friends see in him because often those who love you can see better than you can see when you're falling in love.
&lt;br /&gt;;5.Look at what he reads and what he watches on tv because they will be a reflection of his moral fiber.
&lt;br /&gt;;6.Do your best not to be too physical as this will cloud your vision and confuse your heart.
&lt;br /&gt;;7.It is imperative that a man respect your boundaries without challenging them.
&lt;br /&gt;;8.Ask him to pray for you often,because you will need a man who knows how to cover you in prayer.
&lt;br /&gt;;9.Ask yourself whether you feel at home when you're with him or you act like someone you are not to get him to like you.
&lt;br /&gt;;10.Before you say 'I do' go through premarital counseling with a pastor.
&lt;br /&gt;;TRY THAT LADIES AND SEE HOW IT GOES,Later we will pray together.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d21c90ec4c9d586efcef445e889f3283">			I FEEL GOOD,M IN LOVE AGAIN.......
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WITH MYSELF........what were you thinking?		</conversation>		<conversation id="8b46170cf84e6ad63c0da5c2d6289c1d">			We tend to seek love in the wrong places.When it fails we blame the other person and 4get where we lukd.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>