<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="66005abee5165b39d1fd142f5b6a68da">			IPhone is one of the greatest inventions of this 21st century. This slim and smart cell phone is one of the major attractions for every cell phone lover. Undoubtedly, these phones are very stylish and graceful but these phones are also much sensitive and expansive. So, there is a possibility of anything happen with your iPhone . So, it is highly recommended you to take care of this sensitive gadget. But, sometimes it happens that by mistake your iPhone get damaged and you need a repair. Mostly people prefer to handover it to a local iPhone repair because of low charges. Even they feel so much proud that they saved a lot of money on their iPhone repair but actually they are on a big mistake. There are so many iPhone repair companies available but all of them can easily repair old versions of iPhone instead of latest version. If you are looking for an iPhone4 repair service then never handover your cell phone to these companies.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Just like an iPad, iPhone also has a very sensitive and fully touched screen. It can be easily damaged if you don’t care for it. If you are looking for iPhone4 repair service for your phone’s screen then there are many different shops that offer this service. You can also do it by yourself but it requires some technical knowledge and some extra research to make it easier.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5maXgtaXBob25lcy5jb20vaXBob25lLTQtcmVwYWlyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Iphone 4 repair&lt;/a&gt;; is not a difficult task start. You need to disassemble the whole phone to start. Always make sure that all the parts, especially screws, do not end up getting lost. Also never do this iPhone4 repair in hurry because it might be possible that you misplace something relevant to your iPhone4. Also choose a wide place for this purpose and there should not be lots of thing around you. If you cannot remember how many parts and screws you open then write it on a paper to make sure one part does not end up being mistaken for the other.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The next step is to remove the SIM tray. After that, remove the iPhone antenna. It is secured in place with three glue spots and one should proceed with this step with utmost caution. There are 10 main screws around the phone's sides. Carefully remove all these screws and there are 3 screws which secures the motherboard. Always remember that the battery and motherboard should be removed together and then detached the frame.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After all these process carefully remove the LCD screen and replaced it by the new one. You can do this by loosening 3 clips on the screen's side and removing the LCD. When you totally attached the screen then reconnect all the parts of your iPhone to get back to its original assembled state.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is not a professional way of iPhone repair and there is also a high risk involve in it. So, if you don’t want to take then risk then it is recommended you to handover your iPhone to a good and reputable iPhone4 repair company.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>