<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="aaf5de7f93da5f972f6ee59a6f0d7b10">			The Samsung UN55C6300 was released to the public this past February and it has grown to be one of the most coveted &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGVhcGVib29rcmVhZGVyLm9yZy9raW5kbGVzL2tpbmRsZXMtb24tc2FsZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Kindle on sale&lt;/a&gt;; on the market. The Samsung UN55C6300 has a gorgeous fifty-five inch wide screen and it is the latest offering in the 6300 LED series made by Samsung. With the Samsung UN55C6300 you get a beautiful picture every time the set is used; there are a plethora of features housed in the UN55C6300 that make this device a worthy investment for the consumer that demands nothing but the best. From &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGVhcGVib29rcmVhZGVyLm9yZy9raW5kbGVzL2tpbmRsZXMtb24tc2FsZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Best price on Kindle&lt;/a&gt;; LED backlighting technologies, to clear motion technologies, from the inclusion of an ultra clear panel to an impressive framework, the UN55C6300 was definitely built to impress.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The UN55C6300 has a 1080p high definition resolution so you get remarkable picture quality, sharp, striking colors, and crisp image presentations. The inclusion of a 120 Hertz picture refresh rate reduces image blurring, even during high impact, high action scenes. Samsung has taken the liberty to integrate Touch of Color?? technologies too so that the black framework has a beautiful extra dimension or extraordinary color. The Samsung UN55C6300 is also equipped with ConnectShare Movie features so you can hook up your digital camera or a thumb drive to view your videos, your photos, or listen to your favorite tunes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Check out the Samsung UN55C6300; a set that works via remote control operations and that offers you the ability to choose your playlist. This device uses fifty percent less energy than other HDTVs on the market today and it is Energy Star?? certified. You can even enjoy gaming on the Samsung UN55C6300 with its game mode offerings; you will find that the Samsung UN55C6300 has technologies that enhances game sounds and speeds so that your games are presented in flawlessly realistic presentations.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the UN55C6300 you are getting a set equipped with Wide Color Enhancer Plus?? features for a great spectrum of gradations in terms of color. See all color in a rich luminance and see color saturation that is unrivaled by other HDTV presentations. The UN55C6300 has BD Wise features, AllShare??, DNSe features for superior sound, and it is outfitted with dual fifteen watt speakers for the best soundscape possible. Mount this gorgeous device on a stand or mount it to a wall. Place it anywhere in your home and make it the centerpiece of your entertainment system.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The connectivity of the UN55C6300 is remarkable. Get four HDMI connections, to USB ports, a PC input, a component video input, an Ethernet port, an optical sound output, and access to Anynet+ features and controls. If you are seeking a set with TFT active matrix technologies, LED backlighting, progressive scanning features, ultra clear panel inclusion, LightSensor features, and an endless line of advanced technologies, the UN55C6300 is the set to choose. You will find that not only is the UN55C6300 impressive in terms of its technology and its inner and outer design, but the price is equally impressive.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ee9e61c7a9aa7a4d69791f4cd6f8ba83">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0dGFibGV0cGNyZXZpZXdzLm9yZy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Best Tablet PC&lt;/a&gt;; Comparison: Apple iOS vs Google Android&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although there are a number of different companies, utilising different operating systems (OS for short), now creating brilliant options for tablet computers, the chief tablet PC comparison for almost all consumers still boils down to the Apple iPad's iOS and different  Google Android tablets. So which choice of these two systems (or any other) is the correct one for your needs?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Look and feel:&lt;/strong&gt;;  Most industry experts largely agree that Apple's iOS works extremely well both as a smartphone and a tablet PC operating system. The system works very intuitively on the iPad - particularly if you've used an iPhone or iPod Touch before. The interface can be said to be iOS's best benefit, which no other tablet currently on the market can match.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Apps:&lt;/strong&gt;; In addition to the look and feel seniority, Apple also have a major marketing point with their App Store. There are currently over 350,000 apps available to download for free or buy for a small price from the Apple Store. It's a certainty that when a new app is created by a company or developer, the first version is for the App Store and after that it is ported to other platforms. However, Apple's store is not the sole player in the arena - the Android Market is rapidly growing, passing the 100,000 apps mark in early 2011.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Android has one major advantage on the competition when it comes to apps: it's far more open and has more of a &lt;em&gt;;laissez-faire&lt;/em&gt;; policy to the Market, whereas the App Store exercises very tight controls on every application, particularly in regard to adult content. The Android market allows developers much more creativity and flexibility.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There have also been complaints from some developers about Apple's rigid marketeering, with Apple requiring developers to remove any links from inside apps to the developers own websites. (The benefit to Apple is that they keep 30% commission from every app sale, whereas previously customers may have upgraded from free to paid version from within the developer's own site.)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Hardware:&lt;/strong&gt;; One major difference between iOS and Android is that iOS is exclusive to the iPad, while Android is open source and is being used by a number of different companies. This effectively means that the iPad and iOS are joined at the hip - you can't run the iPad without iOS. The iPad therefore has much more restriction of choice than other tablets, and much tighter pricing. However, those choices that are on the market are all good quality, and the hardware and software do work together harmoniously - crashes are very rare on the iPad.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Android, by contrast, is used in many different tablets from a large number of makers. From Blackberry to Samsung, you have a much wider choice of tablet PC to suit your budget and particular needs. However, you do need to do your homework. Some companies have customised Android and improved it, but some may not work as well and might still be based on older Android releases.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Right now, the iPad is still the most well-known and iconic tablet PC on the market. However, popularity is growing with a number of other tablet PCs. The choice is certainly good news for customers, who now have much more availability to get their exact requirements from a tablet computer. A lot of people still favour the Apple iOS, particularly if they have used other Apple products, but in the end it comes down to doing a tablet PC comparison yourself, by researching, checking them out, testing some in store, and selecting the one that feels like a good match for you.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>