<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="93bcfd3a3151a32dfc5b77672445b4f4">			With computers and printers, it is very convenient to print your own. Use your creativity. Send them a safety poster card for their birthdays. House warming? How about some electrical safety poster?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gift ideas need not be difficult. Why not give them life?&lt;br /&gt;;			&lt;br /&gt;;Safety posters can really make a big difference in how effective a company's safety program works to help prevent and reduce injuries and accidents from occurring in the workplace. However, some companies may be on a limited budget and not have a lot of money to invest. Fortunately there are ways to obtain free posters or produce them at a very low cost.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are websites on the internet where you can obtain a free poster download. All you do is click on a link that is provided and save a copy to your hard drive. They can they be printed out and posted in appropriate areas of the company. Two places that provide free safety posters are the Occupational Safety and Health Administration (or OSHA) and the New York State Insurance Fund. You can find other posters by doing a search for free safety posters using your favorite search engine.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another way of obtaining safety posters at a low cost is to produce them yourself. You can use a simple word processing or graphics program to design them. There are places on the internet where you can obtain free clip art to add eye catching images to the poster. Once you have the design done you can print them using your printer or take them to a low cost printer to have them printed off in bulk.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One other idea for getting new safety posters for your business is to hold a contest where employees can submit their designs.&lt;br /&gt;;			&lt;br /&gt;;The art pieces belonging to Post-Graffiti or Contemporary Post-Graffiti genre admirably have a higher distinctive status than the 'rude' Graffiti or Vandalism. This global art style is especially popular in the urban and the suburban regions of the Eastern and Western countries. Interesting and unique Street Poster Art has found fame among some of the greatest artists.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Correlations&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Street Poster Art does connect with Graffiti and the other forms, like Wheat Pasting, Stencil Graffiti, and Sticker Art. This Post Graffiti Art form has a distinguished contemporary style, different from the local Graffiti or Vandalism.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Artists and the Artworks&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Street artists have shown a cheap and affordable way to produce and display artworks meant to connect primarily with the common public. Exhibition 'Street Art' held in 'Washington Project for the Arts' (1981) displayed work by renowned American artists, such as John Fekner (born 1940) and Lee Quinones (born 1960). Even the art exhibition held at the prestigious Tate Modern Hall in England clearly indicates that the artworks found on the street are not necessarily graffiti.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Interesting and unique Street Poster Art has found fame among some of the greatest artists. Distinctly accomplished Italian poster masterpieces can be witnessed in many prestigious museums and galleries like the International Poster Gallery in Boston, USA.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Conclusion&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Most famous in the US, Street Poster Art has also gained sufficient momentum in Australia and Japan. France, Germany, Ireland, Spain, Brunei, New Zealand, the UK, Canada, and Iran too are the lead contributors to the genre.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeposterz.com%2Fv%2Fpromo.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bfree"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.freeposterz.com/v/promo.php&quot;&gt;;free&lt;/a&gt;; poster&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeposterz.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bposters%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.freeposterz.com&quot;&gt;;posters&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="28163730560fcc30202a4071bfc9fcc1">			It works, and you have the potential of growing your business and or bringing in new customers quickly, but it's a lot of money spent, as well as a huge gamble. And, if you don't know what you're doing with advertising on television, a business owner can find themselves asking for venture capital, in hopes of keeping their business above water, even when their mantra is to operate independently, without acquiring venture capital or seed money.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Television advertising, brochures, flyers, and print advertising are effective means of advertising. They cost a lot of money, just like paying for PPC &quot;pay per click&quot; online advertising. The best forms of advertising in today's information age are article marketing, word of mouth on and offline, social bookmarking, and social networking. Most importantly, when you're article is approved by article directories, other publishers pick up your article and publish them on their websites and blogs, thus placing you in a position to get free traffic, and new potential customers, from the traffic they receive online. This is called &quot;viral&quot; or &quot;reciprocal&quot; traffic, which you had to do no extra footwork for, and is the positive fruit benefited from writing unique articles from scratch, and submitting articles online for free, in hopes to expanding your reach to new potential customers online, without spending a dime!&lt;br /&gt;;			&lt;br /&gt;;Looking for gift ideas? It can be quite a difficult task considering the many choices you have. Why not give them safety posters? They are excellent for birthdays, anniversaries, graduation, house warming, or milestones in life.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My suggestion to giving health and safety poster is as serious as life itself. The wave also welcomed the initial paper form of advertising as Street Poster Art. Even other cities, like Milan (Italy) and Berlin (Germany) appreciated the Post-Graffiti styles and encouraged street artists.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Details&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Street posters are displayed on slick or smooth surfaces, mostly walls, by sticking them with the help of wheat paste or gum. The art pieces belonging to Post-Graffiti or Contemporary Post-Graffiti genre admirably have a higher distinctive status than the 'rude' Graffiti or Vandalism. This global art style is especially popular in the urban and the suburban regions of the Eastern and Western countries. Interesting and unique Street Poster Art has found fame among some of the greatest artists.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Correlations&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Street Poster Art does connect with Graffiti and the other forms, like Wheat Pasting, Stencil Graffiti, and Sticker Art. This Post Graffiti Art form has a distinguished contemporary style, different from the local Graffiti or Vandalism.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Artists and the Artworks&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Street artists have shown a cheap and affordable way to produce and display artworks meant to connect primarily with the common public. Exhibition 'Street Art' held in 'Washington Project for the Arts' (1981) displayed work by renowned American artists, such as John Fekner (born 1940) and Lee Quinones (born 1960). Even the art exhibition held at the prestigious Tate Modern Hall in England clearly indicates that the artworks found on the street are not necessarily graffiti.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Interesting and unique Street Poster Art has found fame among some of the greatest artists. Distinctly accomplished Italian poster masterpieces can be witnessed in many prestigious museums and galleries like the International Poster Gallery in Boston, USA.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeposterz.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bfree"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.freeposterz.com&quot;&gt;;free&lt;/a&gt;; posters&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freeposterz.com%2Fv%2Fpromo.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bfree"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.freeposterz.com/v/promo.php&quot;&gt;;free&lt;/a&gt;; poster&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>