<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b0e11b5f39f4e8df57f03e7176f2ecf5">			&lt;p&gt;;Most people have ideal jobs in their minds, but it is hard for me to get the exact ideal job. I have the dreamy life pattern which does not include an exact job; I want to live the life with free, wonders, challenge and also enthusiasm.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When a person is asked what his ideal job is, he may answer quickly, a doctor, an actor, and so on. But when it comes to me, I feel at a loss. There are all kinds of work in the world, but I cannot decide which kind I like best.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In fact, I realize that what kind of job does not matter too much to me, what matters most of all is contain of the job, what I do in that job, and also what the challenge, the ability I need in my job. Many people prefer to get an easy job with a good salary, that would not require them too much energy and they will not need to be too tired in the job. But it is completely the same ideal to me.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In my opinion, my ideal job must fully utilize my intelligence and knowledge. I have been studying for so many years; the main purpose is to prepare myself for my future job. If most of my knowledge cannot be used, no doubt it is a great waste. I am not afraid of demanding and challenging job, for it is the best opportunity to examine my capability. As a result, it stimulates me to make greater efforts and to achieve more.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;At the same time, however, I attach much importance to the personal relationship at work. A relaxed, harmonious relationship among the companions is ideal, for it is bound to improve the efficiency of work. I cannot imagine how they can cooperate if they cannot get along well, not to &lt;a alt=&quot;cheap ugg boots on sale&quot; title=&quot;cheap ugg boots on sale&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapuggbootmall.com%2Fugg-classic-mini-5854-c-5.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cheapuggbootmall.com/ugg-classic-mini-5854-c-5.html&lt;/a&gt;;]cheap ugg boots on sale[/url]tion any achievement.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;At last, I wish my job will help people directly, thus sense of achievement will make me work harder.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="ade1074fccdb172171e63f2e47cb4521">			&lt;p&gt;;Integrated with genuine sheepskin, they are of great comfort. Light and flexible with molded EVA outsole, they are tagged with excellence and quality. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGVhcHVnZ2Jvb3RtYWxsLmNvbS91Z2ctYmFpbGV5LWJ1dHRvbi01ODAzLWMtMS5odG1sJnF1b3Q7IHRpdGxlPSZxdW90O3VnZyBib290cyBhdXN0cmFsaWFuJnF1b3Q7IGFsdD0mcXVvdDt1Z2cgYm9vdHMgYXVzdHJhbGlhbg__" target="_blank"&gt;;ugg boots australian&lt;/a&gt;; shoes have immensely catered to the need of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaGVhcHVnZ2Jvb3RtYWxsLmNvbS91Z2ctYWNjZXNzb3JpZXMtdWdnLWVhcm11ZmZzLWMtMjBfMjEuaHRtbCZxdW90OyB0aXRsZT0mcXVvdDt1Z2cgYm9vdHMgb24gc2FsZSBjbGFzc2ljJnF1b3Q7IGFsdD0mcXVvdDt1Z2cgYm9vdHMgb24gc2FsZSBjbGFzc2lj" target="_blank"&gt;;ugg boots on sale classic&lt;/a&gt;;, men and children. These lavish boots are an epitome of style. Lavish and fashionable, women's have caused a craze around the world and have revolutionized concept of fashion in footwear's.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;Availability of mens ugg shoes and children ugg shoes has facilitated customers with wide choice. Nothing can keep your children happy throughout the day except Ugg boots. Children Ugg shoes are available in various colors like pink, blue, sand etc and give a comfortable feel. While you wish to buy them make sure that you have specific size. Light in weight and unique in style these boots maximizes comfort level and mark their advent as one of the trendiest statement pieces in today's world of fashion. Ugg slippers have also gain importance for its extreme placate.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;Buying Ugg shoes and slippers for yourself or for your kids is great. With quality these boots are admired for warm and cozy feel. Womens ugg boots are displayed in wide range and size and therefore attention is to be paid before you buy them. Size is always a main concern and when we talk about it, we are supposed to be accurate. Well, below are few points that would help you before you visit or ask them to provide with lovely pair of boots. Take a look:&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Measure your bare foot from heel to the longest toe or you can place your bare foot against the wall then using a pencil mark the top of your toe and acquire correct measurement.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Compare the measurement with 'Size Chart' that are usually available and select the corresponding size.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Don't buy too lose or too tight boots because they usually get loose when regularly put to wear.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Try to buy a half inch loose boots, if you intend to wear socks with them.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; If you are willing to avail long boots or short [url=&quot; title=&quot;ugg sales australia&quot; alt=&quot;ugg sales australia]ugg sales australia[/url] boots take into account the heels they have else you would be raised too much or too short.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Do not guess or just order the same size as your have with you.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Do not convert from other size systems.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Make sure that you are comfortable enough while wearing them and can do work with great ease.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;amp;bull; Remember Ugg boots size can differ from your other traditional boots. If you are using 7 for your traditional boots it might be 8 in Ugg shoes and therefore it would be better to check your actual size while availing them.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;Size chart availability at stores can be of great help to. Therefore, do take a look before you buy these lovely pair of Ugg boots.&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p&gt;;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>