<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="950ccc8b6e8eb14f289b1de085433cbe">			Almost anyone has an excuse for additional storage space.  One of the locations, at your home, that a owner of a house generally finds stuffed with much more stuff is the garage.  There is usually a not too difficult approach to add more space to your wood frame garage, overhead.  Just look at all the overhead space.  Why not make use of it to help you arrange your Garage and do away with unsightly and aggravating mess.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more great info on this topic.  Visit these great resources on  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbyronmcleod1025.livejournal.com%2F899.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://byronmcleod1025.livejournal.com/899.html&lt;/a&gt; .&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Overhead garage storage typically includes a metallic frame that hangs in the timber framing of the interior of your garage.  To be safe, the lumber used in the framing of your Garage need to be a minimum size of 2X6” standard lumber.  The joists in the framing should be no more than 24” apart.  Be sure you have no issues in regards towards the structural integrity of the framework.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After you have determined that your Storage framing will support excess weight you are ready to pick out your storage unit(s).  As said just before this type of storage consists of a metal frame that hangs down from the ceiling.  At the backside of the frame, there exists a steel platform where all types of items may be stored. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One brand of overhead garage storage that may be readily available in sizes ranging from 2’X6’ - 4’X8’ and supporting from 300-600 pounds.  That is enough area and weight efficiency to hold almost everything and to help you get your Garage organized. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another unit, that is readily available, mounts to the ceiling in a similar manner.  However, this unit has the benefit of the storage platform becoming mounted to a pulley structure.  This enables the operator to either lower system and load things on or remove the items they want.  This system removes the likely high-risk use of a step ladder.  This unit is 4’X4’ and holds up to 250 pounds.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fit overhead garage storage.  You will like your Storage and your nearby neighbours will believe you happen to be so intelligent.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>