<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c8cbe8f5b1c3be82f4109b70197f21b1">			If salvation is wholly dependant on The Father's phone and the Lord Jesus Christ working in us and by way of us 24/seven via the Holy Spirit, would it be possible for us to eliminate our salvation?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I hope you get the gist of what I am putting across right here, but let's look at this issue from an additional angle and consult an additional issue, simply because these men and women make emotional statements with no contemplating them by way of first. They chat freely about us losing our salvation but never expound on what they mean by it and how this dreadful scenario could come about if it had been to transpire. You see the problem is they open their mouths, the brain is not engaged, and out pours the verbal drivel. So how can their non-salvation be misplaced? Appropriate right here:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;John 6:65-66 (KJV) And he stated, Therefore said I unto you, that no guy can occur unto me, other than it were given unto him of my Father. 66 From that many of His disciples went again, and walked no more with Him.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So right here we have a lot of learners (disciples) losing their chance to be saved - they went again - they turned absent. Please be aware, learners (disciples) are not saved. Disciples are trainees, people coming to baptism and the acquiring of the Holy Spirit. This indicates these men have been not but saved, but they lost the option to be saved, simply because they could not accept the simple fact that The Father had called them to The Lord. They needed to believe it was all down to them - their idea, their righteousness, their enthusiasm, their knowledge, their cleverness and of program their selection, so that they could experience great about by themselves, tell by themselves how wise they had been and give themselves all the credit by obtaining accepted The Lord as their Saviour - salvation on their terms which means a non-salvation or a counterfeit salvation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Okay, if we now appear at what this girl is stating in the light of the over Real truth we have to assume she is suggesting that we can walk absent from The Lord or flip our backs on Him - a deliberate premeditated determination and something we would want to do. The point is, is a Spirit led believer heading to do this i.e. a person in a shut partnership with his Godly Brother? This would be a betrayal of the worst variety which would then beggar the question: If an individual decides to do that what type of partnership did they have in the beginning? I'll tell you, they had no partnership with The Lord at all, just like those learners (disciples) in John six:66. He has promised by no means to leave us nor forsake us through thick and skinny, so let's be done with this blasphemous nonsense about a accurate son or daughter of God losing their salvation, for it ain't gonna transpire!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Eventually, and to the reader who left the previously mentioned declaration please really feel free of charge to operate off a copy of this post and current it to the up coming blasphemer who tells you, you can eliminate your salvation - with my 'compliments' of training course.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frrm.cc"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://rrm.cc&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>