<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ea636249ec979321415fecb9a82c7c50">			Chrysler's Eagle&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; The Dodge Magnum SRT8 is not the first powerful vehicle that Chrysler has evolved. The Eagle Talon which was among the list of three model names given to a passenger car manufactured and sold by way of the then Chrysler Corporation together with Mitsubishi Motors of Japan in the joint venture known for the reason that Diamond Star Motor, concerning 1990 and 1998. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Talon was then sold in the Eagle brand developed by Chrysler to contest with Japanese imports in your late 1980s. The other siblings with the Talon were the Eclipse which was sold by Mitsubishi along with the Laser which was offered by Plymouth another Chrysler product. Both Plymouth and Eagle may be discontinued but despite the following fact the production of Eagle parts like the Eagle exhaust continues. Your Eagle exhaust is renowned for performance and power. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Eagle Talon together with the Eclipse and the Laser were built on the same platform at the DSM manufacturing facility in Normal, Illinois. Your three vehicles were mechanically the same including engine, transmission, together with drivetrain. In terms associated with exterior features the a few cars only differ in wheels, tail lights, availability of colors, front and rear bumpers, and spoilers. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And speaking of colors the Eagle Talon contains a two-tone body color, to create the 'greenhouse'. Starting with its roof, pillars, door-mounted mirrors the colors was always black whatever the body color. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The other basic characteristics of that Eagle Talon include: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Two panels &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Hatchback &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	2+2 seating (2 front seats and 2 marginal, fold down rear seat designs) &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	4 option levels (beginning with lowest to highest): DL, ES, TSI, and TSi AWD &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Front-wheel drive (FWD) for many option levels except for any top option level which had all-wheel drive (AWD) &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	5-speed handbook or 4-speed automatic transmissions &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Two-tone shade combination &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Hood bulge on the left-hand side of the vehicle that provides it with adequate clearance for the camshaft sprockets/timing belt cover to the 4G63engine &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One outstanding thing regarding the Talon is its success compared to the Eagle nameplate which was a giant flop for Chrysler. While the Eagle failed to gain any market share from Pontiac which was its main rival, the Talon on the other hand was a stellar success and also the only Eagle model that was profitable. The Talon has received a lot of awards and sold across 100, 000 units with its lifetime and produced a cult of fans. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Years ago, developing a wagon model to go along with your sedan line was the. That was before minivans were invented and station wagons presented the only real logical way to move families. Sure, full size vans were available, but they were too large and gas thirsty in order to satisfy the needs of America's families. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Truck Goodness &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using station wagons, seating for about nine was possible together with, if the extra seating room wasn't needed, those family haulers could certainly store a whole lot of yard sales finds, knick knacks, hardware, you name the idea. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Until just lately, wagons were the passing of any model. No one offered them except for a few brave European brands selling niche sport wagons which include Volvo and Mercedes. But, you paid a handsome price for these vehicles. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Dodge Magnum &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Dodge Magnum began to turn the tide, a sport wagon sold from 2005 to help 2008. Dodge proved that a wagon with muscular visual appearance had an appeal that went beyond the standard family hauler visage, offering a macho man mobile or portable. Unfortunately, Chrysler's financial woes compelled the Magnum's discontinuance and several other models. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now, the wagon body style is confined to a couple of compact models including this Volkswagen SportWagen, Subaru Impreza wagon, Audi A3 wagon together with expensive European wagons from BMW and Mercedes. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Hyundai Sonata &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Hyundai Sonata, redesigned with regard to 2011, just may be the following wagon sold in the usa. Available as a sedan in North america, the Sonata is sold for the reason that i40 sedan in Europe which includes a wagon model arriving within 2011. That same wagon may cross the pond for United states consumption and if dealing, we'll have the first sport wagon of its kind since the departure of the Avoid Magnum. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]Dodge Magnum[/url]One of the labels of automobiles and light to heavy duty trucks that is marketed by way of the German yet American-based company DaimlerChrysler AG could be the Dodge.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>