<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="6f149203f9b029d3f4b00d4a229e70b5">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53aG9sZXNhbGVkdmRzb25saW5lLmNvbS9taXNmaXRzLXNlYXNvbnMtMTItZHZkLWJveHNldC1wLTMyNTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Misfits season dvd&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;; is a British comedy-drama series about a group of young offenders forced to work in a community service programme where they attain supernatural powers after a strange electrical storm. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Nathan Kelly Simon Alisha and Curtis were expecting their community service to be boring however after a freak thunderstorm they discover that it is anything but dull. Bestowed with strange powers the five very different teens realize they have a lot more to worry about than just picking up litter. Especially as they discover that they are not the only ones who have been giving strange powers. Secrets will be revealed feelings will be brought to the surface and relationships will be formed and broken. But hey its only 6 weeks of community service what's the worse that could happen?
&lt;br /&gt;;Last Sunday saw the premiere of the third season of &quot;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53aG9sZXNhbGVkdmRzb25saW5lLmNvbS9taXNmaXRzLXNlYXNvbnMtMTItZHZkLWJveHNldC1wLTMyNTQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Misfits season dvd boxset&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;,&quot; a British television show about a group of young offenders who gain superpowers after a mysterious lightning storm. The third season sees off Nathan Young, played by Robert Sheehan, and the introduction of Rudy Wade, played by Joseph Gilgun.
&lt;br /&gt;;Before the season premiere, a 10-minute webisode was posted online detailing the circumstances of Nathan's departure. In it, he uses his new ability to perform &quot;magic&quot; to earn a fortune at a Las Vegas casino. Nathan is caught and thrown into jail, unbeknownst to the rest of the group. All in all, the webisode was fairly entertaining, sending out a well-loved character in a hilarious and fitting way.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ec3d8c5978c6cca0f6895be82afd3554">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53aG9sZXNhbGVkdmRzb25saW5lLmNvbS9tb29ubGlnaHQtc2Vhc29uLTEtZHZkLWJveHNldC1wLTMzOTcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Moonlight dvd&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;follows Mick St. John an immortal vampire and private investigator and his struggle to exist after he was bitten 60 years ago by his vampire bride on their wedding night. It also follows his internal torment as he falls in love with one he should not one who is mortal named Beth a news reporter as well as his dealings with the woman who made him a vampire his sire Coraline.
&lt;br /&gt;;The show is produced by Warner Bros. Television and Silver Pictures. Joel Silver is executive producing with Trevor Munson and Ron Koslow both writing and executive producing.
&lt;br /&gt;;Well, though the actress hasn’t yet announced anything formally, it’s been her highly visible baby bump that let the cat out of the bag!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Well, only recently, the prolific actress was spotted in LA, showing off her pretty big baby bump, which clearly indicates that she is getting ready to welcome another bundle of joy into her life.
&lt;br /&gt;;Though the Hollywood diva is expecting, she shows no interest in revealing anything about the paternal details of her yet-to-be-born baby.
&lt;br /&gt;;Seems as if Hollywood has set in some trend of ‘bringing up your baby without revealing the name of the father’!
&lt;br /&gt;;In the past decade, we have seen several female fatales of the tinsel town, who have chosen to be single mothers and opted not to unveil the paternal details of their babies.
&lt;br /&gt;;Oh gosh! I’m just unable to understand why these celebrities put the future of their kids on stake, for the sake of their own selves!
&lt;br /&gt;;Anyway!
&lt;br /&gt;;While the soon-to-be-mommy is due to give birth at the end of this year, she’s trying her level best to hide the news from the media.
&lt;br /&gt;;But as you know, we’ve got an eagle eye! How could a celebrity even think of escaping us!
&lt;br /&gt;;That too, in case of a thing like ‘Pregnancy’!
&lt;br /&gt;;Silly Shannyn, I must say!
&lt;br /&gt;;Already a mother to an eight-year-old son, Audio Science, Shannyn is known for her remarkable role on the vampire drama series,&lt;strong&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53aG9sZXNhbGVkdmRzb25saW5lLmNvbS9tb29ubGlnaHQtc2Vhc29uLTEtZHZkLWJveHNldC1wLTMzOTcuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Moonlight season dvd boxset&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;; . One can watch Moonlight online to revel in the action that the actress brings to our screens.
&lt;br /&gt;;She’s always been an eye-catcher on the series, courtesy her killer looks and fantastic acting skills.
&lt;br /&gt;;Well, if I exclude her personal life; I have to say that I’m a great fan of Shannyn. She has always been on the top my favorite celeb list.
&lt;br /&gt;;Anyway, I wish the actress gets to download a lot of happiness in her life with the arrival of this new guest.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d89b27a4b5b4da46769f13d18e44baaa">			&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53aG9sZXNhbGVkdmRzb25saW5lLmNvbS9waXJhdGVzLW9mLXRoZS1jYXJpYmJlYW4tdGV0cmFsb2d5LWR2ZC1ib3gtc2V0LXAtMzE5Ny5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Pirates of the Caribbean dvd&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;: On Stranger Tides Captain Jack Sparrow (Depp) crosses paths with a woman from his past (Cruz) and he's not sure if it's love -- or if she's a ruthless con artist who's using him to find the fabled Fountain of Youth. When she forces him aboard the Queen Anne's Revenge the ship of the formidable pirate Blackbeard (McShane) Jack finds himself on an unexpected adventure in which he doesn't know who to fear more: Blackbeard or the woman from his past.
&lt;br /&gt;;This week’s two biggest titles have already come out in Blu-ray editions, but if you’ve been waiting for a cheaper, no-frills DVD option, now’s the time to spring for “&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53aG9sZXNhbGVkdmRzb25saW5lLmNvbS9waXJhdGVzLW9mLXRoZS1jYXJpYmJlYW4tdGV0cmFsb2d5LWR2ZC1ib3gtc2V0LXAtMzE5Ny5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Pirates of the Caribbean season dvd boxset&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;;: On Stranger Tides” (PG-13, $29.99) and “The Lion King” (G, $29.99), which was recently rereleased in theaters.
&lt;br /&gt;;Though Orlando Bloom sat out the fourth “Pirates,” he can be found in “Main Street” (PG, $26.98), which co-stars Patricia Clarkson, Ellen Burstyn and Colin Firth as a businessman who promises to help the suspicious residents of a depressed North Carolina town.
&lt;br /&gt;;Also available is “Larry Crowne” (PG-13, $29.98), in which Julia Roberts enlightens newly unemployed Tom Hanks when he goes back to school. The critically praised “Beginners” (R, $29.98) stars Ewan McGregor as a single guy taken aback when his aged father (Christopher Plummer) comes out of the closet. And Hope Davis, Dermot Mulroney and Christina Hendricks unite to fight through the dysfunction dramedy “The Family Tree” (not rated, $24.98).
&lt;br /&gt;;“The Looney Tunes Platinum Collection: Volume One” (not rated, $59.96) offers 50 classic cartoons, commentaries from Chuck Jones, Mel Blanc and others, hours of documentary footage and bonus shorts. Deleted scenes, storyboard sequences and production diaries bulk up the five-film “Tom Cruise Blu-ray Collection” (R, $57.99), which ranges from “Top Gun” to “War of the Worlds.”
&lt;br /&gt;;And though it’s light on extras, if you’ve never seen the great Hong Kong actioner “Infernal Affairs” (R, $19.99), on which “The Departed” was based, the new Blu-ray release is the perfect excuse.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>