<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7a6884ef4ac01753932aa834ab805be5">			It's likely that you’ve very likely heard of Betdaq?  Betdaq is now among the largest online betting exchanges, a position it has attained during 11 years of outstanding advancement since its launch in the beginnings of the web.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freebetsource.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.freebetsource.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By presenting a number of new ways to bet it captured the imagination of visitors around the entire world.  Originally just a sports betting exchange, Betdaq has since evolved to offer casino and gaming in addition to enhancing its range of sports betting markets and options.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is the significant difference between Betdaq and the typical bookmakers?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before Betdaq came along, being in a position to set the odds was the unconditional reserve of the bookie.  Before Betdaq came along, the odds were set, and you accepted them if you wanted to bet on something to win.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is the crucial difference between Betdaq and various other online bookmakers - it provides the customer this potential to play bookmaker and enables you to lay a selection.  To confirm, laying a selection is identical to betting on it to lose. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is the ability to place bets to lose on Betdaq that absolutely changes the betting landscape, it allows for complex strategies such as those used in the financial community. At a future point in time we will look more closely at these strategies. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Making use of a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.freebetsource.com%2Fbetdaq-free-bet%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.freebetsource.com/betdaq-free-bet/&lt;/a&gt;; to get going with exchange betting. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The sensible way to ease yourself into exchange betting is by way of a free bet offer, typically offered to new customers. This is where new customers will be offered a free bet to enable them get started using their new account. Normally, this free bet will be a match of their first deposit, up to a specified amount. At the time of writing, with Betdaq this is at this moment £30, which is more than ample to help you get started. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Where to get started? It could be that there is a particular sport you like and like to bet on, the chances are that Betdaq will include the event. Using the case of a Premier League football match, there are normally in excess of 45 diverse markets. Potentially to start with, it is best to use one of the more common markets, such as the “match odds,” i.e. which team will win? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One great aspect of Betdaq is that they immediately run courses for new accounts, so once you have set up your account and deposited, these will give you a nice intro to how the exchange operates. There is also a comprehensive set of FAQs and help readily available at Betdaq, covering any queries you might have about the ins and outs of the exchange. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As with a lot of matters in life, the most effective way to learn is to do. So the key recommendation here is that you get stuck in and see for yourself how it works, but at first, do this with the minimum possible stake of £2. This will make certain you don’t fritter away your free bet understanding how things work. At this point, you will notice one of the numerous great features of Betdaq, which is the possible profit or loss indicator.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>