<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e062709dbf62d9761d5771dff2c0ab9a">			These descriptions can be installed for anyone looking to add a martial arts program on their gym, or add additional classes on their existing martial arts school. These are also excellent for someone that's planning to open a fighting styles school and is in need of this type of information to add to a business plan and also proposal. My original plan is always to write up the categories below although it's subject to change and expansion. Here are your categories: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Muay Thai Kickboxing Beginners through Advanced&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; MMA&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Grappling Beginners through Intermediate&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; MMA Fitness&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Boxing&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Sparring Category&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Muay Thai Kickboxing : Beginners &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Precondition:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Equipment Requirement:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Path Time:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Course Frequency:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Course Description:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Assessment:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Curriculum:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Posture&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Footwork&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Your punches&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Kicks&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Knees&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Elbows&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Punch Counters&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Kick Counter&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Clinch Positions&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; : 50/50 Tie Up, Dominant Position&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; - Shin Block, Evade, Ride&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; - Parry, Cover&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; - Right Horizontal Elbow, Allowed to remain Horizontal Elbow&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; : Right Straight Knee, Departed Straight Knee&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; - Right Round Kick, Departed Switch Kick&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; : Jab, Cross, Hook, Uppercut&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; : Step and Slide: Advance, Retreat, Left and Right&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; - Basic Fighters Posture &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Students with a minimum of 1 month training in the Beginners class will end up evaluated for advancement to your Intermediate class. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Then rest for a minute -- no more time. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And start out punching. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Allow punch fly out, drop -- uncontrolled. Do this several times with each fist and arm. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Following, with just a bit more control, try to make your arm being a whip. Loose, relaxed, almost snapping afre the wedding, because it gains so much speed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Practice these whip punches as long as you are able. During the following session, don't add back in control. You read which correctly. Only exert enough control so as to cause a speed to whip action. No more. You would like both your mind plus your muscles to remember that whipping action. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In that case, when you can't punch any longer. Rest... for a morning or two. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The very next time you return to ones punching exercises, you are sure to practice more realistic punching.... &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Practice ones regular punches, but now, imagine the whipping motion in the punch. In other key phrases, superimpose the memories of the loose punch on the controlled punch that you are practicing. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If that imagery doesn't meet your needs exactly, if your punches don't improve after you imprint your loose punch on the regular one, then try imagining that the are punching regularly, but you are relaxing control just a bit -- enough to increase speed. Try to combine the feeling of a loose speed punch with your regular punch. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Although most people make use of the P90X system to lower that unwanted flab, it really mistaken for a total burnout routine. The P90X is essentially a mixture of various workout forms and there are actually 12 different exercise areas into the fact that P90X is divided. Some of these exercises are cardiovascular; some are aerobics while there are lots of good P90X bodybuilding workout routines also included in this set of 12 workout forms. Therefore, p90s it isn't just a weight reduction process; rather it aids the body in getting in perfect shape right at the end of the 90 days to weeks. It aims at building at the right places, and reducing in the wrong ones. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3J3bW1hLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Brazilian Jiu Jitsu in New Jersey&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3J3bW1hLmNvbS8/cGFnZV9pZD0zNDc_" target="_blank"&gt;;Kickboxing classes in NJ&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3J3bW1hLmNvbS8/cGFnZV9pZD03MDA_" target="_blank"&gt;;Kickboxing in NJ&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>