<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e54dedefa0130fd39258cb79031580c7">			Ink-jet technology allows photographers to provide &lt;em&gt;; 'customer-specific' &lt;/em&gt;; calendars and handmade cards - that's &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; photo marketing in the next level. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 'Old School' Tip #4 - Tie-ins Using Other Businesses &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This strategy is especially effective lately. I think it's because many &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; photography addicts are leaving the photography business and taking successful marketing techniques with each other. Tie-ins work with several type &lt;em&gt;; 'people' &lt;/em&gt;; businesses including hair salons, spas, local restaurants, etc. One strategy that functions for me and most of the other photographers that I help is approaching small business owners, introducing myself as some sort of photographer, and offer them my services. My opening question for many years is something like, &quot;Do you need to have photos of your merchandise in your advertising, in your business literature or to your catalog? &quot; Most of them have tried such a need for several photos in the past six months, or so. I specifically word my own question to &quot;plant your seeds&quot; of any pic ideas that they may have been thinking of, but just didn't know where to start next. Often, their answer is no, they do not possess a need - at the beginning. I leave my contact information with them. With business owners, I leave a business card and a article card sized brochure (with work that I've accomplished for other businesses and &quot;planting more seeds&quot;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;. Sometimes, if I'm carrying some sort of camera, I take several snapshots of their business and send these phones the businesses as a follow up, with my contact information on the photos. This tactic doesn't provide fast money, but, it does generate good, long-term revenue. Slowly but surely, more and more businesses are recognizing the need to have photos in their own businesses. This strategy works extremely well for part-time photography business, also. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; 'Old School' Tip #5 - Show What you Got! &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And, there's the &lt;em&gt;; 'granddaddy' &lt;/em&gt;; of &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; techniques; the ' &lt;em&gt;; never-fail, ' 'fool-proof, ' 'never-let-you-down' best of the best - &quot;show them that you're the most effective! &quot; &lt;/em&gt;; In some other words, display your work. Online isn't the only place to display your work. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your display can be as simple as a few small portraits for a store. You can create large contemporary displays within malls or events and also arts &amp;amp; crafts shows or trade shows. What's important is you only display your best work. I want to offer this lesson learned with me displaying my work without giving consideration to who the audience I want to appeal to. I saw it enlarged some beautiful and finely detailed flowers together with had them on exhibit. Many people would stop by, look at the exhibit, and ask for more info .. Photo session follow ups were so-so. Then, one morning, I stopped displaying the &lt;em&gt;; 'finely-detailed' &lt;/em&gt;; images and replaced them using great portraits of &lt;em&gt;; 'regular' &lt;/em&gt;; people - business literally exploded. Session learned: my target audiences (women) don't want &lt;em&gt;; 'finely-detailed' &lt;/em&gt;; photos - no matter how beautiful the flowers are. They wanted &lt;em&gt;; 'softer-focused' &lt;/em&gt;; photos of very regular people. And they didn't &lt;em&gt;; 'tell' &lt;/em&gt;; everyone this until &lt;em&gt;; after &lt;/em&gt;; I changed this displays! Changing my &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; displays and practicing &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; people interaction taught me vital lessons and increased my own photography business. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ub3Zhc3BvcnRzLmdyL25ld3MuYXNweD9hX2lkPTIyMDAyNSZhbXA7U3BvcnQ9MSZhbXA7Q29tcGV0aXRpb249MTcxMyZhbXA7U2Vhc29uPTEwMDA4MSZhbXA7Q291bnRyeT04MiZhbXA7VGVhbT0xNjY1NyZhbXA7Um91bmQ9MjUyNzg1" target="_blank"&gt;;??? ????&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rb3VrZmFybS5nci9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9jb250ZW50JmFtcDt2aWV3PWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2lkPTEwNzplcGlza2Vwc2lpZWtha21pJmFtcDtjYXRpZD0zNjpuZWFtYXNjYXRlZ29yeSZhbXA7SXRlbWlkPTMzMQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;IEK AKMI&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5saWZvLmdyL21hcmtldC9tYXJrZXRuZXdzLzU1NDc_" target="_blank"&gt;;IEK AKMI&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="91866c2a0807a2293458e65a9209623c">			' &lt;/em&gt;; To give an example: there was a time when people were &lt;em&gt;; 'confused and mesmerized' &lt;/em&gt;; with cellular phones! Many couldn't conceive that this telephones worked without wires! Many refused to purchase a cell phone - figuring they were a &lt;em&gt;; 'fad' &lt;/em&gt;; and could &lt;em&gt;; 'get by' &lt;/em&gt;; with the information they've been &lt;em&gt;; 'getting by' &lt;/em&gt;; with for all of this time! Is this familiar to you? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 'Old School' Rule #1 &lt;em&gt;; 'Old-School' &lt;/em&gt;; Has a Place In &lt;em&gt;; 'Modern' &lt;/em&gt;; Times &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ones photography marketing activities should include the &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; principles - with &lt;em&gt;; 'modern' &lt;/em&gt;; adjustments for efficiency and professionalism. To start a photography business without needing modern tools is like looking to successfully run a business with out a telephone - wireless and 'old-school/wired-to-the-wall' type! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 'Old School' Tip #2 - For any Foreseeable Future - &lt;em&gt;; 'Technology' &lt;/em&gt;; Won't Change People &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As advanced as technology is and it is getting, and as convenient as technology is making everyday life for people, and as time-saving as technology has become - people &lt;em&gt;; 'still' &lt;/em&gt;; prefer, and gravitate towards, &lt;em&gt;; 'other people' &lt;/em&gt;; - the human touch. Photographers that can don't forget and build their photography marketing strategy on &lt;em&gt;; 'people-still-needing-people' &lt;/em&gt;; strategies and activities are the consistently successful photographers - no matter what their photography niche. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 'Old School' Rule #3 - Cyber-Space Comes with It's Pluses - Nevertheless, The Masses Still Prefer Literature &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Without a doubt, that's right. Most of the environment &lt;em&gt;; 'aren't' &lt;/em&gt;; online all of the time! Oh sure, the numbers (of people online a good deal of the time) are growing, but, an all-time &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; photography marketing favorite holds a favorite of your masses - literature. All things considered, that's how most photos emerged. Modern technology has made these tools much more effective in marketing with regard to photographers. For example, with the quality of ink-jet printers, I tend to make business cards on an &lt;em&gt;; 'as needed' &lt;/em&gt;; rationale. Also, I can change my business card whenever I want or want to. Being a photographer, not only what's leave them everywhere, I would do so regularly. Likewise with other &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; photography business marketing staples which include brochures, fliers and circulars, for example. Ink-jet technology allows photographers to produce &lt;em&gt;; 'customer-specific' &lt;/em&gt;; calendars and handmade cards - that's &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; photo marketing in the next level. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 'Old School' Tip #4 - Tie-ins Using Other Businesses &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This plan is especially effective these days. I think it's because so many &lt;em&gt;; 'old-school' &lt;/em&gt;; photography addicts are leaving the picture taking business and taking successful marketing techniques with each other. Tie-ins work with many type &lt;em&gt;; 'people' &lt;/em&gt;; businesses including hair salons, spas, local restaurants, etc. One strategy that works for me and most of the other photographers that I work with is approaching small businesses proprietors, introducing myself as some sort of photographer, and offer these my services. My opening question to them is something like, &quot;Do you require photos of your merchandise inside your advertising, in your business literature or to your catalog? &quot; Most of them have had such a need for some type of photos in the past six months, or so. I specifically word my own question to &quot;plant that seeds&quot; of any photo ideas that they may have been thinking of, but just didn't know what to do next. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ub2l6LmdyL2luZGV4LnBocD90b3BpYz0xODkxNzkuMA__" target="_blank"&gt;;IEK AKMI&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tdXNpY3dvcmxkZXhwby5nci9pbmRleC5waHA/b3B0aW9uPWNvbV9zb2JpMiZhbXA7c29iaTJUYXNrPXNvYmkyRGV0YWlscyZhbXA7Y2F0aWQ9MjEmYW1wO3NvYmkySWQ9NCZhbXA7SXRlbWlkPTEyJmFtcDtsYW5nPWVs" target="_blank"&gt;;IEK AKMH&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcHJpZGVyc3RvcmVzLmdyL2Nvc21vcy9zeW5lcmdhdGVzL2llay1ha21p" target="_blank"&gt;;IEK AKMH&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>