<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b5dce7d0ef25511a9dcb9707111c053d">			The single biggest challenge in any call center is having the ability to meet or exceed your call center metrics. Creating consistency is the most difficult challenge for all call center leaders. The solution is simple. Simply provide effective call center training for your front-line leaders.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why is this so important? Front-line leaders determine the success of the center. They touch the most important asset of your center, your call center agents. Call center supervisors (and team leaders) influence productivity, quality and to some extent, customer satisfaction. If these leaders aren't strong then your results will not be strong.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your front-line leaders are faced with many call center performance challenges on a daily basis. How they react determines the outcome (or the result.) So the important question that needs to be asked and honestly answered is how effectively are you preparing your leadership team to address performance issues?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Let's face it, many of the new call center team leaders (supervisors) are promoted from the call center agent ranks. Creating this career path is great if you provide ongoing call center training. Skills need to be developed and proper business processes need to be followed.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Unfortunately, many Call Center's do not have a formalized call center training program put into place to support these new leaders. Call center metrics are positively driven by these front-lined leaders, therefore it only makes sense to properly prepare them to be an effective call center leader.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Through extensive call center best practices research, I believe that there are 15 critical areas that need to be addressed. By providing these to your call center supervisors, as well as, other members of the support teams, you'll find that your overall team delivers better results.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Skills like what it means to be a call center supervisor, coaching, team building and communication just seem obvious. However, topics like understanding individual behavior, positive leadership and listening skills play a vital role in motivating your call center agents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Call center leadership can be a thankless job that is why it's important to have call center training modules like time management and stress management also included. The benefit with call center training designed as modules is really two-fold. First, you can conduct official &quot;;On-Boarding&quot;; training, which includes all of the modules. Or secondly, you can offer training on an &quot;;as needed basis&quot;; and only run an employee or a few through one module at a time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Click Here To learn more about Call Center Training &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYWxsY2VudGVybGVhZGVyc2hpcHRyYWluaW5nLmNvbS9jYWxsLWNlbnRlci1yZXNvdXJjZXMtZm9yLWNhbGwtY2VudGVyLXN1cGVydmlzb3JzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;Call Center Training&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>