<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3dc727403d296b7af57aee92fe107e">			How was your last vacation? Did you have a blast? Did you find excitement? Was there some relaxing time or did your last vacation entail bussing your family around, doing some yard work and other chores? Did your last “vacation” end up being a “stay put vacation”? Why not go for something different this year? When you have a small amount of time off, why not check into some of the adventure travels available near your home. Even if you don’t go outside your home state there are tons of adventures to be had. If you can afford to spend a little more, why not treat yourself to a true adventure? Here are some adventure travels that are well-known favorites.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dog sledding can be a wonderful adventure! You might be under the impression that dog sledding is a professional sport and not for amateurs. If you're thinking about the Iditarod, then you are right. For those who just want to have a little bit of fun and a little bit of adventure, the package deals at Alaskan Husky Adventures is just the ticket. This group offers two and three day package deals. During the day you are given guided tours and trained on the sleds by trained professionals and then during the evenings you relax in the cabins (you need to take your own food). Do you enjoy sightseeing? Do you love being able to explore the places you’ve only read about in books? Why not partake on a sightseeing adventure travels tour of a place your have only fantasized about visiting? Highly favored tourist spots include Greece, Rome, Ireland and Scotland, Africa, China and Tibet. Seemingly there is a sightseeing tour to be had in just about every country in the world, so just pick a location and sign up for a touring trip! Find a guide to teach you about the chosen country’s culture and history. For a cost effective and enjoyable vacations consider   &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bluewater-rvresort.com%2Frv-campgrounds-in-tennessee-amenities"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.bluewater-rvresort.com/rv-campgrounds-in-tennessee-amenities&lt;/a&gt;; . &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you love the thought of being up close to big game? Have you always dreamed of seeing exotic animals in their native habitats? Why not venture on an African Safari. There are tours that go all around the African continent. Choose from one of the many trusted companies and let them show you where to find hippos, elephants and giraffes in their natural environments. Look at prides of lions and packs of hyenas. View birds that you’ve only see in the zoo. If you love animals, a Safari is one of the best ways to experience adventure travels. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Adventure travels don't have to be super expensive (though they can run a little high sometimes). These vacations don't have to be lengthy. Some only last a single day! Why would you choose to let yourself sit around feeling bored when you could choose to spend your vacation having fun and adventures? Because there are so many different kinds of adventure travels and vacations to take your hardest choice is going to be deciding what you want to do the most and where you want to do it! Let yourself have fun!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>