<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="de4df7d11eb726b53681c7298c9ff332">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3V0dWJlLmNvbS93YXRjaD92PW1ZQ3I2ZHhROW1n" target="_blank"&gt;visalus &lt;/a&gt;Reading Visalus Body by Vi Reviews will answer the frequently asked question &quot;;What is Visalus and what do they do?&quot;;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Health is getting higher and higher up on the agenda for many of us these days. If either Ryan or Dale failed to complete their goal for one day they would have to call the other and say, &quot;;I'm just a boy, calling a man&quot;;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sometime after the halfway point of the challenge Ryan had to call Coach Brown to forfeit due to a family tragedy. Like a true sportsman, Coach Brown would not let Ryan complete his call of defeat and instead said he would forfeit as well and call it a draw. Even though the challenge had no winner or loser, the most important development was the challenge itself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ViSalus Body by Vi Challenge - Not One Loser Yet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Out of the &quot;;Dale Brown Challenge&quot;; came the unique idea for the Body by Vi 90-Day Challenge which was launched in July of 2009. It is the Body by Vi Challenge that has been the catalyst for the company's explosion of growth. As of September of this year ViSalus has seen their number of customers quadruple due to the success of the challenge. It is creating remarkable health transformations for those using the products while at the same time increasing the prosperity of those promoting the challenge.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A New-Economy Marketing Strategy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are several aspects that make the Body by Vi Challenge such a success for everyone involved. One is that an incentive is given not only to the distributor, but to the customer as well. The &quot;;holy grail&quot;; for most distributors in any network marketing company would be to not have to worry about a product auto-ship every month. The &lt;em&gt;ViSalus&lt;/em&gt; owners recognized this opportunity and the fact that people have less disposable income right now and came up with what they call the Refer 3, Get Your Next Month Free program. All distributors or customers have to do is help three people join and stay on the Body by Vi Challenge with a kit of equal or greater value to their own. If they do this they will get their products for free month after month.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another aspect that makes the challenge so successful for ViSalus is the &quot;;buy-in&quot;; that is created.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Both distributors and customers are working toward a common goal in most cases which is better overall health and fitness. Stories of weight loss and fitness goals achieved start to be shared among the group and all of a sudden the focus is not so much on the products but the results of the challenge. Selling is taken out of the equation and in its place is promotion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is easy to see why ViSalus has enjoyed so much success over the last year when so many other companies are struggling. They have found a way to address two major problems people have right now and that is lack of money and lack of good health. By coming up with a simple solution to both of these issues, ViSalus is poised to steamroll into 2011 with thousands more Body by Vi Challenge participants.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Are you currently a Visalus Distributor that day dreams about the BodyByVi Bimmer Club? Find out these important techniques today and you will soon have your personal BodyByVi Bimmer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visalus Distributors are psyched for a really good reason; they have a fantastic package to market and an amazing business to be a part of.		</conversation>		<conversation id="80f0c953df73028cc81c9c0b1a58d2b5">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3V0dWJlLmNvbS93YXRjaD92PW1ZQ3I2ZHhROW1n" target="_blank"&gt;visalus shakes &lt;/a&gt;Okay what's the big deal about Visalus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the big companies making their footprint in the network marketing industry is Visalus. You have to do your part as a marketer to learn how to market and create a sufficient relationship with your prospects. Remember that and you will be well on your way to Global Ambassador status.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ViSalus home business opportunity is making a name for itself in the network marketing industry. So is this company a scam or a legitimate home based business opportunity?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Company&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ViSalus Sciences founders Ryan Blair, Blake Mallen, and Nick Sarnicola created ViSalus with a vision to combine passion for people with the principles of health and entrepreneurship. &quot;;ViSalus&quot;; comes from the Latin &quot;;Vi,&quot;; meaning Life, and &quot;;Salus,&quot;; which means Health and Prosperity. The company is based in Troy, Michigan and was founded in March 1997. The company now has offices in California as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Product Line&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ViSalus product line contains supplements and vitamins in pill, capsule, and liquid form as well as weight loss and anti-aging products. The ViSalus Vi-PAK vitamin and mineral packs where the company's first product. They come in an AM/PM divided packs and retail for $150 for a 30 day supply.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the company's more popular product lines is the ViSalus Trim Slim Shape Program. The program contains about every weight loss product available for purchase including shakes, deter mints, recipe booklet, journal, and even a measuring tape to measure yourself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ViSalus NEURO products are energy drinks that are designed to boost not only your body but also your mind.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Compensation Plan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The ViSalus business opportunity is a network marketing business model. To join the company, you can either join as an &quot;;Associate&quot;; for $39, or the &quot;;Executive Success System&quot;; for $499. ViSalus has a unilevel compensation plan which means that you have to have a specified number of &quot;;qualified&quot;; legs as well as sales volume quotas. You also have to maintain a certain product &quot;;autoship&quot;; on a monthly basis to qualify for your commissions. As with any network marketing company, there are levels of advancement. With each level, the pay scale and bonuses increase.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;u&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Summary&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/u&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In conclusion, ViSalus is not a scam. To add to the problem, there are also quite a few scams which will make you lose your investment and waste your time. However if you are looking for a good opportunity and a business model of MLM which is quite comprehensive, consider Visalus.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Visalus is a Vi-Net system of marketing which lets it members earn according to the work and effort they put in to the system. This system of marketing gives the online members, opportunity to earn from a fast and lucrative plan of compensation, by way of commissions and incentives. The Visalus system of marketing provides you with the basics for building online relationships so that you can gather many clients. The system actually lets you funnel a huge stream of online people who are like-minded; thus giving you the chance to convert your online business into a powerhouse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The compensation plan of Visalus is actually quite revolutionary as it provides you opportunities to earn higher commissions and lucrative incentives, which could be a fully paid BMW!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>