<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="9c70543823fffbef1293ec40ad0c5bd8">			When you buy digital cameras for kids, you want to get one that is easy to use, and allows your child to learn how to take pictures as simply as possible. Kids are becoming familiar with technology at ever younger ages so don't be too surprised if your five year old wants a camera. The following are some tips to help you search for the right digital camera for your child.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Depending on how young your child is, you may want to check out the cameras offered by toy companies such as Fisher Price and Disney which are designed for kids. These are real cameras and not just toys, and they are made to appeal to children's tastes, with bright colors, large buttons and easy to use features. Kids are generally rough on their toys so these cameras are sturdy so they can withstand rough treatment. Getting a young child one of these toy models is a good idea if they are young as these companies are experienced at making toys that young children enjoy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will also want to consider the resolution, which is measured in mega pixels. You can end up with blurry photos if the number of mega pixels is too low.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The price of cameras made for kids is kept low by limiting the number of mega pixels. If your child is old enough to notice the quality of the pictures he takes, or has any experience with taking photographs, you may want to consider something a little better. If you want a digital camera that takes higher quality picture than a child's camera, there are decently priced ones available.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Among the other features you should look for in digital cameras for kids, a USB cable can be very useful. If you want to be able to share the pictures you take, print, store or put them online you'll need this USB cord. You won't find this feature in many toy cameras but almost every real camera will have one. Every age child will want to be able to move the pictures from one place to another. As technology advances, it's likely that most digital cameras on the market will come with a USB cable, but it's something you should make sure of when shopping for digital cameras for kids. It may be necessary to purchase one seperately in some cases. Digital cameras for kids are quite more evolved from what they once were. Your child's age is the main factor in how much you should spend. Now that you are equipped with this knowledge you are ready to hit the mall for some shopping. Fortunately, recent advances in technology have made using cameras simpler in many ways.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NyaXR0ZXJnZWVrLmNvbS9zZXNhbWUtc3RyZWV0LWxldHMtcm9jay1lbG1vLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;lets rock elmo&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NyaXR0ZXJnZWVrLmNvbS9uZXJmLXZvcnRleC1uaXRyb24tZ3Vucy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;nerf vortex nitron guns&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NyaXR0ZXJnZWVrLmNvbS9zdGFyLXdhcnMtZm9yY2UtZngtbGlnaHRzYWJlci1hbmFraW4v" target="_blank"&gt;;star wars light fx saber anakin&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>