<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d692049f99bec2dbbd735b3eb0e051de">			The diverse and vast country of India is home to several wildlife reserves, parks and sanctuaries. These parks and reserves provide abundant scope of the nature loving tourists and adventurous enthusiasts to cherish and know the wildlife and nature. Indian wildlife sanctuaries and national parks are rich in their flora and fauna and attract a large gathering of tourists and wildlife enthusiasts from all over the world.  Wild animals, chirping birds, beautiful scenery of dense forests of Indian wildlife sanctuaries &amp;amp; reserves cast a spell in the minds of visitors who come here from different parts of the world. Each and every reserve has its own specialty and has its unique charm and variety to offers its visitors.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ranthambore National Park, Sariska Tiger Reserve, Keoladeo Ghana National Park (formerly known as Bharatpur Bird Sanctuary), Jim Corbett National Park (India’s first national park &amp;amp; tiger reserve), Great Himalayan National Park, Kaziranga National Park, Manas Wildlife Sanctuary, Sunderbans National Park, etc are among popular destinations for wildlife tourism in northern India. Kanha Tiger Reserve and Bandhavgarh National Park in Madhya Pradesh are popular destinations for jungle tourism in Central India. All the aforementioned destinations are very popular among tourists coming from different parts of the world. Many of destinations are also coupled with national parks of Nepal; and provide tourists a opportunity to experience the charm of India Nepal wildlife tour.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Periyar Tiger &amp;amp; Elephant Reserve, Bandipur National Park, Nagarhole National Park, Mudumalai Wildlife Sanctuary, Wayanad Wildlife Sanctuary, B. R. Hills Wildlife Sanctuary, Eravikulam National Park, etc are famous destinations on south India wildlife tour. There are many other wildlife sanctuaries and parks in this country which can lure you. If you are fascinated to India tiger tour then you should considered these destinations; such as Ranthambore, Corbett, Kanha, Bandhavgarh and Periyar.		</conversation>		<conversation id="392ea8fbbb31b71ef0a067d672c1ad13">			Golden Triangle is one of the most sought after travel circuits in northern India. It covers Delhi, Jaipur and Agra as its destinations. Golden triangle is recommended for all those who are visiting India for first time and want to see the best charm of India tourism in short period. On this trip tourists have a great opportunity to see some of the best Indian monuments featuring forts, palaces, temples, museums and modern buildings. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The journey of Golden triangle starts with sightseeing in Delhi, the capital city of India. Red Fort, Jama Masjid, Qutub Minar, Humayun’s Tomb, India Gate, Laxmi Narayan Tempe, etc are prominent tourist attractions in the city. Agra is the second destination and famous for Mughal monuments like Taj Mahal, Agra Fort and Itmad-Ud-Daulah Tomb. Jaipur, the Pink City of India and the capital of Rajasthan, is the third destination. It is famous for magnificent Rajput buildings and historical forts &amp; monuments. Jantar Mantar, Hawa Mahal, City Palace, Birla Temple, Amber Fort, Albert Hall Museum, etc are attractions in the city of Jaipur. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In general, golden triangle tours shall lure you most. These days golden triangle is popular among tourists with its exciting extensions. There are many people who do not just want to see Delhi, Agra and Jaipur. They also need some other fascinating destinations and attractions to make the trip even more enjoyable and fantastic. If you want to see Camel Breeding Farm &amp; Junagarh Fort then you might consider golden triangle tour with Bikaner. If you are religious person and want to see some temples then you should couple the trip with places like Varanasi, Haridwar, Pushkar, Rishikesh, Ajmer, etc. Ranthambore National Park, Sariska Tiger Reserve and Bharatpur Bird Sanctuary are also popular extensions of golden triangle package in India.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more information visit:-  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.goldentriangletour.ws"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.goldentriangletour.ws&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>