<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="dcf7be7cd7d91ee5faa54316d6896635">			Budapest has beautiful natural boulevards, picturesque bridges, captivating attractions, and, of coursesome unique restaurants. Truly, the top restaurants in Budapest are easily among the top restaurants in Central Europe and indeed the globe.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The obstacle facing the majority of tourists coming to visit the city of Budapest lies in the fact that they aren't certain how to find the best restaurants in Budapest. If they stay among the useless tourist restaurants all along Vaci Utca, they end up being stuck with bad stuff and spending way too much money for nothing. If they try Raday Street they have the exact same difficulty: nothing but tourist chow at outrageous rates. Lots of the restaurants in the hotels which might be convenient to the average tourist remain definitely nice places to eat, but they are often international restaurants that do not really show visitors the nature of Hungarian food, so what's the point?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now there's no need to worry that you might not locate the best restaurants in Budapest when you come. Budapest diners may now use a easy online service entitled TableFree.hu. The web site offers its users the chance to search through over 100 of the best places throughout the entire city in order to locate places which are what you are searching for. And there's no need to be concerned that that the restaurant might turn out not to be very good, for the system only partners with places that are clearly the best restaurants in their cuisine categories.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's simple to make use of TableFree to locate a wonderful Budapest restaurant. All a visitor has to do is to navigate to the home page, then go to the &quot;Quick Search&quot; area of the page. Through the quick search, you can choose the price, type of kitchen, and area you find yourself interested in. The site will then show you all the Budapest restaurants that satisfy your requirements, and you can be sure that those restaurants must all be quality places because the restaurants are part of the TableFree site.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're trying to put together a walking tour of Budapest or you simply know you want to eat some place close to the hotel you're staying at, the system can let you find convenient restaurants in Budapest by using a simple map search. That search function will be situated near the bottom of the homepage on TableFree. Just indicate your location and the search map will return the relevant restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The most valuable feature of the system must be how it gives users the chance to book reservations over the Internet, with just a few clicks of a mouse. This is useful for restaurants because it makes it possible for Budapest restaurants to accept online reservations automatically, from anywhere in the world, even in peak business hours or at times when the restaurant isn't open, since the site doesn't sleep. And it's even more wonderful for diners, given that they can connect with restaurants quickly and easily, secure that the booking is noted and marked by the restaurant. That's how the TableFree system makes it quite straightforward to reserve a table at a restaurant in Budapest with full confidence that you'll enjoy precisely the eating outing they're after.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbudapest.tablefree.hu%2Fen%2Fhow-it-works%2F10"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://budapest.tablefree.hu/en/how-it-works/10&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Findependent.academia.edu%2FDavidAvila%2FBlog%2F30202%2FTripadvisor-Sux-Budapest-Restaurants-Techs-Latest-Battleground"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://independent.academia.edu/DavidAvila/Blog/30202/Tripadvisor-Sux-Budapest-Restaurants-Techs-Latest-Battleground&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbudapest.tablefree.hu%2Fen%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://budapest.tablefree.hu/en/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="25b08306d16f3bb1b97f661ee094f49">			The system offers visitors the chance to search through more than a hundred of the best establishments in the entire city to locate restaurants which are precisely what you are looking for. Even better there's no need to be concerned that that the restaurant might not be very good, for the site only works with places that are tops in their price groups.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is really quite easy to make use of TableFree to learn about a nice Budapest restaurant. The only thing that a visitor needs to do is to look at TableFree.hu, and then use the &quot;Quick Search&quot; portion of the page. Through the use of the quick search functionality, you can simply choose the price categories, types of cuisine, and geographical zone you are interested in. The web site will next show you all the restaurants that match your criteria, and then you can be certain that those restaurants will be good establishments because the restaurants are on the TableFree system.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are planning a walking tour around Budapest or you simply realize that you want to try a restaurant adjacent to your hotel, the system will let you find nearby restaurants by means of a map search. The map search function will be found near the bottom of the home page of TableFree.hu. Simply indicate your position and the map will give you the appropriate options.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The most interesting part of the system must be how it gives users the chance to book reservations through the web, with only a couple of clicks of a mouse. This is great for restaurants since it makes it possible for Budapest restaurants to take reservations automatically, because the page doesn't sleep. It's even more useful for diners, given that they can connect with restaurants quickly and easily, secure that the reservation has been recorded and received by the restaurant. TableFree.hu covers every price category, ethnicity, and district available in the city, with the result that people who use the site need not be concerned that they are neglecting an unknown gem.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A second service that seems to be prevalent in this Budapest restaurant space is TripAdvisor, of course, yet that page has its own issues. See what I'm saying&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/unsure.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The TableFree system gets around the issue of useless, nameless restaurant reviews in a couple of ways. First, it only takes on the very best restaurants (in each category, ethnicity, and region) anyhow. In this way, the TableFree system makes it almost unbelievably easy to reserve a table at a top Budapest restaurant with complete certainty that diners will have exactly the eating outing you wanted.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbudapest.tablefree.hu%2Fen%2Fhow-it-works%2F10"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://budapest.tablefree.hu/en/how-it-works/10&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbudapest.tablefree.hu%2Fen%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://budapest.tablefree.hu/en/&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Findependent.academia.edu%2FDavidAvila%2FBlog%2F30202%2FTripadvisor-Sux-Budapest-Restaurants-Techs-Latest-Battleground"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://independent.academia.edu/DavidAvila/Blog/30202/Tripadvisor-Sux-Budapest-Restaurants-Techs-Latest-Battleground&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>