<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="de3ad9d21b0ab0630304ca385092de88">			But using a little know how and some free time, you should be able to fix it yourself.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The very first thing to remember is to wait for your engine to cool off. You may want to wait at least a day after running your car or truck.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your next step may be to disconnect the negative battery cable. But one disadvantage associated with &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RpbWluZ2JlbHRyZXBsYWNlbWVudHouY29tL3RpbWluZy1iZWx0LW5vaXNlLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;timing belt noise&lt;/a&gt;; is you need to replace it every several interval.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the timing belt noise slips just by one tooth, the algorithm stops operating. This can be a real problem when you are miles away from your nearest help!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is no absolute certain way to check that a part has broken down. Instead, changing it at prescription intervals will lessen the chance that it will break before it is replaced. In addition, many mechanics advise changing the water pump at the same time as the belt - even if it hasn't failed - as the vast majority of labor related to updating a water pump was already accomplished when changing this belt. This is your call being a water pump could last providing your car or it could fail at some future point. If the latter, you could be faced with a big repair bill besides the inconvenience of having your car or truck out of commission for many days.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many weekend mechanics feel comfortable enough to replace their car's timing belt noise themselves. With a trusty Chilton and Haynes auto maintenance and repair manual by your side you can pop the hood and remove and replace the part in no time at all. Shop via a reputable online wholesaler to examine your replacement part options and to find a product that is befitting you. Save a bundle of money by carrying it out yourself and avoid that hassles and expense of traveling to your dealer's repair go shopping.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Beneath the hood of your car lies the timing belt noise (T&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;. Consequently, a TB failure is unlikely to damage either, though it will result in your [url=]timing belt problems[/url] shutting down.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As outlined earlier, your owner's manual include the automaker's recommended company interval for changing this timing belt noise. You should also take the time to inspect it every 10, 000 to 15, 000 miles.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On most vehicles, you should be capable to examine the TB just by lifting the hood to your car and removing some sort of plastic covering behind which often it sits. Look for small cracks and fissures in the rubber. Also, inspect the belt's teeth to make sure all of them are in good condition. In the event you see a tooth that is broken or showing signs of advanced wear, change the timing belt noise. In any other case, you will risk the belt slipping when you need it and potentially causing hurt.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your vehicle's timing belt noise plays an important role in the smooth operation of your engine. To avoid expensive repair bills, make sure you change it using the service interval recommended inside your owner's manual.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8ff5d5c5d5b9954d5c029e1ad2f6aff3">			But one disadvantage associated with timing belt noise is you need to replace it every confident interval.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RpbWluZ2JlbHRyZXBsYWNlbWVudHouY29tL3RpbWluZy1iZWx0LW5vaXNlLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;timing belt noise&lt;/a&gt;; slips simply by one tooth, the engine stops operating. Replacing the timing belt noise is some of those precautionary measures you do not want to say later on that you wish you would probably have just gone ahead with. Pay a little now to avoid wasting a lot later.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Let's say you do not replace your timing belt noise whether it is recommended, or simply didn't know that you needed to. This will sometimes get lucky and people who buy a car or truck. The previous owner can have good maintenance records, but neglect to tell you the vehicle is well past needing a timing belt noise. Signs of an bad belt include change in the engine's performance. This includes specific things like stalls, backfires or running roughly with a great deal of vibration. Squealing noises and smoke are two other obvious signs you are having a problem using a belt in your engine. It is recommended you take the car in immediately to a pro before the problem gets worse.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Keep in mind when replacing timing belt noises, many mechanics will offer to replace your water pump. This is usually a precautionary measure. Most water pumps last everything of the car which has no problems. This does not meas they're just exempt from malfunctioning. The reason why the mechanic will offer this service is because with the belt off of, replacing the pump is very simple. They are not wanting to take you for a lot of money as they will not be able to charge you much for labor. A good idea here is to just ask the mechanic what the history is on the water pump in your model car. If the pool pump generally does not fail, it is an activity you can go without the need of.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those with higher performance cars might want to entertain after market timing belt noises. These belts are created to handle a little more abuse than the average timing belt noise. While they cannot handle the abuse some sort of race car driver will use the belt, it will handle a greater revving engine better. This is because the belt is more reinforced in comparison to the average belt. You pays off more for the element, but you will be ready to enjoy the knowledge that your belt is secure.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To ensure that your engine to carry out effectively, the pistons inside combustion chambers must synchronize perfectly along with the opening and closing of your intake and exhaust valves. With a trusty Chilton or even Haynes auto maintenance and repair manual by your side you can pop the hood and replace the part in state. This can result in damage to the affected valve, the piston, and both.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In a non-interference engine, there is more [url=]timing belt problems[/url] room relating to the pistons and valves.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>