<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="13a437c4431803f917404f8c96a5bbbd">			The first step to ensuring that your items make it to your new apartment or home is getting strong, sturdy boxes. This is especially the case if they will be stacked on top of one another in a moving truck. The boxes placed on the bottom will be under quite a bit of pressure, so they must be strong. We all have fragile items that have value to us, so having quality boxes is necessary in order to prevent damage to them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In addition to quality, you also want to have the right sized boxes. They are available in small, medium, large, x-large, and they come in a variety of shapes as well. For instance, you can buy moving boxes that are shaped to fit flat screen TVs, wardrobe boxes that allow you to hang clothing, and boxes suited for various other items such as lamps, pictures, glassware, and so on.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first packing tip then is to use the right boxes for your items. A guideline is to place the heaviest items either in small or medium boxes. For instance, if you packed a bunch of books in a large box, then it would be awfully difficult to carry. By placing them into smaller ones, they will naturally be lighter and far less of a burden.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other items that go into small moving boxes include DVDs, small appliances, tools, kitchen utensils, magazines, electronics, and so on.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Medium moving boxes are suited for kitchen items, toys, stereo equipment, and certain appliances.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Large and extra large moving boxes are reserved for computers, other larger electronic items, lamps, blankets, sheets, and pillows. Their good for items that are bulky but lightweight.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always be conscious of what you are packing into a box, as you want to make sure that it's not too heavy to lift.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wardrobe boxes are recommended because you can hang certain clothing just as you would in your closet. A prime example are dresses. No woman wants to fold their dresses and pack them into cardboard boxes. Wardrobe boxes are also good for jackets and other clothing that you want to avoid wrinkling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be sure also to buy dish pack boxes so these items are adequately protected. These boxes are usually double walled, and can be used to pack dishes, glassware, plates, among others.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you have a lot of office files, then you might want to consider buying file moving boxes. They are designed specifically to hold legal or letter sized folders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldmVyeWJveC5jby51aw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Removal boxes&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="88903d374b63d943f8fc3f00411cf033">			Supplies needed when getting ready to move include moving boxes, padding and tape. These boxes come in a variety of sizes and dimensions to fit any item and can be purchased online or at retail stores. When moving, using uniform sized boxes is recommended, as it allows for easy stacking.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Type of Boxes&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Boxes come in many sizes, from small boxes that can easily be held in the arms, to huge boxes that require two people to lift. Large boxes can be used for bulky, light items such as stuffed animals or pillows or blankets. Smaller boxes should be used for heavy items such as books.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you purchase the boxes from a moving supplies company, you may be able to purchase specialty boxes. These boxes are designed for specific items. For example, to pack fragile glasses, there is a box which contains an insert that divides the interior into smaller square spaces. This allows each individual glass to be placed in each square without knocking against another glass.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For papers and folders, office supply stores sell special filing boxes specially designed to fit letter or legal sized folders. These cardboard boxes would work for storing and moving. Built in holes on the sides function as handles for easy lifting.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Labeling Boxes&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you purchase moving boxes from a moving supply company, chances are that there is a preprinted area designed for labeling. Labeling boxes will help identify the contents of each box. Boxes can be labeled identifying the room it was packed from or whose belongings are inside. It can be labeled with the general category of the items inside, such as clothes or dishes. If valuable items are packed inside, it is not recommended that the item be labeled specifically on the box, due to possible theft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Moving on a Financial Budget&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those who are on a tight financial budget, it is still possible to pack and move. Renting a moving truck and moving the boxes by yourself without professional help can save you in moving costs. Ask friends and family for assistance in moving. Check local grocery stores for empty used boxes that may be in good condition. Newspaper or linens can be used as padding to wrap items inside the boxes. Instead of using moving boxes for light, bulky items, use heavy duty garbage bags instead and tape them securely shut. Instead of using the more durable, thicker moving blankets, consider using any existing blankets or comforters or even sheets to help protect large furniture items.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When organizing the packed boxes, it may be a good idea to separate the fragile items so that they are placed on top of the stacks of boxes in the moving truck. For important, valuable items such as important documents or jewelry, it is not recommended that these items get packed in with the other boxes in the moving truck. They should be kept close on hand so that they do not get damaged or lost during the move.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldmVyeWJveC5jby51aw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Packing Materials&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="4d4fb98b59db52542fdd806edf615e8e">			Supplies needed when getting ready to move include moving boxes, padding and tape. These boxes come in a variety of sizes and dimensions to fit any item and can be purchased online or at retail stores. When moving, using uniform sized boxes is recommended, as it allows for easy stacking.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Type of Boxes&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Boxes come in many sizes, from small boxes that can easily be held in the arms, to huge boxes that require two people to lift. Large boxes can be used for bulky, light items such as stuffed animals or pillows or blankets. Smaller boxes should be used for heavy items such as books.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you purchase the boxes from a moving supplies company, you may be able to purchase specialty boxes. These boxes are designed for specific items. For example, to pack fragile glasses, there is a box which contains an insert that divides the interior into smaller square spaces. This allows each individual glass to be placed in each square without knocking against another glass.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For papers and folders, office supply stores sell special filing boxes specially designed to fit letter or legal sized folders. These cardboard boxes would work for storing and moving. Built in holes on the sides function as handles for easy lifting.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Labeling Boxes&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you purchase moving boxes from a moving supply company, chances are that there is a preprinted area designed for labeling. Labeling boxes will help identify the contents of each box. Boxes can be labeled identifying the room it was packed from or whose belongings are inside. It can be labeled with the general category of the items inside, such as clothes or dishes. If valuable items are packed inside, it is not recommended that the item be labeled specifically on the box, due to possible theft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Moving on a Financial Budget&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those who are on a tight financial budget, it is still possible to pack and move. Renting a moving truck and moving the boxes by yourself without professional help can save you in moving costs. Ask friends and family for assistance in moving. Check local grocery stores for empty used boxes that may be in good condition. Newspaper or linens can be used as padding to wrap items inside the boxes. Instead of using moving boxes for light, bulky items, use heavy duty garbage bags instead and tape them securely shut. Instead of using the more durable, thicker moving blankets, consider using any existing blankets or comforters or even sheets to help protect large furniture items.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When organizing the packed boxes, it may be a good idea to separate the fragile items so that they are placed on top of the stacks of boxes in the moving truck. For important, valuable items such as important documents or jewelry, it is not recommended that these items get packed in with the other boxes in the moving truck. They should be kept close on hand so that they do not get damaged or lost during the move.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldmVyeWJveC5jby51aw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Packing Materials&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>