<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="84763f65f644d41994751f7100d4d24">			.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oaWdobGFuZHBhcmtkdW1wc3Rlci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Roll Of DumpsterHighland Park&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55b3V0dWJlLmNvbS93YXRjaD92PTJ3OFk5cm93eUhn" target="_blank"&gt;Rent a Dumpster Highland Park&lt;/a&gt;The Holiday Season is a beautiful season in the Dallas Metroplex, despite the fact that the ground isn't constantly blanketed in snow. Central Presbyterian Religious, at 402 N. University St., presents Bethlehem Revisited from 6 to 9 p. m. Dec. 5-7 together with Dec. 12-14. A candlelight Christmas Home Tour will be from 2 to 8 k. m. Dec. 6-7 and Dec. 12-14. Enchanted Pines, a chain link ice-skating rink at South Rogers and Madison roadways, opens Dec. 5 and will be open Fridays to Sundays as a result of Dec. 28. Details: WaxahachieChamber. com. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;If you are going to visit Kuala Lumpur, you should consider Genting Highlands in your itinerary. Genting is a famous highland resort in Malaysia and it is accessible by car inside 45 minutes (52 kilometers) in the capital of Malaysia. This is the sanctuary for excitement, with regard to retreat and for family vacations. The highland resort can be found at approximately 2, 000 feets above sea level. With its cool climate together with all the luxuries and excitements, Genting highlands is always a favorite travel spot for the domestic tourists and for the international people to Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Genting website hosts a world-class casino, an indoor and a chain link theme parks suitable for your family, international shows, pubs and discos, shopping arcades, an interior archery range, game arcades, a topsy-turvy for kids, a 18-hole par-71 golf course, etc. For your right away lodging convenient, there are five luxury Genting Hotels to your selection. It's a City of Entertainment in Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt; Addressing Genting Highlands: &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. &lt;u&gt; As a result of car &lt;/u&gt;: Genting Highlands can be reached from Kuala Lumpur or from Kuantan via this Karak Expressway. For visitors who are from the northern regions of Malaysia, with the link road passing in the Batang Kali town may be the shortest path to reach Genting Highlands (stop from Plus Expressway with Tanjung Malim and set off for Batang Kali city). &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. &lt;u&gt; By Genting Exhibit bus &lt;/u&gt;: The Genting Express bus is available from Puduraya Bus Fatal, Pasarakyat, KL Sentral Stop and Terminal Putra LRT Gombak within Kuala Lumpur. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. &lt;u&gt; By taxi &lt;/u&gt;: Taxi service from Kuala Lumpur to Genting is accessible at Puduraya Bus Terminal &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. &lt;u&gt; As a result of cable car &lt;/u&gt;: Before reaching to Genting Highland at the township of Gohtong Jaya, visitors will have the option to experience a breathtaking ride up to Genting Highlands via that Skyway Cable Cars. This 3. 4-kilometer ride to Genting Highlands will take approximately 11 minutes, traveling at an amazing high speed at 6 meters per second. You can entry to the Skyway Station at Gohtong Jaya through the Genting Express bus, as a result of car, by Limousine discipline or by Luxury discipline. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. &lt;u&gt; As a result of Limousine coach &lt;/u&gt;: 24/7 door-to-door Limousine service is available for pick up at anywhere nationwide. Booking is usually done at the Kuala Lumpur International airport. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. &lt;u&gt; By Genting Luxury coach &lt;/u&gt;: The Genting Luxury coach service leaves in the Kuala Lumpur International International airport and from many destinations across Malaysia. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. &lt;u&gt; Some others &lt;/u&gt;: Helicopter service is usually available for charter. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;em&gt; Luxurious Genting Hotels: &lt;/em&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can find five superior Genting hotels.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>