<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e4b948d0239c52133e61191d58525c05">			Panasonic was established in 1918 by Konosuke Matsushita.  Their first commercially produced devices were actually a 2 way light socket adapter and an accessory plug adapter. The earliest Matsushita goods ended up being extremely popular since they were of higher quality with a reduced cost. These founding principles are alive in Panasonic in the present day with superior quality electronic devices with premium abilities but no  premium price tag. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Following The Second World War, Panasonic expanded dramatically. Panasonic merchandise, particularly the transistor radios soon became internationally renowned. Exports to the United States escalated at a fast pace as Panasonic established manufacturing plants world wide. Matsushita 1st launched U.S. offices in New York City in 1959 as Matsushita Electric Corporation of America (MECA). Panasonic’s rapid advancement attracted worldwide attention and in 1961, Panasonic’s founder, Konosuke Matsushita in fact made the cover of Time Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since then, Panasonic continues to be a leader in technological know-how. Panasonic has had plasma TVs which were often the largest commercially available.  Panasonic &quot;1sts&quot; in the plasma HDTV market place range from the 1st seventy inch plasma, the first 103&quot; plasma and now has a 152&quot;  plasma TV. While at the same time distributing a line of LCD televisions, Panasonic has refined and enhanced the plasma TV technology to present some of the finest plasma televisions available while some other leading manufacturers like Pioneer, Mitsubishi and Fujitsu discontinued the plasma technology and fled the plasma marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A primary reason a number of the plasma TV manufacturers dropped plasma technoligy was the fear of regulation banning the plasma devices that traditionally utilized much more power than the competing Liquid crystal display technologies. Panasonic persevered and designed plasma televisions that require way less power and are considerably thinner to match Liquid crystal display television sets. The Panasonic plasmas are unmatched in black level, luminosity, off axis viewing and very fast pixel response times by their Liquid crystal display challengers. Image “burn in” and plasma screen life that plagued earlier on plasma TVs have both long been reduced by way of the improved designs. These characteristics produce a much better viewing experience than competing brands and technologies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Panasonic Viera series of high definition (HD) TVs is just about the best currently available and includes Liquid crystal display, 3D enhanced LCD, plasma and 3-D enhanced plasma televisions. Besides televisions, Panasonic manufactures all sorts of consumer electronics. When you invest in a quality device, you should maintain and repair that device to obtain the utmost enjoyment and product life. When searching for an authorized Panasonic television repair center around the Chicago land metropolitin area you will find only one choice, Rex Service Company.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rex Service Company is a member in good standing with National Service Alliance (NSA), Electric Service Dealers Association (ESDA) and NESDA (National Electronic Service Dealers Association). Rex Service has a business license in the Village of Worth Illinois, has workman’s compensation insurance and liability insurance coverage. Rex Service is also rated favorably by the Better Business Bureau. Call Rex Service Company today at: 800-HI-REX-TV (800-447-398) or visit us at 7030 W. 111th Street, Worth Illinois 60482&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tvrepair.biz%2Fpanasonictvrepair.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tvrepair.biz/panasonictvrepair.html&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tvrepair.biz%2Fsonytvrepair.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tvrepair.biz/sonytvrepair.html&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tvrepair.biz"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tvrepair.biz&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f7175a2905d95972c71d297a33e8aa74">			Panasonic was founded in Nineteen Eighteen by Konosuke Matsushita.  Their initial commercial devices were actually a two way light bulb socket adapter along with an accessory plug adapter. The first Matsushita products were highly regarded because they were better level of quality with a lower cost. Those founding principles are alive within Panasonic today with quality consumer electronics with top notch functionality without a high price tag. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After World War 2, Panasonic grew dramatically. Panasonic products, especially the transistor radios soon became globally renowned. Exports to the United States escalated at a fast pace as Panasonic located manufacturing facilities world wide. Matsushita first opened U.S. locations in New York City in 1959 as Matsushita Electric Corporation of America (MECA). Panasonic’s rapid advancement attracted world wide awareness and in 1961, Panasonic’s CEO, Konosuke Matsushita even was on the cover of Time Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since then, Panasonic continues to be a leader in technological innovation. Panasonic has had plasma TVs that were some of the largest available for sale.  Panasonic “firsts” in the television marketplace include the 1st 70 inch plasma, the earliest 103&quot; plasma and now has a 152 inch  plasma television. While at the same time distributing a line of LCD televisions, Panasonic has polished and improved the plasma TV technology to provide some of the finest plasma televisions available while other leading manufacturers like Pioneer, Mitsubishi and Fujitsu abandoned plasma development and left the plasma marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A primary reason a number of the plasma TV producers dropped plasma was anxiety about regulation prohibiting the plasma devices that historically consumed a lot more power compared to the rivalling LCD technology. Panasonic persisted and created plasma TVs that use way less electrical power and are much thinner to match LCD sets. The Panasonic plasma televisions happen to be unparalleled in black level, brightness, off center viewing and very fast pixel response times by their Liquid crystal display challengers. Image “burn in” and plasma display lifespan which plagued earlier on plasma TVs have both been minimized by way of the improved designs. These features give you a much better viewing experience than competitive brands and technologies.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Panasonic Viera line of high-definition (HD) televisions is just about the very best you can get today and includes Liquid crystal display, 3D enhanced LCD, plasma and 3D enhanced plasma. Besides TV's, Panasonic manufactures a variety of consumer electronics. When you invest in a high quality product, you maintain and repair that unit to receive maximum satisfaction and product life. When looking for a factory authorized Panasonic television repair shop around the Chicago land area there is just one single option, Rex Service Company.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rex Service Company is a proud member in good standing with National Service Alliance (NSA), Electric Service Dealers Association (ESDA) and NESDA (National Electronic Service Dealers Association). Rex Service carries a business license from the Village of Worth Illinois, has got workman’s compensation insurance and liability insurance coverage. Rex Service is also rated favorably from the Better Business Bureau. Phone Rex Service Company now at: 800-HI-REX-TV (800-447-398) or visit us at 7030 W. 111th Street, Worth Illinois 60482&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tvrepair.biz"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tvrepair.biz&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tvrepair.biz%2Fpanasonictvrepair.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tvrepair.biz/panasonictvrepair.html&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tvrepair.biz%2Fsonytvrepair.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tvrepair.biz/sonytvrepair.html&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>