<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="7">		<conversation id="78199afcd4cad6a4b98a6ca1658b7946">			&lt;div class="fontRenderer"&gt;;&lt;div id="originalText_bbf7a32afbefcc574d1201f888856191"&gt;;Yeaaa.....so i just started this and i really need some new friends so if anyone is interested...i like emo,skater,punk,goth,or scene people lolz.But i have my bestie on here and i need more...help a girl out??&lt;/div&gt;;
		&lt;script type="text/javascript"&gt;;
			var filenames = ["/s/j/class.fontrenderer.js"];

			ComCore.BootLoader.loadJavascriptFiles(filenames, false, function() 
			{
				new ComCore.FontRenderer("_2311e7a543cbd382b972f5244547c946c7c4586d5c26f424d074b8810e443782", "Yeaaa.....so+i+just+started+this+and+i+really+need+some+new+friends+so+if+anyone+is+interested...i+like+emo%2Cskater%2Cpunk%2Cgoth%2Cor+scene+people+lolz.But+i+have+my+bestie+on+here+and+i+need+more...help+a+girl+out%3F%3F", "bbf7a32afbefcc574d1201f888856191");
			});
		&lt;/script&gt;;&lt;/div&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5781d5ac40ba192d557326753a85b2ca">			Ok i found out i was in a coma for a year when i was five and i lost all of my memorie!
&lt;br /&gt;;Why didnt anybody tell me this?!
&lt;br /&gt;;And i find out i had a twin sister that died at birth and my REAL MOM is dead!
&lt;br /&gt;;And at this time of my grieving i have nowone to talk to.
&lt;br /&gt;;And the one person who i want to talk to hates me and they are my cousin!
&lt;br /&gt;;Now i wonder every day now what things were like b4 now,b4 the coma,b4 i was born.
&lt;br /&gt;;I dont know what to belive now.
&lt;br /&gt;;And Josh Benmore if you read this i want you to know.
&lt;br /&gt;;Im glad we met and i love you and i need to talk to you.		</conversation>		<conversation id="55e770f9adc421940b46c617370175f">			I never think it would end this way.
&lt;br /&gt;;I always thought that we would stay the same.
&lt;br /&gt;;But now i know that i was wrong.
&lt;br /&gt;;You completely forgot our song
&lt;br /&gt;;You took my heart and broke it to bits.
&lt;br /&gt;;Now everything i do is like a hit.
&lt;br /&gt;;I cant stop wondering how it could have been.
&lt;br /&gt;;But now i know i will never love again.
&lt;br /&gt;;This is the last straw.
&lt;br /&gt;;To where im walking down a empty hall.		</conversation>		<conversation id="277d2d77baaf9ca2a65c00857c13e53d">			Okay so I went to school today and hung out with my friend at Advisor/Advisee class.
&lt;br /&gt;;And I ask her if she can hang this weekend because I plan my weekends a whole week ahead.
&lt;br /&gt;;And she says to me this exactly &quot;I am not allowed to hang out with you cuz my dad don't like u&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;I am sitting here thinking &quot;Wtf he used to love me what happened?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;And she said its the fact I have piercings!!
&lt;br /&gt;;That is kinda fucking prejudice don't you think?
&lt;br /&gt;;But I do not care anymore if her dada wants to be a dick let him.
&lt;br /&gt;;But I wish I could see my baby boy (Josh) in person sometime.
&lt;br /&gt;;I would love to see him. If you read this I hope you know I fucking Love You 4ever &amp; Always babe.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But peace out people.
&lt;br /&gt;;Robyn		</conversation>		<conversation id="7817f27c530cb1d40e3da87238dca298">			Okay so I was on here with my baby boy Josh. And Me,Matty,and Travis here a huge slam on the door. We go out there to make sure it wasn't Kimmy (my lil sister) or anything worse than that. So we go out there and my dad is drunk off of his ass! He comes running towards me calling me every name in the book and knees me as hard as he can in my stomach. I end up throwing up blood and he hits Matty in the balls. Making him bad off. And then he hits Travis in his newly placed stiches in his lower stomach. How the hell did I end up with such a crazy father??!!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But the only thing I want to do right now is talk to my baby boy Joshua. I really miss him so much right now. And he would make me feel so much better. So josh babe...if you read this then please send me a massage or something because I really would love to talk to you. I love you baby boy.		</conversation>		<conversation id="4dac2649fd4c057f1081cbaa3a67c48d">			Something horrible happened tonight.
&lt;br /&gt;;Me, Matty, Travis, Jake, and my sister Amy were throwing a party tonight.
&lt;br /&gt;;There was a lot of people and a lot of drinking.
&lt;br /&gt;;Me and Matty and Travis had to leave because it was getting out of hand.
&lt;br /&gt;;So Travis is driving in front of me and matty and I notice nowone is holding on to his wheel.
&lt;br /&gt;;He passed out at the wheel.......and......and he died.
&lt;br /&gt;;MY OWN FUCKING BROTHER DIED!!
&lt;br /&gt;;I will never forget him and I miss him so much.
&lt;br /&gt;;I am so sorry Travis with all my heart.		</conversation>		<conversation id="bfe88026eff625e0ee49c90f171fbc47">			Okay so my stepmom and dad told me that my mom abandoned me when I was 5.
&lt;br /&gt;;But I have been talking to everyone else in my family and they said my dad kidnapped me.
&lt;br /&gt;;And my sister died but turns out my father killed her!
&lt;br /&gt;;I am terrified that I live with him.
&lt;br /&gt;;I just want to leave and be with the one guy who will always make me happy (Josh) but I know that I probably can't do that.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Josh if you read this please talk to me. I need you now more than ever. I love you.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>