<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f1bfac23239d2153cfb6adafc93cd675">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWJhZy1hdS5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;gucci australia&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cheap Gucci Handbag From Designs&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wise have already been stranded on the desert isle during the last three decades, you will have undoubtedly read about Gucci. And may reigning across the fashion world on a huge amount years, without totally without warrant. Gucci makes superior, stylish apparel and accessories for those distinguishing shopper.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guccio Gucci founded this fashion empire in Florence, Italy in 1906. Originally, their core business was the creation of leather products, particularly saddlery. By 1938, is know for Gucci had evolved into lodge logic to become a wide variety of products, so they opened their first retail shop for the Via Condotti in Rome.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gucci new to line of handbags for your Fall/Winter 2005/2006 months are just one more spectacular addition thus to their little difference of designer accessories. My particular favorite from that collection is recognized as &quot;Braided Straps&quot;. It is actually created from the attractive patterned material Gucci is now so well recognized for, and it is beige, ebony, and white in color. The trim and straps are crafted from fine white leather, and also you guess it he straps are braided! We are utterly fond of this bag.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I had also taken a liking towards the &quot;Bardot&quot; model. It's a stunning beauty comparable to its namesake, Brigitte Bardot. This purse is constructed from warm, supple, brown leafy leather having wonderful pattern embossed with it. The metal clasp is really slick, and appears for being very durable. We have an 8 inch shoulder belt, and the trademark Gucci logo is stamped into many of the polished metal hardware.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is so hard to have a gal to find the perfect purse. We find a way to collect them the path boys collect comic books. Concerning given up on wishing to curb my interest in having new handbags, and Gucci bags are in truth the ones Irrrm a sucker for most! I quite literally lust after their purses. I enjoy being the envy of females everywhere when i strut down the block with my Gucci handbags, pretending that we are a supermodel at the runway. Only Gucci has that impact on me!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>