<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="682df28e69da0e1efb07d5677ea1707f">			You'll often see this shortened and will see the abbreviation look like this: 100W or 100w. If you are using a compact fluorescent the number will be more like 16w.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Bulb Shape&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;With Philips Lighting, for example, there are at least 50 bulb shapes in incandescent light bulbs. With halogen and halogena' you will find at least 32 bulb shapes. In Philips Fluorescent and Compact Fluorescent groups there are at least 38 bulb shapes. And lastly with HID, Specialty and LED light Bulbs there are over 50 bulb shapes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;object width=&quot;;640&quot;; height=&quot;;360]&lt;param name=&quot;;movie&quot;; value=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fv%2F303YNr6AVWo%3Fversion%3D3%26amp%3Bamp%3Bhl%3Den_US"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/v/303YNr6AVWo?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_US&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;/param&gt;;&lt;param name=&quot;;allowFullScreen&quot;; value=&quot;;true]&lt;/param&gt;;&lt;param name=&quot;;allowscriptaccess&quot;; value=&quot;;always]&lt;/param&gt;;&lt;embed src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fv%2F303YNr6AVWo%3Fversion%3D3%26amp%3Bamp%3Bhl%3Den_US%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/v/303YNr6AVWo?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_US&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; type=&quot;;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot;; width=&quot;;640&quot;; height=&quot;;360&quot;; allowscriptaccess=&quot;;always&quot;; allowfullscreen=&quot;;true]&lt;/embed&gt;;&lt;/object&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are using a PAR38 in your recessed lighting, that same bulb shape is available in an incandescent, halogen, compact fluorescent or metal halide. The overall length may vary a little but the basic shape of the light bulb will be the same.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How do you know what bulb shape you have? The letters used aren't really abbreviations. Examples of bulb shapes: BT15, BR40, PAR38, T4, G25, A19 and so on. A19 is your common incandescent light bulb often used in table lamps. F, B &amp;amp; BA Shapes are used generally in chandeliers and sconces. BR, ER, PAR, R and others are used in recessed lighting and some outdoor lighting. G are globe light bulbs commonly used in vanity lighting. This is not all the shapes but you get the idea.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you live in California, you might be surprised to know that the state requires contractors of new construction to insert certain fixtures that only use compact fluorescents. These will often take PL bulbs shapes. They are PL-H, PL-S, PL-C, PL-L and PL-T. They vary in regards to base style and length and number of tubes you see on the bulb.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Base Type&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;The most common base types are Medium base and Candelabra base. Medium base is the regular size that is roughly 1&quot;; in diameter. Candelabra base is the much smaller base that is used mainly in sconces, chandeliers and some small portable lamps.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In California the base types of the plug in light bulbs are written like this: G24d-3, G23, 2G8-1, G24q-1 or something in a similar sequence.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Voltage&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Voltage should be chosen based on the voltage of power that is coming into your home. This is indicated in either 120V or 130V. If you have put a 120V light bulb in a table lamp and you've blown a couple pretty quickly, you most likely need a 130V light bulb.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Low voltage lighting is 12 volts or 12v and is generally halogen light bulbs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Spot Vs Flood&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Spot or a flood often used in recessed cans each have varying degrees of swath of light. It might be 10(degrees), 25, 32 or 40 or any number around this range. Spots are a narrower beam and flood light bulbs have a larger beam of light.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Color&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Sometimes you will see on your bulb a number like 827, 830, 835 or 841. All of these numbers are the different colors that Philips compact fluorescent plug ins come in. Other light bulbs may come in varying colors as well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By grasping these simple indicators, most will be able to figure out what kind of light bulb they are holding. Good luck to you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN0ZXJubGlnaHRpbmcuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Led Mr16&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="ddd92f496bc06848a92493c5d8217bcf">			To learn more about LED lighting don't forget to visit the copy writers website at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN0ZXJubGlnaHRpbmcuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Led Mr16&lt;/a&gt;;. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Compact Fluorescent Lamps &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;object width=&quot;;640&quot;; height=&quot;;360]&lt;param name=&quot;;movie&quot;; value=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fv%2F303YNr6AVWo%3Fversion%3D3%26amp%3Bamp%3Bhl%3Den_US"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/v/303YNr6AVWo?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_US&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;/param&gt;;&lt;param name=&quot;;allowFullScreen&quot;; value=&quot;;true]&lt;/param&gt;;&lt;param name=&quot;;allowscriptaccess&quot;; value=&quot;;always]&lt;/param&gt;;&lt;embed src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fv%2F303YNr6AVWo%3Fversion%3D3%26amp%3Bamp%3Bhl%3Den_US%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/v/303YNr6AVWo?version=3&amp;amp;hl=en_US&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; type=&quot;;application/x-shockwave-flash&quot;; width=&quot;;640&quot;; height=&quot;;360&quot;; allowscriptaccess=&quot;;always&quot;; allowfullscreen=&quot;;true]&lt;/embed&gt;;&lt;/object&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CFLs operate similarly to conventional fluorescent lamps where electricity is needed to activate mercury heavy steam that&amp;nbsp; resides in the glass tube. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;are becoming the option for energy efficient lighting there isn't any varied bulb solutions, and the easy training which the light output are usually layered and controlled in comparison to CFL bulbs. Educating yourself about any type of PAR bulbs you now have and doing a bit homework on what exactly LED PAR replacement bulbs are obtainable will go further towards helping you generate a great purchase. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;In today's technologically-advanced conditions, there is a remote for just about anything, including the the amount of light inside or outside of your property. They operate like a remote for your TV or BLU-RAY player. What makes these remotes a lot more interesting is they can usually come with three different measurements. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will find a keychain size which helps you turn on up to two lights or appliances from outside of your property. Then there is a card size remote that controls around four appliances or lights from outside of your home. The palm pad controller allows you to operate up to help you 16 lights in addition to appliances throughout your own whole home. These various push-button control lighting methods mean you can pull up to your property and turn certain lights on before you decide to even enter, the great safety element. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Multi-Channel Remotes &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A growing number of remote usage has become encouraged in earlier times but people still had to get up to adjust lighting until not long ago when lighting can be adjusted with a simple push of a button for a remote. First introduced ended up the remote light dimmers which might be single channel remotes that only encourage the controller to modify the light that it is connected to. Put simply, you could not adjust every other light in their home with that certain remote. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That is definitely no longer the result as now remote systems are obtainable that power as many as four channels of light throughout the home by using a single online computer support. What is better about these newer systems is likely safe and relatively inexpensive too. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; The variety of Uses Of RCL &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This list is virtually endless for reasons to locate remote control lighting (RCL). Imagine yourself getting yourself into bed at night and having the capability to control your home's light functions right from your bed. Perhaps you forgot to turn a light off completely downstairs, or maybe you heard an audio outside of your house in the middle of the night and that means you reach over adequate the touch to a button you may light up the of your house - that is the sure way so that you can scare off an intruder. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Perhaps your son or daughter awoke in the night time to a negative dream or is not really feeling well; once you first hear a whimper you can actually control the lights within their room which will furnish immediate comfort until you can get there.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>