<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="838037676f7e17fa75a5dd6ad40d6f34">			Religious tolerance in few past decades induced growth of different forms of wicca, or practices which entail utilization of witching forces and capabilities for profit of practitioner.  Astonishingly, stimulant for developing of witchcraft was connected to well-being of society, rather than with mental and inspirational matters, as it happed earlier. &lt;br /&gt;;So broad amount of research has been conducted for wicca and witchcraft last times, hence it’s almost unrealizable for  me to state something fresh.  Even if I set goal of this post just to display leading trends in modern witchery from software developer viewpoint. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I produce software to perform magical rituals and have experience with several crafts : candle magick, lunar magick, wicca spells, knot magick, sigil magic, becharms, etc.  The common trend, existing in all occult traditions is to devote more attention on outside, instead on inbuilt aspects of a ritual. This is the ground why individuals seek for so-called secret spells, or charge spell caster to reach several goals. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although theory of witchcraft  rites is extremely flexible with one criterion – resultant, almost all  such “secret magic spells ” and “ distant rituals ” go wrong, because person didn't elaborate wishing clearly. E.g., wicca spells to banish debt has became extremely fashionable for the last few years. But if you cautiously analyze wish “to banish debt”, you will realise, that in reality this is around obtaining job, inheriting or obtaining money. Just there’s no means to get rid of debt, take out to return it, to fill bankruptcy or to kill creditor. In regard to this such magic spells as “to banish debt” might not function and may institute unpredicted result. Unluckily, inability to analyze causes and results of magic rites or wicca spells has become widespread tendency now, which in turn lead to origination perception in society about witchcraft as a charlatanry. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Evidently envisioning your wish is not sufficient for successful witchcraft ritual. And if you remember Harry Porter or akin books, success depend upon vast majority of components. Yet do not be disappointed with fancy imaginaries of  fiction books. It’s not casual to realize working magic ritual, but it is not really complicated. Manhood exists thousands years and elaborated model and prerequisites for magic ritual to be effective. And the most crucial prerequisite is preparation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wizard must be in specific mental and physiological conditions to do ritual or cast magical spell. Sometime such state is achieved getting intoxicants, drugs, or even with oxygen deprivation. But a great deal more often magical rituals are not accompanied with peculiar preparation at all. And most resources, whether they are spell scripts, net books of shadows, or neighboring witches, do not supply recommendations how to prepare for rite. I think, the central reason - because theydo not know how to prepare for wicca ritual or casting magical spell.  I do not mean space consecration of  athame purification rituals. Because they are easy, they are known.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You too can find huge amount of free magic spells : passion spells, money spells, sorcery spells, curing spells.  Still it’s very challenging to understand the generic mechanics of magic ritual, including preparation. You may try it and render testimonies, whether about serviceableness of the software program, or about its factual effectivity : &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fewicca.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ewicca.net&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fewicca.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ewicca.net&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="72fd572fe26fbb19286b47f3936f77f">			Religious tolerance in few past decades energized development of diverse kinds of witchery, or practices which involve use of witching powers and abilities for do good of practitioner.  Surprisingly, stimulant for development of witchcraft was related to wellbeing of society, rather than with mental and religious subjects, as it occurred earlier. &lt;br /&gt;;So enormous amount of research has been complete for wicca and witchcraft last times, so it’s virtually unfeasible for  me to state something different.  Even if I determine goal of  article merely to display leading tendencies in todays witchcraft from software developer stand. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I program software programs to execute magic rites and obtained experience with several practices : candle magick, lunar magick, wicca spells, knot magick, sigil magic, becharms, etc.  The standard trend, present in all occult practices is to devote more attention on outside, rather than on internal aspects of a ritual. This is the ground why individuals hunting for so-called secret magic spells, or charge spell caster to gain some goals. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although theory of wicca  rites is exceedingly flexible with one measure – final result, majority of  such “secret magical spells ” and “ distant rituals ” fail, because someone didn't elaborate wish understandably. For example, magic spells to banish debt has turned extremely fashionable for the recent few yr. Still if you cautiously analyze wishing “to banish debt”, you will realize, that in reality this is about finding job, inheriting or obtaining money. Just there’s no means to get rid of debt, except to return it, to go bancrupt or to kill creditor. In this respect such spells as “to banish debt” might not function and may bring unexpected result. Alas, unfitness to analyse causes and results of magical rites or wicca spells has become general tendency now, which successively result in origination perception in society about witchcraft as a charlatanry. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obviously understanding your wish is not sufficient for productive wicca rite. And if you remember Harry Porter or akin books, success depend on wide majority of components. Nevertheless do not be disappointed with fancy imaginaries of  fiction movies. It’s not easy to realise working magical rite, but it’s not really complicated. Manhood lives on thousands for really long time and elaborated framework and requirements for magic ritual to be effective. And the most critical prerequisite is preparation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Witch must be in particular psychical and physiological state to execute ritual or cast spell. Sometime such condition is achieved getting alcohol, drugs, or even with oxygen deprivation. But much more often magic rites are not went  with peculiar preparedness in the least. And majority of resources, whether they are magic spell books, internet books of shadows, or neighbouring witches, do not supply instructions how to prepare for ritual. I believe, the central reason - because theydo not know how to prepare for wicca ritual or casting magic spell. Still if we discuss preparation for wicca ritual, one can not offer proposition, we must provide explicit recommendations or instructions. And the only standard of their feasibility or trustworthiness is working rite.  I worked up recommendation for preparation and doing wicca rites and applied them in eWicca, Electronic Wicca Assistant. You may try it and supply testimonies, whether about serviceability of the software package, or about its practical effectivity : &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fewicca.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ewicca.net&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fewicca.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ewicca.net&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>