<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="3e8aa0ff151597c8dc52b57a1c809779">			Mohamed Merah &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXJlbm1pbGxlbmRyZXNzZXNpbnVrLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Karen Millen Dress&lt;/a&gt;; explained his attacks, reported by other assassination plots: For hours,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXJlbm1pbGxlbmRyZXNzZXNpbnVrLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.karenmillendressesinuk.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.karenmillendressesinuk.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;  the assassin of Toulouse spoke with the police. Now a TV station has released the audio recordings. The government and relatives of the victims are outraged, the public prosecutor.
&lt;br /&gt;;Paris - The deeds shocked France, the country held its breath for days: Mohamed Merah killed in three bombings in March, seven people before it on 22 March was shot dead by police elite. Now the use of a TV makes the case in France for a heated debate. The station has broadcast tape recordings of conversations between the attackers and the police and thus outrage.
&lt;br /&gt;;The French Interior Minister Karen Millen Manuel Valls, condemned the decision of TF1 to publish excerpts of the recordings. He accused the station, not to respect the families of the victims. There, the question arises how the station came on the records.
&lt;br /&gt;;The Paris public prosecutor's preliminary investigation of data accepted by judicial Karen Millen Dresses investigation for breach of confidentiality. Relatives of the victims of the assassin Mohamed Merah were shocked and horrified. Victims' lawyers announced an expedited motion to introduce a ban on any further broadcast of sound recordings. The broadcasting authority CSA said it had recommended that the TV stations to refrain from broadcasting.
&lt;br /&gt;;TF1 was sent on Sunday evening for the first time excerpts from the recorded negotiations between Merah and the police. Karen Millen Dress The assassin had to explain his crimes and described further assassination plans. TF1 has claims to be about four and a half hours of audio material to the talks.
&lt;br /&gt;;Merah On 11 March, a paratroopers shot dead a few days later, two more soldiers. Again, only shortly before he killed a Jewish school in Toulouse, three children and a teacher.
&lt;br /&gt;;The 23-year-old had declared himself a member of the Islamist terror network al-Qaeda. After he had asked the authorities, he barricaded himself in his home in Toulouse. He was shot dead by police after a 32-hour siege.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a35fa2d3d4b54d2e56c067a72514d623">			Only lift the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXJlbm1pbGxlbmRyZXNzZXNpbnVrLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.karenmillendressesinuk.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.karenmillendressesinuk.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;  helicopter pilot to be a folk song, then detonated a Hellfire missile - allegedly&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXJlbm1pbGxlbmRyZXNzZXNpbnVrLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Karen Millen Dresses&lt;/a&gt;; between Afghan civilians. On the Internet, a clip has surfaced to show U.S. soldiers in a street attack. The authenticity of the video has not been definitively established.
&lt;br /&gt;;Kabul - The clip lasts no longer than three and a half minutes - but he could bring the commanders of U.S. forces in explanations. The photo shows how the crew of a combat helicopter fires at people from the air. Before a match, the pilot raises the aircraft radio to the chorus of the folk song &quot;American Pie&quot; to. Then the rocket explodes on the ground
&lt;br /&gt;;The video portal LiveLeaks put the clip on his page. It is not to definitively clarify whether the audio recording is actually original or added later. So far there is no official opinion of the U.S. Department of Defense. From the command of ISAF, it was only that one is aware of the video.
&lt;br /&gt;;According to the clip's Karen Millen description, the recording is to be created in September 2009 in Wardak province, southwest Karen Millen Dress of the capital Kabul. It will involve members of the 101st Airborne Division-.
&lt;br /&gt;;On the video, several people can be seen, staying at a street. Here too, the clip further description is limited. Thus, it should involve farmers, &quot;the sow poppy seeds on the street.&quot; This could be meant as a sarcastic reference to possible explosives. Again and again, opponents of the Allies hide homemade roadside bombs. Periodically it comes to serious explosions.
&lt;br /&gt;;First, speak helicopter crew still on the way forward, then (at the 1:39 minute mark), a voice Karen Millen Dresses  intones the famous line: &quot;Bye-bye, Miss American Pie.&quot; Seconds later, a fireball rise up over the road. Apparently the crew has shot a Hellfire missile. &quot;Good Hit&quot; comes immediately after the impact from the off.
&lt;br /&gt;;Several people who survived the first attack apparently shaky on the pictures to see how they seek protection. Shortly after they got back under fire. After 3:39 minutes hidden from the video.
&lt;br /&gt;;Earlier this year turned up a video, allegedly urinating on the members of an infantry unit on the bodies of dead Afghan civilians. In March, the massacre of a U.S. soldier, 16 people died in the town of Yan Najib.
&lt;br /&gt;;Such incidents strain relations between the foreign armed forces and the Afghan civilian population always hard		</conversation>		<conversation id="542d5aa3f6e9de2af7107b29b565a33f">			Micro-loans to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXJlbm1pbGxlbmRyZXNzZXNpbnVrLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Karen Millen&lt;/a&gt;; help the poorest of the poor to stand on its own two feet.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rYXJlbm1pbGxlbmRyZXNzZXNpbnVrLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.karenmillendressesinuk.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.karenmillendressesinuk.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;  But what started as a good idea going, more and more exploited by profit-driven investors, says the insider microfinance Hugh Sinclair. He got out - and expects in a book from the industry.
&lt;br /&gt;;It sounds so simple and ingenious: With a loan of 100 € or 200 may be a poor woman in Bangladesh sewing machine and buy materials and start a small tailoring business. Others are investing in a tea room or shop. With the revenues from these &quot;micro enterprise&quot; can be handled interest and principal payments, and there is little prosperity into the house. If all goes well, the poor must soon no longer be poor.
&lt;br /&gt;;For this idea was Muhammad Yunus, 2006 Nobel Peace Prize. More than 30 years after the founding of the Grameen Bank microcredit for the poor worldwide fame, they have grown into a 70 billion dollar financial services industry. But the dream, &quot;to banish poverty in a museum&quot; with the loans, is now as distant as ever. In recent years, accumulated the critical reports. More and more scientific studies have found no effect of microcredit armutslindernde, while many borrowers stuck in a debt trap. Even many of microfinance representatives clearing up somewhat sheepishly, that the influence of small loans is unclear.
&lt;br /&gt;;The exorbitant interest rates of sometimes over 100 percent per year, and the sometimes brutal methods with which the repayments are enforced, give rise to additional doubts about the social ethos of the industry. These doubts should now get new food.
&lt;br /&gt;;What counts are repayment rates and yields
&lt;br /&gt;;On 9 July is the book of Karen Millen microfinance consultant Hugh Sinclair on the market. In &quot;Confessions of a microfinance Here sufferer&quot; (the German translation of the English original title), he tells of his ten years of experience as an employee and consultant credit forgiving microfinance institutions and microfinance investment funds. He sees himself as a &quot;whistleblower&quot; in an industry that has betrayed its ideals and deceive the world public opinion systematically.
&lt;br /&gt;;After a business degree Sinclair believed to have found a job in the microfinance sector, the ideal niche to bring something good with his skills. But the deeper he penetrated into the industry, the more he discovered inconsistencies: He found incompetent, corrupt and sometimes simply criminal microfinance organizations. Especially him to create the balance between the social mission of a hand, and the commercialization of micro-loans made on the other.
&lt;br /&gt;;By microfinance institutions to operate profitably with appropriate interest rates, commercial investors can be recruited to the microfinancing institutions provide the necessary capital for further growth are available. Like that you can help the poor without it cost someone something, it was believed. But it soon turned out that the poor could still abkn?pfen much higher interest rates, and thus achieve good profits for the investors did. As the loans are used, whether for a sensible business idea or for cigarettes and alcohol, as they will be repaid and whether they have ultimately had a positive impact on the lives of the poor - all this is secondary for-profit investors. What counts, are repayment rates and yields.
&lt;br /&gt;;This painful realization is characterized in detail by Sinclair in his memoirs book-like. For several years he worked for the Karen Millen Dress Dutch investment fund Triple Jump, which among other things, invested in the Nigerian microfinance institution Lapo (Lift Above Poverty Organization). After extended stays in Nigeria wants Sinclair discovered that Lapo effective interest rates of around 125 percent a year and requested that the deposits of its customers confiscated illegally and had a disastrous management structure. As he expounded his findings in triple jump and later as a special microfinance rating agencies confirmed the findings, he expected his employers outrage over the state. Instead, would triple jump and other investors - including the German bank - is investing heavily in Lapo. The desire for high profits outwit the social motives output says Sinclair.
&lt;br /&gt;;Behind the beautiful facade of the microcredit
&lt;br /&gt;;The more intense with Sinclair microfinance investors concerned, is the clearer it became that it was at Lapo not an isolated incident, but a &quot;systematic behavior in the microfinance investment community form&quot;. The sector had been &quot;busy financial vultures&quot; of which were found with small loans, a fertile breeding ground for lucrative investments.
&lt;br /&gt;;Sinclair's autobiographical book is original and extremely entertaining. There is no systematic scientific analysis, which attacks the idea of ??micro-credit theory. Rather it is the diary of an insider, who with wit and charm only and then describes his alienation from his lonely struggle against the cult-like micro-finance community. &quot;There should be a book you can read on the beach,&quot; says Sinclair himself the &quot;common man&quot;, not just the experts, he wants to persuade them to look behind the beautiful facade of microcredits.
&lt;br /&gt;;Still, that is his problem: Sinclair's book is mostly not about the random observations from the Karen Millen Dresses world of a microfinance practitioner beyond that swims against the tide. So it can be a profound lack of judgment, the role that microcredit can actually play in reducing poverty. After the numerous dark scenes, it is then quite surprising if the sector at the end of Sinclair still eliciting a positive thing. He immediately reported by a few &quot;good&quot; micro credit banks that lent money at reasonable interest rates, avoid over-indebtedness of clients - and hardly made profits.
&lt;br /&gt;;Sinclair's piecemeal approach will loose him to enter the insiders of the industry rightly accused of superficiality. But it will also ensure that the controversy over the first micro-finance expert groups will leave.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>