<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2f614eaf6a80171229a0a7a15346815b">			Minimizes allergens &lt;br /&gt;;In case you have fragile epidermis, insecticides and other compounds seen in regular cotton will intensify dermatological disorders. Having said that, organic clothing made using the bamboo herb is anti-microbial. This means that the previously mentioned eco clothing shall naturally destroy microorganisms. The good news is that we have a number of non-chemical clothes available for sale. This includes organic panties as well as other underwear which are likewise comfortable for those who have sensitive skin. Learn more facts about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54eWxlbWNsb3RoaW5nLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;organic clothing&lt;/a&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Minimizes dangerous chemicals &lt;br /&gt;;The amount of herbicides and pesticides found in conventional cotton farming provide about 25 percent of the worldwide use. Most of the pesticides soak into the fiber and they land in ones sheets and ones attire that can in turn lead to serious dermatological complications and in the worst of all situation, skin cancer. The runoff from these herbicides saturates the grounds and they can end up in the food items we ingest or even the water we take in. For that reason, buying non-chemical clothes will go very far in saving the earth.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lushlee.com%2Fimages%2Fclothing-shoes%2F09%2F12%2Fsublet-eco-clothing.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lushlee.com/images/clothing-shoes/09/12/sublet-eco-clothing.jpg&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Durability &lt;br /&gt;;Non-chemical clothes are long lasting as compared to their regular alternatives. For example, a organic T-shirt created from man-made materials lasts for roughly 15-20 machine clean cycles. In that case, the fibers inside the t shirt start to destroy. An organic T-shirt has a lifespan of approximately a hundred machine wash cycles.   For that reason, organic clothes last more than the regular clothes and will save you plenty of cash. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Top quality&lt;br /&gt;;Non-chemical clothes are created using materials which are anti-microbial. That is to say that the material kills unwanted organisms. The fabric is likewise mold resilient and this prevents hazardous UV rays. For that reason, organic and natural fabrics are definitely much more remarkable in standard for the man-made materials. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even if you're not thinking about greener way of living, the pros earlier mentioned should be enough to influence one to obtain non-chemical clothes.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>