<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="81a04185d6095486df0031f759040144">			&lt;h1&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50YXhwbGFubmVyY3BhLmNvbS9pcnMtcHJvYmxlbXMucGhw" target="_blank"&gt;;tax return preparation&lt;/a&gt;; - Do You Need an  &lt;/h1&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;i&gt;;Businesses and individuals not only need to pay taxes on the money earned in the U.S., but also any wages earned overseas&lt;/i&gt;;. There are international tax laws that deal with this type of situation and in most cases, it is best to hire an  to help with preparing tax forms of this nature. This allows the overseas worker to take advantage of any and all legal credits and exemptions without risking tax fraud. Attorneys that specialize in this type of taxes know all the ins and outs and the proper way to proceed in any type of situation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Ftax_attorney.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/tax_attorney.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]If you have worked abroad and have any questions regarding international taxes, then you should consult an international tax attorney. They also help with other situation, such people who have property, businesses or other assets abroad. They can also advise international companies when it comes to mergers, expansions, leases and contracts. &lt;u&gt;;The international attorney also negotiates tax agreements between companies and the United States, and assist with structuring the company from a tax perspective&lt;/u&gt;;. Such attorneys can prove to be a great asset for individuals and companies alike when it comes to international taxes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Ftax_preparer.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/tax_preparer.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]Foreign earned income exclusion, which reduces the amount of taxable income for those who are working abroad, has a very complicated procedure. The  can help you in checking if you qualify for the foreign earned income exclusion or not. The attorney can help you by letting you know if you may qualify and assist you in preparing documents and filing forms on your behalf. There are two test for the foreign earned income exclusion, the bona fide residence test and the physical presence test. The attorney can help you in deciding which one of the two describes your situation. Overseas taxes can be quite tricky if you do not know what all it entails, so it is best to have professional. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2FUS_Taxes.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/US_Taxes.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;i&gt;;It is wise to plan ahead and consult an international tax attorney before doing any overseas work&lt;/i&gt;;. The attorney is an expert and is able to help clients make the right decisions when it comes to foreign activity to avoid problems later on. You can keep foreign taxes as low as possible if you take out time to do planning. Preparing taxes becomes very easy and less trouble if planning has be done before hand. It is important that you have an expert at your hand because tax law can be ambiguous and tax law change frequently.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d94b00c7ce78624fbc765f1d2db7154a">			&lt;h1&gt;; The Importance of [url=]tax attorney[/url] &lt;/h1&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;i&gt;;Businesses and individuals not only need to pay taxes on the money earned in the U.S., but also any wages earned overseas&lt;/i&gt;;. For this type of taxation, there are international tax laws, which are different from those applied to income in the U.S. For such situations, it is best to hire an  who can help you in filing the tax forms. &lt;b&gt;;Hiring an international tax attorney helps a person who has to pay international tax in taking advantage of all the legal credits and exemptions&lt;/b&gt;;. Attorneys who works specifically for international tax understand all the ins and outs of the international tax laws and understand the proper way of filing taxes and returns. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Ftax_problem.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/tax_problem.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]If you have worked abroad and have any questions regarding international taxes, then you should consult an international tax attorney. Such attorneys also provide help to people who have businesses or properties abroad. They are also knowledgeable regarding mergers, expansions, leases and contracts regarding international companies. &lt;b&gt;;International tax attorneys can also negotiate tax agreements between companies and the United States. They can also help in structuring the company from a tax perspective&lt;/b&gt;;. The service of this type of tax attorney is invaluable for many, including both companies and individuals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Ftax_return_preparation.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/tax_return_preparation.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;b&gt;;The  can also help those who want to know if they qualify for the foreign earned income exclusion that reduces the amount of taxable income for those working overseas&lt;/b&gt;;. The attorney can help you by letting you know if you may qualify and assist you in preparing documents and filing forms on your behalf. There are two test for the foreign earned income exclusion, the bona fide residence test and the physical presence test. The attorney can help you in deciding which one of the two describes your situation. Overseas taxes can be quite tricky if you do not know what all it entails, so it is best to have professional. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2FIRS_Problems.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/IRS_Problems.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;i&gt;;It is wise to plan ahead and consult an international tax attorney before doing any overseas work&lt;/i&gt;;. The attorney is an expert and is able to help clients make the right decisions when it comes to foreign activity to avoid problems later on. You can keep foreign taxes as low as possible if you take out time to do planning. This can also save a lot of time and effort at the end of the year when preparing taxes. It is important that you have an expert at your hand because tax law can be ambiguous and tax law change frequently.		</conversation>		<conversation id="186262d418da7cc1584db33a500a30d0">			&lt;h1&gt;;[url=]tax attorney[/url] - Why You Need an  &lt;/h1&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;i&gt;;Businesses and individuals not only need to pay taxes on the money earned in the U.S., but also any wages earned overseas&lt;/i&gt;;. There are international tax laws that deal with this type of situation and in most cases, it is best to hire an  to help with preparing tax forms of this nature. An attorney can help an international taxpayer in taking full advantage of the tax exemptions and legal credits that apply to international tax. Attorneys who works specifically for international tax understand all the ins and outs of the international tax laws and understand the proper way of filing taxes and returns. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Fhelp_IRS.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/help_IRS.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]The international tax attorney is there as advisor to help with questions for anyone who has worked abroad. Such attorneys also provide help to people who have businesses or properties abroad. If you are an international company, then they can help you with regards to mergers, leases, expansions and contracts. Whether it is structuring a company from a tax perspective or making tax agreements between a company and the U.S., an international tax attorney can provide good guidance. Hiring such an attorney can prove to be invaluable for companies and individuals who have matters regarding international taxes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Ftax_return_preparation.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/tax_return_preparation.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]Foreign earned income exclusion, which reduces the amount of taxable income for those who are working abroad, has a very complicated procedure. The  can help you in checking if you qualify for the foreign earned income exclusion or not. The attorney can help you by letting you know if you may qualify and assist you in preparing documents and filing forms on your behalf. The attorney can also explain the difference between the physical presence test and the bona fide residence test and help you decide if one of these describes your situation. &lt;b&gt;;It is best to have a professional who can help you with the overseas taxes as the laws regarding such taxes can be quite ambiguous&lt;/b&gt;;. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;center]&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com%2Fimages%2Ftax_attorney.jpg%26quot%3B%2F%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.usexpattaxescpasattorneys.com/images/tax_attorney.jpg&quot;;/&gt;;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;p align=&quot;;justify]&lt;i&gt;;It is wise to plan ahead and consult an international tax attorney before doing any overseas work&lt;/i&gt;;. Because an attorney is an expert, he will help you in making the right decision and avoiding an sort of problem related to foreign financial activity. Planning ahead can keep cross-border taxes as low as possible and above the board. Preparing taxes becomes very easy and less trouble if planning has be done before hand. &lt;u&gt;;Tax laws are tricky and change, so it is best to have someone at your disposal who stays on top of changes and knows tax laws work&lt;/u&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>