<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f47b21c8dc86d2eb27b742ac6bf3b982">			Online presence is one of the best ways to ensure that your business succeeds and makes it to its financial goals, and a Seattle SEO company can be the best way for you to get to that place. As specialists in their field, they can get you the traffic that you're looking for.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What's that you say - you don't know what SEO is? Well, it stands for search engine optimization, and it's a process where you or a company but the right data in the right places in order to internet web crawlers to give the greatest value to the most important words. It's the process of putting your business address in a location where search engines can find the numbers and point the way to it for shoppers on the hunt.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Have you ever stopped to think about how it is exactly, that Google and Yahoo come up with their ranking numbers? How is it that they get the data that is automated into the search process when people go looking to buy things? The answer is that it is all based on very specific mathematical formulas, proprietary as they may be, that web crawlers are constructed to verify during the searching process.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Seattle SEO companies can also help you with pay per click campaigns. Basically, they will search out people with banner advertisements that are related to your web content. The arrangement is that every time someone clicks their ad on your site, you get paid a certain amount. This is an arrangement where everyone wins, from the consumer to you and the advertiser. Though not strictly SEO, traffic increase is still a result.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And do you know why rankings are so important in the online world? Because they are pretty much all that matters to a consumer who doesn't know any better otherwise. If you have two similarly companies that you know nothing about, which one are you going to pick to look into? The easy answer is the one at the top - and that's why SEO is so important - YOU want to be at the top, and you want to be the one that people recognize is special.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Internet shoppers are also a different kind of shopper than a consumer who has been around in the past is. They know exactly what they are searching for, no looking through the yellow pages for them! So they rely on search engines to tell them about you. If they are looking for you, they want to find you on the top.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And yes, traffic is important, but make sure that you have a great product first. Don't put the cart before the horse!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So feel free to let a Seattle SEO company help you and your business out, it might be the best decision that you've made all year, because it's a technical job that everyone isn't good at - give yourself a chance to succeed!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I'm a marketer with a passion for writing about &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pointit.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSeattle"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.pointit.com&quot;&gt;;Seattle&lt;/a&gt;; search engine optimization&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d614869d52696b6d2cd7ec335f9fc294">			SEO is short for search engine optimization. People and businesses are creating SEO content for their websites so that they can get the traffic that they need to be successful. For people and businesses who are unable to do this themselves, there are lots of companies in the Seattle area that can help you build your website with SEO.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why do you need SEO for your website? If you made a website for no reason at all, you might not need SEO but if you have a website that was made for receiving traffic, you need SEO. It can help you get a drastic increase of traffic to your website. Traffic is important for your website because it is how your website will survive.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many Seattle companies that know how to apply SEO to websites and they are so good at what they do, they help other people and businesses apply SEO to their on sites. The companies have years worth of experience with SEO and creating keywords that need to be used on the site.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Because each individual website is different, the SEO keywords used on the website will differ from one another. SEO keywords are words that people commonly type into the search box of any search engine. Some popular search engines include Google and Bing. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the proper SEO keywords are used, the website will turn up on the results page. When an individual types keywords into the search engine, if those keywords match the SEO keywords and content on your website, those individuals will automatically see a link to your website along with other websites that utilize the same keywords. The goal is to have your website link on one of the first page of the search results page.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Traffic is a necessity for any website because it is how people spread the word for their site and ultimately receive business. The primary purpose of building and designing a website is to have people on the Internet looking at your website on a regular basis. Utilizing SEO keywords will drastically increase the number of visitors to your website.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You might not know how to use SEO keywords for your website. That is where the Seattle SEO companies come into place. They will help you, with all of their experience, use the right keywords in your web content so that you can get more traffic, more visitors, and reach ultimate success.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you have such high traffic, your website will get the recognition it deserves. You may also be able to make more money if you depend on ad revenue or business from visitors to the website. If you want to really see how well SEO effects your website, add a hit counter to the site and see for yourself how many more visitors you receive after you start using SEO content.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I'm a professional SEO with a passion for writing about &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pointit.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSeattle"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.pointit.com&quot;&gt;;Seattle&lt;/a&gt;; SEO&lt;/a&gt;;. You can learn more by visiting my favorite &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pointit.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3BWebsite%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt%3B"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.pointit.com&quot;&gt;;Website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>