<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="5253d9701bc34702b397442868757aa0">			TULSEE
&lt;br /&gt;;                                                                     a fountain of love..........
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I ll never forget the day, when I saw her To the main road to Bargarh……..
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It was an auspicious winter morning. With a great excitement I finished my daily work and left my home with my bicycle with a high spirit.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The morning hour opened the book of nature before me. When I looked up I found the sky full of wonders. It was looking quite clear, calm and blue. On the grasses I found dew drops of water, which were looking like beautiful shining pearls. Once I tried to pick up them but all in vain. All the sights and sounds had a wonderful effect on my body and my mind became refreshed and my body active. I thought to me the nature is on its duty.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But suddenly a cool breeze blew and touched my mind heart and soul. I tuned to see that and lost my balance and fell down. That was really an impressive silhouette painting of a painter. That breeze saw me with a vanity. Perhaps she was about to speak something to me but I couldn’t made her speak. For the first time I felt that both of we are long acquainted.  Than I stood up with a kingly sensitiveness and waited there under the old banyan tree near to a field, taking a hope that that cool breeze will must return……..
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The sky was looking bright and bright, the dew drops were already disappeared but still I was waiting there with a great anxiety …But all in vain my hopes changed to despair, my heart burst into tears and finally I returned my home…
&lt;br /&gt;;That was my last day in home, and then I returned to my hostel and made myself busy in study. But that face was always in my eye and heart. I couldn’t forget her as she was in …...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Every pages of my library book …….
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the tinkling of clock ………
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the rustling of leaves ……….
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the flapping of flags ……
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the whistling of air……..
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the pealing of cloud………
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the drizzling   of rain ……..
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    In the babbling of stream ……
&lt;br /&gt;;                                    And everywhere……………………….
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dharmendra Tripathy		</conversation>	</conversations></author>