<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2c23f14e58f864cccb5172e6414e084a">			Does one travel? The BOB is a perfect companion. Have no fear flying from coast to coast - the BOB does nothing but help you with ones things, as it's sturdy enough to hold on to over 60 pounds. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I'll be honest, when our child was created, we did not purchase a BOB. We knew we wanted one someday when it's time to get back into shape. We bought a Bugaboo. That's right, we're THAT WILL couple. Although the Bugaboo can be a well-made stroller, it seriously lacks any kind of ability for anything other than shopping. It's difficult to fail and fit in your trunk. I can just handle a curb. It cannot go off road because the froth front tires wear. It's a pretty stroller that's been pushed by celebrities. Don't buy the hype. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At three months, I surprised my wife and bought a BABY TREND. I purchased the 2008 model (you will find there's new, redesigned model for 2011 that's a lot better) to surprise my significant other. When it came, once we used it, we could feel the relief. What must mean? The comforting realization that now we can finally go anywhere with our baby. BOB = mobility. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At four months, we sold this Bugaboo and couldn't end up happier. We have traveled with our home in Austin tx to both coasts and the Gulf of mexico. We have traveled this mountains of Colorado and the streets of downtown. Our BOB is our savior. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're considering an efficiently brilliant infant stroller, you've found it. Using a weight capacity of 70 pounds (over the single) and a fixed five-year warranty on shape; limited one-year warranty on small parts and materials, you cannot go drastically wrong! &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;There are several different BOB strollers you may choose from. They range from your everyday strollers for your fitness guru models. BOB strollers do offer multitude, but with choice together with quality come higher bills. If you are not prepared to get a high-end stroller, this manufacturer is not for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here are the 6 different BOB strollers it is possible to choose from. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Trend &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This model is most effective for light jogging and on a daily basis errands. It has a 12&quot;; swivel front wheel that could be locked, and 16&quot;; again wheels. This stroller offers more colors options than some other models with five to choose from. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Revolution 12&quot;; AW &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This model is built for everyday use. Offering a swivel front table and smaller back added wheels it makes maneuvering in tight spaces easy. It also gives the option to lock entry wheel when jogging and also walking on uneven floors. They have included a state of the art suspension system to build a more comfortable ride. You'll have the choice of three different colors. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; Infant stroller Strides Fitness &lt;/b&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The following model is custom built for fitness gurus. It offers exercise bands and some sort of manual that fits within the handlebar console. The Stroller Stride Fitness was created by a fitness expert to help parents stay in condition, and is used with Stroller Strides fitness instructional classes. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Detailed information on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lam9nZ2luZ3N0cm9sbGVycmV2aWV3cy5jb20vYm9iLXN0cm9sbGVycy1zZS8_" target="_blank"&gt;bob&lt;/a&gt; can be found at main website.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>