<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="6e6a2fd18dc10249813b2d055232fb14">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZGtzb2Z0d2FyZS5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/166522634_16604112_44436062.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;*	XBRL is the Financial and Operational business reporting offshoot of Extensible Markup Language (XML), which is a freely licensable, open technology standard (or Vocabulary) used to exchange business information electronically. XML is the universally preferred data description language used to describe the storage, manipulation and exchange of data via the internet.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	XBRL is a language for the electronic communication of business and financial data which is revolutionizing business reporting around the world. In India, now as per MCA specifications, filing of financial statements in XBRL mode is mandatory for certain class of companies.  
&lt;br /&gt;;*	XBRL electronic standard will allow for efficient retrieval and analysis of financial information, thus enabling better, faster and more consistent information, resulting in higher quality decision by investors.   
&lt;br /&gt;;XBRL is:
&lt;br /&gt;;*	An Open Technology standard for reporting and analyzing business and financial information.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Software agnostic, or independent.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Accounting framework neutral.
&lt;br /&gt;;XBRL is not:
&lt;br /&gt;;*	A Standardized chart of accounts.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	A way to require the reporting of specific information.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	A transaction level activity (although it can summarize general ledger transactions) 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The idea behind XBRL is simple. Instead of treating financial information as static text – as in a standard internet page or a printed document – XBRL provides an identifying tag for each individual item of data, whether numeric or textual. This tag is computer readable and allows the information to be used interactively
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;MCA Taxonomy and XBRL Instance Document&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;MCA has provided the Taxonomy which forms the basis for tagging financial and business information in XBRL. This Taxonomy is an electronic classification system of tags defining thousands of business reporting concepts (including Text) and their relationships. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;XBRL Instance Document&lt;/strong&gt;; is the end result of how a preparer creates XBRL data. It contains report information typically complied from internal ERP or Financial reporting systems that have been marked up or tagged in XBRL.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;eXBace promises to be web-enable the business reporting process for preparers, regulators and users. It significantly improves the efficiency and effectiveness of the business reporting processes of Organizations.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;eXBace follows the Mantra “BETTER and FASTER”&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Better&lt;/strong&gt;; – Accurate, Easily to use, Import and Export facility to almost all formats and Comprehensive Product
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Faster&lt;/strong&gt;; – No Rekeying, Instant User Access and most efficient reports for faster information retrieval
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;eXBace:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;*	eXBace is a solution for converting and filing Financial Information of the Company in XBRL Format as per MCA mandate
&lt;br /&gt;;*	eXBace is a One Stop Complete &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZGtzb2Z0d2FyZS5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;XBRL Software&lt;/a&gt;; - On Document editing/Tagging, Quick Viewing, Advance Validating and Finally extensible reporting
&lt;br /&gt;;*	eXBace is an Intelligent Solution that enables automated processing of business information and hence cut out laborious and costly processes of manual re-entry and comparison.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Improve the overall quality and accuracy of data obtained from companies.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Reduce potential errors from manual entry through machine transfers of reporting information.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Increase the speed at which financial decision can be made by analysts, investors, lenders rating agencies etc…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;eXBace Advantages:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;No need to be XBRL Expert - No Training Required&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;User-friendly interface:&lt;/strong&gt;; User friendly interface to input latest year annual report information against XBRL tags. The 'On Document' tagging feature allows the user to seamlessly tag facts and text blocks that are scattered across the document.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tagging of Financial and Non-Financial data: eXBace is powered to create financial data for Current Year and Previous Year with taxonomy in one go and Non-Financial data i.e. Auditor’s Report, Directors Report etc. with ease.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Advanced Validator:&lt;/strong&gt;; eXBace ensures accuracy by using in-built validations at entry level to prevent data entry errors. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Generation of XBRL Instance Document:&lt;/strong&gt;; Generation of XBRL instance Document as per MCA Taxonomy.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Advance Features:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;*	Add and Edit facilities for footnote.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	HTML formatted content for Text Block
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Import Company Details through CIN from MCA.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Quick Access to Forms through Favorites Panel.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	E-mail facility for generated Instance document
&lt;br /&gt;;*	XML Viewer.
&lt;br /&gt;;*	Non-Financial Data import from other company.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Our Customer Support Service:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For us, a friendly and flexible approach is the key to satisfying our customers. To build the necessary trust and to assure our customers of the quality of our services, we remain in constant contact with them, regularly train our customer service staff and, when developing new solutions, we always consider what fundamental benefits will facilitate the communications options for our clients. Our customer-oriented approach is second nature to us here at KDK Softwares - We know you only get one chance in this life, so we get it right, the first time and every time.
&lt;br /&gt;;Qualified KDK Technical support engineers help you resolve unlimited incidents quickly and efficiently. Coverage is provided in official hours per day, we are in effort of making our services available 24x7x365-days per year.		</conversation>		<conversation id="22349a259909ea2459c6fce6723fefec">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZGtzb2Z0d2FyZS5jb20vZVhCYWNlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/166522634_16604112_44436062.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;XBRL Viewer&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;XBRL Viewers help die users of a XBRL document to view it. The users can drill down to the related taxonomies for detail information. Some of the software has in-built provision to make further analysis from the available data. Data viewed from XBRL Viewers can be transferred to Excel or other databases. The XBRL file viewer tool is a simple standalone application that allows you to review every minor detail in an XBRL instance document'.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;XBRL Viewers are generally available free of cost. SEC has announced that the source code for the Interactive Financial Report Viewer that enables investors to analyze companies' interactive data filings is now available via its Web site for free use by the market.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Advantages of XBRL Reporting&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;XBRL reporting system has revolutionized financial reporting, and also use of those reports by the Stakeholders. Advantages of it can be summarized as follows;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Interactive data will enable investors and other external users to make more productive decisions. Instead of wading through incomprehensible financial disclosure, investors can have access to meaningful information in a form which is more suitable for them.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. From the accountants' point of view, it will enable them to prepare error-free accounts. Since accounting data are mapped into some recognized taxonomy, all errors arc to be sorted out at this stage.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Auditors can detect errors in tagging financial data with the help of available application software. Adoption of XBRL will significantly lower both internal and external audit costs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Objectives of any taxation system are accuracy and traceability on the basis of calculation, and compliance of rules and regulations. The accuracy will be provided by unambiguous data point definition as well as well-defined sources of the information. Since most of the values used to calculate and report taxes are, in turn, derived, capabilities of the compliance system to trace such values all the way to the original or atomic information elements is essential. Finally, if the business rules and formulas used to assess taxes are documented, coded and understood, it is relatively straightforward to predict tax liability where and when a business transaction is taking place.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Real time analysis will help internal management to prepare reports for endless variety of internal management decisions.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thus, it will bring paradigm shift in the world of financial reporting.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;XBRL Adoption by India&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Reserve Bank of India is going to launch the Basel II reporting system using XBRL through the existing Online Returns Filing System (ORFS). A Committee has been constituted under the Chairmanship of Shri V Leeladhar, Deputy Governor for the purpose (&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.rlji.org.in"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.rlji.org.in&lt;/a&gt;;).
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Institute of Chartered Accountants of India constituted a Group on XBRL in January 2007, under the chairmanship of the President, ICAI. While building the taxonomy, three broad reporting categories have been considered, taking into account the different reporting requirements. These are
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Commercial and industrial
&lt;br /&gt;;2. Banking companies
&lt;br /&gt;;3. Non-banking finance companies
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recently, the Group has finalized the draft general purpose financial reporting XBRL taxonomy for commercial and industrial companies and also for banking companies. These drafts cover the financial statements, viz., Balance Sheet, Statement of Profit and Loss, and Cash Flow Statement and the related non-financial information. The draft taxonomy has been developed conforming to Indian Accounting Standards and1 Company Law while adapting the architectural features of the IFRS general purpose taxonomy 2006. The ICAI has already issued Exposure Drafts for both types of companies. India has also launched &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZGtzb2Z0d2FyZS5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;XBRL India&lt;/a&gt;; in collaboration with XBRL International.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Conclusion&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It has already been proved that XBRL is versatile and very much useful for financial and business analysis to the investors and other stakeholders. Based on its success story, all the countries are coming forward to adopt this reporting language. Many countries have made its application mandatory, and others are in the pipeline. In the next few years it is going to be adopted by all the countries. Though India has made a late entry, still she is moving at a faster rate to catch up with others. The accountants in India will have to make ourselves ready to take the challenges of introduction of XBRL in India.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Author Bio:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;KDK Software launches eXBace &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5leGJhY2UuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;XBRL Software&lt;/a&gt;; for e-filing of business financial reports in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5rZGtzb2Z0d2FyZS5jb20vZVhCYWNlLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;XBRL filing&lt;/a&gt;; format by MCA mandate.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>