<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="cf715eaa6f7648c51e2eb81bed2b9f1f">			A &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N0b25lcnBlcmlvc3BlY2lhbGlzdHMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Dentist Columbus&lt;/a&gt;; can help you fight bad breath and other dental problems.  Halitosis, more commonly known as bad breath, is the number one mouth problem people have. If you're experiencing halitosis regularly, it is usually because of factors like cavities, bacteria and gum diseases. Brushing routinely helps prevent this, but to totally cure it, you will need to find out what exactly is causing your halitosis.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A much neglected area which can cause halitosis is not keeping good oral health care. To promote a healthy mouth, you should brush your teeth at least once a day if not after every meal. Combining regular brushing with flossing and tongue scraping will further enhance oral cleanliness by helping to remove additional food particles which the bacteria feed on. A clean mouth is a fresh smelling mouth so always brush as much as you can. Despite halitosis having a number of source factors, one of the main reasons is the consumption of certain food types that actually promote bad breath. These foods are generally high protein foods such as meat and certain dairy products which are fed on by the bacteria in the mouth. The bacteria synthesize this protein creating a smelly byproduct which is a major cause of the foul stench associated with halitosis.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Teeth with significant decay are said to have caries, or cavities. Brushing your teeth and flossing will help prevent this. You should also be careful about the food you eat, like avoiding junk food. Tooth cavity is another popular dental problem. This is caused by plaque that forms an acid with the sugars and starches of the food in our mouth. This acid ruins the enamel of our teeth, leading to tooth decay. This harmful acid may also lead to tooth erosion, where teeth are loosened and cracked. Factors that affect this process include oral hygiene, diet, meal frequency, saliva production, and heredity.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tooth sensitivity is what happens when you feel pain upon biting something or when eating hot and cold food hurts. This is caused by any of these: tooth decay, loose fillings, cracks that expose sensitive parts of your gums, or damage to the tissue inside a tooth. Using toothpaste made specifically for sensitive teeth is best, along with a toothbrush that has soft bristles. You should also consult your dentist to check on why your teeth are sensitive. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Consult your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N0b25lcnBlcmlvc3BlY2lhbGlzdHMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Dentist Columbus&lt;/a&gt;; if you also have canker sores. Unlike cold sores, canker sores appear inside the mouth. These mouth sores aren't contagious. There may be only one canker sore or several and they often return. Their exact cause is unclear but some experts believe that immune system problems, bacteria or viruses may be concerned. Fatigue, stress or allergies can increase the likelihood of a canker mouth sore. A cut caused by biting the cheek or tongue, or reactions from hot foods or beverages may contribute to canker sore development. Intestinal problems, such as ulcerative colitis and Crohn’s disease, also seem to make some people more susceptible.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>