<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c58e3aee517f481b362fb7fe640003ff">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXJ1aW5jYWp1bmdsZS5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Peru Vacations&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Having a Peru Vacations you will find many archaeological sites in Peru like Inca Trail ruins,Ollantaytambo,Pisac on the sacred valley ,and many more. Going on Peru vacations fascinates a lot of travelers day by day to the Peru and Cusco(the heart of the ancient Inca empire.) not only offers historic sight but also provide hiking, Inca Jungle trail that involves biking and walking with 80 km bike downhill on this trail we would have the best views of peru vacations as well as rafting, trekking for adventure enthusiasts. Food is one the highlights of Peru which are surely not to be missed.
&lt;br /&gt;;If you are planning for a Peru vacations, you have to be careful choosing the best places on Peru to not miss anything and to have an unforgettable experience choose more excurtions that always finish on Machu Picchu.
&lt;br /&gt;;Peru is a unique destination. Its living culture, impressive history and diversity of natural resources make a visit there a truly unforgettable experience. From Cusco to Machu Picchu of the Inca's path, or traveling through the jungle or over Machu Picchu byTrain , discover a new adventure in each of its attractions to experience a really different vacation. Perú is Rich in pre-Inca and Inca archaeological treasures, biodiversity and ecosystems, as well as cultural expressions, traditional customs, artistic performances and the best cuisine in the region, Peru lets the traveler experience not only cultural tourism, but a huge range of possibilities in community, adventure, or ecological tourism as well as other special interest travel. Its attractions are revealed through the country’s variety of natural regions: the stunning Amazon jungle.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXJ1aW5jYWp1bmdsZS5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Peru vacations&lt;/a&gt;; invites you, with a pisco sour or a glass of sweet chicha morada, to enjoy the best Adventure packages in Peru, the landscape of valleys and Andean mountain peaks, the imposing view of Machu Picchu and the magic of Incas Cusco, while discovering the sounds of the Amazon. Whether on the coast, the mountains or the jungle, discover a culture and history that continue to live through the joy and warmth of its people.Machu Picchu Trail
&lt;br /&gt;;Itinerary of Classic Inca Jungle Trail 4 days and 3 Nights
&lt;br /&gt;;Day 1 CUSCO – SANTA MARIA (Biking):
&lt;br /&gt;;From Your hotel, we will pick up at 7:30 am traveling by bus to Abra Malaga, we will down by car until San Luis which bikers will change in to the kit provided by us (gloves and helmets) following a 5 minute briefing by our professional tour guide, watching the beautiful valley of the Convention. Visit Wamanmarka archaeological site. In Santa Maria spend the night in a family lodge.(peru vacations)
&lt;br /&gt;;Day 2:SANTA MARIA - SANTA TERESA - TREKKING
&lt;br /&gt;;Around at 5.30am or 6:00 am, enjoy the breakfast after We will begin our walk along paths filled with vegetation typical of the area. We will walk through original Inca Trail segments. Then, we take a bath hot springs in Santa Teresa. Overnight in a great Hosting family. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Day 3: SANTA TERESA -AGUAS CALIENTES
&lt;br /&gt;;We will wake at 7:30 am aproximately and have a delitious breakfast we will Cross hanging bridges and we will move in a barrage on the River Vilcanota, noting along the way wide variety of wildlife. we will find waterfalls from glaciers see also coca and coffee plantations we test our adventure and adrenaline .Staying overnight in Aguas Calientes in a basic lodging.
&lt;br /&gt;;Day 4:AGUAS CALIENTES - MACHU PICCHU - CUSCO
&lt;br /&gt;;An early rise today, as you will take the first bus to Machu Picchu at 5.30am, reaching Machu Picchu at 6am we'll go walk to Inti Punku (Puerta del Sol) to watch the sunrise, which with luck will coincide with a beautiful sunrise! Our guide will leave no stones unturned but feel free to challenge their knowledge of Inca history. Afterwards you have free time to dally with the llamas and show off your photographic skills. Those who still have the will can tackle Huaynapicchu, which actually looks down on Machu Picchu. A frequent bus service takes visitors back to Aguas Calientes, where you will catch the train to Ollantaytambo and then the bus to Cusco.
&lt;br /&gt;;Tour Inclution
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Transport from Cusco to Abra Malaga bike ride begining
&lt;br /&gt;;- English/Spanish speaker professional guide during all Inca Jungle Trail 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Mountain bike with front suspension, gloves and security helmet. 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Entrance ticket to Machu Picchu
&lt;br /&gt;;- Meals, including lunch on the first day through until breakfast on the last day. 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Accommodation includes homestays with hot water 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Hostal in Aguas Calientes, last night 
&lt;br /&gt;;- First Aid kit 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Entrance to Machu Picchu . 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Train back to Hidroelectrica 
&lt;br /&gt;;-Expedition Train(better train than backpacker) Back from Aguas Calientes to Cusco 
&lt;br /&gt;;- Guided visit to Machu Picchu and the ruins along the trail.
&lt;br /&gt;;- Train from Hidroelectrica to Aguas Calientes 
&lt;br /&gt;;- One box Lunch
&lt;br /&gt;;SOUTH AMERICA CUSCO-PERU ADRESS: AV. EL SOL 948 OFFICE 324 OFFICE PHONE:+51-84-632699 (from 10:00 am to 7:00 pm)
&lt;br /&gt;;MOBILES PHONE:+51-84-984540762 /+51-84-984721664 /+51-84-984721654 (all 24 Hrs)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=reservations@peruincajungle.com"&gt;;reservations@peruincajungle.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.peruincajungle.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.peruincajungle.com/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>