<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="734fb490ec716d5688576cdae6157a9f">			EM Featured Merchandise Widget is a magento extension that enables to display off the showcased items in a particular classes, buying and range of items displaying by your alternative. Extensions formulated to perform with both equally Magento Neighborhood version, Magento Enterprise version as nicely as Magento Go platform.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.emthemes.com%2Fmedia%2Fcatalog%2Fproduct%2Fcache%2F1%2Fthumbnail%2F800x%2F17f82f742ffe127f42dca9de82fb58b1%2Fe%2Fm%2Fem_newproductswidget-gridview_1.png"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.emthemes.com/media/catalog/product/cache/1/thumbnail/800x/17f82f742ffe127f42dca9de82fb58b1/e/m/em_newproductswidget-gridview_1.png&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lbXRoZW1lcy5jb20vY29tbWVyY2lhbC1tYWdlbnRvLWV4dGVuc2lvbnMvZW0tZmVhdHVyZWRwcm9kdWN0c3dpZGdldC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;magento featured products&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Merchandise Description&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you have but a Magento keep? , if your reply is &quot;No,&quot;, then you may possibly come across the exciting Magento Themes at our demo retail store. And if you're prepared for a Magento keep, you can uncover good extensions, they had been created by the qualified programmers. Just one of them is EM Showcased Merchandise Magento Extension.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the Magento aid, you can choose capabilities to items. These attributes contain Characteristic Items, Scorching Goods, Particular Solutions. And EM Showcased Goods will support you set them on every individual function. It can research throughout all of your info or a couple of types that you pick. In addition, it can classify and kind solutions in accordance to teams, so clients can effortlessly research and collection. Furthermore, this attribute is useful for the conduite and disposition of your goods.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can simply set up EM Showcased Items and organize as you like, you can decide on the acceptable position for these merchandise in the Magento template. With our specific instructions, you can become a fantastic supervisor, and your fiscal situation will be improved.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;HIGHLIGHT Functions:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;    Present featured solutions in certain types or all types&lt;br /&gt;;    Configure item listing purchasing.&lt;br /&gt;;    Configure quantity of solutions to present&lt;br /&gt;;    Present merchandise as listing or grid or your individual custom made template.&lt;br /&gt;;    Caching time to pace up your site load&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Additional Details&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/b&gt;;Edition R13846&lt;br /&gt;;Compatibility one.four.one, one.4.two, 1.five, one.six&lt;br /&gt;;Locales readily available in this deal English (US) en_US&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Buy now:  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.emthemes.com%2Fcommercial-magento-extensions%2Fem-featuredproductswidget.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.emthemes.com/commercial-magento-extensions/em-featuredproductswidget.html&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>