<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d63e1e6442d8c334a918b46f02e209b2">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsideeffectwww..wikispaces.com%2FSide%2BEffects%2Bof%2BHGH"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://sideeffectwww..wikispaces.com/Side+Effects+of+HGH&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flucasmcclain1024.bravejournal.com%2Fentry%2F68031"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://lucasmcclain1024.bravejournal.com/entry/68031&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Flucasmcclain102.xanga.com%2F754646634%2Fsteroids-side-effects%2FMany"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://lucasmcclain102.xanga.com/754646634/steroids-side-effects/Many&lt;/a&gt;; depression medication side effects can be very unpleasant. Some of the medications may target serotonin as well as other neurotransmitters or without the serotonin. The chemicals they affect are mainly norepinephrine and dopamine. This depression medication side effects include:nausea, fatigue, weight gain, sleepiness, nervousness, dry mouth, and blurred vision. The side effects are less severe than the older type medications.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Selective Serotonin Reuptake Inhibitors (SSRI's)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is also a newer type of medication that has gained a lot of popularity and has proven to work quite well. This medication works by affecting serotonin in the brain. This medication side effects include: sexual problems, drowsiness, sleep difficulties, and nausea. In adults over 65 it can cause and increase in falls and bone fractures.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All medications can cause thoughts of suicide in young adults and should not be prescribed for use in children and caution in young adults. Withdrawals also can occur with all depression medications and medication should never be abruptly stopped doses need to be gradually reduced over time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Green Tea Side Effects: They Exist But Don't Be Afraid!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although green tea has many health benefits some serious side effects also exist.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These side effects only occur, if at all, when consumption is high, during a longer period of time. After all, the United States Food and Drug Administration (FDA) wouldn't categorize green tea as &quot;Generally Recognized as Safe&quot;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most of the side effects are associated with the caffeine content in green tea.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Caffeine, the scapegoat.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some of the negative side effects related to excessive caffeine consumption during a longer period of time are:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Insomnia (unable to fall asleep)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Restlessness&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Anxiety&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Irritability&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Upset stomach (gas)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Nausea&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Headaches (from dehydration)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Tremor (uncontrollable muscle contraction and relaxation)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Loss of appetite&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Diarrhea&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Vomiting&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Heart palpitations (a rapidly or forcefully beating heart)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Irregular heart rhythm (arrhythmia)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Increased blood sugar levels&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Dizziness&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Frequent urination.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Side effects: the rest...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other green tea side effects are:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Allergic reactions&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;People can be allergic to green tea ingredients such as the tannins or caffeine, identified through unexplained skin rash, hives, itching, swelling of the mouth or throat, wheezing, or difficulty breathing or swallowing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These exceptional allergic reactions are similar to, say, a peanut, bee sting, or shrimp allergy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Health issues&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some health issues may occur when drinking green tea, such as:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Iron deficiency anemia. Polyphenols (mainly tannins and catechins) found in this type of tea bind to non-heme iron. Although this anti-oxidative effect is desirable in the fight against cancer, this mechanism may impair the utilization of dietary iron. In other words, polyphenols lower the iron availability and absorption from foods; tea extract decreased non-heme iron absorption by 28%.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two independent studies involving children from different ends of the world (Great Britain and Saudi Arabia) found they may optimize their iron status by avoiding tea with (or after) meals. The interaction between tea and iron can be mitigated, however, by the addition of high sources of vitamin C or consuming tea between meals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Conversely, a 1998 study argued that the reduction in iron absorption may be of benefit to patients with genetic haemochromatosis.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Thiamine deficiency. Another potential side effect is that green tea reduces the absorption of thiamine (vitamin &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;, which can lead to a condition known as Beriberi (nowadays known primarily to alcoholics, people on fad diets, or persons undergoing long-term starvation) where one version attacks the cardiovascular system and another version attacks the neurologic system.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Liver disorders.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>