<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="ed1d62215fb121a6f2c3056538fe8f80">			Girl is on the couch making out with a hot guy, her cellphone rings...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl:Hey babe, I'll be right back. I need to take this call.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Boy: Yeah okay. Sure.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;She walks into the next room.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: Hey! What's up?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy [on her cellphone]: Nothing, hey hun, do you think we could go do something later tonight? What are the chances my boss let me get out early.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: Yeah, sounds great!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy [on her cellphone]: Okay. I'm right by your house, I'll come to get you now.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: That's not such a good idea...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy [on her cellphone]: Why not?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: I'm busy right now... sorry.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy [on her cellphone]: With what? It's our anniversary! You didn't make any other plans did you...?
&lt;br /&gt;;In her head she yells, CRAP! Throws clothes back on quickly.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: No No... I was just eating... with the family.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy [on her cellphone]: But I thought you said your family was away this weekend, up at your resort?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The guy walks into her house, turns the corner into the hallway. Goes downstairs, and finds his best friend on her couch, half un-dressed, trying to pull his pants back on and his girlfriend pulling her shirt over her head.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy: What the heck is going on?!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: I can explain! Please listen to me!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy: Benny? How could you do this to me! Rachel! I thought you loved me! And yet, your sleeping with MY BEST FRIEND!!!!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: John...!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;John with tears in his eyes, he rushes out of room, and slams the door.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Benny climbs out of the window, starts his car, and drives off down the street.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl runs after her boyfriend. Yelling....
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: NOOOO! Please!! Come back John!! Pleeeeeasssse????!! She falls down and cries.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;John turns around, looks straight at his girlfriend in tears.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;John: Why? Rachel, why? I loved you! Oh my God, I'm in love with a whore. Does this mean I have to pay you now?!
&lt;br /&gt;;Here take this as the cash. He drops a ring box on her lap.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;She opens the ring box. Her jaw drops... Before her eyes is a diamond wedding ring.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Girl: You were going to propose?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guy: Yeah... how dumb was I? And as he slowly walked back to his car, his headlights faded... And she was in despair.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Later that night, the girl got a phone call from the police saying he had died of an overdose of drugs and when they found him he had a picture of him and her in his hands
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you love/like someone, and you want them in your life forever. Repost in 380 seconds as &quot;cheating hurts.&quot; Or your true love will walk away from you
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Did you no that every night b4 u go to sleep there is 1 person of the opposite sex thinking of you. they want 2 kiss u, they want 2 b with u, they r always thinking about u, this is all true and not fake. if u repost this in 5 min the person that is longing to b with u will approach u within 1 month and ask u out or grab you and kiss u. but if u break this chain no 1 will like u or ask u out again for 5 years		</conversation>		<conversation id="70f342ba801ab4770114f1d997a5fdc3">			This is called PAN Marriage !!!!! The first person to comment you saying &quot;I do.&quot; will be your Facebox Husband/Wife. Now, this is just for fun. You'd be surprised who wants to be yours.		</conversation>		<conversation id="68c74e378224dcc1c7a8abc8bc6564f7">			You Can Ask Me 1 Question And 1 Question Only And i Promise To Give An Honest Answer Copy And Paste This To Youre Blog , U will Be surprised Wot You Get Asked		</conversation>		<conversation id="bef61ae96c8a5138fbd2e1c21eb05d0a">			1. Getting kissed in the pouring rain
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Have that one hott kiss where your pressed against the wall
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Have a guy that thinks you're the world
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Have a guy that holds on as long as possible when giving
&lt;br /&gt;;hugs
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. A guy that whispers he loves you in your ear
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. Have that moment where you just gaze into each other's eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. When you cry, he kisses your tears away.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. When you're not with your guy he's all that you can think
&lt;br /&gt;;about
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. Wearing his jacket (or his sweatshirt) and everytime you
&lt;br /&gt;;breath in, his scent surrounds you
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10. A guy who will watch any movie with you, no matter how
&lt;br /&gt;;teary eyed you may get.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;11. A guy who squeezes your hand
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;12. A guy that says he loves you and means it
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;13. A guy that will play her favorite song outside her window
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;14. A guy who is loyal
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;15. A guy that will sing to you no matter how bad he is at it.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;16. A guy that will kiss you on the forehead.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;17. A guy that will call you beautiful or adorable...not hot,
&lt;br /&gt;;fine, or sexy
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;18. A guy that will never judge you for how you look.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;19. A guy that says cheezy stuff to you just to make u smile
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;20. A guy that is the same when he is with you and when hes
&lt;br /&gt;;with friends
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;21. A guy that tells you everything honestly.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;22. A guy that is good with your family and introduces you to
&lt;br /&gt;;his family
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;23. A guy that will always let you win
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;24. A guy who stands up for you no matter who he is against
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;25. A guy who calls you at night just to say 'hi' and see how
&lt;br /&gt;;your day has been
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;26. A guy who tells you that your smile makes everything better
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;27. A guy who will sit on the phone with you when you're sad,
&lt;br /&gt;;even if you're quiet
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;28. A guy who you can hangout and have fun with
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;29. A guy that will just randomly call you for no reason at
&lt;br /&gt;;all, just because he misses you
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;30. A guy who will hold your hand through the roughest parts of
&lt;br /&gt;;life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;31. A guy who would love you forever no matter the
&lt;br /&gt;;circumstance.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;32. A guy who wouldn't mind you wanting to get all dressed up
&lt;br /&gt;;and do your make up for him. Even if he says he likes you
&lt;br /&gt;;better without make up.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;33. A guy who you can be yourself with and would
&lt;br /&gt;;still tell you that you are amazing to him.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;34. A guy who runs his fingers through your hair, like he's
&lt;br /&gt;;washing your worries/troubles away.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;35. A guy who tells you you make his day better, just for being
&lt;br /&gt;;you
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If your a Girl and you want this or think its sweet post this
&lt;br /&gt;;with the title &quot;Every Girls Dream&quot; If your a Guy and you would do this
&lt;br /&gt;;or think its sweet post this with &quot;I'm Every Girls Dream&quot; Repost
&lt;br /&gt;;this in 1 minute and something amazing will happen to you tomorrow		</conversation>	</conversations></author>