<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="ad93c215420c2b100ebc1a7ebbd6e892">			Nike, recognized for its trademark swoosh symbol, sounded an upbeat note about services and upcoming major sporting events.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Our timing &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS93b21lbi1uaWtlLWx1bmFyZWNsaXBzZS1zaGllbGQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Women Nike LunarEclipse+ Shield&lt;/a&gt;; is a great choice as we head into an exciting season of sport that starts a few weeks with the Final Four (NCAA basketball championships) and then builds to your Olympics and Euro champs,&quot; said Parker. &quot;These are the moments we love.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Net gain for the quarter that ended Feb. 29 rose to $560 million, or $1.20 per share.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That's dissimilar to $523 million, or $1.10 per share, in last year's fiscal third quarter. And it beats the $1.17 per share that analysts polled by FactSet expected an average of.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The company, located in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1ncmlmZmV5LW1heC1pLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Air Griffey Max I&lt;/a&gt;; Beaverton, Ore., said revenue rose 15 percent to $5.85 billion, just beating the $5.82 billion analysts expected. North American revenue rose 17 percent, Western Europe revenue rose 4 percent, Central and Eastern Europe revenue rose 9 percent, China rose 25 percent and emerging markets rose 23 percent.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A weak spot was Japan, still coping with the earthquake and tsunami of last year. There, revenue rose 3 percent, but it fell 3 percent when adjusted for currency fluctuations.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a125e1b2c48c7329127ce091c8f58825">			Meanwhile, Rivera recently sold arranged of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25pa2VsdW5hcnJ1bm5pbmcuY29tL2tvYmUtYnJ5YW50LWJhc2tldGJhbGwuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Kobe Bryant Basketball&lt;/a&gt;; &quot;South Beach&quot; Nikes, that she bought for $170 in late 2010, for $900.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;People try and finance their (shoe) habit,&quot; says LaVelle &quot;V-DOT&quot; Sykes, who owns a Chicago shop called Overtime, where he and his staff sell sneakers on consignment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;They'll say, 'I'm going to 'rock' one pair and sell two,&quot; he says, mentioning people who wear one pair and try to find buyers for the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25pa2VsdW5hcnJ1bm5pbmcuY29tL25pa2UtZHVuay1zYi1oaWdoLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk SB High&lt;/a&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;You see moms, pops, aunties, a lot of people, across all color lines.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Often, though, sneakerheads are young men very young, 20s and 30s, many of whom now use online to show off their &quot;kicks.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And companies like &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25pa2VsdW5hcnJ1bm5pbmcuY29tL3dvbWVuLW5pa2UtZHVuay1zYi1sb3cuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Women Nike Dunk SB Low&lt;/a&gt;; are utilizing that instant, word-of-mouth communication to their benefit, marketing experts say.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;When I started in this business back in the '60s, there were no such thing as a blogger,&quot; says Michael Carberry, a former advertising executive who is now a marketing professor at American University in Washington.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read more:&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS9lcm5pZWRveWxlMTAyNS9ibG9nLzIwMTIvMDMvMjQvcGVvcGxlLW1ha2Utc3VyZS10by1maW5hbmNlLXRoZWlyLXNob2UtaGFiaXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;People strive to finance their (shoe) habit&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="80b7bfcd8b326816cf6b7c23aa49b6e1">			McKinney Boyd running back Bryan Driskell won MVP honors Sunday at the Dallas Nike Football Training Camp. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With Aledo star Jonathan Gray headed to UT, the senior stands out as among the best running backs in Dallas-Fort Worth. Driskell said he doesn't mind the attention with Gray right out of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLXNob3gtdHVyYm8tMTEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Shox Turbo+ 11&lt;/a&gt;;, but he liked the process. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;It's an advantage to have the competition, to compete for the top spot, so it's a bittersweet feeling,&quot; Driskell said with a wide grin. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With his stock constantly going up, Driskell has brought interest from Baylor, Texas Tech and Auburn. His work in the classroom doesn't hurt him either. Harvard, Yale and Duke have all taken interest on the speedster. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Driskell said a few schools are lining up to watch him at upcoming spring practices, and he anticipates offers from Texas Tech and Baylor. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With a possible choice looming between Ivy League and BCS teams, Driskell's father Stan said your decision is all up to his &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS93b21lbi1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtc2t5bGluZS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Women Nike Air Max Skyline&lt;/a&gt;;. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;He has to go to a place where he feels comfortable,&quot; Stan said. &quot;His mother and I communicate a lot about the fact that it's not just a four-year decision for him, it can be a 40-year decision.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It may grown to be a tough choice, but Stan said he couldn't be more excited for his son. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Bryan has worked extremely hard to arrive at where he is, and it's consolidating for &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS9haXItam9yZGFuLW1lbG8uaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Jordan Melo&lt;/a&gt;; right now,&quot; Stan said. &quot;I'm a proud father.&quot; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Driskell rushed for more than 2,000 yards and scored 30 touchdowns last season.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read more:&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS9lcm5pZWRveWxlMTAyNS9ibG9nLzIwMTIvMDMvMjYvYm95ZC1yYi1pcy1tdnAtYXQtbmlrZS1mb290YmFsbC10cmFpbmluZy1jYW1w" target="_blank"&gt;;Boyd RB is MVP at Nike Football Training Camp&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="c6956c955b5111f9e4a89e3ed00add17">			Really the only person in the quintet not to lead his team in scoring -- though he's not far behind Blake Griffin -- Paul is third in the league in assists and ranks second in steals. His trade to the Clippers, which spawned the infamous &quot;Lob City&quot; moniker has done approximately create highlights; Paul has produced the perennially-moribund franchise relevant. Arguably the league's best pure playmaker, Paul instantly transformed the Clippers into a Western Conference contender, nevertheless with Griffin and other weapons also attracting attention, it is difficult to say he shows off even more than the other names on this list.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My Write-name is Adidas Basketball,who is a editor of zoombasketballshoes.com,which contain a great deal of information about Adidas Basketball,Air Jordan,Nike Air Max 90 an so on.Welcome to visit our website--&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS93b21lbi1uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtdGFpbHdpbmQtMjAxMC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Women Nike Air Max Tailwind+ 2010&lt;/a&gt;;,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS9haXItam9yZGFuLXJldHJvLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Jordan Retro&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="329fb7bd40d634ce9dd40779e09030ff">			The ad has sparked interesting reactions among my lady runner pals, starting from &quot;that's SO cute, sweet, etc.&quot; to &quot;why can't she just be running because she would rather run? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The latter sentiment is echoed somewhat in this AdWeek column by writer Rebecca Cullers - she calls the ad &quot;fake girl power&quot; and suggests it's this is the usual paradigm of &quot;man saves woman&quot; flipped, as in &quot;Why does one side will have to be weak and in necessity of saving?&quot;-&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS93b21lbi1uaWtlLXNob3gtYWdlbnQuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;SaleNike Shox Agent (Nike Air Max) running shoes&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cullers writes:  &quot;I know I'm purported to feel all warm and happy about this new little love story, and I know I'm in the minority. But I look like I'm speaking up for boyfriends, husbands, and dads everywhere when I say that I don't believe we chicks need to depict you dudes as bumbling, inept and totally incapable just to make ourselves feel better.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I had a different reaction - I didn't swoon over the couple going the length for love, and I didn't fume over the apparent plot trajectory of woman-only-fuled-to-great-things-by-the-love-of-a-good-man. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Probably the greatest byproducts of completing a marathon for me has been the remainder confidence that my feet will not fail me. They will take me long distances if I need them to. Running has made me strong and mobile. I don't will need to rely on wheels or motors to get me where I want to go. I won't ever really be stranded.-&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56b29tYmFza2V0YmFsbHNob2VzLmNvbS9rb2JlLWJyeWFudC1iYXNrZXRiYWxsLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Kobe Bryant Basketball&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is exactly what I based on in this ad - the woman's freedom. She wants to be somewhere, she laces up her hot pink sneakers, she goes. She gets there.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>