<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="214f4305af5b54a301f1ae1309ef12b4">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chrismentormee.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.chrismentormee.com/&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chrismentormee.com%2Fwho-is-chris-farrell%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.chrismentormee.com/who-is-chris-farrell/&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chrismentormee.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.chrismentormee.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blog traffic is the thing that many blogger will say is their primary trouble. You can discover an awful lot of programs on the Internet for getting traffic but most of those programs are just garbage. You'll find great ways to get more visitors to your blog and in the following paragraphs we are going to be looking at social bookmarking as a way to get this traffic you need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One thing you should know about social bookmarking is that the social websites themselves will be able to boost your site visitors almost instantly. Something else you need to know is that every time you post one of your blog posts on these social bookmarking sites you end up building backlinks. And backlinks are one of the primary tips to getting traffic from the search engines. And also the more backlinks you obtain the higher your blog will normally rank within the search engines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The way to do this is to join to as many high page rank social bookmarking Internet sites as you can. Some of these higher page rank websites are usually sites like Google Bookmarks, Hi5 and Reddit. Needless to say there are a huge selection of social bookmarking Internet sites that are available online. Actually, your best bet would be to subscribe to about 50 of these sites. The search engines are a fantastic place to start when your looking to put together a list of websites. Although this will be very time consuming to sign up to all the websites, it will be worth it in the end.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At this point every single day when you add a completely new post to your blog you will need to take the hyperlink to that post and add it to each and every social bookmarking site. In the beginning you may find that this can take about 2 hours a day but in time you will be able to cut that down to about an hour or so. This technique when done on a daily basis can give you an instant surge in your website visitors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Something you might want to consider are those who will actually go out and set up a bunch of social bookmarking sites for you and usually just ask for about 5 to 10 dollars to do this for you. Of course this will still leave you with needing to login each day and post to the sites. For those of you who would like an easier way to get these links published on social bookmarking sites there are a pair of programs that could help. The a pair of systems which will do this for you are only wire and ping. fm. The two of these programs will immediately post your links to the social bookmarking Internet sites using your login details for each website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In a nutshell, social bookmarking can really supply your website visitors the boost that it needs to take your earnings to a higher level. You should also understand that every time you produce a post and bookmark that page you will be developing 40 to 50 backlinks to your blog which will also help with your search engine ranking.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8d1bdc4b2cd301230c703d4646cf11ac">			Alternative sourcesof energy that are not harmful to our environment need to be found, and the hunt for them is pressing. In addition to corruption and poverty, the mess our world is in right now is aggravated hugely by pollution. Many groups - and businesses - are worried about this and are taking steps to effect a reduction of greenhouse gases and other pollutants. Traditional sources of power are responsible for creating a lot of poisonous pollution, which is why clean, renewable sources of power are avidly sought. Majority of people are still uneducated when it comes to renewable energy, and how it can impact their lives. What follows is descriptions and explanations of the best known alternative sources.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Probably the best known alternative is solar, which collect energy from the sun's rays in solar cells. The rays of the sun fall on thermal panels which transform the heat to electrical power. Also, steam can be generated by the rays hitting parabolic mirrors, causing the water to get hot. You don't need to rely completely on science, though, since a lot of light and heat can be channeled into your home merely by drawing the drapes or opening the blinds. Nighttime or clouds obscuring the sun present a problem, though, since they keep solar energy methods from operating well. As a result of the cost involved, there are few large solar power stations.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wind power is yet another energy source which is becoming more popular these days. Driving almost anywhere these days allows one to see big-bladed wind turbines. Electrical eergy is produced by the wind using electrical generators. Electrical networks nationally are currently being provided electrical energy from large-scale wind farms. Smaller wind turbines are also being erected by homeowners and companies to supply their own electrical needs. Aside from the fact that it doesn't have detrimental byproducts, is that you can rely on the wind to blow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Then we have geothermal energy, which wells from the center of the earth. Turbines are run by steam released through drilling into hot rocks found deep under the surface of the earth. This becomes the power source to run electric generators, and done the right way will produce no damaging by-products. Geothermal plants can be autonomous in producing an energy source, but are expensive to put up. Falling water, which drives turbines to create electrical power, has been used for quite a while now at dams. One other way to harness the kinetic energy of water is provided by its tidal flow.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One can only be dumbfounded by the abundance contained in nature when discovering the many alternative ways it produces energy. People have to become more aware and play a larger role in taking care of our planet, and learning  about  renewable energy sources  is  one way  to  begin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.superbgarden.com%2Fbusiness-news-america%2Fnew-internet-marketing-products%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.superbgarden.com/business-news-america/new-internet-marketing-products/&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.senditbro.com%2Funcategorized%2Fchris-mentor-me-is-almost-here%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.senditbro.com/uncategorized/chris-mentor-me-is-almost-here/&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.andreatam.com%2Ftop-home-based-business%2Fhow-to-promote-chris-mentor-me%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.andreatam.com/top-home-based-business/how-to-promote-chris-mentor-me/&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bestbookcombo.com%2Fhome-based-business%2Fchris-farrell-is-a-great-teacher%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.bestbookcombo.com/home-based-business/chris-farrell-is-a-great-teacher/&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>