<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="28960b61a38ae8b0ad424a905fcc04f3">			And here goes a real key secret in what cases the patterns are indeed indicative of a reversal but in what cases brokers trap TA pattern-fanciers Is there someone doubting the fact that patterns are known not only to traders, but as well to brokers with their mouths watering to make a rod for the backs of lovers and connoisseurs of the above patterns, just like on the sample chart below - Fig. GBPUSD H1 chart as of May, 09-11, 2005, a classical &quot;;inverted Hamp - S&quot;; (See Note below)At 1.   However, the latter did not meet competition and stopped operations in spring, 2002. The author of the paper just hinted that even the alliance of the 3 biggest world banks could not make any serious competition to Organizer of the &quot;;game&quot;; at Forex (to Consortium or somebody else). Williams concerning &quot;;Trading chaos&quot;; that rules Forex What's important, all methods of this author issue from this postulate. He states that trends are created by traders, whereas brokers just realize these trends and place traders' orders.   Your trading system must not be just a mixture (farrago) of various techniques. After reading heaps of books on Forex , all of them make complaints about &quot;;such a mess in their heads instead of enlightenment&quot;;. you must get used to work with the demo account according to this technique to such extent of automatism that you &quot;;sense' it as your own initial (original) trading system of the work at Forexc. You must clearly see what pointes, &quot;;borrowed&quot;; from other authors, can help you personally to work at Forex , to improve your trading system for getting extra profits.   AND WHAT'S NOW Nowadays many of traders are impotent to gain under 3 pts spread without commission and slippage. Thus, this book is intended for those willing to perceive Forex market laws. In order to get understanding of the way 5-10% of successful traders obtain profits, let's at the outset analyze the reasons and the way the outstanding 90% of traders suffer losses. It occurs despite the amount of literature on the issue equals to hundreds of fundamental books, written by authors, having gained capitals expressed by means of more than 7-digit figures (G.   Because of the constant shift in the directional bias in each currency pair, that &quot;;trending condition&quot;; exists less than 20% of the time in the Forex. What this means to the trader is when using indicators to identify profitable set-ups, those set-ups are going to occur infrequently. In fact, computer models show that when using a simple moving average or a combination of SMA's, a profitable set-up will occur once every 42 days. So the solution has been to attempt to develop an indicator that will find more frequent set-ups.   A Forex trader must understand that the exponential moving average does not take into consideration breaking economic news and current action analysis. The 200 EMA indicator does have an advantage of showing you the trader's psychology of what they feel the currency price should be but by no means as an indicator for trading Forex. To trade Forex you must have basic knowledge and information on how the market moves, interest in learning, and common-sense. You must develop your own strategy according to current market events, pricing, and resistance.   &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50cnVzdGVkaGYuY29tL2luZGljYXRvci90b3AtaW5kaWNhdG9ycy90aGYzLXNjYWxwZXItYW5kLXN3aW5nLWluZGljYXRvci8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Swing Indicator&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>