<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="7a3cc9a31fa59da596a215fc8b021c3e">			 Time-domain description of the objective physical characteristics of speaker element in the timeline, with the change of time-frequency domain characteristics of their changes. Time domain characteristics of the change process not only in the frequency of the speaker unit is described in response to state, but also changes the time course of the response described speaker unit status, namely, from the perspective of a comprehensive three-dimensional picture of the response characteristics of speaker units. This is very important, but often overlooked by people! It should be noted that many comments on the subjective feelings, such as low sound is clean, the background is clear, if levels of clear, sound the depth of field etc, speaker unit is closely related to the time domain characteristics. As the speaker units in different time-domain characteristics of the speaker system was given various shapes personality. According to personal views, speaker unit in time domain is an objective evaluation of the merits of a speaker unit performance, or essential and very important aspect. As a designer speaker system is necessary for the speaker unit on the time-domain characteristics of a more in-depth research and analysis. Accumulated along the spectrum after (commonly known as waterfall) and the speaker unit step impulse response is time-domain characteristics of some of the more intuitive and visual expressions. Accumulated along the spectrum after only applies to the testing speaker unit features analysis, features and analysis on the speaker system (including the voice box within the standing wave situation) more helpful. Also be emphasized that the time-domain characteristics of the test on the environmental factors is very sensitive. Under normal circumstances, to select the anechoic chamber as test environment, otherwise, test results will be unreliable.
&lt;br /&gt;;4, electrical impedance characteristics
&lt;br /&gt;;       This is the speaker unit's basic features, as well known. It describes the speaker unit of electrical impedance model of the size varies with the frequency of the situation. The figure is Vifa5 &quot;(c13wg-08-08) the impedance characteristics of modules, from Europe by the acoustic test system given in CLIO.
&lt;br /&gt;;         We can learn by impedance speaker unit DC impedance, resonant frequency, resonant impedance peak of the size of the rated impedance and the inductive coil size and so on. Here are two points which should attract attention:
&lt;br /&gt;;   1, the size of voice coil inductance
&lt;br /&gt;;      Usually woofer f&gt;; 200Hz, the impedance characteristics will show a monotonic increase in the rate increase reflects the size of voice coil inductance. Excessive inductance speaker will adversely affect the work unit (especially on the frequency characteristics) and the Divider difficult. To reduce the inductance of voice coil speaker unit, often using the magnetic circuit and circuit approach to compensation to be resolved.
&lt;br /&gt;;   2, the size of the resonant impedance peak
&lt;br /&gt;;      Resonance peak is too large will also have speakers near the unit in which the frequency of adverse effects work, which is especially prominent in the tweeter, in production should be given appropriate control and processing. The figure is an &quot;element of the impedance characteristics, can be seen tweeter resonance peaks appear in the people most sensitive hearing band 1K-2K is 2 frequency system, the combination of high and low frequency department, handled properly, will produce sound effect made the band hard, round and so do not feel bad.
&lt;br /&gt;;5, distortion characteristics
&lt;br /&gt;;       We often say that the distortion should include harmonic distortion, intermodulation distortion, transient distortion, phase distortion, harmonic distortion and other sub-linear and nonlinear, steady and unsteady distortion. Here we mainly discuss the impact of several large and capable of being used in electro-acoustic test system as described in the distorted form, to further deepen the objective understanding of the speaker unit.
&lt;br /&gt;;    1, harmonic distortion
&lt;br /&gt;;       Harmonic distortion is the most common speaker unit nonlinear distortion. Harmonic distortion caused by the main speaker unit is a vibration system and the nonlinear magnetic circuit system. Work practice, can improve the speaker unit of material (diaphragm, positioning support piece, fold rings, etc.) to improve the magnetic properties and the linear system to improve the speaker unit of harmonic distortion. The figure is the JBL products (model: JBL806G-1 S/N-1645) harmonic distortion curve, the system is given by the LAUD. From the figure we can see that the harmonic distortion characteristics of the unit, or good, except in a very low frequency outside the second harmonic distortion below 2%, while the third harmonic distortion better than 0.2%.
&lt;br /&gt;;         According to the information and practical experience of listening, in general, harmonic distortion below 1%, there is a good sound effect; harmonic distortion under 3% are likely to be perceived by the people; harmonic distortion of 5% When the annoying sound effect; if more than 10% harmonic distortion, the subjective sense of the intolerable. Meanwhile, people are more sensitive to the odd harmonic distortion. Third harmonic distortion is usually much smaller than the second harmonic distortion should be (in a different order of magnitude) will have a good sound effect. In practice, we often see this situation, speaker unit of the third harmonic distortion and second harmonic distortion is the same in an order of magnitude, and even the weight of the third harmonic distortion of second harmonic distortion than the weight of more Great. This speaker unit should be said that there are many areas that need improvement, and its sound effect is disturbing. Therefore, the size of the odd harmonic distortion, can not but cause us more concern. To obtain a better sound effect, we must also improve the speaker unit in the odd harmonic distortion make greater efforts.
&lt;br /&gt;;    2, transient distortion
&lt;br /&gt;;      Transient distortion is due to speaker vibration system can not keep up cell changes in electrical signal distortion caused by. This distortion can usually pass the test speaker unit step response of the rising and falling characteristics of features to express. Rising edge of the characteristics of reflected sound speaker unit rate should be the starting instant case, while the falling edge of the characteristics of reflected sound speaker unit should disappear suspension damping. People know that the speaker unit of the signal response of the &quot;Speed&quot; and &quot;damping&quot; in the subjective listening evaluation of a large impact. There is also a more vivid expression of the falling edge characteristics is after speaker unit along the cumulative spectrum. After the above two from the accumulated along the spectrum chart is easy to see, after the accumulated along the spectrum from the entire band image of the speaker unit described in the disappearance of the damping signal, different frequencies have different characteristics of the falling edge, but also speaker unit that is under different frequencies have different transient response (and transient distortion). Therefore, reflected in the subjective listening on that we heard 10 million kinds of speakers with individual unit and speaker system (which in this article are described in the time domain characteristics).
&lt;br /&gt;;   3, phase distortion
&lt;br /&gt;;      Electrical signal through the speaker unit, the electric and acoustic phase change in the formation of phase distortion. As previously mentioned, as the phase distortion of the subjective sound evaluation of the impact of listening more and more attention by people, especially the speaker system, acoustic phase distortion on the field, positioning the subjective listening evaluation of the impact of production can not be ignored. Have information on some people's hearing on the high frequency phase distortion to be more sensitive than the low frequency.
&lt;br /&gt;;      Phase distortion in addition to phase-frequency characteristics can be expressed, it can also be expressed with the group delay characteristics. Generally speaking, in the mid and high frequency, group delay&gt;; 3ms, the effect on the speaker system will produce audible playback of. The figure is a two-way loudspeaker system group delay characteristics of the case. We can see that half of graph shows the group delay characteristic around the 4K, group delay&gt;; 4ms, is not difficult to determine, there is a crossover phase did not butt good reasons, will be listening to the subjective evaluation with to adverse effects.
&lt;br /&gt;;         Causes phase distortion produced in addition to speaker unit itself, the main frequency divider design is unreasonable and the installation of the speaker unit layout of unreasonable reasons.
&lt;br /&gt;;6, directional
&lt;br /&gt;;       Point feature is speaker unit in all directions in space, the frequency response. It is the perspective from space described speaker unit outside the space in the reference axis frequency response situation. We mentioned the speaker unit of frequency domain characteristics, time characteristics, then the features here can be said to point to the spatial characteristics of speaker unit, speaker unit is one of the important features.
&lt;br /&gt;;      According to acoustical theory, the low frequency sound waves radiated by speaker unit speaker unit is much larger than the wavelength of the side of the diaphragm, the acoustic radiation at this time no obvious directional. But with the increase in frequency when the speaker unit wavelength of the radiation acoustic speaker unit is equal to or less than the side of the diaphragm, the sound radiation will be generated along the reference axis focusing of acoustic radiation pressure generated clear direction, in listening room for the non-uniform phenomenon, the effect of subjective listening seriously affected. Therefore, it is easy to know, every speaker unit size will be provided for their practical edge frequency limit. Speaker diaphragm area of the larger units, in fact, the lower frequency with the border. For example, 8 &quot;woofer and practical boundary frequency of approximately 1.8K. The figure is an 8&quot; woofer point to the measured frequency response characteristics of the situation can be seen from the diagram, the reference axis high frequency response up to 5.5 KHz, when the deflection of 30 degrees, its high-end frequency response only to 2.2KHz. 
&lt;br /&gt;;       Point to features usually can not point to express the characteristic frequency response curve, you can also use the directional diagram of the means to express. As shown below, is a CLIO system testing vifa 1 &quot;treble unit (Model: d25TG-85) directional nature of maps, the map was pointing directional with good heart shape, indicating the high unit when the 10KHz there is still a good directional. good point to get a good feature is the minimum requirement of subjective evaluation of one listening.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>