<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e36e32082102bb40391ecfe6cd085e41">			One more thing you will find out regarding smoking is the fact that many individuals could never quit without getting some kind help to do so. And so, the &quot;;Stop Smoking Today&quot;; program is what we will be having a closer look at.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the best things about this method is that the success rate associated with quitters is 98%. When you look at all the drugs and patches that happen to be on the market you'll find that this has a better success rate than all of them. A test was initially performed on 5, 000 men and women and they all had a chance to use this method to quit smoking. They were happily surprised to determine that in just a months time 99. 7% of those individuals were able to quit smoking. Although the percentage dropped just a little at the 6 month mark, 97. 2% of them were still able to continue being smoke free. As a way to break this down for you 4, 860 men and women were able to quit smoking out of 5, 000 individuals in the test group. These numbers are an absolutely amazing percentage for a quit smoking percent rate.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are other options for individuals to stop smoking like, one on one therapies, support groups and also the patch, but none of them are as successful as this system. The biggest issue with all these other methods is that they don't stop the urges. They can lessen the cravings, but they never eliminate the cravings entirely. This can be the biggest reason why many individuals who try quiting employing these methods fail.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rob Mellor is the creator of this method and it is so effective because it uses NLP therapy that he just happens to be an expert in. 38 minutes is all it could take to end up having you be an ex-smoker. I am sure you recognize that not everyone will be able to quit after using this program just once, so for some people you may need to use this program every day until your smoking cravings are gone. For some people they are able to quit in just the first day but others will take longer. If You have Gained Something Out of Reading this Document then You Wouldn't Desire to Miss Out on this Piece of Valuable Details - &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.craigbaldenhofermd.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.craigbaldenhofermd.com/&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I am certain you have heard about all the side effects that people have to deal with when they quit smoking, this program will not generate side effects. You will find that a number of people who quit smoking start packing on the pounds or end up being extremely short tempered. On the other hand this system will have none of these side effects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You will discover this program on the net and it is offered as an immediate download. $47 dollars is exactly what you will have to pay to get this program, however if you think about it, that is a lot less than what you would pay for your next carton of cigarettes. And if for any reason you might be one of the 2% that this method didn't work for, you will be pleased to find out that you will get your money back. Therefore if this does not work for you, you will get your money back.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>