<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2a9a675a8320d0cf813f8951f170a6ed">			Let's get started by reading my post on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F19568683%2Fa-sodium-free-alternative-to-water-softeners-version-169"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/19568683/a-sodium-free-alternative-to-water-softeners-version-169&lt;/a&gt;, I will i implore you to ask you to produce an open mind. If you may well definitely would like to know more info on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsaltless66water.xanga.com%2F753019322%2Fdoes-the-salt-free-water-softener-really-work-ver--937%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://saltless66water.xanga.com/753019322/does-the-salt-free-water-softener-really-work-ver--937/&lt;/a&gt;, this article can definitely help you understand more about the subject issue. If you are currently ready let's participate in and appearance what this is certainly exactly about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you're currently considering buying a salt free water softener, then you're probably trying to decide between a Pelican Natursoft or the NuvoH2O. The reviews are very mixed. Either 1 star or 5 stars, not much in between. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What are the benefits and reasons for using a salt free water softener? These questions are being asked by people today regarding the water in their home. The general answer would be to control sodium, have less impact on the environment, and to save money in the long run.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For people that have high blood pressure or hypertension, controlling the sodium in their water with a salt free water softener can be a possible solution. The amount of sodium that a normal salt based one puts into the water may be minimal, but small amounts of sodium can have an impact on individuals who are trying to limit sodium in their lives. Adding just a little salt into the water can pose as a health problem for those that are at risk.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A softener that doesn't use salt also helps to reduce our effect on the environment. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The salt used in traditional softeners eventually ends up in the ground water and soil and can have a negative impact on the delicate ecosystems around us. A study showed that a single family household will put as much as 500 pounds of salt into the ground a year. It's not hard to see that the gradual build up of salt can really affect our environment over time, especially affecting our ground soil, plants, tress, and the animals around us. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some areas in the country have already put a ban on regenerative salt water softeners to decrease the impact.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The salt free water softener saves money over time. It may cost more upfront, but in the long run will save money since it uses little electricity or none at all to condition the water. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As the crystal structure grows, the flow of water and friction and movement of additional hardness minerals against the crystal structure, will cause small pieces to break off and flow with the water through the pipes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The small pieces, that have broken from the crystal structure into the water as suspended particles, continue to attract hardness minerals and prevents them from sticking to the insides of the pipes, water faucets, showers, water heaters, and dishwashers. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As they flow with the water they continue to grab the hardness minerals from the water creating micro crystals.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The salt free water softener does not use any electricity and the whole system is made up of water flowing past the calcium carbonate crystal structure for it to function correctly. So if you're looking for a salt-free water solution, you owe it to your health to check out the new technology of conditioning magnets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/sterlingjones/blog/blogid=4308575" target="_blank"&gt;http://en.pan.netcom/sterlingjones/blog/blogid=...&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fsaltfree31h20con%2Fjournal%2F1929217%2Fthe-truth-about-salt-free-water-conditio.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.getjealous.com/saltfree31h20con/journal/1929217/the-truth-about-salt-free-water-conditio.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fblogbud.com%2Fcgi-bin%2Findex.pl%3Fpoemnumber%3D451258%26amp%3Bsitename%3Dsterlingjones%26amp%3Bpassword%3D310331s7RLpvj6hdU74151.3103%26amp%3Bpoemoffset%3D0%26amp%3Bdisplaypoem%3Dt%26amp%3Bitem%3Dblog"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://blogbud.com/cgi-bin/index.pl?poemnumber=451258&amp;sitename=sterlingjones&amp;password=310331s7RLpvj6hdU74151.3103&amp;poemoffset=0&amp;displaypoem=t&amp;item=blog&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>