<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="9">		<conversation id="41dfed47fbebb4e7e6843d34aa6a0d01">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jennyreviews.com%2Fhealth-and-beauty%2Fnono-hair-removal-system%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.jennyreviews.com/health-and-beauty/nono-hair-removal-system/&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Unwanted hair can be a huge hassle: shaving needs to be done everyday and can leads to cuts, scrapes and dry skin; waxing is uncomfortable and when done professionally can get costly and laser hair removal is effective but very expensive. Women have been longing for a treatment to remove unwanted hair that is affordable, convenient and pain free for years now – with No!No! Hair, the answer is finally here.		</conversation>		<conversation id="27e9194f8fd728a6a804c2e8d8958c5e">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.excaliburbrokerage.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.excaliburbrokerage.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Term Insurance is generally the least expensive and least complicated type of affordable Life Insurance. It provides life insurance protection at a low cost for as long as premiums are paid, or for a specified period of time, such as 10, 15, 20, or 30 years.		</conversation>		<conversation id="150ddb0beda10466b4ee7887ead0ae66">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.purelynewborn.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.purelynewborn.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Purely Newborn Photography specializing in the art of newborn natural light photography. The first couple of weeks of life are the most brief and miraculous. Ensure those memories of your newborn baby are captured for a lifetime.		</conversation>		<conversation id="16c1be09cf3071c4ea938e8d783a556d">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ebizuniverse.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ebizuniverse.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;eBizUniverse Web Design did a great job re-doing our website. Please contact them if you need web design:1900 E. Golf Road,Suite 950Schaumburg, IL 60173847-220-9541		</conversation>		<conversation id="7e26f9550e572312aacf881c235fb389">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fstream.fidoo.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://stream.fidoo.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Fidoo, which stands for Fashion Information Distribution Organization Online, is an online search engine that can pinpoint the availability of any brand in any store in any location within the USA.....talk about a shopoholic's dream! Fabulous fashionistas, lost tourists, and tired travelers....Fidoo is your fashion GPS! Fidoo also provides a space for individuals to create their own fashion profile and to view articles, photographs and blogs of fashion news, events.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9ed36abb1d5cdacf3bb8e7d0e393c3af">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.scuf.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.scuf.net&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Most web directory entries are also not found by web crawlers but by humans.[1] The categorization is usually based on the whole web site rather than one page or a set of keywords, and sites are often limited to inclusion in only a few categories. Web directories often allow site owners to submit their site for inclusion, and have editors review submissions for fitness.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8592e71dd033e43d95ff4e8821edb2bb">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.legaljohn.co.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.legaljohn.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Legal John provides legal direction on criminal solicitors, PPI claims &amp; criminal barristers in London		</conversation>		<conversation id="7acb4ed6886c833b4f139e3410d38008">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.fivesite.co.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.fivesite.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Fivesite are experienced website designers who operated in London and across the UK to very high professional standards		</conversation>		<conversation id="7d8cfc1bb1d6645dd057319c860b8fba">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.searchwithphonenumber.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.searchwithphonenumber.com/&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Search with phone number to find name and address. Address search with phone number for location or name search with phone number to find owner info.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>