<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f49a9240c49aff973b21a4bcff7059b6">			This is the time of the year when the&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myphillylaser.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myphillylaser.com&lt;/a&gt;; of us are showing much more skin. You may be slim and toned, with rock solid abs and sculpted arms, but a hairy back or perhaps a bumpy, red ingrown bikini area can definitely kill your thing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Should you choose your quest, you will &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myphillylaser.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myphillylaser.com&lt;/a&gt;; that active sun-tanning generally is a &quot;no-no&quot; when doing a training course of laser hair removal treatments. This is good advice. Active sun-tanning ought to be avoided within two weeks of a laser hair removal treatment. This includes using a tanning booth or active sun worship by the beach or by the pool.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There's a two causes of this. First, the skin is much more responsive to the sun (and therefore, a sunburn) for 2 weeks following a laser treatment. While any sunburn is bad, sunburn on skin that has recently been given a laser could be more damaging to that skin.&lt;br /&gt;;Second, the lighter your skin is, the more &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myphillylaser.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myphillylaser.com&lt;/a&gt;;  each laser treatment will be. This is because the laser is absorbed through the pigment it fires upon.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myphillylaser.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myphillylaser.com&lt;/a&gt;; harnesses the pigment within the hair to kill the follicle. The more pigment you have in your skin (whether from genetics or from a suntan) the more gently the skin must be treated.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The good thing is that most people take more precautions than ever before in the sun. Dark tans are out, and sunscreen and good skin care are in. If the stubble on your legs is making you crazy, and you can limit your sun exposure, it'll most likely be &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myphillylaser.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myphillylaser.com&lt;/a&gt;;  for you to begin or continue your laser treatments. And then year shaving could be a subject put to rest.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This short article provided by    laser hair removal Philadelphia. Style Medspa is making laser treatment affordable AND convenient with many locations throughout the Philadelphia area, Narberth or Montgomeryville.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myphillylaser.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myphillylaser.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>