<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="2af5c3a6a465f90c2ba4c80b847e9a6d">			The focus of this costume is making the outfit retro or simply vintage. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Retain the following items in mind when building the final &quot;nerd suit&quot;: a couple of thick-rimmed, taped-up black eye glasses; a button-up shirt complete with the top button buttoned and that has at least one pocket protector with actual pens hinged for many years; hair gel; pants that will be, preferably, about 3 to several inches too short for you; matching belt; suspenders (think &quot;Larry King&quot;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;; Oxford-style footwear and practically knee-high white-colored socks. Apply a generous amount of hair gel to that hair and part that (think Alfalfa in the Little Rascals). &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your pants ought to be pulled-up as far as they'll reach-practically as if you were wearing them available your chest! If you're a female, you'll dress fairly similarly, but with a few key distinctions. Nerdy females usually have either unkept or weird hair-dos. A skirt is almost always worn by the female nerd (as opposed to the male high-rise pants) and knee-high socks with the same Oxford-style shoes. As soon as applying makeup, be sure to get that different shades clash with each other and (optionally) make it unevenly applied. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Halloween &lt;/strong&gt;; and also All Hallow's Eve. Just the name conjures up all kinds of creepy, spooky, spine tingling thoughts for this purpose special night. When the dead awake and roam planet earth anything can happen. The decorations are becoming more sophisticated than ever. From the days involving &lt;strong&gt;; jack-o-lantern &lt;/strong&gt;; s and spooky ghost costumes made from cutting holes in your mother's white sheet, this day is becoming more advanced in regards to costumes and decorations guaranteed to entice goose blobs. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Setting up the Entrance to your house of Horror &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Commencing at the entrance of your property you can set the stage for the terror that lies inside. Turn your front yard in to a graveyard with tombstones that glow and then a mist making machine will enhance the eerie effect. A couple of ghosts seemingly floating above the tombstones will enhance the effect. One of the substantial skeletons in cages hanging from the front porch screaming to be let out will don't forget to make one wonder if they should proceed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; The main Room of Terror &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After you enter through the door that generally seems to open by itself the very first thing you see is your life-size ghostly white butler waiting to serve you. What he might have to serve you is a surprise. Before you took very many steps in the room, a lifelike rat runs across the floor in front of you (they are remote controlled and actually look being a rat). Thunder is actually booming and lightning is usually flashing. Eerie organ new music is playing. Suddenly from high in the corner a corpse swoops down in front of you and back up to the ceiling. You hear voices begging for help in the next room. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; The other Room of Terror &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After you finally make it to another room, without running out entry door, you creep in the doorway expectantly. All is dark and in the corner you see a strange light that generally seems to hang from the air. &lt;/em&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nbGFtaXouY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;deguisement&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="b061ca48c0e427ea7a82b5be1471e205">			.&lt;br /&gt;;Halloween is quickly approaching of course, if you're searching for costume outfit ideas, let us help you find an exciting costume for this once a year spooktacular event! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The majority of your ideas may come easily from watching your favorite movies, or you may find about the hottest trends for any holidays in your preferred magazines, and come up using a really creative idea to get a great costume character. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nevertheless, if you happen to be at a loss for a unique costume idea this coming year, times a ticking! Don't fear, we can offer you a list of the newest Halloween suits available, and add a little twist that will make a hilarious splash for your outfit this coming year. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Halloween fun starts whenever you create that unique fancy dress costume, that everybody wonders how you invented that concept! Many adults and small children love to be the biggest market of attention with the the majority of creative characters that nobody else will have, and that's a tough task alone when there are a wide selection of retail stores selling this also Halloween costume. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The preferred costume tips we can offer to ensure that you don't have half a dozen people with the same Halloween outfit, is to try and mix and match that costume, in order to create an outrageous combination, which will have your friends and relations howling their heads off of! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Think Out of the Costume Box To Get hold of Those Creative, And Excitement Juices Flowing! If you're having a little trouble picking out something that will really your party guests, remember you must think outside the box! If you need a little push in the right direction, let us provide few of our suggestions to obtain you started, and see if you possibly can expand on our outrageous Halloween tips. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Turn into a Vampire Baby: Just ponder over it for a second? Dracula needed to be born and brought into this world just like us, so did you consider he came into this world together with his fancy ensemble? Of training course not, so how about taking a large blanket for some sort of diaper, a full-size complexion color or light gray body tights, cape, white-colored face paint, blood, and a pair of fangs. Add a baby bottle packed with deep red cranberry moisture and VOILA! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now with all your baby vampire outfit ready to defend myself against the dark underworld of infants, we are sure you can imagine the laughs you can get, and I bet you wouldn't have thought that Dracula would be getting his/her gruesome cheeks pinched so much during the night time. After your party, it's going to be rather painful crawling back up your coffin. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here's another wacky one! Cross-Dressing Darth Vader: Find a really awful dress, ideally off-white or pink, and get hold of a Darth Vader mask. Now we're sure along with the popularity of Star Wars that you would run into many Vader costumes, but while they may be switching over to this dark side that night time, you will be flipping-over on the Darth Vader Cross-dressing aspect. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Come on, can't you picture this great idea! &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nbGFtaXouY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;deguisement adulte&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>