<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="49f5ddc7feab558c7c7062caad03346d">			Since the raised Terri was deprived of the post of Captain of England and after the resignation of coach Fabio Capello, three lions ' new leader has been outstanding. Although recently a England national team match, Tottenham lumbar discitis Parker to wear the skipper's armband, but who are not sure Parker on the captain to appear in the European Cup. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0LWtpY2tzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWh5cGVyZHVuay0yMDExLWMtMjEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;nike hyperdunk 2011 for sale&lt;/a&gt;;Rumors are also numerous on the captain of the road, not including Steven Gerrard, Wayne Rooney the core role, the young goalkeeper, Hart became one of the candidates. But the veteran Joe Hart Manchester City-Creaghan said directly: Hart is not to become the new captain.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bill Kerrigan is a city and one of the most outstanding goalkeeper in the history of the England national team. He comes from a city youth camp, and in 1967 in Blackpool and Manchester City in the Carling Cup put on the first show, after 16, Bill Kerrigan became a city in front of the main, and has followed the team to win the League Cup and the  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0LWtpY2tzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtMjAxMS1jLTE0Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap nike air max 2011&lt;/a&gt;;    European Cup winners ' Cup and many other honors. In addition, he also serves as a substitute for the England national team play in 1982 FIFA World Cup.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;, Referring to the may serve as the post of Captain Hart, Bill Kerrigan blunt: &quot;goalkeeper important areas too far away from the stadium, goalkeeper could only be master of his area, when the game masters in defense he is. So Hart would not necessarily fit to become the goalkeeper. ”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Creaghan considered post of Captain should be derived from non-goalkeeper players who, because their effects can play a full role. But throughout the world football, goalkeeper, being captain I'm afraid for the success of a few. Examples of Spain Real Madrid both goalkeeper Casillas, who is a very good goalkeeper he completed the duties of Captain, often seen in the Real Madrid game he announced his teammates in defense, and the Spain national team, Martin Carthy himself as the captain who has played a World Cup and the European Cup Winners Cup. Is also coincidentally, Creaghan effect when the England squad, ahead of his two main forces in front of goalkeeper has become the team captain, James Rhee-Hilton-Clemence and England legend Peter had served as captain of the national team.		</conversation>		<conversation id="dff0195c8b6b51a6ad18791ef12b0316">			Tottenham Bolton in the FA Cup, Bolton midfielder Fabrice Muamba because of a heart attack on the field in a coma was urgently sent to hospital, Muan-Palestinian situation settle down now finally was relieved by all people who care about him, but it also sounded a warning in order to prevent similar incidents from happening again, Tottenham Club to take the lead, heart check arrangements right away all players accepted.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Effects due to Fabrice Muamba, Villa Premier League Bolton of the week had been postponed, but Jamie Redknapp stressed, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0LWtpY2tzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1ncmlmZmV5LW1heC0xLWMtOC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;griffey 1 for sale&lt;/a&gt;;  Tottenham to stoke English Premier League match of the week there will be no extension, he warns Tottenham players to concentrate on preparing for the game. In order to avoid Fabrice Muamba, and Tottenham had arranged for their players to accept three heart check. Tottenham's heart doctor Advisor Sharma said: &quot;today, all players receive a heart scan. ”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fabrice Muamba in the event, Tottenham is in addition to Bolton, affected by the largest team, Tottenham striker Defoe shocking scene &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0LWtpY2tzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1tYXgtanItYy0xMC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;nike air max jr for sale&lt;/a&gt;; on the pitch so far to leave a deep impression, to appease the players emotions, psychological expert fallinf players of Tottenham has been sent out, but there are some indications, the psychological impact of this there may be some delay.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Jamie Redknapp said: &quot;Saturday Muan alarmed by the events of the bus so that all people, this can have some impact, despite the difficult environment, but we must unite insisted on playing our season. We will provide the support they need to players, helped them get rid of this effect, we will always think of Fabrice Muamba and wishes he could recover. ”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Lucky is that we already have a cardiologist on the training ground, today we arranged checks for players, so we can eliminate the fear of any player. They need the game, that's for sure. They realized that this was no accident, that is the probability of one out of 10,000 things that appear, in my football career, I have never seen something like this. On Saturday things too hard to believe, this is a never before seen on the pitch. I don't think any of us believe it will happen, when you realize what happens when this hell is astounding. ”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tottenham these arrangements is reasonable, because in site see Fabrice Muamba coma Hou, in shocked after, believed many players will has &quot;I will also encounters also event&quot; of concerns, this undoubtedly will will to players were brings negative of psychological effect, but in after heart check and psychological enlighten Hou, believed Tottenham players should can get rid of this shadow, again in Stadium Shang show out himself of strength.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>