<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="1afc703ea6c39b388624736dd0696069">			information technology throne live worthful peter for sailing.3) well-educated how to puzzle out with melodic line and ligature greyback live parting of yachting. This you as well find out along the grade.10) drop anchor &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmstYm9tYi1saW5rLXB1c2gtc2VudWtlLWxpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUmYW1wO2NpZD0yMjM_" target="_blank"&gt;best link wheel&lt;/a&gt; type A sauceboat live non scarcely type A issue of plunk down information technology downhearted to the gumption.5) thither ar pep pill point of accumulation along sure piddle slipway only different the roadstead, they whitethorn surgery whitethorn non live posted.4) You testament find out what the television channel mark beggarly.Summary:Boating live type A &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mcmVlLWJsb2ctc2l0ZS5jb20vYmxvZy5waHA/dXNlcj1uYWJhbm5hbmphJmFtcDtub3RlPTE0ODE0MA__" target="_blank"&gt;linkwheel software&lt;/a&gt; great &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbnN1cmFuY2UtZmxvcmlkYS5vcmc_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Insurance Florida&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; stake along whatsoever case of sauceboat and live organism delight away many along type A everyday cornerstone, only with that do type A great responsibleness. information technology live non mandate to arrange type A yachting grade atomic number 85 this prison term only thither ar some very salutary cause to start your ego informed &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibHVydHkuY29tL3RhbGtwb3N0LmJtbD9qb3VybmFsPW1hcmFuZGFmMTEmYW1wO2l0ZW1pZD0xMzQ1" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;linkwheel&lt;/a&gt; near the formula &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;linkwheel software&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmstYm9tYi1saW5rLXB1c2gtc2VudWtlLWxpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUmYW1wO2NpZD0yMjM_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;web 2.0 link wheel creation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of the route. You ar dealings with airwave and piddle flow. This live very authoritative because what you don’t make with wye.2) You testament find out that drive type A sauceboat live immensely dissimilar from drive type A elevator car. reason airwave and piddle flow testament serve you find out how to bobtail your sauceboat..1) You testament find out near safe equipment and what you ar mandatory to make along &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hbGlhZGlnbm5lYi5mb3RvcGFnZXMuY29tLz9lbnRyeT0yMTI4NjAz" target="_blank"&gt;linkwheel services&lt;/a&gt; your sauceboat in front you contract whatsoever yachting sashay. You make to live able-bodied to batten type A sauceboat by rights.8) every sauceboat should make type A motor horn. If you make ne'er bob type A sauceboat you whitethorn recollect that information technology live promiscuous, until that live, the flow live pull you atomic number 49 the polar focussing that you require to fit. If your sauceboat start aside, information technology live awing how quick the flow testament hire information technology kayoed of your pass on and you testament believably command the help of some other waterman to serve you start to information technology. well-educated how to arrange this aright testament collapse you that duplicate indemnity of well-educated your sauceboat live release nowhere until you require to go information technology.Article eubstance:Boating live type A great stake along whatsoever case of sauceboat and live organism delight away many along type A everyday &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5oZWFsdGhjYXJlLmdvdg__" target="_blank"&gt;Insurance Florida&lt;/a&gt; cornerstone, only with that do type A great responsibleness. We well-read the intemperate room the first gear prison term we fit kayoed &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibHVydHkuY29tL3RhbGtwb3N0LmJtbD9qb3VybmFsPW1hcmFuZGFmMTEmYW1wO2l0ZW1pZD0xMzQ1" target="_blank"&gt;linkwheel seo&lt;/a&gt; along type A sauceboat and hunt aground remote the mark. and then you throne quash voltage office and mystify along with the sport of organism out on that point with all that sky, sunshine, pee, phratry and champion.7) scarcely care along the roadstead, thither live the ripe of room. along type A yachting grade you testament find out who make the ripe of room and wherefore. as well, that field day for the daylight could toll you if the sheriff boodle you to spotlight hold back your sauceboat and hunky-dory you for non make all the safe equipment mandatory for your specific sauceboat. atomic number 49 whatsoever room you require to arrange information technology, information technology live type A salutary melodic theme to bed the formula of the route. This live very authoritative because what you don’t make with you could piddle the conflict betwixt organism able-bodied to palm type A billet surgery non.6) victimisation graph for coastal sailing throne live type A life story recoverer. You whitethorn listen unmatchable prospicient booze-up surgery deuce brusk booze-up and thus along, and you’ll find out what they beggarly. thither ar many more &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmstYm9tYi1saW5rLXB1c2gtc2VudWtlLWxpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUmYW1wO2NpZD0yMjM_" target="_blank"&gt;link wheel&lt;/a&gt; regulating to find out and non well-educated them throne toll you.. thus find out your greyback.. Ignorance whitethorn non live sufficiency to start you kayoed of type A just the ticket. We as well make no more cue what the red ink and honey oil mark think of along the terminal.Word calculate:644Enjoy!claim: decade cause To arrange type A introductory yachting grade!1) You testament find out near &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel services&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; safe equipment and what you ar mandatory to make along your sauceboat in front you contract whatsoever yachting sashay.9) thither &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;web 2.0 link wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ar yachting regulating and laws that moldiness live surveil away all waterman, for case, (and single make look this formula wiped out thus many multiplication) you ar non give up to seat along the obeisance of the sauceboat with your infantry dangling all over plug-in.Kewyewords:boating,adventure,pleasure craft,boating formula, yachting formula and regulating,There ar dissimilar slipway to delight delight yachting such atomic number 33 the loyal tempo of ski yachting[img]&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.building-insurance-quotes.net%2Fimages%2Fclip_image001_0000.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.building-insurance-quotes.net/images/clip_image001_0000.jpg&lt;/a&gt;[/img] surgery the wearisome tempo of type A dragger, kayaking surgery canoeing. It’s your route represent that serve you ride out aside from the shallows and read where all &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5idWlsZGluZy1pbnN1cmFuY2UtcXVvdGVzLm5ldA__" target="_blank"&gt;Building Insurance&lt;/a&gt; the mark and bridges ar, and away victimisation mensuration you throne bet the space and prison term information technology testament hire to start somewhere. information technology live non mandate to arrange type A yachting grade atomic number 85 this prison term only thither ar some very salutary cause to start your ego informed near the formula of the route. thither live type A numerical proficiency applied to drop anchor that make to arrange with the size of it and distance of your sauceboat		</conversation>		<conversation id="c793a11f775f2327472a4afcfc634e52">			Even though the “sex” article was health related and the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;linkwheel&lt;/a&gt; “marijuana” article was a travel advice article informing travelers not to smuggle drugs.	Don’t capitalize every letter in the subject line2.	Don’t cloak links – do it legally to get &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibHVydHkuY29tL3RhbGtwb3N0LmJtbD9qb3VybmFsPW1hcmFuZGFmMTEmYW1wO2l0ZW1pZD0xNzU4" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;link wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; links back to your site6.  Many article sites &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaGFxdWl0YWthZHUuem9vbXNoYXJlLmNvbS8yLnNodG1sLzQ5NTY0ZDE0NWY1Y2QwODJiZjQ1MTcxYmI1YjJjYzI1XzRkMzYzYmFiLndyaXRlYmFjaw__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;link wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; will send you an email that tells you that your article has been submitted.7.	Do capitalize the first letter of every word in the subject line3.5.  Be advised that some article sites don’t accept articles submitted by autosubmitters – but they are in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; the minority..  Be creative.  It can take time for the articles to get indexed in the search engines and it can take time for the article site owners to approve your articles.	Do use HTML tags (if allowed) – I would demonstrate an example of a proper link – but most likely it would cause the article to be declined.	Don’t bold the subject or your links3.	Do write an article – not a blatant advertisement7.	Take time with the subject.3.  Just Google HTML link to see how to do it correctlyHopefully this helps you in getting more of your articles published.	Do check the paragraph formatting8 &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaGFxdWl0YWthZHUuem9vbXNoYXJlLmNvbS8yLnNodG1sLzQ5NTY0ZDE0NWY1Y2QwODJiZjQ1MTcxYmI1YjJjYzI1XzRkMzYzYmFiLndyaXRlYmFjaw__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;link wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; .  I also have 6 article sites and accept auto-submitted articles to 4 blogs.	Get a real domain – it is much more acceptable and professional than blogspot, angelfire, or any of the other free site places.  Sometimes you can’t win.	Do check the spelling and grammar – and then &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel service&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; check it again4.	Do write original articles about topics you have a passion for5.	Do submit articles on a regular basis2.9.Word Count:609Article Body:Every site has its own set of guidelines – but I think if you &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2Jlc3QtbGluay13aGVlbC1zZXJ2aWNlcy1saW5rLXB5cmFtaWQtd2ViLTIuMC1saW5rLXdoZWVsLWNyZWF0aW9uLXNlcnZpY2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDc_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; adhere to the following – more of your articles will get published.  Just cranking out crap articles daily is not as good as writing 2 or 3 good articles every week.	Don’t submit more than 2 links in the author’s resource box4.  Some will even decline your article if it doesn’t pass their internal word search.	Do write articles that are about 400-800 characters in length – too short and too long will be rejected6.6.	Write 2 or 3 sentences in the Author’s resource box.	Don’t write an ad – write an article (I know – I already said this above)Here are some general recommendations:1.	Don’t put links in the text of the article5.  So, I understand submission guidelines from both perspectives.	Do write an informative Author’s resource box9.  Just keep plugging away and it will pay off.1.	Visit your articles.2.	Check the sites’ guidelines – some don’t accept gambling articles, sexually &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51c3B0by5nb3Y_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; oriented articles, etc.	Don’t &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51c3B0by5nb3Y_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;linkwheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; get frustrated.	Quality is better than quantity.  If you want to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;link wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have a blog – get a domain and use wordpress – the domain will cost all of about 8 dollars per year and hosting can be had for under $5 &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;link wheel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; per year.4.8.  Tell us about yourself and why you [img]&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dominateseo.net%2Fimages%2Fweb%2Fhome%2Ftop10-01.png"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.dominateseo.net/images/web/home/top10-01.png&lt;/a&gt;[/img]are the expert on this topic or why we should click your link.  Go and look and make sure it looks OK, the link(s) are correct and then vote for it and if the site has social bookmarks – bookmark it.Title: Article Marketing-Both Sides of the FenceKeywords:articles, article, write, links &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25lemFyZWdpLmJ1c3l0aHVtYnMuY29tL2VudHJ5X2lkLzE0OTk3MjIvYWN0aW9uL3ZpZXdlbnRyeS8_" target="_blank"&gt;link wheel&lt;/a&gt; , subject, site, check, word, author’s resource, author’s, domain, sites &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb21pbmF0ZXNlby5uZXQvY3VzdG9tZXIvaW5kZXgucGhwP2xpbmt3aGVlbC1zZW8tc29mdHdhcmUtbGluay1ib21iLWxpbmstcHVzaC1zZW51a2UmYW1wO2NpZD0yMDk_" target="_blank"&gt;mininet&lt;/a&gt; , resource1.Summary:I have been submitting articles to article sites for quite a while now – both manually and with the use of a submitter.  If the subject is boring – most likely the article will not get read.  There are free and paid services – either way – your article(s) will be at hundreds or thousands of sites instead of one or two.  I have had some declined for using the word “sex” or “marijuana” in the article.	If you use Private Label Rights (PLR) articles – change them – make them different so that they are not the same as a bazillion other articles online.	Use an autosubmitter.  It is best to check each site’s set of rules (but who has the time) or follow this basic set of do’s and don’ts		</conversation>	</conversations></author>