<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="81596cf87397bc8c333e59e65744787e">			He attended his guests with much politeness, during their stay of two days; and he put down the time thus spent, as consumed in a sea voyage from Beyrout to Acre. The moment they left, the royal pilgrim went ashore&lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26gt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; handbags outlet&lt;/a&gt; again, and happily accomplished the remaining distance to Jerusalem, through Nassara and Nablous, without any other hinderance &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci factory&lt;/a&gt;or obstruction than his going one night to see a French vaudeville, while supposed to be enjoying his well-earned repose at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci outlets&lt;/a&gt;Kama or Muddin. And thus was accomplished that royal pilgrimage that was never performed. The King reached Jerusalem without going there; and the people saw him return who had never departed.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&quot;; Well,&quot;; said Harold Knudtzen, &quot;;the Kings&lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26gt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; outlet&lt;/a&gt; of Saxony are no longer such simpletons. The present Monarch loves, indeed, good wine, i craftily qualified; but he also, like Uzziah, King of Judah, loves husbandry. Josephine herself had not half so frantic a passion for flowers as he ; and not for flowers alone in their beauty, —not for botany, either, merely for &lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26gt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; outlet online&lt;/a&gt;amusements sake, but for phytology and pharmacy, as connected with it.&quot;;&quot;;He lisped Linnaeus,&quot;; said Lowenskiold, &quot;;before &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci outlet online&lt;/a&gt; he could speak plainly.&quot;;&quot;; And, by reputation, be knew Tournefort better than be did Knecht Rupert,&quot;; added Harold.He himself told us, when we met him in Dalmatia,&quot;; continued the latter, &quot;;that he could spell Dodecmdria and Trigynia before he could read Grimms Story-Book; and that&lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26gt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; mens watches&lt;/a&gt; he knew the meanings of monopetaloics and cam- paniform before he was acquainted with the languages from which the terms were derived. I never saw a man so eager in pursuit of apetalous amentaceous flowers; and as for carryophylous&quot;;	&quot;;Leave off your abominable phrases!&quot;; said I, &quot;;and begin by telling me how you two very modest fellows introduced yourselves to the acquaintance of the Sove¬reign of Saxony.&quot;;&quot;; The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci mens watches&lt;/a&gt; introduction was effected through a very light- hearted and intelligent fellow-botanizer, whom we met on our way from Zara up to the mountains. We had all three lost our way while endeavouring to find an infundihdiform &quot;;	&quot;;Nay,&quot;; interruptedI, &quot;;I care not what you found, if you choose to tell it in pentameters.&quot;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="ec6ea055471cf75ba788eda22a83bab2">			&amp;quot; Well,&amp;quot; resumed Knudtzen, &amp;quot; we were in a wild part of the country,—weary, hungry, cold, and in the dark. Wan¬derers could not well be in a worse plight. We were as flute as Junos columns near the church of St. Helia; and the skeleton doing duty there for that of St. Simeon of Judaea, the pride and palladium of&amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; handbags outlet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; the people of Zara, looked in far better condition, and in, especially, better raiment, than could be boasted of by us humble pedes¬trians. We &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci factory&lt;/a&gt; had walked many leagues, when we reached a sorry inn kept by a Gipsy, where we hoped to find rest and refreshment, but were permitted to enjoy neither. Our swarthy host stood in his door-way, like&amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; outlet&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; Horatius Codes at the head of the bridge. Beds he did not even profess to find for travellers. He had not slept in one himself for years, and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci outlets&lt;/a&gt; was none the worse, he said, for the privation. Leopold asked for wine.
&lt;br /&gt;&amp;quot;We have three sorts of wine, said the Gipsy, c which travellers like yourselves once tasted and paid for. I have the very wines which &amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; outlet online&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;the seven Schwaben asked &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci outlet online&lt;/a&gt;for in the Qoldenes Kreutz at Ueherlingen. &amp;quot; 4 What! old Sauerampfer ? cried Lowenskiold. &amp;quot;  The same, said our singular host.  It is not quite so sour as vinegar, hut it will pierce the marrow of your bones like a sword; Do! nothing in the world! that is precisely it! Tou will want three men each of you. For Dreiman¬nerswein is three times as rough and ten times as sour as vinegar; and he who drinks it must be held fast by two men, while a third pours the liquid down his throat!&amp;quot; And &amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; mens watches&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt;what of the third of these Olympic beverages ? said I.&amp;quot; It is called Bachenputzer, and has peculiar qualities too. He who lies down to sleep with a flask of it in his body, must be aroused every half-hour, and turned over. Otherwise a pint of Bachenputzer would eat a hole right through his side! &amp;quot; The Gipsy laughed aloud as &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci mens watches&lt;/a&gt; he uttered these words. We ourselves laughed in despite of our vexation; and, somewhat startlingly, a fourth voice took up the cachin- natory affection, and laughed even louder than the ori¬ginal three.		</conversation>		<conversation id="31839bc05b97b3d8e1ef8c39d732686d">			As the new-comer stood in the light of the door-way, the landlord touched his cap, withdrew hastily into the passage, and slammed the door in our faces, leaving us in Cimmerian darkness, summer trousers, and a&amp;amp;amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;amp;amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; handbags outlet&amp;amp;amp;lt;/a&amp;amp;amp;gt; drizzling rain. The matter was no &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci factory&lt;/a&gt; longer risible, and we were beginning to be seriously annoyed, when the mysterious stranger, whom we could but indistinctly see, invited us to accompany him we knew not whither, and hospitably to partake of we knew not what. We accepted the invitation most gratefully; and after a full half-hours walk, we found ourselves on the skirts of a wood. In less than half that time, we subsequently reached &amp;amp;amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;amp;amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; outlet&amp;amp;amp;lt;/a&amp;amp;amp;gt;aneat little house within the wood itself; and I do not think ten minutes had elapsed, ere we had made such toilette as travellers may, and, with &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci outlets&lt;/a&gt;some doubts as to the reality of the circumstance, detected ourselves in the act of eating vermicelli soup, and wondering how it had reached us.&amp;amp;amp;quot; Before our repast was entirely dispatched, our host, in whom we &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci outlet online&lt;/a&gt;saw a young, well-made, and exceedingly amiable personage, informed us that he was on a botaniz¬ing expedition for the benefit of an establishment in Northern Germany; that he had been two months set¬tled in the house in which we then were, and that he had already given temporary shelter to three plant-&amp;amp;amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;amp;amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; outlet online&amp;amp;amp;lt;/a&amp;amp;amp;gt; explorers, who had resorted, in their need, to the house of Djewitzki, the Gipsy, and who had found to their sorrow, that it had nothing of the quality of an inn about it, except the sign.&amp;amp;amp;quot; We talked of flowers that night,&amp;amp;amp;quot; continued Knudt- zen, &amp;amp;amp;quot; as though they were the foremost as well as the fairest things in all the world. But we were sciolists in the science, and, contrasted with us, our host was a sage. He knew that &amp;amp;amp;lt;a href=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com%26amp%3Bamp%3Bamp%3Bgt%3Bgucci"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.guccifactoryoutlets-us.com&amp;amp;amp;gt;gucci&lt;/a&gt; mens watches&amp;amp;amp;lt;/a&amp;amp;amp;gt;agrimony was under Jupiter, and ange¬lica under the Sun in Leo; that milfoil was under the influence of Venus, and that garden basil was a herb of Mars. If every new idea be worth the knowing, why, we gained knowledge by the information, that all the dodders are under Saturn. We heard, for the first &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ndWNjaWZhY3RvcnlvdXRsZXRzLXVzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;gucci mens watches&lt;/a&gt;time, the virtues of the plant enchusa.&amp;amp;amp;quot;&amp;amp;amp;quot; But,&amp;amp;amp;quot; interrupted Lowenskiold, &amp;amp;amp;quot; we were enabled to remind our host of what Dioscorides says about it,—that if any who have newly eaten of it do but spit in the mouth of a serpent, the reptile instantly dies.&amp;amp;amp;quot;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>