<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="9">		<conversation id="67fbdb4a16570af4894b393a66b1b0b6">			Juno are a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;web design&lt;/a&gt;  company that focuses on results and conversions. Working closely with clients Juno's team has the ability to create the right type of website to fit around your needs whilst ensuring it ranks highly in search engines by using search engine optimisation (SEO) techniques. Content management systems allow clients to update the website themselves keeping a fresh feel and being in touch with their visitors; no longer should a site be simply created and left, Juno  believe that it's an ongoing process to increase conversions, bring more visitors to a site and expand the site's reach as a whole.		</conversation>		<conversation id="832243a5604ba9bdd44e752e3c164fd9">			What does your house say about you? The items you chose to decorate your house can reflect on your own personality so interior design is an important part of any socialite's life! Designers worldwide know that the devil is in the detail, one out of place item in your home can ruin any chic look you were looking to create. Interior design can be very addictive and some people even move home to work on a new fresh canvas!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS9pbnRlcmlvci1kZXNpZ24v" target="_blank"&gt;interior design&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="7bee894b1fcaf505cb5a4597a34a5580">			Web designers and web developers are two completely different sets of skilled workers.  Web design BUILD a website from scratch and often do things that isn't even seen by users in the “back-end”.  Web designers create the look and feel of a website and may never even get their hands dirty with code or back-end systems.  So when you're looking for either a developer or designer remember that they are completely different kettle of fish!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/126981083_3726903_29072499.jpg" /&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="359da1f64696d82c3be4cfa7a6abd44a">			&lt;object width="336" height="295"&gt;&lt;param name="movie" value="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4293179"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name="wmode" value="window"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;embed src="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4293179" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowFullScreen="true" wmode="window" width="336" height="295"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;On the 6th of June 1944 a Reginald Trery Wiltshire landed on Juno Beach in the midst of what was later known as D-Day. He then went on to lead successful missions as a tank commander in world war two. Sixty two years later his grandson David Wiltshire founded a web design company in Nottingham. Having been inspired by his grandfather’s wartime past, he named this company Juno Web Design.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over the years Juno has diversified its offering and services to clients using a strong mix of custom built web applications and open source software. This ensures all clients are provided with the best user experience and content management systems available alongside constant updates and new features once their site is launched. This also ensures rapid development of your website and a quick call to action.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We maintain a strong internal recruitment system with passion, determination and the willingness to learn being key points that we look for in the web developers, designers and others wanting to work with us. This is backed up by a strong internal training system that allows all staff members to learn what they want to learn and we set internal goals to make sure they achieve this over periods of time with the help of others amongst our team.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We do &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;website design&lt;/a&gt;   and we are proud of it.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d6341973c5fa1bbe84c9e50fb0c73450">			When &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;web designers&lt;/a&gt; create a website they tend to make several main versions of it and have to then make many more alterations before it is finally finished.  The fact that websites are just digital pieces of information means that it's very cost effective to make big changes such as a different background colour; image trying to do these designer changes to a bricks and mortar shop!  Clients generally tend to like to tweak websites created by designers which takes up a lot of man hours and sometimes a lot of stress.  Whenever you create somebodies brand, consider these 'tweeks' in your pricing.		</conversation>		<conversation id="3d7a7d18a5560bbcfce88c8d9f84f237">			Web designing can seem like an easy job, all the designer has to do is move a mouse right?  WRONG, it's a very skilled job and requires knowledge of user experience, branding and attention to detail.  Graphical programs like Photoshop aren't beginner friendly and require at least half a year's training to use effectively.  Look at obscure websites like ones for a local plumber or builder, you'll see a ghastly array of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS9uZXdz" target="_blank"&gt;web designing&lt;/a&gt; attempts, many of which include comics sans or other graphical atrocities!  The best way to design a site is to copy your favourite elements from many other sites, if you pick popular sites then these will have had many experts opinions on the design and will work well with conversion rates.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e9970135d84bbf244bb9e30d2a3df0cb">			Web design for ecommerce is getting more and more complicated; even with the market becoming saturated and prices being driven down through competition, additional web development needs are again increasing costs.   An ecommerce site now needs features that weren’t an issue a few years ago including on-site SEO, EPOS management, mobile phone versions and social media integrations to name a few!  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS93b3Jr" target="_blank"&gt;Ecommerce web design&lt;/a&gt; teams generally stick to old methods and use tried and testing web templates, which they can brand up.  The cream of the crop such as Juno Web Design use bespoke systems for each client based on conversion rates, SEO and brand exposure.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b29d5b421905334e68c39fefe169b440">			Nottingham is a vibrant city with many creative businesses close to the city center.  Home to many sub-cultures (such as the gothic rock scene), Nottingham is awash with designers from classical to contemporary.  With it’s central UK location on the M1 and relatively cheap rental rates, many web companies are settling in Nottinghamshire as an alternative to the expensive capital London.  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS93ZWItZGVzaWduLW5vdHRpbmdoYW0_" target="_blank"&gt;Web design in Nottingham&lt;/a&gt; has now over 100 companies competing for business alongside a vast majority of print designers.  If you are looking for a web designer in Nottingham then chose a big company with an impressive portfolio.  Juno Media work with many large brands and are situated in Nottingham, their number is 0845 544 1766.		</conversation>		<conversation id="cfba00b25c8b4499abe97a227762dbce">			If you’re looking to take the next step with your business, and want to begin selling and marketing your products online, the best thing you can do is to create a website. Designing and making a website can be a very tricky task, one which many people would struggle to do without the help of a good web design team. Often businesses work with a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdW5vd2ViZGVzaWduLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;web design&lt;/a&gt; company when they’re looking to produce a new website, or simply update the branding on their existing websites.  Web designers have the job of taking all of the clients wants and needs into consideration, before designing a site that looks appealing, but is also practical for potential customers to use. The cost of having a web designer produce a website for your business depends on many factors including: the type of website, how complex its design is and the length of time it takes to design it.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>