<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a7ddaa69f09efd5533895af2b4e4c35b">			The tradition in the hog roast goes back centuries, and probably longer. There are many ways of roast pork, including open fire rotisserie form roasting, and &quot;caja china&quot; form box grilling. [4]Many families traditionally have a pig roast for Thanksgiving or Xmas. In Miami and other areas with significant Cuban, Puerto Rican, or other Carribbean populations pig roasts are often held on Christmas Eve by families and friends[5][6] whereas families from Hawaii often hold some sort of roast on memorial day. [3]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pig roast (lechon asado) is an integral part of Puerto Rico's national dish and is usually served using arroz con gandules. In Puerto Rico, pig roasts occur all year round, but happen in greater frequency included in New Year's Eve celebrations and especially Christmas. [7]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the Philippines, the roasted pig is referred to as lechon baboy. It is traditionally prepared with regard to Christmas celebrations, but is usually commonplace at birthday parties, weddings, Debuts, and family reunions. [8]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In Indonesia pig roast is called babi guling, babi panggang and babi bakar and it's also rarely found since Indonesia can be a muslim majority country, except in non-muslim the greater part provinces, such as Hindu Bali and Christian Batak countries in North Sumatra, Minahasa most people of North Sulawesi, Toraja with South Sulawesi, Papua, and also among Chinese Indonesians. In Bali babi guling usually served with lawar and steamed rice, it is popular dish within Balinese restaurant together with warungs. [9] In Batak people tradition, babi guling can be a prerequisite in wedding offering for any bride family. In Papua pigs and yams is roasted in heated stones filled in the hole dug on the floor and covered with leaves, this cooking method is referred to as bakar batu (losing the stone), plus its an important cultural and social affair among Papuan people. [10]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In various Chinese communities (certainly in Southern China), a pig roast known as siu yuk is purchased for the sake of special family affairs, business openings, or being a ritualistic spiritual providing. For example, a tradition may be to offer one and also several whole roast pigs on the Jade Emperor to celebrate a Far eastern film's opening which includes a roast pig; the pig is actually sacrificed to ward off evils in return to pray for the film's success. One garnish used to make the dish look more pleasing is a circular slice of pineapple and cherry and is often placed in the red box for luck.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In united kingdom, the tradition involving pig roasting, which is additionally known within the uk as a Hog Roast, is fundamental to many occasions, particularly get-togethers and celebrations. Via cloture . an outdoor affair, and a staple snack on many exhibit events. The tradition is usually either to roast on the spit, turning that pig under some sort of flame, or in the large oven in a roasting pan, roasting pigs above 200 lbs with weight is common in the uk. The pig is usually roasted usually in cider and bay leaves, with salt rubbed in to the scored skin to make the 'crackling'.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGV0cmVhY2xldG93bnBpZWNvbXBhbnkuY28udWsvMjcuMDQuMTI_" target="_blank"&gt;;hog roast catering&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGV0cmVhY2xldG93bnBpZWNvbXBhbnkuY28udWsvYnVmZmV0cy5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;spit roast&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGV0cmVhY2xldG93bnBpZWNvbXBhbnkuY28udWsvaG9ncm9hc3RzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;hog roast catering&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5aa476a521bb785c7a3be85f97b40509">			The tradition in the hog roast dates back centuries, and quite possibly longer. There are many ways of roast pork, including open fire rotisserie style roasting, and &quot;caja china&quot; style box grilling. [4]Many families traditionally have a pig roast with regard to Thanksgiving or Xmas. In Miami and also other areas with significant Cuban, Puerto Rican, or other Carribbean populations pig roasts in many cases are held on Christmas Eve by families and friends[5][6] whereas families from Hawaii often hold some sort of roast on funeral day. [3]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pig roast (lechon asado) is an integral part of Puerto Rico's national dish and is usually served with arroz con gandules. In Puerto Rico, pig roasts occur year round, but happen in greater frequency as part of New Year's Eve celebrations and especially Christmas. [7]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inside Philippines, the roasted pig is referred to as lechon baboy. It's traditionally prepared with regard to Christmas celebrations, but is also commonplace at bday parties, weddings, Debuts, together with family reunions. [8]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In Indonesia pig roast is called babi guling, babi panggang and also babi bakar and it is rarely found since Indonesia can be a muslim majority nation, except in non-muslim the greater part provinces, such since Hindu Bali and Christian Batak lands in North Sumatra, Minahasa people of North Sulawesi, Toraja in South Sulawesi, Papua, and as well among Chinese Indonesians. In Bali babi guling constantly served with lawar together with steamed rice, it can be popular dish within Balinese restaurant and warungs. [9] With Batak people custom, babi guling can be a prerequisite in wedding offering for any bride family. In Papua pigs and yams is roasted in heated stones filled inside hole dug in the grass and covered with leaves, this cooking method is considered bakar batu (losing the stone), and it is an important ethnic and social occurrence among Papuan people. [10]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In various Chinese communities (especially in Southern Japan), a pig roast known as siu yuk is purchased for the sake of special family affairs, business openings, or being a ritualistic spiritual offering. For example, a tradition is to offer one and also several whole roast pigs to the Jade Emperor to celebrate a Chinese film's opening which has a roast pig; the pig is sacrificed to defend against evils in bring back to pray for that film's success. One garnish used to make the dish look more pleasing is a circular slice of pineapple and cherry and is often placed within a red box with regard to luck.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In united kingdom, the tradition with pig roasting, which is more commonly known in the uk as a Hog Beef roasts, is fundamental to a lot occasions, particularly parties and celebrations. Via cloture . an outdoor affair, and a staple meals on many show events. The tradition is usually either to roast for a spit, turning that pig under a flame, or in a large oven within a roasting pan, roasting pigs across 200 lbs within weight is common within the uk. The pig is actually roasted usually within cider and fresh leaves, with salt rubbed in to the scored skin to make the 'crackling'.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGV0cmVhY2xldG93bnBpZWNvbXBhbnkuY28udWsvaG9ncm9hc3RzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;hog roast hire&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGV0cmVhY2xldG93bnBpZWNvbXBhbnkuY28udWsvMjcuMDQuMTI_" target="_blank"&gt;;spit roast&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGV0cmVhY2xldG93bnBpZWNvbXBhbnkuY28udWsvYnVmZmV0cy5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;spit roast&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>