<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c6153ad02f454947c59d3c7a3e8ee01b">			Your Nebraska possesses vast grasslands, Ponderosa pines, quiet prairie streams, rocky bluffs, river valleys, and sandhill buffalo ranges. The &quot;Cornhusker State&quot; greets visitors the best way nature intended - having a standing invitation to unforgettable outdoor adventures. It is really an ideal destination location for RVers and campers with lovely Nebraska campgrounds and Nebraska RV camping resorts during the entire state.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In west central Nebraska near Gering, Wildcat Hills State Park your car, Nature Center, and Big Game Reserve overlooks its northern border Platte River Valley. Wildcat Hills' terrain is a rough-and-ready blend of forested canyons and rocky hillsides. Interestingly, almost all of the native stone structures at this park were built through the Depression-era Civilian Conservation Corps. A more moderen, split-level Nature Center blends nicely into Wildcat's existing terrain with such improvements as a mock Ponderosa pine extending from very beginning to second-story ceiling. Its northern border wall of the center sports tinted glass panes designed to allow guests to discreetly observe birds munching at window-mounted feeders. Additionally there is a buzzing, live bee colony and interactive computer displays that focus on local birds and endangered species. Hikers and cross-country skiers enjoy the park's nature trails and footbridges encompassed by mountain mahogany and cedar trees, yucca plants and wildflowers. At the enclosed, Big Game Reserve, visitors can catch morning views of bison, elk, bobcats and coyotes. (Before arrival, RVers should contact the park office for specifics of vehicle size restrictions for the summit access road.)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lake McConaughy, or &quot;Big Mac,&quot; and Lake Ogallala State Recreation Areas are headquartered in Ogallala inside Platte River Valley of southwestern Nebraska. &quot;Big Mac&quot; may be the state's primary reservoir, measuring 20 miles long, four miles wide, and 142 feet at its deepest point. Moreover, its 100 miles of shoreline and sandy white beaches give you the perfect setting for waterside recreation. Lake Ogallala, the &quot;little lake,&quot; is alongside McConaughy. Together, they equal to a huge fishing arena. Anglers pull several kinds of record-breaking bass, walleye, yellow perch and rainbow trout out there clear, chilly waters. Besides first-class fishing, favorite hot weather activities with this park include swimming, boating, sailing, windsurfing, sailing and diving. Fall brings waterfowl hunters to McConaughy/Ogallala and winter will be the serene season for ice skaters, backpackers and ice boaters.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nebraska National Forest's Bessey Playground is based near Halsey inside central the main &quot;Cornhuskers State.&quot; As the world's largest man-made forest, it is really an extraordinary woodland first conceived when botanist Dr. Charles Bessey heard an Indian legend about pine forests growing on Nebraska's sandhills. Bessey speculated whether such woodlands may make a comeback. And, in 1902, he implemented experimental sandhill tree plantings. His seedlings - red cedars, jack and Ponderosa pines - were the humble beginnings of today's Nebraska National Forest. Besides prolific trees, the Bessey Recreation Area provides the Forest Service's only pool area, and also fishing and hunting options, hiking trails, and tubing fun around the Middle Loup River. Stay nearby - you will find there's range of Nebraska campgrounds and Nebraska RV camping resorts just around the corner. For the sweeping view of the forest with an insider's consider the park's fire detection methods, guests may climb a stairway for the observation deck at Scott Lookout Towers. At the top of the towers, they could also spot forest dwellers like prairie chickens, antelopes and porcupines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Indian Cave State Park is found Shubert in Nebraska's far southeastern Missouri River Valley. &quot;All-natural&quot; is the foremost way to describe Indian Cave, which has been named for any mystifying sandstone cavern containing prehistoric images etched by ancient inhabitants. Hikers, backpackers and horseback riders discover a nice selection of trails, in addition to plenty of fishing action around the mighty Missouri. Riverbank anglers catch bullheads, bass and the occasional sturgeon. Dramatic color changes make Indian Cave territory glow in autumn and snow-seeking winter guests find a recreational bonanza - wide open spaces for merry sledding and cross-country skiing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aXNpdG5lYnJhc2thLmdvdi9jb21wb25lbnQvbXlwbGFubmVyL2RldGFpbC80My8yMDAwMDEz" target="_blank"&gt;;National Monument Nebraska&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aXNpdG5lYnJhc2thLmdvdi9jb21wb25lbnQvbXlwbGFubmVyL2RldGFpbC80My8yMDAwMDEz" target="_blank"&gt;;Road Trip Nebraska&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>