<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="2d3cdc91d4825431c83d510881ba6dd6">			WP Text Pro is often a text messaging platform based inside of of wordpress that easily enables you to ship broadcast texts!&lt;br /&gt;;You could mail out text messages towards your clients for as tiny as one cent a message!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/josephtanmarketing/blog/blogid=7944790" target="_blank"&gt;;WP Text Pro - Text Messaging Software&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get telephone quantities in U.S., Canada &amp; The U.K. in local area codes. $1 per month per cellular phone number. Unlimited telephone amounts. Perfect for local businesses to ship out text messages from a local cell phone number!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inbound and outbound sms start as low as 1 cent each in the United States and North america. In the United Kindgom, they are 4 cents a communication. Currently our platform works with U.S., Canada &amp; U.K.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When your key phrases are connected with telephone figures, regardless of the keyword and key phrase you ought to use for the marketing campaign(s) -- it's open to you at no additional charge!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Risk nothing with our Thirty day no questions asked money back refund. For any reason if you aren't happy, let us know and we will refund your money.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can get started for as very little as a one time fee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WP Text Pro can be a text messaging platform based within of wordpress that simply allows you to deliver broadcast texts!&lt;br /&gt;;It is possible to deliver out text messages for your customers for as very little as 1 cent a communication!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obtain telephone amounts in U.S., Canada &amp; The U.K. in local area codes. $1 per month per telephone number. Unlimited cellular phone numbers. Perfect for local businesses to mail out text messages from a local telephone number!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inbound and outbound texting begin as little as a cent each in the usa and North america. Inside the United Kindgom, they are 4 cents a communication. Currently our system works with U.S., Canada &amp; U.K.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When your keywords are associated with mobile phone amounts, no matter what key word you want to use for your personal promotion(s) -- it's open to you at simply no extra cost!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Risk nothing with our One month no questions asked cash back guarantee. For any reason if you aren't happy, let us know and we are going to repay your money.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You'll be able to get started for as minimal as a one time fee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WP Text Pro is really a text messaging platform dependent within of wordpress that simply means that you can deliver broadcast texts!&lt;br /&gt;;You'll be able to mail out text messages on your consumers for as minor as 1 cent a message!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get phone numbers in U.S., Canada &amp; The U.K. in local area codes. $1 per month per mobile phone number. Unlimited telephone quantities. Perfect for local businesses to deliver out text messages from a local cellphone number!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inward bound and outgoing sms begin as little as one cent each in the United States and North america. In the United Kindgom, they're Four cents a concept. Currently our system works with U.S., Canada &amp; U.K.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since your keyword phrases are associated with mobile phone figures, whichever keyword you should use for your campaign(s) -- it's open to you at no more fee!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Risk nothing with our Thirty day no hassle money backrefund.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8ee8cd6d336415d91d30ed3cf55bdab1">			WP Text Pro is often a text messaging system primarily based within of wordpress that conveniently permits you to ship broadcast texts!&lt;br /&gt;;You'll be able to send out text messages towards your shoppers for as tiny as one cent a communication!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dvcmRvbmhvbGxvdzkyMjA1NTUuYmxvZy5oci8yMDEyLzAzLzE2MzA0NTQ4NTYvd3B0ZXh0cHJvLXJldmlldy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;WP Text Pro - Text Messaging Software&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Buy cellular phone quantities in U.S., Canada &amp; The U.K. in local area codes. $1 per month per cell phone number. Unlimited cell phone quantities. Perfect for local businesses to ship out text messages from a local telephone number!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Incoming and outgoing text messages begin as low as 1 cent each in the usa and North america. Within the United Kindgom, they are 4 cents a communication. Currently our system works with U.S., Canada &amp; U.K.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Because your keyword phrases are connected with mobile phone amounts, whichever search phrase you ought to use for the marketing campaign(s) -- it's on hand at zero additional fee!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Risk nothing with our 30 day no hassle cash back guarantee. Unconditionally if you're not satisfied, inform us and we shall give you back your money.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can get started for as very little as a one time fee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WP Text Pro is usually a text messaging platform based inside of wordpress that very easily means that you can ship broadcast texts!&lt;br /&gt;;You can send out text messages to the buyers for as little as 1 cent a communication!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obtain telephone figures in U.S., Canada &amp; The U.K. in local area codes. $1 per month per telephone number. Unlimited cellular phone quantities. Perfect for local businesses to ship out text messages from a local cell phone number!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inward bound and outgoing sms start out as low as 1 cent each in the usa and North america. Inside the United Kindgom, they're Four cents a concept. Currently our platform works with U.S., Canada &amp; U.K.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since your keyword phrases are connected with phone amounts, regardless of the keyword and key phrase you need to use for your personal promotion(s) -- it's accessible to you at simply no additional charge!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Risk nothing with our One month no questions asked money-back guarantee. For any reason if you're not joyful, let us know and we can give back your money.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can get started for as minimal as a one time fee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WP Text Pro can be a text messaging platform primarily based within of wordpress that effortlessly lets you ship broadcast texts!&lt;br /&gt;;You could deliver out text messages for your buyers for as minimal as one cent a message!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Acquire phone numbers in U.S., Canada &amp; The U.K. in local area codes. $1 per month per mobile phone number. Unlimited cell phone quantities. Perfect for local businesses to send out text messages from a local phone number!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inbound and outbound text messages start out as little as one cent each in the United States and North america. Inside the United Kindgom, they're 4 cents a communication. Currently our platform works with U.S., Canada &amp; U.K.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When your keywords and phrases are associated with telephone amounts, no matter what keyword you would want to use for the strategy(s) -- it's available to you at no more cost!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Risk nothing with our 30 day with no hassle refund policy.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>