<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="cf521d124535d8ab515fd373399dc0b">			The Mercedes Benz SL-Class handles sleek and fine! Smooth ride, upgraded interior and exterior attributes and all round fun make this a classic for auto enthusiasts today. Let's see why!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SL-Class Models&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Taking a glance in the SL models, the Mercedes Benz SL boasts a two turbo compressor, a V12 front engine with 5,980 cc six liters, overhead cam and three valves per cylinder. Reported fuel financial system employing premium unleaded fuel 91 is EPA highway 19 miles per gallon and EPA city 13 miles per gallon having a multi-point injection fuel technique plus a 21.1-gallon tank, powered by a 450 kW, 604 horsepower SAE torque at four,800 rpm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Security and braking attributes incorporate four-wheel anti-lock and brake help systems, corning management for brakes, four disc brakes / airy discs, electronic traction and brake distribution systems, tire kit and immobilyzer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Outdoors measures a length of 178.5 inches, 71.five inches in width, 51 ins in height having a wheelbase measuring one hundred.eight ins plus a front and back track measuring 61.8 ins and 61.one ins respectively, plus curb turning at 36.two feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215YW5pbWVsaXN0Lm5ldC9ibG9nLnBocD9laWQ9MzIyNjU3" target="_blank"&gt;Mercedes-Benz GL-Class - How is the car after being used &lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although inside measurements are 37.seven ins front headroom, 53.9 inches front hip space, 42.9 ins front leg room, 54 ins front shoulder space and and interior volume of 57.8 cubic feet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoyable attributes for all passengers and driver incorporate a Bose audio system with anti-lift theft protection and code, satellite and CD player, 11.two cubic feet of seating room, a cellular phone, onboard pc for speed and fuel functions and much more.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To look at digital full color images and read extra info regarding the Mercedes Benz automotive line - and especially additional about within the Mercedes Benz SL model - race more than to the web and surf all-around. Study automotive evaluations, check out automobile specs, print out vehicle posts and download full colour auto photographs. Grab your calculator or use the one on your PC to examine the different priced packages, checking credentials of the various contenders. In quick, find out more by simply typing inside the models of the Mercedes Benz you would like to verify out in search engines like google.		</conversation>		<conversation id="126afd330cbcca729a18570504f5aae5">			There are few of items that can equal the fantastic feeling which comes when we drive along slick drop prime with roof down on a normal summer time day. R170 platform of SLK compressor initially came in 1997 for the model year 1998 and competed with BMW Z3. It used to be a class apart with its folding hardtop. It is extra weight though marred its overall performance of 193 hp two.3 L charged I4 engine and automated transmission. The SLK featured in Auto and Drivers 10 finest list for quite a while in 1997. All of the SLK's were not create in Bremen, Germany, the SLK 320 were build in South Africa and Mexico.Mercedes Benz SLK 230 were returned 1998 using a convertible hardtop. It was the first modern automobile which combined the structural adjustments to encompass the weather resistance gains which comes with a hardtop in addition to a wow issue of pretty two seats convertible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bHRpbWF0ZWFydGljbGVkaXJlY3RvcnkuY29tL2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWFydGljbGUmYW1wO2FydGljbGVfaWQ9NzA5Mjk1" target="_blank"&gt;Is it worth to buy a used Mercedes-Benz M-Class?&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Initially these SLK230s have been powered using the supercharged 2.three liter, 4 cylinder engine which gave 185 horsepower output. It was proficient at good performance, the engine sounded harsh and rough, if we compared it with all the engines obtainable in the SLKs critical contenders like Porsche Boxster. Even though the German name would make a rough engine like Kompressor worthwhile even using the seems which are genuinely cool. Mercedes expanded the SLK line up to add the SLK320 which was driven by three.2 liter V6 engine which had been taken straight from your C class. This six cylinder engine was much more refined for any car or truck which had the 3 pointer start. The sports character was totally justified in 2002, when the SLK32 AMG joined the fray, with its V6 engine and production of 349 brake horse power. The six cylinder engine was additional smooth and impressive and it was also not as well harsh on gas financial system. Dependent on the model, fuel ingestion for SLK320 is rated at between 12.0 nod 13.0 L/100 Kms in the city and between eight L/100 kms on highway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This 4 cylinder SLK230 has very good benefit only in city driving exactly where it gives 11l/100 kames. Highway data is at 8L/100 kms. If your definitely a devotee of AMG tuned vehicles, you ought not to retain fuel economic system factor in thoughts. SLK32 AMG is rated at 12.5L/100 kms within the city and 9.5L/100 kms on the highway. SLK's basic mechanical parts, engines and transmissions operate properly as reported by Customer Incidents, however the magazine also informs us of a couple of troubles about electrical component for some earlier models. 1999 model received the CR's recommended points, for other models of 1997, 2000 or 2003 there weren't an conclusive incidents we there as there was no adequate data there. SLK was once again revised to an even better extend in 2004 with enhanced overall performance in thoughts. The new Platform R171 was one of the greatest autos on the year. The SLK's are currently currently being built in Bremen, Germany and Mexico city. Regular repairs and parts could price higher for this kind of cars which can be a pricey affair so you ought to thoroughly investigation on this element when comparing the data with what other contenders have to give you before you decide on shopping for. SLK was topic of recall for some headlamp aiming process matter. The luxury worth of SLK's trick roof have kept the resale worth significantly increased. A 1998 SLK230 is still really worth $20,000 more than third of its true price tag. In comparison E320 sedan is just really worth $16000 regardless of its original price staying $10000 more than the SLK.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>