<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a659eefae7e94adc8a5fb202f05738bc">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgtrenz.com%2Fbig-12-football-championship-game%2F158%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://gtrenz.com/big-12-football-championship-game/158/&lt;/a&gt;; , A notable 33-0 Holiday Bowl conquer Arizona put an exclamation mark on a very good season for the Nebraska Cornhuskers, yet head coach Bo Pelini, who is now 20-8 during his first two seasons practical, isn't satisfied. Anything short of an important 12 title and an important BCS bowl game would certainly be a disappointing season, especially considering that the Huskers could have easily achieved both of people goals last season. Overlook the controversy in last year's Giant 12 championship game around the officials putting one second back at the clock for Texas that will kick the game-winning subject goal. Had Nebraska not booted the eliminate out of bounds to provide Texas such great particular field position, the Huskers were sitting pretty to pull off the upset. That heartbreaking defeat motivated the Huskers to teach hard for their run game, and it helps keep them motivated throughout any 2010 season. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Offense:  What's amazing is that Nebraska surely could win so many games just last year despite having among the list of worst offenses in your Big 12. The Huskers ranked at the side of last in the league (99th nationally) as a whole offense, only averaging 322. 8 yards per game. The Huskers also ranked close bottom of the Giant 12 in scoring offense (No. 8), averaging only just 25. 1 points for every game. While Pelini wants far more production from the running game, Nebraska's run offense was solid last year. Roy Helu Jr. did many of the damage, racking up 1, 147 lawns and 10 scores. Whereby Nebraska really struggled seemed to be its passing game. Quarterbacks Zac Lee and even Cody Green were both inconsistent given that the Huskers ranked No. 11 with the Big 12 (101st nationally) through passing offense. Lee is expected to acquire the first crack as nice. He doesn't have that should be great, but he should also be good enough to keep your opposition honest when that stacks the box to eliminate the power running game. Should the Huskers do take to your air, they'll be looking to get the ball in the particular hands of playmaker Niles Paul. Paul caught 40 passes for 796 yards plus four scores last months. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Defense:  There was zero better defense in FBS college football with regards to scoring in 2009. The Huskers led place by only allowing 10. 4 factors per game. Chew on this subject for a moment. One team scored more as opposed to 20 points on Nebraska virtually all season. While the Huskers will probably miss Ndamukong Suh, there is enough creativity remaining to boast the nation's best defenses again in fact. Now, the spotlight will owned by 1st-team All-Big 12 resistive tackle Jared Crick. The guy that lined up next to Suh tallied 73 discusses and 9. 5 totes in his sophomore months. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgtrenz.com%2Fbig-12-football-championship-game%2F158%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://gtrenz.com/big-12-football-championship-game/158/&lt;/a&gt;; , With organizations like Texas, Oklahoma, Oklahoma State and Texas Tech - it appears like the south is the place to stay college football this yr. Robinson makes for a highly trained leader and together the Cowboys use a fighting chance of winning it or no less than making it to a finals. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgtrenz.com%2Fbig-12-football-championship-game%2F158%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://gtrenz.com/big-12-football-championship-game/158/&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="56937bd6b52617823df29ff0ce5ba61c">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgtrenz.com%2Fbig-12-football-championship-game%2F158%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://gtrenz.com/big-12-football-championship-game/158/&lt;/a&gt;; , A striking 33-0 Holiday Bowl win over Arizona put an exclamation mark on a good season for the Nebraska Cornhuskers, and yet head coach Bo Pelini, who is now 20-8 on his first two seasons face to face, isn't satisfied. 5 sacks in his sophomore year or so. Crick isn't quite like athletic as Suh, but he is as powerful and has excellent technique. Plus, his continuous motor doesn't stop. Fellow 1st-team All-Big 12 pick out Prince Amukamara is another player to observe. He recorded five interceptions the season ago. This is a deep, disciplined defense happy to terrorize the Big 12 yet again. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prediction - 1st Huge 12 North - Pelini possesses a championship-caliber defense, and the offense ought to be better than it was a year ago. With this in imagination, there's no reason to reflect the Huskers won't experience the in the Big 12 name game this December. Find out how I have the rest of the league stacking up into my 2010 Huge 12 football predictions. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Were yet to see various powerful teams from Large 12 North because so far it feels like forever since the teams of this South have dominated this Big 12. There is not a hope of that switching anytime soon however considering that the gap in the potential in the two division is just increasing if anything. So just as all the recent yrs, the great teams to the Big 12 are all section of Big 12 South. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgtrenz.com%2Fbig-12-football-championship-game%2F158%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://gtrenz.com/big-12-football-championship-game/158/&lt;/a&gt;; , With leagues like Texas, Oklahoma, Oklahoma State and Texas Tech - it looks like the south is the place to be in college football this year or so. It is definitely the most beneficial division there is immediately. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That also means the fact that the winner of the South title is likely to win the Big 12 championship title definitely. What happens in South is what we should actually have to notice, as usual. So let's consider the power packed south teams that had been placed on the top 3 list with the Big 12. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Texas Longhorns - They are amongst the favorite picks for several an expert and analyst this season. But some of individuals also place them a little bit behind their rival Oklahoma. However, there are still folks who believe that they still contain a better chance of receiving the Big 12 every one the others. Their quarterback Colt McCoy is pretty capable of matching Oklahoma's Mike Bradford. With McCoy appearing supported by his close friend and wideout Jordan Shipley, the 'Horns could have a good chance of winning now round. The entire Offensive make is back as well. Once coach Mack Brown finds an acceptable tailback to stabilize the particular ever turbulent backfield, the 'Horns will prove to be an unstoppable force for their current line up. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Oklahoma Sooners - Its Heisman winning quarterback Sam Bradford is making a return this season in addition to being quite certain that he is looking for payback. Robinson makes for a knowledgeable leader and together the Cowboys possess a fighting chance of winning it or as a minimum making it to any finals. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgtrenz.com%2Fbig-12-football-championship-game%2F158%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://gtrenz.com/big-12-football-championship-game/158/&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>