<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ac16894de9459f73a27bb4be7661dbf5">			I do not have kid and will like to have one or more in the future.I like kids they are the leaders of tomorrow and they need to be taking good care of.I have several interests, just to name a few, I enjoy running and biking on my local trail. I also like to travel, (I have been wanting to go all over U.S.A). I like to relax with a cup of coffee and listen to music. I also enjoy working on my house, I am currently finishing an addition, and front deck. I also enjoy taking my boat out on the lake for a little R&amp;R. What ever I am doing, there's usually music involved. I listen to all genres of music. I work as a business lady.I manage my late father business, He was a business man supplies Goods like Beans,cocoa. He have a small store. I am just starting the business this year. I go around to meet with his old clients to get payment from them and know when they need Goods. I enjoy the challenge of it. I have a silly side (especially around my parent while they were still alive). I never imagine living my life without them while they were still living, so my match would have to be willing to accept my kind of person. I enjoy making people smile/laugh and if i get on a roll, u'll probably be doubled over. I enjoy life's simple pleasures, the smell of fresh cut grass, playing in the warm rain, the couch and the intimate time with that someone special. I have a great ear for listening, a logical mind for friendly debates, and a serious side for life's important decisions.
&lt;br /&gt;;I am looking to share life's ups and downs, highs and lows, with someone that shares these ideas. However I am not looking for games, drama, Etc. If you aren't over your ex, or think you &quot;might&quot; have feelings for her, then I'm not your girl.I'm honest and respectful, and only ask the same.
&lt;br /&gt;;Thank-you for taking the time to read this profile and getting to know a little about me.
&lt;br /&gt;;If you think you can keep up with me.......
&lt;br /&gt;;Let me know and you can drop me you num. Lol		</conversation>	</conversations></author>