<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="bd9f5335ad2213d95369fe273afee0fa">			 Have you ever had these problems going on together with your iPod Then this method just may well make your iPod start working once again!&lt;br /&gt;;Actions&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Change your iPod on. Make certain the battery is billed up adequate to turn it on.&lt;br /&gt;; 2. The unhappy iPod or sad folder should &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2lhbGtpbmdzamVyc2V5c3Nob3AuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.officialkingsjerseysshop.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.officialkingsjerseysshop.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; pop up on the screen.&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Put your ear up towards the iPod and you will hear the clicking sound inside (it seems like a auto trying to begin up, when it takes a few tries turning the keys)&lt;br /&gt;; 4. While the iPod is nonetheless producing these seems, just take the iPod in a single hand, open up the palm of one's other hand, and smack the slim side in the iPod in opposition to the palm of the other hand. [WARNING: This strategy is verified to perform as an effortless method to repair iPod tough push misalignment, but it could outcome in future hardware problems. This really is only a Short-term remedy to repairing an iPod, along with the issue might occur back again (activities differ). Other strategies of reviving a dead iPod are obtainable beneath and could be much safer]&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Continue smacking it on its aspect for no less than 6 occasions, while the iPod is trying to turn on. The crucial is usually to loosen the difficult drive.&lt;br /&gt;; 6. Following this can be must resume normal perform. If it does not, study below.&lt;br /&gt;; 7. You will find several approaches around which have all effectively fixed iPods, so don't give up hope but.&lt;br /&gt;; 8. If, even so, you're a a lot more hands-on sort of individual and do not want to trouble trying iPod help via your computer, skip for the bottom of the steps web page for information on how to open and fix internally.&lt;br /&gt;; 9. The first reccomended actions are from Apple's assistance website.&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Try to wait 30 minutes whilst iPod is charging.&lt;br /&gt;; 2. Attempt an additional FireWire or USB by means of Dock Connector cable.&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Try one more FireWire or USB port on your laptop or computer .&lt;br /&gt;; 4. Try to disconnect all gadgets from your computer's FireWire and USB ports.&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Try to download and install the latest edition of iPod software package and iTunes. apple/ipod/download/&lt;br /&gt;; 6. Try these five steps (recognized because the 5 Rs) and it might conquer most iPod problems. apple/support/ipod/five_rs/&lt;br /&gt;; 7. Try to put the iPod into Disk Mode if it fails to seem around the desktop. docs.apple/article.htmlartnum=93651&lt;br /&gt;; 10. If none from the above has worked for you, then you should try the subsequent:&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Try and connect your iPod with an additional laptop or computer using the iPod updater pre-installed.&lt;br /&gt;; 2. Still can't see your iPod, put it in Disk Mode and hook up having a laptop or computer, as opposed to undertaking a Restore on iPod Updater. Go and format the iPod instead.&lt;br /&gt;; 1. For Mac laptop or computer:&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Open the disk utility, hope your iPod appears there (still left hand side), highlight it&lt;br /&gt;; 2. Go to Tab &quot;Partition&quot;, click either &quot;Delete&quot; or &quot;Partition&quot;, if fails, skip this stage and visit 3&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Go to Tab &quot;Erase&quot; , pick Quantity Format as &quot;MAC OS Extended (Journaled), and just click Erase, again if fails, skip it and visit 4&lt;br /&gt;; 4. Same as step 3, but open the &quot;Security Options....&quot; and decide on &quot;Zero Out Data&quot; prior to click Erase. It is going to consider 1 to 2 hrs to full.&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Eject your iPod and do a Reset&lt;br /&gt;; 6. Open up the iPod Updater and simply click &quot;Restore&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; 2. For Windows computer:&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Go to folder &quot;My Computer&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; 2. Hope you'll be able to see &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2lhbGtpbmdzamVyc2V5c3Nob3AuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.officialkingsjerseysshop.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.officialkingsjerseysshop.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; your iPod there and proper simply click on the iPod&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Decide on &quot;Format&quot;. Make sure the options are at &quot;Default&quot; and that &quot;Quick Format&quot; isn't examined&lt;br /&gt;; 4. Now pick &quot;Format&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Eject your iPod and do a Reset&lt;br /&gt;; 6. Open the iPod Updater and simply click &quot;Restore&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; 7. In case you do not manage to do a &quot;Format&quot; on a window laptop or computer, try and use some third celebration disk utility software, e.g.&quot;Partition Magic&quot;.&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Windows consumers having trouble with their iPods should locate a Mac consumer. In many circumstances when an iPod won't show up on a Pc that it'll show up on the Mac. Then it may be restored. When the Pc user returns to his personal computer the iPod will probably be acknowledged through the Pc, reformatted to the Pc, and usable once again. By the way, it functions in reverse too. A Mac user often could get his iPod back again by connecting it into a Pc and restoring it. Notice:* It will not make any difference no matter whether the format is completed or not, the important is usually to erase (or partly) the corrupted firmware information around the Hard Drive from the iPod. Immediately after that, when the iPod re-connected using a computer, it's going to be acknowledged as an refreshing exterior difficult generate, it'll show up on the iPod updater.* It's not a difficult issue to get a Mac user to locate a window base pc, for any Pc user, whenever they can't discover any Mac consumer, they are able to go to a closest Apple Store for a favor.* You might have to switch about the Pc and Mac, try and do numerous attempts among &quot;Format&quot; and &quot;Restore&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; 11. iPod still doesn't operate Keep likely with these steps.&lt;br /&gt;; * Diagnostic mode resolution:&lt;br /&gt;; o For those who have tried difficulty shooting your iPod to no avail immediately after all of the steps above, probabilities are your iPod has a hardware dilemma. The iPod's built-in Diagnostic Mode is a fast and simple strategy to establish for those who have a &quot;bad&quot; iPod.&lt;br /&gt;; o You'll want to restart your iPod before putting it into Diagnostic Mode. Check that your maintain swap is off by sliding the swap absent in the headphone jack. Toggle it on and off to be secure.&lt;br /&gt;; o Press and maintain the following combination of buttons simultaneously for around 10 seconds to reset the iPod.&lt;br /&gt;; + iPod 1G to 3G: &quot;Menu&quot; and &quot;Play/Pause&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; + iPod 4G+ (contains Image, Nano, Online video, and Mini): &quot;Menu&quot; and &quot;Select&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; o The Apple logo will appear and you need to really feel the difficult generate spinning up. Press and maintain the following sequence of buttons:&lt;br /&gt;; + iPod 1G to 3G: &quot;REW&quot;, &quot;FFW&quot; and &quot;Select&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; + iPod 4G+ (consists of Picture, Nano, Online video, and Mini): &quot;Back&quot; and &quot;Select&quot;&lt;br /&gt;; o You'll listen to an audible chirp audio (3G models and greater) as well as the Apple brand ought to seem backwards. You're now in Diagnostic Mode. Navigate the checklist of exams employing &quot;REW&quot; and &quot;FFW&quot;. The scroll wheel will not perform whilst in diagnostic mode. For additional particulars on Diagnostic mode might be identified at methodshop/mp3/ipodsupport/diagnosticmode/&lt;br /&gt;; o Make an effort to do the 5in1, HDD R/W and HDD scan checks. Some profitable situations have been noted right after the operating the handful of exams under the Diagnostic mode. In situation it will not perform inside your case, and the scan checks reviews display some mistakes then it proves your iPod has a hardware difficulty and it requirements a repairing services.&lt;br /&gt;; * Format your iPod having a start off disk:&lt;br /&gt;; o I have not tried this remedy myself, I noticed that there had been couple of profitable instances that the consumers managed to obtain their iPod (you have to place your iPod in disk mode just before connecting having a personal computer) mounted through the personal computer, which was booted by a program startup disk. For Mac, you are able to use the Disk Utility (around the Tiger OS system disk), for Pc consumer, you can utilize the window OS system disk. Make an effort to uncover a approach to reformat your iPod, once more it doesn't make any difference which format (FAT32, NTFS or HFS+) you select, the key is usually to erase the corrupted system files on the iPod. Then eject your iPod and do a Reset to switch out from Disk Mode. Reboot your personal computer in the normal way, connect your iPod back with it, open up the iPod updater, and hopefully your iPod will seem there for the Restore.&lt;br /&gt;; 12. The subsequent tutorial will train you how you can open up your iPod and attempt to repair it. This need to almost certainly be accomplished as being a final resort, for opening your iPod will probably void your warranty. Furthermore, if executed wrong, your iPod could maintain permanant harm although your problem could have ben effortlessly aided by other processes.&lt;br /&gt;; * The best tutorial I have go through on how to open up an iPod is right here: forums.ipodlounge/showthread.phps=&amp;threadid=93789/&lt;br /&gt;; 13. That tutorial is how to open a 3rd/4th Generation iPod, despite the fact that most are similarly accomplished. Google it if you are not satisfied and want much more detail; you can find a great deal of great sites on the market.&lt;br /&gt;; * The moment inside, you can find several strategies you can use which have all been used to repair iPod difficulties. Make sure the hold change is on! You do not wish to hit a button and mess something up! The techniques will probably be listed in order of how productive I believe they may be.&lt;br /&gt;; 14. Disconnecting the Challenging Generate and Booting Technique.&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Now that your iPod is open up, you must see your tough drive lying flat on best. The ribbon cable attached for the difficult generate is detachable, so do not be scared.&lt;br /&gt;; 2. Gently pull the difficult generate absent in the cable in which it really is linked, although holding the cable lightly in hand. You don't need to rip it out the motherboard.&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Your hard generate ought to simply break free. Now that it really is out, it is possible to perform with it, look around, but the point would be to give it a little rest.&lt;br /&gt;; 4. Next, now the tough generate is out, carefully flip your iPod over so you are looking in the display. Be careful not to rip the ribbon cable by the maintain swap.&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Get the iPod off of hold purpose, thus enabling the buttons once again.&lt;br /&gt;; 6. Change the iPod on. You might recieve an error message, and you could have the ability to access menus.&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Should you get an error message, try restarting the iPod.&lt;br /&gt;; 7. Now change the iPod off.&lt;br /&gt;; 8. Reactivate the maintain change. Your experiment is full.&lt;br /&gt;; 9. Reconnect the challenging generate as located prior to, and carefully replace the back cover. Hope it works.&lt;br /&gt;; 15. Business Card Technique.&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Now that your iPod is open up, you must see your difficult drive lying flat on top.&lt;br /&gt;; 2. Get a standard business card and fold it in half.&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Place the folded business card on top rated of the difficult generate. (The idea is that your iPod's hard push is too loose and the folded business card will put pressure on it when enclosed for a productive spin and no just click. This functions frequently). Do not fold it a lot more than the moment unless you have a reason, because far more pressure on the tough generate may preserve it from spinning, causing even far more issues.&lt;br /&gt;; 4. Carefully area the lid again on the iPod, making confident the card is in place correctly.&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Close up your iPod and hope it functions.&lt;br /&gt;; 16. Time to Spend Some $$ Approach.&lt;br /&gt;; 1. Get a job.&lt;br /&gt;; 2. You most likely have a hardware difficulty (like me), and you probably require a new hard generate. Google it. eBay it. A typical replacement difficult push isn't as considerably as a new iPod, but you may need to shell out a couple bucks in the event you want it fixed.&lt;br /&gt;; 3. Look at it as an opportunity to upgrade. Maybe look into buying a bigger difficult generate to maintain more useless shit. It will nonetheless cost lower than a new iPod.&lt;br /&gt;; 4. Examine above for info on how to replace your hard generate. It really is not tough.&lt;br /&gt;; 5. Pray it's a hard drive problem after you bought a single and cannot return it.&lt;br /&gt;; 17. If you've read this significantly, you've attempted everything, and your iPod nevertheless isn't fixed, then ask someone else already. You've been up all night reading this tutorial and trying my methods and you happen to be most likely sick of this anyway. Or just steal your friend's iPod.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tips&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Ensure the iPod has enough battery power to show on.&lt;br /&gt;; * An option is open up your iPod (which voids the guarantee) and squeeze the push and it's enclosing padding. There is apparently some grounding that can occur loose and this may fix things up once more. This worked for me and a friend and if you are extremely careful once you open the situation, it's significantly less violent than smacking it about.&lt;br /&gt;; * You'll be able to also visit an Apple retailer and ask to replace the battery! These are happy to support you!&lt;br /&gt;; * Don't steal your friend's iPod.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Warnings&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;* Before trying these techniques, contact Apple and see if you could get your iPod replaced for free.&lt;br /&gt;; * This strategy need to only be as a last resort. If Apple's suggestions don't perform, first try running a chkdsk function in your iPod.&lt;br /&gt;; * Don't break the difficult drive!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>