<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="9059ae35d1e53ba3d066c98fd943e652">			Can good hair care really prevent women's hair loss? This is not a question that can be answered with certainty. For some women, this will not be enough. If you are genetically disposed to lose your hair, good hair care won't do a whole lot to keep it from happening. What it can do is make sure that the hair you have left is healthy and well maintained. Taking the best possible care of your scalp and hair will, in many instances, help to prevent hair loss in women. Losing your hair is an unpleasant and even frightening possibility for most women. We will now look at some of the most effective ways to keep your hair as healthy as possible.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's so important to keep the right amount of moisture in your hair. Your hair can become brittle if there's not enough moisture present. You can do that with water intake and using a reputable hair conditioner. But, you should use an herbal rinse if your hair is oily, and then do not use the conditioner. You'll only weigh your hair down if you use the conditioner on your oily hair. You will weaken your hair follicles with chronic excess weight on your hair and scalp. Ask your stylist about that for more information. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dyeing the hair is something that every woman experiments with at least once in her life. Some women become quite addicted to dyeing their own hair. So... we understand, and if you do this practice, then do not begin the process at your roots. Do your roots in the last 10 to 15 minutes of the process. If you put dye on them too soon the dye can seep into the follicle and cause it to become inflamed or even infected. Then, what you may accidentally do is begin the whole process of hair loss in yourself. You can do it safely, but if you want to be sure - just see a professional colorist. You'll pay more, but you can rest assured it will be done right.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If perhaps you discover the material here well written and instructive, you might also enjoy others published by the article author.  As a freelance writer, the subjects covered are actually amazingly broad. For instance, anyone can click here to see what he authored about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhaXJzYWxvbnR1Y3Nvbi5jb20vdHVjc29uLWhhaXItc2Fsb25zLW1lbnMtc2Fsb25zLWZvci1zaG9ydC1hbmQtc3R5bGlzaC1oYWlyLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;regis hair salon around Tucson&lt;/a&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This should not need to be said, yet we will - combing your hair every day is extremely important. If you need a brush, then of course you brush your hair each and every day. If you do not comb your hair every day it will get matted and your scalp could get clogged with too much oil. Believe it or not, but dreadlocks are not the healthiest practice to use because they can cause this to happen. There are lots of reasons to practice proper hair care, even if you are not trying to prevent women's hair loss. The simple truth is that good hair care leads to healthy hair and a healthy scalp. You are in a better position to retain your hair when your scalp is healthy. So make sure that you take the time to properly care for your scalp and hair each day. It isn't that hard. You can accomplish everything we've discussed here without much effort.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>