<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b8a423c5e386d541e51dcb8b3f9a6c69">			If you want to go to a Halloween party or at least try to get some free candy, then you need a costume. Complain all you want, but there’s nothing lamer than showing up to a Halloween party without one. And don’t even try any of “I’m going as myself” crap. Even if you’re totally wild for Halloween, sometimes coming up with a cool, original costume can be a challenge. So, we have put together a set of guidelines to help inspire some ideas and narrow down your choices.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Firstly, plan ahead. The absolute worst place to find yourself in, short of having no costume at all, is running around last minute trying to figure out what you want to be. By then, not only have all the good ideas been taken, but even if you do come up with something, you’re going to have a hard time getting everything together. Halloween stores sell out of stuff quickly, so make sure you’re stocked up at least four or five days in advance. You really don’t want to be standing in the clearance aisle of the drugstore looking through a bin of ill-fitting costumes in open plastic bags. Also, do yourself a favor and have a dress rehearsal. Make sure your costume fits, and that all the different pieces work where they’re supposed to work. For you and your costume, the two scariest words of Halloween are “wardrobe malfunction.”
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Secondly, don’t be afraid to dress subdued. No one says you have to go balls-to-the-wall elaborate for Halloween. Sometimes a cool mask or some creative face paint combined with some formal wear more than gets the job done. It can be a good way to stand out when everyone else looks over-the-top crazy. Best of all, costumes like these are totally flexible and can have countless variations. In fact, a nice suit alone could work perfectly if you’re the type of person who’d never be caught dead in one. Defy expectations by doing something unexpected — that’s what Halloween is all about.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Thirdly, don’t get too conceptual. Sure, everyone will be talking about each others’ costumes on Halloween, but that doesn’t mean you want to be stuck all night explaining what you’re supposed to be. An abstract costume, or one that’s merely undercooked, can lead to a truly frustrating evening. So, unless you know for a fact that you can pull it off, you might not want to go as the SATs or your favorite flavor of Doritos.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly, be timely. It’s something hard to judge, but if you’re going to go as a real person you have to keep it current. There’s no strict set of rules for this, and no time constraints, but chances are if no one in your office or none of your friends are talking about it, then it’s not going to make a good costume. So, Steven Slater is totally out, though feel free to go as anyone whose reality show is currently airing new episodes on either MTV or the Discovery Channel, but definitely not Bravo or TLC. If you have an idea, but you aren’t quite sure how to pull it off, flip through some tabloids or run a Google image search. But again, make sure you’re looking at current pictures. You don’t want everyone to know how ill-informed you really are.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hope the tips are helpful, click here to get more information about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2h0dHA6Ly93d3cuZ29vZG9yaWVudC5jb20vQ29zcGFseV9Db3N0dW1lc19DNjg4" target="_blank"&gt;Halloween Costume&lt;/a&gt;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>