<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b236891565041e9068d0df8a6f122989">			So, for now, we're focusing on military and air invasion type games.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Army Driver&lt;/b&gt;; - Drive the jeep and shoot everyone that gets close. Using the WASD movement format to control the jeep, us W to move up A to move left S to move down and D to move right. To shoot press either the space bar or the left mouse button.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Castle Crasher&lt;/b&gt;; - Use a catapult to destroy enemy castles. Using the mouse to aim, simply hold the left mouse button to shoot, but be aware if you hold it too long the stone will be shot but will not make it very far. Hitting the castle will make soldiers appear and start coming at you, you can aim and kill these with the catapult as well. Be careful with aiming and destroying, because you only have so many stones for each level.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Call of Duty 2&lt;/b&gt;; - Try to kill as many enemies as possible, WWII style game play. Aiming with the mouse and firing by clicking the left mouse button this game has several other versions for both online and game systems. But in this version you want to make sure you look both ways and view the total screen or you will die. If you see a red blinking line on either side of the screen that means you are being hit from that side.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Bin Laden Blast&lt;/b&gt;; - This game is simple yet fun for any true American patriot. All you have to do is shoot Bin Laden as many times as possible before time runs out. Aim with the mouse and left click to shoot, when you need to reload simply left click the red reload sign. You only have a minuet to shoot, so start shooting now.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;D Day Normandy&lt;/b&gt;; - You are stationed at Omaha Beach during D Day, and the plan is to shoot them before they shoot you. The game has a WASD movement format (W is up A is left S is down and D is right) and to cycle through available weapons you press the space bar. Auto reload is active in this game so no pausing (with the p button) while you are firing with the left mouse button. If you need to talk to a soldier or, if you need to get on a truck you click with the left mouse button onto the selected target.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are all some of the more popular ones to download free games that you can access at least part of the game to check out before you would buy the full version. With almost anything that is free, you will either find that you have only one or two levels you can reach before you have to purchase the full version to access all levels of the military games, or there are advertisements that pop up everywhere. When a toolbar is in Floating Mode you can reposition it on the screen by moving your mouse pointer into the Title bar, holding your left mouse button down and dragging it to where you would like it to go.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you would like to quickly dock your floating toolbar back to where it was originally docked, just Double Click on the Toolbars Title bar.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb29sLWFuZC1xdWlldC5jby51ay9wY19jYXNlX2FjY2Vzc29yaWVzL25leHVzX3NpbGVudF9tb3VzZV9zbTg1MDBiX2JsYWNrX3dpcmVkX21vdXNlX1AxMTI3Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nexus Silent Mouse&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="eac9a15200259cfc2429b53127c4cfb2">			Just because you didn't collect tax from your customers doesn't mean you don't owe that money to the state or states.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do NOT ignore the nexus issue. This is the HUGE mistake that many business owners are making. Get clear on tax obligations, then create a strategy to minimize their effect. Otherwise you may be exposed to huge tax bills, and penalties that could easily drive you out of business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Business owners in Rhode Island found this out the hard way. In the spring of 2009, the state sent notices to 1,200 business owners about outstanding, unpaid sales taxes. In most of those cases, &quot;notice&quot; meant state tax officials showing up at the business and locking the doors, forcing business owners to close down until the taxes were paid, or those owners could prove that the state's records were wrong.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As confusing as it is to potentially have 50 different definitions of what it means to have nexus in a state, there are actually three different types of nexus situations (sales tax nexus, income tax nexus and 'not income tax' nexus) potentially for each state. So, it's not 50 different definitions: it could actually be as high as 150 definitions. (Plus, of course all the other cities, counties and taxing units who all want a bite of what you've got.)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you have a nexus problem? Don't ignore it. It'll only get worse. Get an expert on your side and use them to clearly define what is nexus in your case and what you need to do about it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Among the best announcements in the recently concluded 2010 Mobile World Congress in Barcelona is the official debut of what is considered the Nexus One clone or the Nexus One with Sense UI among techies. This is the HTC Desire, also known as the HTC Bravo which is no doubt one of the most powerful smartphones on the planet.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is powered by the same powerful 1 GHz Qualcomm QSD8250 Snapdragon processor and runs the latest Android 2.1 ??clair OS using the popular HTC Sense UI. It is not surprising that a comparison between the OEM parent behind Google's Nexus One and its own Desire gets the limelight between would-be owners of either and potentially remorseful owners of the Nexus One.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Head to Head Comparison&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Specs-wise, the two are essentially twins. Apart from running the same OS powered by the same processors, they both have a stunning 3.7-inch Wide-VGA AMOLED capacitive touchscreens with multitouch input technologies with the same accelerometer, proximity and ambient light sensors. The HTC Legend and HTC HD Mini are also due at around the same time with confirmation to follow.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The SIM Free HTC desire is a network unlocked mobile phone, this allows the Desire to be used on either pay monthly or pay as you go SIM cards from any network carrier.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The price may look expensive but remember there are no network subsidies when buying SIM Free phones, they can be used on any network and are yours to keep.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is already talk from the networks as to who will be supporting the HTC Desire, these include confirmation from T-Mobile and Orange as well as Vodafone for releases around early to mid April.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbGl4eWEuY29tL2Jsb2cvNDE5MTc4MS9NaWNyb3NvZnQtRXhjZWwtV29ya2luZy1XaXRoLVRvb2xiYXJz" target="_blank"&gt;;Microsoft Excel - Working With Toolbars&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>