<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="6">		<conversation id="1bcd1261915a4028656df1a256d410a">			hhhhmmmmm.......bakit kaya ganun? all i want in my life is to make my family happy.....but the simpliest thing sometimes will be the most difficult to do.........i never wanted any matterial thing,,,,,,,all i need is love and happiness.....		</conversation>		<conversation id="a79dd11a2ac0de8f80edc4f2f680e4eb">			I want to meet Someone who is in love and can talk about all things under the sun with the SO.
&lt;br /&gt;;Someone who wakes up in the morning!!!!!!, gets out of the house immediately, and thank God for another splendid day.Someone who sees a person's real worth just like......ME.Someone who works at the U.S. National Library hehehehehehehhe....WHY NOT!!!!.Someone who has written a book (or journal) about his/her family's chronicles including his/her grandparents and uncles and aunts    oowwwwww!!!!yeah it maybe sounds stupid but its really catches me.Someone who wants to save up money together with me and go see the ends of the world,,,till my last breath.
&lt;br /&gt;;Someone who never gives up to become a better person...for others and for God.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Someone who makes a difference,,,,,, SOMEONE who can be a FRIEND TO ME		</conversation>		<conversation id="6e24925a305b32efc0791e5cc7d6bf1c">			All of us experience change in our lives. Change is the one constant in our lives. There are changes that we look forward too and change that we fear. However, one thing is for sure. Things will not stay the same no matter how much we would like them too. When a life change occurs, we have two choices in how to respond. We can despair that a change has come and assume that things will be worse, or we can look with excitement at the new possibilities that the change presents.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b977eb628c4b338b66933da8e75e5a5e">			People just look at me
&lt;br /&gt;;Look enough to stare
&lt;br /&gt;;not noticing the inside of me
&lt;br /&gt;;They just look at the clothes I wear
&lt;br /&gt;;They don’t know how I feel
&lt;br /&gt;;They think I’m always glad
&lt;br /&gt;;But there’s something they don’t no
&lt;br /&gt;;I’m the one who’s feeling sad
&lt;br /&gt;;They think I always win
&lt;br /&gt;;but really I always loose
&lt;br /&gt;;they think my life is so great
&lt;br /&gt;;but they couldn’t stay one day in my shoes
&lt;br /&gt;;You may think I’m strong
&lt;br /&gt;;You may think I’m tough
&lt;br /&gt;;but you have no idea my life is so rough
&lt;br /&gt;;every time I’m in my room
&lt;br /&gt;;you’ll see water go down my eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;you’ll ask me what’s wrong
&lt;br /&gt;;I’ll put on a fake discies
&lt;br /&gt;;people say that I am to good to get hurt
&lt;br /&gt;;but I’m just like everyone else
&lt;br /&gt;;I wish that could work
&lt;br /&gt;;everybody says I look to good
&lt;br /&gt;;and I’m just a tease
&lt;br /&gt;;but I cry my eyes out then put on a cheeze
&lt;br /&gt;;when love came into my life
&lt;br /&gt;;surprisingly that was something I feared
&lt;br /&gt;;I never thought I’d be feeling like this in all my 23 years
&lt;br /&gt;;yes I’ve been in love
&lt;br /&gt;;yes I got hurt
&lt;br /&gt;;you would of thought all she do is fight &amp; flirt
&lt;br /&gt;;but you are wrong about everything
&lt;br /&gt;;I was wrong at it to
&lt;br /&gt;;now I see love’s agony
&lt;br /&gt;;and what it can do
&lt;br /&gt;;that’s why I’m here
&lt;br /&gt;;to throw away this stress &amp; strife
&lt;br /&gt;;to start all over
&lt;br /&gt;;maybe a new life
&lt;br /&gt;;but people over here
&lt;br /&gt;;is the same as over there
&lt;br /&gt;;they just look at your appearance
&lt;br /&gt;;and the style of your hair
&lt;br /&gt;;never to look in the inside of me
&lt;br /&gt;;never to care
&lt;br /&gt;;I was brought into this world
&lt;br /&gt;;realizing life’s not fair
&lt;br /&gt;;so if you really think…….
&lt;br /&gt;;I look to good
&lt;br /&gt;;I dress to nice
&lt;br /&gt;;I never get hurt
&lt;br /&gt;;I’ll never stay by a guy side
&lt;br /&gt;;and the word love
&lt;br /&gt;;I can’t describe
&lt;br /&gt;;your wrong about that too
&lt;br /&gt;;I’m just like everyone else around me I’m just like you…….		</conversation>		<conversation id="b46e49794c91d09bdafba114b50e7cbf">			” I always thought that there was this one perfect person for everybody in the world, you know, and when you found that person the rest of the world kind of magically faded away, and, you know, the two of you would just be inside this kind of protective bubble, but there is no bubble, I mean if there is you have to make it, I just think life is more than a series of moments, you know, we can make choices, and we can choose to protect the people we love, and that’s what makes us who we are and those are the real memories “		</conversation>		<conversation id="74443f7f900aa0cc66742d8785a98b7f">			“I’m too young for great responsibilities.”- that’s what I thought.  I guess I’m acting very immature despite the fact that I’m a teacher. Yes. I’m a teacher.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I thought it would be too easy for me if I stopped teaching Koreans but I was very wrong! I was a big full of shit! I left issues unsolved but honestly I didn’t mean to do that. I was just careless! Wrong decisions really devastate me! It usually happens! I dont know why.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And so I venture into the real world of the so called  “educator”. This is it! Being a teacher really sucks!! I needed a year for adjustment ( I think ). It was a lot of work. I cant even look at myself in the mirror. I’ve got eating disorders. I cant force myself to smile. I’m always angry. Always busy! Always crying! Always afraid of everything!! Always pressured and all that. In short I’m not happy with what’s happening in my life! My life sucks!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I tried searching for stress relievers and stuffs but it didn’t worked out. I’ve got tired of my life! I always wish for a super typhoon so that classes would be canceled!  I wanted to give up and quit! That’s how my mind work now. I’ve realized how miserable I am. I was totally wrecked! I really am.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Happiness is what I’m after. I don’t know… Its just that I’m sad.. I’m tired and sick of everything here. I just hope one day I would find true happiness		</conversation>	</conversations></author>