<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="91bb94473e59a19609df7fc7131c0c73">			I think that for most of you reading this, a good quality combination HEPA and activated carbon air cleaner will work best.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whichever kind of air purifier you decide to buy, read as many reviews as possible. Try to find unbiased, high quality ones. This will help you to decide on the best air purifier for you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Ionic air purifier reviews&lt;/b&gt;; abound all over the internet, on manufacturers' sites, resellers' sites, enthusiasts' sites and of course, the ubiquitous spam. Ironically, even reviews need to be reviewed!&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reviews by manufacturers themselves are often just slick advertising. Years of tuning our minds off at the sight of TV commercials tend to put us on guard when assessing such presentations, be they in print or on air. Some manufacturers, perhaps more deep-pocketed, feature accolades by independent third party institutions. These would seem acceptable. Nevertheless, thoughts of behind-the-scenes financial incentives are hard to dispel for a movie-going generation so often bombarded with conspiracy screenplays.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reviews on manufacturers' or resellers' sites also often feature accounts by users who wax lyrical about the wonders they have experienced since they bought the ionic air purifier. These are personal and subjective experiences of individuals who have benefited in various ways. They sound genuine. Testimonials made by honest, ordinary people. No reason not to believe them. But are these reliable reviews? We all like to believe so since we enthusiastically lap them up, dreaming of how wonderful it will be when we enjoy the same benefits. All it takes is a click of the buy button or a trip to the nearest departmental store. Hold on, hold on. Doesn't it sound too perfect? Not a whimper of discontent. Cherry-picking comes to mind, that is, only positive feedback is featured.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another source of anecdotal (or experiential as opposed to empirical or scientific) reviews may be our well-meaning relatives, friends, and acquaintances. &quot;Have you tried Brand X Purifier? I'm using it and my morning allergic reactions have disappeared! Why don't you try it?&quot; Heard that one before? Or someone else says, &quot;Using Brand Y Purifier at home is just burning electricity for no good reason. I'm going to dump that useless piece of junk right now! Take my advice, don't ever waste any money on it.&quot; Such personal comments are often relied upon when decisions are made about whether to buy a purifier. They are offered with no personal gain and no malice.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Resellers of multiple brands of purifiers should logically make every effort to move the stocks that they have on hand. One would expect that their reviews are objectively done. That might be so in a brick and mortar business world. But these days, resellers need not carry any stock. All they need are beautifully crafted images from purifier manufacturers with whom they are affiliated. With drop shipping, there is no need to carry any inventory at all. The profit-driven reseller would naturally give heavier emphasis to the principal who rewards with the best margin. It is only sensible to take such reviews with a huge pinch of salt.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Ionic air purifier reviews&lt;/b&gt;; occasionally arrive in the form of a spam e-mail or an on-screen pop-up, pop-under or whatever. Even if they have different models of air purifiers, they still have to come up with the same lab results for a more reliable air purifier reviews.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FpcnB1cmlmaWVyc3Jldmlld3MubmV0L2RvLXlvdS1uZWVkLWFuLWFpci1wdXJpZmllcg__" target="_blank"&gt;;air purifiers reviews&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5f942c91dde86ad42d895e94f6895248">			developed to combat SARS and otehr airborne problems.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here are the top 5 beginning with the Best&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;#1: AliveAir Machine.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PROS: The only 9-stage air purifier&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Technologies: HEPA, UV, tio2, Pre-filter, Negative ion, Auto sensors (detects Pollen, Odor, Dust) Active carbon, Catalytic grid, &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Price: $350 &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Room Coverage: 800 Sq. ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Replacement HEPA Filters; About $30&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;What we liked best - includes the nanotech virus grids, and the 3 new pollen sensors in a 9-stage unit at an affordable price.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Buying Hint: Look for sales at their online warehouse (&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.aliveair.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.aliveair.com&lt;/a&gt;;)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;#2: IQAire&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PROS: 3-stage, including a good-sized HEPA&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Technologies: HEPA, pre-filter &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Price: $799 &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Room Coverage: 800 Sq. ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Replacement HEPA Filters; About $189&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;#3: Bluair&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PROS: 3-stage Air Purifier&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Technologies: HEPA, electrostatic &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Price: $529 &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Room Coverage: 385 Sq. ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Replacement HEPA Filters; About $119&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;#4 Austin Air&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PROS: 4-stage air purifier&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Technologies: HEPA, Zeolite, 2 pre-filters, carbon&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Price: $449 &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Room Coverage: 800 Sq. ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Replacement HEPA Filters; About $99&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;#5: PlasmaWave&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PROS: 4-stage&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Technologies: Washable pre-filter, true HEPA filter, and washable nano-silver mesh/carbon filter. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Price: $370&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Room Coverage: 280 Sq. ft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Replacement HEPA Filters; About $99&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many people find that having an air purifier in the home is essential. They might be someone in the home that has severe allergies or the air cleaner could take away pet smells or the smells from an old house. It is also common for some home owners to have air cleaners just for the sheer pleasure of knowing that their air quality is top notch. There are some comparable machines that are designed to clean the air you breathe.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;IQ Air health pro plus, is an expensive system to have. It is ideal for anyone with absolutely severe allergies. It uses a Hyper HEDA filter and it can clean a huge 900sq foot room. It also comes with a filter change alert system and a five year warranty.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Austin Air Health Mate is a model with lots of perks. It is easy to maintain which has many fans. It is packed with a HEDA/carbon filter pack that only has to be replaced ever 3-5 years, which is unlike other systems which have to be changed every few months. It claims to eliminate 95% of particles as little as 0.1 micron. The only drawback with it is that it is noisy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Honeywell Enviroacaire is a lower end air cleaner. It is able to only clean up to 390sq foot or less and it is pretty noisy. The plus is that it is fairly cheap so that it can appeal to someone who doesn`t want to spend lots of money. It also has a permanent style filter that just has to be vacuumed out twice a year, and it has an odour reducing carbon pre-filter that does have to be replaced from time to time. This system takes the air from its sides and shoots it out the top for superior air cleaning.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Allerair Airmedic is a system that is used in hospitals, offices and homes. It takes air from 360 degrees and is able to remove lots of things from the air, such as chemicals, particles, gases and odours.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Allen paralda is a system that has no pre-filter. Let them know your room size and what kind of substances you would like removed from your home.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FpcnB1cmlmaWVyc3Jldmlld3MubmV0L2RvLXlvdS1uZWVkLWFuLWFpci1wdXJpZmllcg__" target="_blank"&gt;;air purifiers reviews&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>