<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="789c9640a98347f6d745a0edf28915a1">			Does your core marketing message align with everything else you portray to the customer? Does it represent a beneficial value proposition to them?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Are the targeted clients and leads a proper fit? Does the sales process maximize the use of selling time instead of burdening down the sales professionals with outdated selling methods that trap them into low performance?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you continue to work on identifying and removing de-motivators, you may find that you get more than a few improvements in behavior and in performance from formerly &quot;;weak&quot;; team members.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Neuro-Linguistic Programming or NLP is better known to be an approach that goes hand in hand with psychotherapy and organizational change. NLP was co-founded by Richard Bandler and John Grinder. NLP is vital and very helpful in finding alternatives for people to have better lives. This notion has greatly influenced psychotherapists and hypnotherapists to undergo NLP training. NLP courses aim to teach a connection between language and a person's neurological processes hence the term Neuro-Linguistic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;NLP training Courses are available practically all throughout the world. It is now being offered to broaden people's perspective on how they can change, improve, or in other words &quot;;reprogram&quot;; behavior that is not acceptable or in worse cases damaging to the life of a person.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One important term that you will hear in the world of NLP is 'meta-program.' In NLP, the word 'program' is synonymous to 'strategy.' Meta-programs can be considered as the mind's preferences which results to a distinct personality or behavior. Meta-programs are also sometimes called mental filters because they manipulate the ideas that you have in your head which gives way to preferences in behavior and personality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some examples of meta-programs that are related to motivation are listed below.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Towards/Away. This signifies your motivation direction. Some people are motivated to move towards pleasure or positive results while others are motivated to move away from the source of problem. Either of the two motivation directions is okay but having a balance between the two is probably the best.&lt;br /&gt;;Internal/External Frame of Reference. This is all about where you get your direction. There are other types of meta-programs but this article only focused on motivational meta-programs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogabond.com%2FCommentView.aspx%3FCommentID%3D275684"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.blogabond.com/CommentView.aspx?CommentID=275684&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>