<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="9f674d647d0e6924a1f490e694c8548">			Investing in a smart phone deserves a smart case that protects your iPhone 4. Budget cases can be found that would fit your look and features for your phone. The most important function of a case is, naturally, to guard your phone against harm, but you can also choose one you like the appearance of. Here are just a few ideas to consider when shopping for iPhone 4 cases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Otterbox Defender seems to be the popular case for the iPhone 4, it comes with a built in screen protector as well as a holster. You can still use your phone when it’s in its case as there is a thin membrane that protects your touch screen. Did you know that you can charge and sync your phone when in its case? This case gives you a firm grip on your phone as well as the coating is resistant to finger prints. The Otterbox Defender is a solid protection for your iPhone 4, it sells with retailers for $50 but have seen it with online retailers for less. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Belkin Shield Eclipse is an unusual iPhone 4 cover in that it consists of two distinct parts. With having the upper part clear made from hard polycarbonate shell ,and the lower part colored this still allows the iPhone logo to show and have a secure soft touch grip. Getting a durable case to protect your phone is very important against daily living. Belkin strikes again with their approach to designing a high quality accessory with this phone case. The Shield Eclipse is available in several colors and sells for about $30.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is perhaps not the most common dinner table topic, but tablet back protectors does seem to crop up in many peoples lives at some point. Quite when or how you will reach this point I can’t say, but I do know [url=]Buy new iPad cases[/url] can be confusing to the best of us. Through my articles here it is my greatest hope that you learn about the topic, and enjoy it. So if you are ever asked about it you will be able to give a detailed reply on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2V2ZW50cy5oZW5vbGVxbGVuYmF0bHllczQ5OTIzLnBvZG9tYXRpYy5jb20vZW50cnkvMjAxMi0wNC0wMVQwMl81OV81OS0wN18wMA__" target="_blank"&gt;Buy new iPad cases&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Zagg company has a product line that is popular for its InvisibleShield. This military grade plastic is used for these skin cases, and they are scratch proof. Light as a feather and almost see through, as the name promises. Keeping all the features visible to everyone can be done with this iPhone 4 case. Keep in mind, however, that this is soft skin designed to protect the phone against scratches and smears, but not hard impact. Are you concerned about dropping your phone, then look for a harder case. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Because the iPhone 4 is a device that performs many functions, you should take good care of it. You'll know that your phone won't easily break or get scratched if you get a good quality case. You should also look for a case that suits your personal style. Consider one of the iPhone 4 cases discussed above when looking at cases.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;About the Blog Poster&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may be surprised to read some of the things I am going to tell you about tablet cases, after all they are not all common knowledge. It is though a topic which I have had a great deal of interest in for many years now, and so I really want to share my interest with you. If somehow though I have made any errors, or missed out anything important about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FobWFkcm9sbGluczcxNy53aWtpc3BhY2VzLmNvbS85K1ByZWRpY3Rpb25zK1Vwb24rTmV3K2lQYWQrQ2FzZXMrVGhpcytDb21pbmcrWWVhcg__" target="_blank"&gt;Buy new iPad cases&lt;/a&gt; then please let me know so I can fix things. I wish you found this interesting. Should you wish to find out more about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50YWJsZXQyY2FzZXMuY29tL3RhYmxldHMvYXBwbGUtaXBhZC0yLw__" target="_blank"&gt;iPad 2 cases&lt;/a&gt; then please check out this webpage.		</conversation>		<conversation id="55974482e9f49f8c4d5f42c68a32d6ff">			Now that you've bought your iPad it's important to consider accessories to protect and make it more functional. You don't of course have to run out and buy every accessory available but there are likely ones you will need. Depending on what you will use you iPad for there are a few accessories you will want. As far as productivity goes the following accessories for your iPad can come in handy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A great accessory to listen to your music on your iPad without disturbing others is the Apple in-ear headphones with remote and mic. The iPad has built in speakers, unlike the iPod which is scarcely audible when you remove headphones. While this is convenient in one way, there are times when you're better off listening privately, and Apple's in-ear headphones give you great sound quality seldom found in such small headphones. The headphones can be used with the iPad, iPod or iPhone. An cheap pair of headphones will fit the iPad, but the sound quality will be poor. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Think of a screen cover as an essential accessory and a must-have. The screen cover will minimize the damage to the screen and this will occur when we carry our devices with us, even when we are extra careful. The screen can also get very dirty from oil and grease and dirt from our fingertips, what the unit can be operated with. It's also likely that at some point or another, coffee will get spilled on it. Screen covers will keep it safe, but won't detract from the appearance or affect your control of the device since the covers are made from a think silicone. A thin silicone is used to make these protective covers and they will allow you full control of the device and will keep it safe, and won't alter the appearance too much. Screen covers made of a thin silicone will keep it safe and won't affect appearance or your ability to use it. Screen protectors are made by many different companies, and you can often find them online at reasonable prices.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A few of the things I am going to tell you about tablet back protectors may be a surprise to you, after all it is not a topic we talk about every single day. It is though a topic which I have had a great deal of interest in for many years now, and so I really want to share my interest with you. If somehow though I have made any errors, or missed out anything important about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvZWNkY3JrdWxyZmZic2dmZ3hmcGYvY29udGVudC9tYWtpbmcteW91ci1saWZlLWxlc3MtY29tcGxpY2F0ZWQtdGhhbmtzLXRvLW5ldy1pcGFkLWNhc2VzLWtub3dsZWRnZS00Nzc4OTYx" target="_blank"&gt;Buy new iPad cases&lt;/a&gt; then please let me know so I can fix things.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the most essential iPad accessories is probably a stylus pen. While you can use your fingers to operate the device, a stylus offers more precision. You can use a stylus to draw on your iPad or to jot down notes as you would in a notebook. There are many stylus pens available, and they usually cost between ten and fifteen dollars. Online you can usually find good deals, like 3-packs. Regardless of what you use your iPad for, a stylus pen is a very useful accessory. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The various accessories available can expand the capabilities of the already impressive iPad. Some of these accessories are made by Apple while others are offered by third party companies. While the above iPad accessories are not the only ones worth considering, they are among the most popular.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;i&gt;About the Blogger&lt;/i&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you spoke with my friends they would probably tell you I know too much about tablet cases, though to be honest they always seem quite interested. I do however keep on getting the same questions about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2tpdGNoZW5hcnQtaXN0LmNvbS8yMDEyLzAzLzMwLzMtZXN0aW1hdGlvbnMtZm9yLW5ldy1pcGFkLWNhc2VzLXRoaXMteWVhci8_" target="_blank"&gt;Buy new iPad cases&lt;/a&gt; from the people around me, so I thought it might be easier to put all the facts down here and save myself from repeating my answers over and over. Please let me know, after reading, if there is anything else you want to know. I expect you found this exciting. If you wish to find out more about [url=]tablet cases[/url] then please take a look at this webpage.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>