<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d43474585c7e19b28250ad615254c759">			&lt;b&gt;; Seniors May be Vulnerable to Many Options Identity Theft &amp;amp; Economical Theft including: &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Investment fraud &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Mortgage fraud &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Check cashing fraud, either forging seniors own personal checks or those made payable to seniors &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Charge card fraud &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;: Phony charity solicitation scams &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- You've gained so-called &quot;prize&quot; money awards where they must provide information that is later raised for theft &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Unfortunately, identity theft, financial scams and frauds with elderly is that far too often perpetrated by someone seniors know and trust like a caregiver or family member. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; What makes the elderly likely focuses on for identity theft and other financial crimes? &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Older persons may fall into a number or all the types below and these combinations make sure they are attractive targets for financial crimes. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Some senior who planned well for retirement have an overabundance of money, savings, cash supplies and home equity offered. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Since many seniors already have what they need or have more profit available, they are less more likely using credit. Those who aren't actively using their credit often don't check credit file regularly. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Although there are many exceptions, senior citizens are generally less &quot;technologically savvy&quot; and will be unaware of many of the scams that are based mostly around Internet usage. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;several. Seniors that are subject to others care and assistance like retirement home staff, home caregivers and family members may be taken advantage of, as their personal information is easily available to others. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sadly the case of identity theft of the 100-year-old man in Florida is not an isolated crime. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Even more True Crime Stories involving Elder Abuse and Identity Theft &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Within Anchorage, Alaska a 57 yr old man plead not guilty to 17 counts involving identity theft, fraud and criminal impersonation. He used the details of an 82 yr old man to obtain 7 credit cards on which he charged $34, 000 with merchandise. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An individual elderly care provider within Hinesville, GA was arrested for financial identity fraud and elder abuse. Her 43 victims range in age from 60-100. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With Birmingham, AL a CNA (certified nursing assistant) had been charged with elder use, neglect and identity theft. She took personal information with a nursing home patient and purchased over $5, 000 in goods and services. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's not necessarily strangers or caregivers who take advantage of seniors. A resident within a Boulder, CO nursing home was recently taken advantage of by her son together with granddaughter who stole above $16, 000 from her by abusing her electrical power of attorney to benefit themselves. The granddaughter had been arrested for 92 matters of identity theft and forgery. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;It always amazes me what some people will do to hurt a person's reputation. In the case of Republican Vice-Presidential candidate Debbie Palin, it has gotten more than ugly. From the minute she stepped on stage when John McCain introduced her as his going mate, the vitriol started out. In addition, it haven't and probably will not end until Election Day. She will probably be one of the most investigated and examined candidate with the media since George They would. Bush nominated Dan Quayle. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The reason why? Because the main mode media was caught off of guard. They did don?t you have a say in McCain's choice. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGFza2FsZWdhbGRlZmVuc2UuY29tL2F0dG9ybmV5LWFuY2hvcmFnZS1hbGFza2EuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Anchorage Alaska Attorney&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>