<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d1d8c8cb2092af008d20e08e11610f7f">			The difference of 15% to cut through the original price is immediately grown from the burden for customers. That is why he or she can afford to sell a Tv set at an outrageously low price. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When a company produces its products dirt low-priced, it doesn't mean not wearing running shoes has low standards, particularly having a quality. The Vizio company is able to sell its Vizio 32 from a low price without all compensation on its parts and not to say on quality, because they can come up with straightforward solutions and superior industry models. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbuyviziosv472xvt92.wordpress.com%2F2011%2F09%2F18%2Fvizio-47-1080p-sv472xvt-review%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://buyviziosv472xvt92.wordpress.com/2011/09/18/vizio-47-1080p-sv472xvt-review/&lt;/a&gt; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fblog.php%3Faction%3Dshowdiaryentry%26amp%3Bdiary_id%3D2089504%26amp%3Bgo%3Dmonroerobles511"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.getjealous.com/blog.php?action=showdiaryentry&amp;diary_id=2089504&amp;go=monroerobles511&lt;/a&gt; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwallinside.com%2Fpost-242237.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://wallinside.com/post-242237.html&lt;/a&gt; And so, you're looking at getting a large screen TV as they are considering the Vizio 47 1080p (model SV472XVT LCD). Previous to making your purchase, it's a good idea to find out more concerning TV you're considering, so you're able to make an informed choice to be certain you're happy with it you've chosen. A TV is usually a big investment, so that may help you make your decision, here's some the informatioin needed for the Vizio 47 1080p. Read on and good luck with selecting a TV! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why should I pick out a Vizio TV?&lt;br /&gt; Vizio TVs are widely looked upon as great value for money when it comes to their size and capabilities offered. The Vizio SV472XVT 47&quot;; style offers superior screen sizing with full HD (high definition) and even supports HD gaming to have awesome, large-screen gaming experience like no other! Vizio window screens offer great viewing through any angle and good sound quality, with a few built-in speakers, to actually enhance your movie together with gaming experience. Most models enjoy the latest standards and jacks, as well as several features. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How does Vizio look when placed against other brands of TV SET?&lt;br /&gt; Vizio is great value in comparison to other brands as well as highly competitive in a large-screen TV market. Vizio TVs are not invariably the top-performers in scientific tests of large-screen TVs but are several of the lowest priced for the particular features offered. In the end you have to decide whether you're following a great TV for an awesome price, or a top-of-the-range TV for a top-of-the-range price! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is the image quality any good?&lt;br /&gt; Yes, the Vizio 47 1080p hdtv has excellent picture quality at 920x1080 pixels, in a true movie theatre past experiences. Picture quality is superior from any angle, an advantage if you will aren't sitting directly working on the screen! The Vizio 47 1080p hdtv has the benefit of excellent motion-following technology, making in a great clear picture. Movies always look better on a larger screen, so if you have the room it's definitely worth it for the 'at property movie experience'! &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So now that there is some more information for the Vizio 47 1080p (model SV472XVT), you are prepared to make your decision on regardless of whether to go ahead and get. Vizio has a wide range of great features, is excellent affordability, and customers who have purchased are happy with their choice. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Vizio's the newest name in television watching movies today, and there's no doubt about the reason.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>