<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="c92b3e850b9a0620e77930e6694cbfe8">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsu-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;  Mini Hamburger Speaker for iPhone iPod laptop MP3&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Hamburger Mini Speaker delivers full bass and big, high quality sound from a mini speaker!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They are hungry for good audio? They are starved for portability and sound delicious at the same time? If so, you’re lucky because we have a juicy hamburger mini speaker fresh from the grill with your name on it for you! This small, inconspicuous speakers really, it is to believe. The “Hamburger” form is really advanced technology, these pint-sized speakers with powerful bass that makes other mini-speakers gives drooling. Your friends will be amazed that a speaker that fits in the palm, can fill the room with great sound and solid bass. The Hamburger Mini Speaker, you can have portability and great sound in a cool device.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Hamburger Mini Speaker sounds (and tastes) great with all your portable gadgets that have a 3.5mm audio out jack, including your iPod, PSP, NDS, CVFH-N03,MP3 player, MP4 player, laptop, notebook, netbook, CD player, mobile phone, and PDA. The Hamburger Mini Speaker is great for sharing your tunes while relaxing outside, vacationing at the the beach, driving in the car, hanging out with friends at school or at the mall, or even relaxing at home and in the office.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In search of a tasty items for resale? The Hamburger Mini Speaker is exactly what the boss ordered. Order a few today, you enjoy these mini-speakers for itself and then the other will sell on your Internet storefront with other profit potential to enjoy. Then take bulk orders for maximizing your profits resale. This amazing gadget is in stock and ready to send directly to you or your customers of your best source for high quality, low price Gadgets		</conversation>		<conversation id="aad1f7c16ba8c4e1a3e15824be0c0b73">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsu-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;  Mini Hamburger Speaker for iPhone iPod laptop MP3&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Portable Speakers   &lt;br /&gt;;Portable speakers that bring your iTunes to life and also make fantastic mens gifts. This Fathers Day or perhaps Christmas, why not spoil Dad with some of these great gift ideas for men.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All portable speakers and mens gifts are in stock and ready for immediate shipping - The Gifted Man for all your men's gift ideas.		</conversation>		<conversation id="77f9382c7c960685b384797c6adafa0d">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsu-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;   The world first patent mini speaker——Speakers can  charging for mobile phone,iPad, iPhone, MP3, MP4, mobile fn-38&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Along with the rapid development of science and technology, the high-tech digital products has been popular to everyone, and especially the ones that is easy to carry. For example: ipad, iphone, MP3, MP4, MP5, etc. But they have a common characteristic: all are with built-in lithium battery. And the lithium battery can be on work for only a few or dozens of hours after charging. &lt;br /&gt;;We also become puzzled when enjoying the high-tech, it is suddenly out of power, all the work and entertainment can't continue. Today, Shenzhen Zena Electronics Co., Ltd. (&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;) develops a worldwide patent product charging for mobile digital products anywhere and anytime &lt;br /&gt;;First, mobile products generally have a USB charging line and can charge through the line. &lt;br /&gt;;Second, most mobile digital product can make a sound, but effect is poor, it is completely not satisfying the demand of the digital players . &lt;br /&gt;;According to the above points, Shenzhen Zena Electronic Co., Ltd. (&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;) developes a mobile, portable speaker which can charge for ipod, iphone, mobile phones, MP3, MP4. The volume of the speaker is small, so it is convenient to take and the sound quality is pefect, and it have a USB interface which can charge for a variety of digital products, and the lithium battery is the Nokia cell phone battery sold all over the world. The battery can come down and be charged by other charging equipment, then the sound box itself is with a USB charging line, this would solve the digital products died suddenly.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.su-speaker.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.su-speaker.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>