<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="37c9f2a289b6098c81fb4af84c0199cf">			Also, having the broker go to the property directly will let you meet him or the woman's; which we will talk more about below.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So, precisely what is the broker actually going to actually do to comprehensive the BPO?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Pull comparables &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Take photos in the property and the bordering area &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Approximation repair costs &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Form an opinion with the properties value in the market &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; Write it all up on a short-term report and send it on the lender &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;That effect - the opinion - can make a huge difference in your deals. If the BPO cost is $100, 000; and the lender is able to take 90% of BPO benefits, your net offer should be $90, 000 or higher. If the BPO cost is $120, 000; now your net offer will have to be $108, 000. A high BPO can and routinely does kill deals. You can sometimes grab the bank to order a second (or maybe a third!) BPO, but your goal ought to be to get the BPO for a value that supports ones short sale offer, the very first time out.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So; with that said, how can you (legally!) impact or influence the BPO benefits?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt; &lt;ol&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Be ready! &lt;/strong&gt; This broker will pull their own comparables, and so should you. Remember, everything is subjective. Take properties and values with you that you think best represent the value of the listing, and share those with the broker. Create your own personal repair estimates, as well, to help you compare notes while using the broker. Your repair estimates should include both the more dental items (like peeling car paint and damaged counter tops) as well as the more serious issues (like foundation cracks or maybe a leaky roof). &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Show up! &lt;/strong&gt; Not everyone might recommend this, especially Digital Investors, because it takes time, but you will need to show up, especially if the location is nearby. Also, if you do a whole lot of business, it will help to develop a relationship along with the broker doing the BPO. Don't be a pain in the ass, but do pay focus on what they are noting! Make certain the broker themselves come to the property (some brokers will unethically send in surrogates for a cut in the lender payment) - and make sure that the borrower is NOT home! To control the situation to the best to your ability, you should become the one there answering questions. We shouldn't have to bring up this, but you undoubtedly are a professional, so act like an individual - dress appropriately and bring a company card along. &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Retain the property as-is, no fix-ups! &lt;/strong&gt; You want the house to accurately reflect the condition it is in. The following isn't an open house; you don't need light scented candles in each room, dim the equipment and lighting, put on opera music and place silk Ficus plants in the foyer. If there is usually damage, point it out. If the broker missed something, make a note of it, especially in areas they will might not look (like the attic or the attic). &lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt; Follow-up and Close Strong! &lt;/strong&gt; When the broker finishes their walk through, you should examine your notes. Ask them if they have an initial ballpark estimate. Many BPO agents will give high values - when these aren't reasonable, now is the time to speak up. Make sure you mention crime statistics and other neighborhood items if they forgot. You can quite possibly give her your indicated property value. Remember, it's your last opportunity to say anything they missed, so ensure you take advantage of it! Everything else you do, complete &lt;i&gt; not &lt;/i&gt; end up overbearing! Any stories on genital herpes virus treatments have done to tackle a BPO? Any scary stories? We'd love to hear them in the feedback!&lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpdC5seS9IUVR4bHM_" target="_blank"&gt;take survey online&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>