<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="9d38922d47664bcfc3f2ecd3abcf7949">			The most crucial types of parrots are classified within the following:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Amazons&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Cockatoos&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Grey Parrots&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Macaws&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Conures&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Parakeets&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Lovebirds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Cockatiels&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Budgerigars &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Amazon online Parrots &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o medium to fairly big sized birds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; u mainly green in color with patches of red, yellow and blue on the wings, tail and face&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o posses really loud voices and often talk in the company of strangers&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o older men Amazons (over 3 years old) can end up aggressive, especially the hawk-headed birds &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Cockatoos &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o they are big compared to Amazons&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o very intelligent and intensely sensitive and nervous parrots&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o possess erectile crests that will raised and lowered at will&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o glimpse cute and cuddly&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o adults might inflict very painful bites in any other case trained properly&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o demand constant attention and may be difficult for most people to take care &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Camera &amp;amp; Timneh Gray Birds &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o regularly medium to large size pet parrots&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o two categories of gray parrots, the Timneh Gray and also the African Gray (and also Congo Gray)&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o very sensitive but extremely intelligent birds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o Timneh Grays have great abilities to mimic wide selection of sounds including human being speech&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o quiet inside presence of strangers&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o hand-reared parrots are very prone to feather plucking&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o can be extremely loud but rarely some sort of noise nuisance &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Macaws &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o considered the largest parrots&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o more compact ones, like Hahn's together with yellow-collared, are noisy but make very good pets&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o active, inquisitive and often mischievous&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o chatty and able to learn to talk&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o powerful beaks that can damage furniture and crash nuts&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o large ones may require more aviary space rather then a cage&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o not suitable for home with young kids &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Conures &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o result from South Africa&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; u fairly small but usually active and confident&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o bright orange and yellow sun conure, Patagonian and blue-crowned conures have loud piercing voices&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; u very curious but interesting&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o able to help talk but posses squeaky voices when using human speech&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o happy to sleep in roosting boxes placed inside the cage&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o known as 'nippy' birds as they are prone to bite very readily &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Parakeets &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o &quot;Parakeet&quot; is loosely used to cover a wide range of smaller parrotlike birds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o most because of Australia or Asia&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o they can be leafy-green colored, ground-feeders spending most of their time on the cage floor&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o unlike the majority of parrots, they are not noisy at all&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o active together with highly social creatures, require large flocks and kept in aviary&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o very independent and thus do not bond very well with human&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o respond perfectly to training but poor mimic of human special message &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Parrotlets &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o smallest of all parrots, about the size of a sparrow&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o mainly green in color and quite easy to keep in cages&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o need plenty of time to fly around (outside the house their cages)&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o bond well with people&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o voices may be loud at times nonetheless they are not noisy parrots &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Eclectus Parrots &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o choice to large sized puppy parrots&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o men and women have different plumage&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o males get bright leaf-green with red and blue patches on their flanks and wings, while females have smart red with patches involving purple or blue on their flanks and wings&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o body feathers can be extremely fine with beautiful hues&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o eat dieting of fruits, flowers, buds and a few seeds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o do not adapt well as interior companion birds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o adults may be both noisy and aggressive&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o prone to help self-plucking behaviors &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Lovebirds &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o small and active, short-tailed parrots originate from Africa&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o best secured in pairs as they cannot usually bond with humans as most other parrots do&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o posses shrill voices and can make calls at sound&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o do not copy human speech&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o often kept in aviary rather then companion birds &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Cockatiels &amp;amp; Budgies &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o most popular parrotlike birds and both originate from Australia&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o natural color of budgies is bright green with fine scalelike pattern of non colored documents markings above but at the moment, they come in great variety of colors due to not bothered breeding in captivity across generations&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o budgies may not be difficult to keep but require a long time with its keeper if kept alone&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o capable associated with talking and learning many words and phrases in small, squeaky noises&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o very effective and busy birds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o cockatiels are larger birds and they make a good pet&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o natural shade of cockatiels is gray with white on the wings and yellow-orange patches in the head&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o able to learn to talk nevertheless with loud, harsh noises&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o very dynamic and busy birds&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; o can get taught to obey some requests and commands &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I hope you find these simple tips on different kinds of parrots and some of their unique differences useful. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;You walk by some sort of bird shop, or visit the aviary at the zoo, and there may be several types of birds. You study them, and to wonder, &quot;What different types of parrots are there anyway? How many types of parrots are there? &quot; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Actually, there are more than 350 parrot types the fact that every species and sub-species in the group. Many of the most common parrot types are from Australasia along with the tropics. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Bird Families &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All parrots, of whatever parrot types or breeds they're just, belong to the logical order Psittaciformes. That scientific order is further separated into two different bird families: Cacatuidae and Psittacidae. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That Cacatuidae family includes only the Cockatoo, a bird that is native to Australia and islands near that continent. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The 2nd parrot family, the Psittacidae, includes all of the true parrot types. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Cockatoos &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To most people, the cockatoo can be a large white parrot with a feathered head crest that it can lift high with regal splendor. That is, however, only one of the parrot types in this family. There are twenty one different cockatoos, and not every one is white. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. The palm cockatoo a brand new dark gray, with red cheek sections below the eyes - cheek patches that change to a deeper red when this bird becomes excited and alarmed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. The male gang-gang cockatoo is dark gray which includes a cherry red head together with red crest. This parrot type is often called the red-headed cockatoo. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. The Major Mitchell's cockatoo is often called a pink cockatoo due to its soft pastel pink shade. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NoYWR0aG9tcHNvbjkyMi5kZXZpYW50YXJ0LmNvbS9qb3VybmFsL0RpZmZlcmVudC1UeXBlcy1vZi1CaXJkLUZvb2QtMjg2NjE2Njg3" target="_blank"&gt;;Bird Watching - Food to Attract Birds&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NoYWR0aG9tcHNvbjkyMi5zaXRlcnVuLmV1L2luZGV4LnBocD9wZz05Nzc4Nw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Homemade Oriole Bird Food&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NoYXduYmVuamFtaTkyNTE3LndlYnMuY29tL2FwcHMvYmxvZy9zaG93LzEyNjAwODg1LWltcHJvdmUtYnJlZWRpbmctc3VjY2Vzcy13aXRoLXZldGFmYXJtLXBhcnJvdC1wZWxsZXRz" target="_blank"&gt;;Different Types of Bird Food&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>