<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="cbc4cc52a3ce9ce05dfad9600de146f6">			Many women would agree that there are a few things in life as rewarding as motherhood. These women would also agree that having children takes a major toll on your body. For this reason, there has been a major increase in the number of mothers that are seeking mommy makeovers from a trusted plastic surgeon. With the help of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWF1dGlmdWxmaWd1cmUuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;Los Angeles Plastic Surgery&lt;/a&gt; women are able to turn back the clock. A top to bottom makeover is common for women after childbearing is completed.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most women struggle with the impact of pregnancy and aging on their body. With the help of a “mommy makeover” plastic surgeons are able to repair the disfiguring affects of childbearing. Pregnancy affects each woman differently. Age and genetics play an important role in how the body recovers from childbearing. Giving birth and breast feeding can have profound negative effects on women. Often times, fat will accumulate in the hips and abdomen causing them to lose their hourglass shape. A mommy makeover typically consists of a breast lift with or without breast implants, a Liposuction Los Angeles, and a tummy tuck. The procedures are intended to tighten any lose skin, remove pregnancy fat, and reduce stretch marks.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A mommy makeover appeals to young mothers as quick fix for stubborn post pregnancy fat. Older moms see a mommy surgery as a way to slim down after pregnancy while also controlling aging itself. There are many well-known plastic surgeons in Los Angeles and Beverly Hills who offer a mommy makeover for women that want their abdomen and breasts back to the way they looked before pregnancy. When breast surgery is done, women may feel sad to see that they are left with sagging breasts with less volume. With the help of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWF1dGlmdWxmaWd1cmUuY29tL2JyZWFzdGltcGxhbnQtbG9zYW5nZWxlcy5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;breast augmentation Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;and a breast lift, patients are able to fully recover from breast feeding. If a mother wants to achieve a larger breast size, implants may be necessary. Saline implants are the most popular type of implant used.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Once breasts are made fuller and perkier, mothers notice that their abdomen is not as flat as it used to be. The postpartum “pouch” that many women have is often a combination of excess skin, fat, and stretch marks. It may be impossible to significantly improve the abdominal area with diet and exercise. When excess skin and fat are the issue, a liposuction or tummy tuck may be the solution. A tummy tuck is often required to create a permanent solution for stubborn fat and excess skin. During this procedure, muscles are tightened and excess skin is removed to create a flat pre-pregnancy abdomen. For many women, cosmetic surgery is a well deserved reward after all of the challenges of motherhood.		</conversation>		<conversation id="6dadb942a284495931368796b2aebdc1">			To decide between a tummy tuck and lower body lift, you need to consider what body areas bother you the most. After massive weight loss, each patient loses fat differently. Some patients will lose a significant amount of abdominal fat, while other patients may not lose as much. Some patients will lose a significant amount of fat from their thighs and buttocks, while others may not. Another variable is how well the skin will contract or shrink-wrap around the area of fat loss. The amount of skin contracture depends on your age, the amount of weight loss, and the quality of your skin.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To decide between a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXZlcmx5aGlsbHNsb29rcy5jb20vYmV2ZXJseWhpbGxzLXR1bW15dHVjay5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;Tummy Tuck Beverly Hills&lt;/a&gt; and a lower body lift, you need to consider what each procedure will do for you. Both the tummy tuck and the lower body lift will remove abdominal skin and fat. In addition, both the tummy tuck and the lower body lift involve tightening the rectus or abdominal muscles and led to a flat abdomen. However, the lower body lift goes much further than a tummy tuck.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are bothered by your outer hips, love handles lower back, and buttocks, then a lower body lift may be the better surgery for you. The lower body lift or 360 body lift involves an incision that extends completely around your body and removes skin and fat from your entire torso. The incision extends from just above the pubic region, around the hips, and meets in the back. The lower body lift will remove skin and fat from the abdomen, outer hips, lower back, and buttocks. This can result in a flat abdomen, contoured outer thighs, and a lifted buttock. In comparison, the tummy tuck only removes skin and fat from the central abdomen; the tummy tuck does not address the hips or the buttocks.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another benefit of the lower body lift over the tummy tuck is the minimal chance of a dog-ear. A dog-ear is a collection of skin and fat left at the ends of the incision/scar. This can occur after a tummy tuck if the incision was too short and not enough skin and fat were removed. A tummy tuck dog-ear is usually corrected by extending the incision and removing the excess skin and fat. The lower body lift has minimal chances of a dog-ear because of the design of the surgery and the fact that there is no end to the incision. Some tummy tuck dog-ears are so large that to remove the dog-ear, the incision needs to extend further towards the back. This results in a longer incision and is sometimes called an &quot;;extended&quot;; tummy tuck. The problem with the “extended” tummy tuck is that the incision is longer, but it does not truly lift the outer thighs. In addition, an extended tummy tuck does not raise the buttocks. Usually a lower body lift is better than an extended &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWF1dGlmdWxmaWd1cmUuY29tL3R1bW15dHVjay1sb3NhbmdlbGVzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;Tummy Tuck Los Angeles&lt;/a&gt;because the lower body lift raises and tightens the outer thighs and buttocks.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In conclusion, if your outer hips, thighs, and buttocks bother you, the lower body lift may be a better procedure for you than a tummy tuck. The body lift is a longer and more involved procedure, but addresses more areas in a single surgery than the tummy tuck.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For more information about the lower body lift and the tummy tuck after massive weight loss, please read more on our web site at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bodybykatzen.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.bodybykatzen.com&lt;/a&gt;. To view the lower body lift procedure, please go to “You Tube” and search for “360 body lift avi”.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>