<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e6620471d34f48857fa18a07c5e7ff69">			The soothing and relaxing sounds of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nYXJkZW4tZm91bnRhaW5zLmNvbS9DYXRlZ29yaWVzLmJvaz9jYXRlZ29yeT1HYXJkZW4rRm91bnRhaW5z" target="_blank"&gt;;garden fountains&lt;/a&gt;; will bring an unequaled feeling of tranquility and enjoyment for your life. Garden fountains are gorgeous when they are the centerpiece of a garden so it's sad when they just languish in a corner of the yard unseen. In order to have optimum use out of this item of outdoor furniture, make sure it could be seen and enjoyed. Do not let a fountain to be overshadowed by plants or tucked into a corner that usually goes unvisited.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A garden fountain can be a stunning piece of art that should be loved simply for its elegance, but it has to be viewed for that to take place. If the garden fountain is really big, the property owner may want to consider getting more than one fountain. Set that one as the attraction after which search for a couple of others that will complement it. Place those two in areas in need of a focal point. Find one that's large and creates a bold statement with color or design.  Keep in mind that outdoor water features need to be put where individuals will see them. A fountain might seem large when a person is standing beside it, but any time it must be viewed from a distance; it becomes evident that it's too small for the place. If the seating area is around a corner of the garden, the fountain may be difficult to view.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So as to make sure your garden water fountain fits your needs, make sure you seek advice from an expert to determine which one would work best for you personally. Some need filtered water to avoid calcium build-up. Others will need chemicals put into them to prevent algae accumulation. But no matter what kind of garden water fountain you get, there are some easy maintenance tips you have to keep in mind to keep the structure running smoothly.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Regardless of how purified or filtered your water supply may be, it will get polluted ultimately. You may hire a professional for the job, but always make sure you ask the manufacturer how often the water will need to be changed. You must sustain water levels.  Regularly looking into the unit's water level will ensure the water pump's longevity. Particularly in the summer time in which you might need to put water from time to time in order to fight against evaporation. Winterize: If you are living in a cold-weather region make sure you empty the water before every winter. And if it gets notably cold in your neck of the woods, you might want to bring the outdoor water fountains inside. This could even make a nice interior accessory for your house by having a live fountain inside. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Garden &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nYXJkZW4tZm91bnRhaW5zLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;water fountains&lt;/a&gt;; will last for a long time with proper care, especially during winter freezes or severe summer heat. Water fountains should be carefully guarded to avoid drying or cracking and it is better to use distilled water to avoid the development of algae. A garden fountain is a lovely addition which will add beauty and pleasure to any size outdoor area, yard, outdoor patio, or terrace.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8be07255e97351ad1195916900fec006">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nYXJkZW4tZm91bnRhaW5zLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Water fountains&lt;/a&gt;; are among the stunning ways to beautify your own home while also including a bit of serenity, nothing beats the look and feel that an indoor painting or any wall decor can offer. Whether you are designing your home on your own or remodeling to give your living space a facelift, outdoor wall fountains or slate wall fountains brings your décor to a totally new level. All you really need to do is discover the best piece to add to your house and you will have a pleasant addition that you could enjoy as well as all of your guests who visit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Indoor waterfalls and interior water wall fountains change silent homes and offices into soothing natural conditions rich with all the sound of flowing water. Recognized for their soothing and therapeutic powers, wall fountains add the calming sounds of water for any space, while incorporating a aesthetically spectacular focal piece. Combine it with your family room, or even in the foyer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wall Fountains can also add an extremely natural and organic feeling to your house or office. The natural sounds of trickling water down a fountain waterfall can produce a soothing habitat to live or work in. Wall Fountains are a good addition to any home or garden. No space for a water fountain? Bring a wall fountain to the rescue! Just install the wall features on any wall, post, fence, (or up against the wall having a floor wall fountain) etc, load with water, and plug the water feature pump cord in. They work outdoors or indoors. It's an instant water feature for the interior or exterior.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Indoor fountains make a daring, sophisticated statement inside your lobby or office. You can even combine your company logo into one of the designs, offering an extraordinary focus for any place of business. If you are short on room, an indoor wall fountain takes up no floor space. They're as simple to hang as a picture, but their beauty is moving, flowing, and constantly enchanting. Modern wall water garden fountains often employ the brilliance of polished metal to permit owners to take pleasure in the most stunning effect. They are available in steel and copper and other metals. Most of the wall fountains possess a cascade of water which runs around the surface of the metal in a sheet, which enhances the shine of the metal itself. These are extremely popular in offices and boardrooms. Wall water features with this design also work beautifully for corporate-branded water features.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Water &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nYXJkZW4tZm91bnRhaW5zLmNvbS9DYXRlZ29yaWVzLmJvaz9jYXRlZ29yeT1HYXJkZW4rRm91bnRhaW5z" target="_blank"&gt;;garden fountains&lt;/a&gt;; are great to look at, obviously, however they can provide other benefits. Every indoor wall garden fountains generate particles called negative ions. These tiny particles are created by the turbulence of falling water, and each one has an electrical charge. These particles act like an air filter by connecting with smoke and dust particles within the air, hauling them to the floor. The air inside your home is often more polluted than the air outside, and you can help make your environment healthier using a water wall fountain.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>