<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="e7c7572db27d2a05df44cce4978db5f5">			Although the wedding is the existence of the world since ancient times the ceremony, but the bride wedding gown at the wedding but not to 200 years of history. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWRkaW5nZHJlc3Nlc29uc2FsZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Wedding dresses uk&lt;/a&gt;;   on the moon should be the prototype of 1700 BC to 1550 BC, ancient Greek aristocratic dynasty of three generations of women Minnow worn bare chest, sleeves to the elbow, chest, waist position by a thread in the breast below the lower dressed bell-shaped dress, the overall tight fitting clothing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now the bride wo?e white gauze dress hem trailing ce?emony was originally a Catholic servic?. Sinc? ancient times in so?e Eur?pean countries are theoc?atic st?te system, peopl? get married have t? go to chu?ch fo? the priest or pastor of prayer and blessing, t?is can ?e consider?d formal leg?l marriag?, ?o the ceremon?, th? brid? wore w?ite clothing to God th?t sincer? and pure.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Western 19th century, when the girls get marr?ed there ?s n? uniform worn by the bride dress ?olor specificat?ons, ?ntil 1820 y?ars ago, t?e white grad?ally became widely-used wedding dre?s color. This ?s because t?e Brit?sh Q?een Victoria wor? ? white wedding d?ess elegant. Then you can choo?e t?e c?lor as the colo? of yo?r &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWRkaW5nZHJlc3Nlc29uc2FsZS5jby51ay82LW1hdGVybml0eS13ZWRkaW5nLWRyZXNzZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;maternity wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;  .
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since then, the white wedding will be a for?al w?dding d?ess, now, some people do not unde?stand t?e origin? ?f the wedding, his ingenuity, t?e ?ride's wedding dress ?ade of p?nk or light ?lue color, t? ?how gorgeous. In fact, acco?ding t? Western custo?s, only married wo?en, the wedd?ng can use colors such as p?nk or sky bInexplue, to show the difference w?th the first marriage. Now day, you c?n buy the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWRkaW5nZHJlc3Nlc29uc2FsZS5jby51ay8xMi1jaGVhcGluZXhwZW5zaXZlLXdlZGRpbmctZHJlc3Nlcw__" target="_blank"&gt;;inexpensive wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;   at stores or ?uy the?e online. Today, mor? and more people bu? it online, because it i? cheap. En?oy yo?rself at t?e wonderful day! Good l?ck!		</conversation>		<conversation id="65f7b2e7e283b9576bd5546560c0660e">			I will tell you something about the wedding dresses, even legend about the first wedding dresses. However, we can buy &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5icmlkYWx3ZWRkaW5nZ293bnMuY2Ev" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;   by any way.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sixteenth-century Europe, the Royal Iris? lov? to hunt, in a summer afternoon, the ?oyal family and nobles with their shotguns, riding ?orses and flocks ?f b?agle hunting in a sm?ll town in Northern Ireland, met Miss Ros? laundry ?n t?e ri?er, Richard Earl s?ddenly was l?ve at first sight, M?ss Ros? w?s innocent and elegance captivated at the sa?e time, Mis? Ros? als? handsome, up?tanding Earl Richard left ? deep meaning ?f love.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hunting back co?rt of the Earl ?f sleep ?t nig?t, ?nd in the feudal society can not accept the situation, c?urage to put fo?ward the door properly, household? n?t on th? Ro?e ?as bo?n in r?ral areas to ma?ry the idea popp?d the q?estion!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As E?rl's insistenc?, refus?d to giv? u? in order to count the Crown put forward a request ?as ?lmost impossible, I hope, Miss R?se sewing in ? ?hite robe overnight (at th?t time th? ?abit of not w?aring wh?te silk wedding), The length requirement ?s met, th? agency from the Royal Irish church to witness the stage door of the white chu?ch robe.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Request, Richard Earl thought that marriag? has almost ?ecome ?anish favorite, but t?en Miss Rose does not agree, actually, ?nd the ?hole town residents stayed up all night together, sew out before dawn ? ver? delicate design lines and simple yet be?utiful atmo?phere ?f the 16-meter Royal white robe, w?ite ro?e when this sent to Ireland the foll?wing day th? ro?al family, th? royal famil? w?s certainly n?t impressed by th? hig? emotional de?ign touched b? the King and Que?n in Ireland and completed under the pro?ise of t?e sacred fairy-tale wedding ?ith the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5icmlkYWx3ZWRkaW5nZ293bnMuY2Ev" target="_blank"&gt;;winter wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;  .
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This i? the first wedding dresses of t?e origin of the world. Now you can buy any c?eap wedd?ng dre?ses ?n the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5icmlkYWx3ZWRkaW5nZ293bnMuY2Ev" target="_blank"&gt;;wedding dress stores&lt;/a&gt;;  .		</conversation>		<conversation id="bd0fbd88ded92000cc3662b6b3afd3a9">			Although the form of love is always supporting role, but the set of thousands of pet are essential in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWRkaW5nZHJlc3Nlc29uc2FsZS5jby51ay8xMi1jaGVhcGluZXhwZW5zaXZlLXdlZGRpbmctZHJlc3Nlcw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Inexpensive wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;  ! See the dazzling array of wedding window, the new people seem to panic, do not know how to proceed, in the end what kind of wedding do best for you? Then follow me and see it, do you dream of the perfect bride. I will create the perfect bride by your gall gown wedding dresses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wedding dresses classification is ba?ed on: The female body curves, thin, transparent, gel, soft, smoot?, light, eleg?nt, subtle, h?zy be?uty of ?uman b?dy ?nd s? filling. Wedding dres? in the style are ? line wedding dres?es, ?all gown, empire, mer?aid, sh?ath and ?o on. Let m? t?lk about that perfect gall gown &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWRkaW5nZHJlc3Nlc29uc2FsZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;wedding dresses uk&lt;/a&gt;;  , and now most of the brides are choosing this style.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gall gown wedding dresses pro?inent che?t, emphasizing the sl?nder waist, flared h?m was op?ned, the o?erall sha?e of fitt?ng ?ody-fitted, has ? strong three-dimensional feeling, put the princess line d?ess ?ould loo? char?ing. Princess line ?f vertical clear cut m?nner, the vertical lines can mak? the bride loo? more slender ?hysique, ?moother lines, symmetry. Adapted t?pes of ?our bodie? are many. Petite slim b?dy but the bride, ?ou ?an choose waist high ceiling des?gn, the hem lin?s str?tched Ministry. Chest f?ll of th? brid?, should choos? some of the neckline o? deep V-neck, neck look more slend?r. If you are t?e maternit? woman. Please don???t worry about your body, ?ou can al?o s?ow your beauty at y?ur wedding. Just remembe? the ba?y is the lov? of your wedding, yo? c?n consider the perf?ct gall gown &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWRkaW5nZHJlc3Nlc29uc2FsZS5jby51ay82LW1hdGVybml0eS13ZWRkaW5nLWRyZXNzZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;maternity wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;  . You can also t?e most shining star at your day. After read this I hope I can help you with your w?dding dress. In add?tion, I ?ope you can ?njoy your?elf with you wonde?ful day. Good luck! T? be the m?st beautiful bride!		</conversation>		<conversation id="ed99e45f2e25a589c7f16b5e83cdda37">			&quot;Is the most beautiful bride, the bride for some of the fat, gold yarn designers introduced a&quot; off the shoulder wedding dresses &quot;, which would allow them to be more confident and beautiful. We can also tailor-made wedding dress the guests,&quot; Winter Gold Yarn 2011 designed to reflect the cut dress, &quot;China wind&quot;, while also embracing the elements into the Western, elegant, beautiful shine, highlight the theme of design and a strong sense of color contrast. Black, white, dark blue, purple, etc., will be 2011 gold gauze &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5icmlkYWx3ZWRkaW5nZ293bnMuY2Ev" target="_blank"&gt;;winter wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;   with autumn colors.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ?ight c?oice ?an help you modify figur?, highlighting t?e advant?ges and w?ong w?th your weaknes?es will ?e exposed t?. Together to find the ?ost suitable &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5icmlkYWx3ZWRkaW5nZ293bnMuY2Ev" target="_blank"&gt;;cheap wedding dresses&lt;/a&gt;;   for you? wedding ?eady to pi?k ho?es to give the sisters ?ake ? small reference.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Arm, the bride ?an choose ? thic? card sleeve or off the shoulder dress, this has the effect of ?overing the wedding, but the color lighter sleeves, do n?t ch?ose, ?ecause ther? will be expansion of t?e white sense, but to make the arm more thick, can t?ke advantage of the veil pl?y the role of cover, or use the same color, f?bric s?awl ? little more light, the effect is also good.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Below t?e collar resting on the ?houlder, collarb?ne and s?oulders exposed, cover the part of the upper a?m sleeve. This style of most of the fe?ale body ?s ?ery fit, chest size medium ?r relatively plum? women w?ar would ?e particularly b?autiful. However, if the arms a?e not ?sed t? compare fat or b?re shoulders, yo? can try the foll?wing describes t?e Portrait collar shape. Suitabl? f?r: chest fullness, pear shaped women a?e not suitable: ?road shoulders, thick arms. Style f?r mo?t women, the shoulde? falls under the collar, c?n ?eveal a b?autiful long ne?k, clavicl? and tall, elegant ?ut relatively thic? uppe? arms, ?houlders to? broad, t?ick back muscles of women, is inappropriate. Today you can b?y off th? shoulder wedding dresses at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5icmlkYWx3ZWRkaW5nZ293bnMuY2Ev" target="_blank"&gt;;wedding dress stores&lt;/a&gt;;   o? you c?n buy the dress?s online. I think y?u must be the ?ost beautiful bride ?t the day!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>