<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a9e4d7d9497b6924bc2e611964fde78">			&lt;h1&gt;;Might the Samsung Galaxy S3 be a noteworthy update?&lt;/h1&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is close to that time  again when the MWC is due to arrive in  Barcelona. If you're anything like us, you might already be desperately looking forward to the launch of the Samsung Galaxy S3,  largely expected to make an appearance. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As always a large number of cutting edge phones will be showcased within the Three days, but we have no doubt that the Samsung Galaxy S3 is set to be the most impressive Android to take the stage.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most certainly amongst the many mobile phone industry journalists and professionals, there's talk about hardly anything else apart from the arrival and seeing the initial special sightings of the Samsung flagship mobile phone for 2012.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;h2&gt;;Samsung Galaxy S3 features you are likely to see&lt;/h2&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are numerous varying beliefs zooming around in regards to the form and main features likely to accompany the Samsung Galaxy S3. Some of these speculations are unclear or hard to comprehend, which is the reason we have sieved through all of them in order to solve the rumours and give you our thoughts as to what we predict Samsung will deliver to the table. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nYWxheHlzMy5vcmcudWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;Galaxy S3&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYW1zdW5nZ2FsYXh5czMub3JnLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;Galaxy S3 Deals&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;2gb Random Access Memory&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Super AMOLED Plus Hi-def 4.65inch screen with 1280 x 720p resolution&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;1080p hd video recorder&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;12MP back camera&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Android 4.0 Ice Cream Sandwich and TouchWiz - Samsung’s customisable graphical user interface&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Quad 1.8 Gigahertz central processor&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;h2&gt;;Design of the Samsung Galaxy S3&lt;/h2&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As far as good looks are related it happens to be remarkably comparable to the Samsung Galaxy S2. However when you really think about it, it’s actually normal nowadays for manufacturers to stumble on a well-accepted style and then essentially stay with it. If it ain’t broke why fix it? So perhaps, the moment Smart phone aficionados are content with the basic appearance, it’s primarily the ability and important features that seriously mean much to them and steer their buying selection strategy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;h2&gt;;Samsung Galaxy S3 roll-out rumours&lt;/h2&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Everything until now has suggested strongly at an April in-store release of the Samsung Galaxy S3, even so,we have more than a sly notion that it may wind up being deferred. Samsungs vice president of sales and marketing even pointed out that they are currently going over their other options and will come to a decision in the near future. The Samsung Galaxy S2 was launched in the US months after the rest of the globe, which resulted in a dissatisfied crowd of State side prospective buyers. Due to the disappointment that delay made across the water, Samsung would most likely elect not to duplicate a phased introduction. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Samsung Galaxy S2 is still flying out of the shops and the demand for this device displays no sign of waning as yet. Up to now, this smartphone has continued to fly off the shelves and Samsung could very well decide to wait for the Samsung Galaxy S2 to diminish in attractiveness before unveiling the Samsung Galaxy S3. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This new alteration of strategy can easily direct Samsung to position itself to challenge the launch of the iPhone 5. Considering the iPhone 4S was introduced in September, it’s a pretty sure bet to assume how the Samsung Galaxy S3 may also hit the stores by the the fall. Who wouldn’t love to be a fly on the wall in the Samsung and Apple hq war rooms to experience the fallout of that clash? Samsung Telecommunications managed to generate colossal incremental growth last year. With Samsung solidly looking forward to their mobile phone business to amplify by an additional Thirty percent this year, in so far as Apple is related Samsung are unquestionably the opponent to have a very close eye on in 2012.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Therefore who do you predict will come up on top of smartphone mountain, the Samsung Galaxy S3 or perhaps the iPhone 5?		</conversation>		<conversation id="acf66d8475785565896bdb7321cc3925">			&lt;h1&gt;;The Galaxy S3 could be possibly the most outstanding launch of 2012&lt;/h1&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The mobile community scarcely bothers to perk up and take serious notice of the launching of a fresh new Smartphone, until of course it’s of the Apple type. Interestingly, may possibly all set to alter because of the emergence of the Samsung Galaxy S3. We have got a new invitation solidly in the schedule for the Samsung Galaxy S3 to make its first appearance at the MWC 2012 located in Spain by the end of February. The Samsung Galaxy S3 will no doubt be heralded as one of the brightest high points of the cell phone marketplace of 2012. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We will see a lot of excitement encompassing the new and breathtaking phones however the Galaxy S3 is set to be the device that just about every person is going to be raving about.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most certainly amongst the countless phone market journalists and experts, there is certainly talk about little else other than the arrival and seeing the initial precious sightings of the Samsung flagship smartphone of 2012.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;h2&gt;;Samsung Galaxy S3 specific features you might see&lt;/h2&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are lots of different thoughts hovering around regarding the style and specifications expected to accompany the Samsung Galaxy S3. A number of them are conflicting, so we’ve scraped through the junk and  provide you with what we think is a pretty good summary of what you can reasonably assume.. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NhbXN1bmdnYWxheHkwMC50dW1ibHIuY29tL3Bvc3QvMTc3NzYyNTgwMDUvc2Ftc3VuZy1nYWxheHk_" target="_blank"&gt;;Samsung Galaxy S3 Deals&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aG91Z2h0cy5jb20vbW9oYW1tZWRnb256MTAyNi9nYWxheHktczM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Samsung-Galaxy-S3&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;32gigabytes storage&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;4.65inch Hi-def display&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;1080p high-definition video&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;12MP back end camera&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Ice Cream Sandwich Android 4.0&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;A 1.8 Gigahertz quad core processor chip&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;h2&gt;;Style for the Samsung Galaxy S3&lt;/h2&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So far as aesthetics are related it happens to be very close to the Samsung Galaxy S2. On the other hand once you really think about it, it’s highly ordinary these days for brands to come across a popular style and then literally stick with it. If it ain’t broken why mend it? So maybe, when Smartphone lovers are contented with the over-all look, it’s primarily the functions and options that really mean much to these people and steer their buying decision process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;h2&gt;; Samsung Galaxy S3 is just around the corner?&lt;/h2&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Irrespective of statements of a spectacular Samsung Galaxy S3 launch in the springtime, we have reason to believe there are actually solid reasons to question that arrangement. Moreover the Samsung head of sales has openly said that they are still in the process of setting up a concrete time and date for its launch. The Samsung Galaxy S2 was launched in the US a few months later than other parts of the globe, which generated a disgruntled pack of State side shoppers. Samsung could be planning ahead to ward off this scenario again. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Samsung Galaxy S2 is considered incredibly successful, and remains the only principal threat to the iPhone 4S. They could well choose to delay the introduction of the Samsung Galaxy S3 to ensure they don’t cannibalise the formidable current product sales of the Galaxy S2. Or simply it may basically be that they want to be fully definite that they may easily unleash the Samsung Galaxy S3, going straight in featuring the Ice Cream Sandwich Operating System as opposed to Gingerbread. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of course, it might all simply be a crafty plan to change tactics and go eyeball to eyeball with the iPhone whenever it comes out in the fall. It could be considered a signal that Samsung has taken a leaf out of Apples book, and made the decision that a private, invite only, Samsung organised event would be a much more fitting and striking kick off for the Galaxy S3. Presently the iPhone 4S is without any genuine threats in the market sector but we predict the Samsung Galaxy S3 will change more or less everything. If Samsung are adjusting their game plan, then Apple will surely be looking fretfully over their shoulders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Are Samsung just about to enjoy a killer of a strategic mind game with Apple? Or do they go all out to grasp charge of the Smartphone challenge? Tell us what you believe and we’ll report the most common opinion.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>