<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2a7b33e371954c8f619478907bb9dbe2">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmVzdGFzaG9wLXR1dG9yaWFscy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;prestashop tutorial&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmVzdGFzaG9wLXR1dG9yaWFscy5jb20vMTAtdmlkZW8tcGFja2FnZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;prestashop&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; I am often asked to look at websites and tell the owners what I think of it in terms of search engine optimization. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o 	 &lt; b &gt;; Contented Scanning &lt;/ b &gt;; - look at the contented on the screen, are their related inside links being second-hand? Are images being second-hand to display text? Are header tags being worn properly ( true click, view source, and a quick &quot; find &quot; for H1, H2, H3 ) &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o 	 &lt; b &gt;; Images &lt;/ b &gt;; - hover the curser over a couple of the images, are image alt tags worn? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o 	 &lt; b &gt;; Site Maps &lt;/ b &gt;; - Going back to the URL, add sitemap. xml at the end of the URL to verify if an XML sitemap exists or not. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o 	 &lt; b &gt;; Frequently updated satisfied &lt;/ b &gt;; - Look for blogs, news sections, articles or press releases. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;DING! 2:00 minutes are over! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now that was a lot to look over in a very short 3 minutes. By looking over these elements I can make a quantity of initial suggestions on what can be completed to make the site search engine forthcoming. This very fast site analysis by no means will tell me what it will take to rank for your keyword; however it is a fantastic initial point for your on page optimization. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On page optimization is a technique that some people don't take critically. As you have seen it only takes roughly 3 minutes to analyze what needs to be fixed in order to have a search friendly website. Don't skip this step! It doesn't take long and it will benefit your search results in the future. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is ASP. NET? ASP. NET stands for Lively Server Pages. NET and is urban by Microsoft. ASP. NET is worn to create web pages and web technologies and is an integral part of Microsoft's. NET framework vision. As a member of the. NET framework, ASP. NET is a very valuable tool for programmers and developers as it allows them to build dynamic, well-off web sites and web applications using compiled languages like VB and C #. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ASP. NET is not imperfect to script languages, it allows you to make use of. NET languages like C #, J #, VB, etc. It allows developers to build very compelling applications by making use of Visual Studio, the development tool provided by Microsoft. ASP. NET is purely server - side technology. It is built on a frequent language runtime that can be worn on any Windows server to host influential ASP. NET web sites and technologies. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the early days of the Web i. e. before the release of Internet Information Services ( IIS ) in 1997, the contents of web pages were largely still. These web pages essential to be constantly, and manually, adapted. There was an pressing need to create web sites that were go-ahead and would update automatically. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Microsoft's Energetic Server Pages ( ASP ) was brought to the market to meet this need. ASP executed on the server side, with its output sent to the user's web browser, thus allowing the server to generate go-ahead web pages based on the actions of the user. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These server - side technologies are vital contributions to the development of the Web. Amazon. com, eBay. com, and lots of former popular web sites use ASP. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmVzdGFzaG9wLXR1dG9yaWFscy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;prestashop tutorial&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmVzdGFzaG9wLXR1dG9yaWFscy5jb20vMTAtdmlkZW8tcGFja2FnZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;prestashop&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>