<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b8e33cd32dc8f0a6eac8c4b9c6bd0e87">			There are several symptoms of a locally advanced cancer of the breast: a stage 3 cancer, having a size bigger two inches and lymph node metastasis; swelling on the skin, or a big, matted cluster of lymph nodes inside the armpit; or it will be stuck for the chest muscle, or ulcerating through the skin.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They are all indications the breast cancer is likely to have spread to elsewhere in your body, at least microscopically and for that reason when they are discovered, surgery isn't the first step taken. Lymph node sampling isn't necessary. You can find frequently a matter whether a diverse excision is even possible. In the event you very large breasts, it might be, but if your breasts are small, surgeons might not be able to get enough surrounding tissue out with no mastectomy. It the tumor is stuck to the chest muscle or ulcerating over the breast skin, a direct local treatment will not be feasible in any way; removing the muscle or all the skin that is ulcerated might not leave sufficient tissue to sew back together again.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dailystrength.org%2Fpeople%2F793333%2Fjournal"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.dailystrength.org/people/793333/journal&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All this generally suggests that it would be smart to start a systemic instead of local treatment, usually by using chemotherapy which is now fairly generally agreed upon in the medical community. Normally, the drugs used are Adriamycin and Cytoxan and/or Taxol or Taxotere. This can not eradicate the entire tumor, however, if it doesn't, it could possibly still do a couple of things: it can destroy the cells of cancer that have spread to numerous organs this means you will shrink the tumor size to the size which can be more easily managed with surgery or radiation. Oftentimes, chemotherapy is continued for three to four cycles and then the situation is re-evaluated. In the event the tumor has shrunk, a lumpectomy (the surgery of a small tumor or perhaps a lump); if you have no change, surgeons head for a surgical technique called mastectomy, or surgery of the breast. Even when the tumor appears to have disappeared, there might still be some cancer cells present. Most doctors always need to at least a lumpectomy then and there where the tumor where the tumor had been to see what's actually left. If your lumpectomy is clear or shows clean margins, you might be a candidate for radiotherapy. Similarly, if doctors can perform a lumpectomy and clear margins as the lump is small, that besides radiation is actually a sensible treatment. If there's still a sizable lump or perhaps a lot of cancer in the margins, your best option might be to complete a mastectomy with or without immediate breast reconstruction. In the case of an ulceration that doesn't have enough skin to sew back together, breast reconstruction have not only a cosmetic but also a medical advantage: reconstruction provides skin from another part of the body.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After lumpectomy or mastectomy, some women with stage 3 breast cancer receive high-dose chemotherapy and stem cell rescue (bone marrow transplantation). Understanding that many of these locally advanced cancers are extremely aggressive, many doctors feel that a higher dose of chemotherapy makes sense. Different hospitals have different preferences in treatment order and combinations. Most centers do chemotherapy first and many of them are able to do a mastectomy. A variety of them will consider breast conservation surgery, in the event the lump becomes small enough and they usually telephone radiation therapy. Combinations of treatments within this kind of cancer of the breast produce better response rates.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbreast-cancer-guide.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://breast-cancer-guide.net&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>