<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="570d9c325a820a7ec887ce569a0e7013">			It was ordinary prescription contact lenses that had the greatest impact on my daughter's life. Allowing her to swap her glasses for make contact with lenses in her middle teens was possibly 1 of the very best issues we have ever completed for her. Her whole character altered for the far better so when she expressed an interest in color contacts we had been far more than pleased to investigate.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J0dWdhbGVudGlsbGFzLmVzL2VzL2ItZHVhbC1jb2xvdXItY29udGFjdHMtYi1jLTY2L2R1YWwtY29sb3VyLWdyYXktY29udGFjdC1sZW5zZXMtcGFpci1wLTE4Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;;lentes de colores&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My daughter had to wear glasses from a extremely early age due to the fact she is very long sighted. She also had to wear an opaque patch over one eye for an hour a day for years to right a 'lazy eye'. The reason for the patch was to encourage the lazy eye to operate much better. It worked but it took months and months as I remember it. Neither the glasses nor the patch did anything for her self-confidence and so she spent most of her early years as a very, self-conscious mouse of a girl. This quiet character persisted into her early teens, long after the eye patch had been dispensed with.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My daughter has been interested in dance considering that she was very little and I have to say, she is fairly good at it. When it came to performances she never ever excelled because she would not use her glasses. She wasn't comfortable with wearing them on stage. However she couldn't see anything without having them and that presented very a dilemma for her. What she would have given for a pair of color contacts back then.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2x1a2VtYXJzaGFsbDEwMjMuZG11c2ljLm5ldC9qb3VybmFsLzEzMjA1OA__" target="_blank"&gt;;lentes de colores&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We decided to attempt her out with make contact with lenses as soon as she was old adequate and are we glad we did. She changed literally overnight. She became more confident and outspoken. No longer did she suffer at the hands of the bullies in school due to the fact now she had 'attitude'. Her schoolwork improved and so did her dance performances, rather drastically also. I stood back in awe at the difference those tiny speak to lenses had created.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;She doesn't use color speak to lenses quite often but when she does they can make a very dramatic impact on her look. She occasionally wears them when she goes out in the evening and wants to make an impression.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b3J0dWdhbGVudGlsbGFzLmVzL2VzL2ItZHVhbC1jb2xvdXItY29udGFjdHMtYi1jLTY2L2R1YWwtY29sb3VyLWdyYXktY29udGFjdC1sZW5zZXMtcGFpci1wLTE4Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;;lentes de colores&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My daughter is now studying medicine at university and she is carrying out really well indeed. I believe that make contact with lenses are at least partly responsible for this success even though sometimes you can catch her utilizing her glasses when studying, possibly simply because it tends to make her look like a far more severe student.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>