<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2c58b011b25e050cf2f7136b7f9a3306">			Due to Casio's reputation for reliability, each ladies Casio Baby-G BG-191-1B2ER comes complete with a 2 year Casio guarantee.&lt;br /&gt;Women thrive on novelty and for them accessories hold as much importance as their clothes. From earrings and watches to pendants and anklets, everything has to be in coordination with the outfit. With the distinctive and alluring looks, ladies ceramic watches are an example of one such accessory that no style conscious woman would ever do without.If you are planning to gift your lady a ceramic watch this season, you will come across an unbounded range of watches but choosing one that will compliment your lady's style could turn out to be a tedious task.Hence, I bring to you some tried and tested tips that will assist you while you select a watch for your special lady:Type of Watch:When choosing the type of watch, you have two options to choose from - quartz or mechanical. The quartz watch, on one hand, has under its cover reliability and durability, but at the same time this watch does not call for much expenditure and maintenance efforts. The mechanical watch, on the other hand, involves a touch of engineering plus a great craftsmanship. If taken care of, these watches are known for their durability and are capable of becoming heirlooms.Shape of the Watch:There are a range of shapes available but before you pick the tab, find out what's your lady's style. For instance, if she is fond of the retro style, you can present her a watch with a rectangular dial; if she is less towards feminism, you can present her one with a square shape, and in case you want to gift her something that will always remain in style, the round dial is the ultimate choice.Band of the Watch:While talking about the band, there are two options available - a strap or a bracelet. The bracelet, on one hand, grants a formal appeal while the strap lends a more contemporary appearance. Available in a range of materials, from leather to rexine, the ceramic watch brings with it unequaled style.A ceramic watch is simple yet elegant, a style and not a fashion. So go ahead and gift your lady her present for the season, a present that she'll hold dear and treasure for life.&lt;br /&gt;Ceramic watches are the unsurpassed options that can replace your outmoded watch with style and elegance. However, you might be in a double mind when it comes to ceramic watches, since ceramic is an extremely delicate material; but with an advancement in technology it can be converted into a scratch-resistant and durable material, thus making it suitable for ladies ceramic watches.Let us now take a look at a few pointers we might find helpful while purchasing a ceramic watch, so that we don't end up tossing and tumbling between the ranges of choices.•PriceThe price bracket for a ceramic watch is as wide as the distance between the sky and the ocean. On one hand, we have the classiest of watches, which of course, cost a handsome amount but are accompanied by unrivalled sophistication. Whether she chooses gold, sliver, or platinum, a watch can accent her clothing and figure perfectly.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbndhdGNoem9uZS5jb20vcm9sZXgtbWlsZ2F1c3MtcmVwbGljYS1jLTMwMF8zMDYv" target="_blank"&gt;rolex milgauss replica &lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbndhdGNoem9uZS5jb20vcm9sZXgtYWlyLWtpbmctc3MtcmVwbGljYS1jLTMwMF8zODQv" target="_blank"&gt;rolex air king&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbndhdGNoem9uZS5jb20vcm9sZXgtcmVwbGljYS1jLTMwMC8_" target="_blank"&gt;rolex watches&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>