<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="cdc22a6c08e331b5b48201a454284795">			It is then become the basic reason why some men actually want to make the size of the penises to be bigger. Some men do not want to pass a process that will take so much time to make the dimensions of their penises to become bigger. Therefore they are happy to take much money to get your house a kind of surgery to their penises. Although the surgery can never be hurt, the recover might get some times and could also cause some pain. The disadvantage of this surgery is that there is a possibility that the penis might break because the surgery is a process which is not natural in any way.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are actually two other ways which is often used for you who definitely are afraid to undergo any penis surgery but really want to enlarge penis. The first way that is done is pumping penis simply by using a device which is called penis pump. From the name of it, it is sure that you can pump the penis on this device regularly in everyday until you get the very best size of penis in accordance with your opinion. The process in generating penis bigger by carrying it out is of course organic because actually, the pump is simply a device to help making the penis bigger. Since it is quite natural, time is of training needed. It means that the size will probably be bigger and bigger gradually. That is why, for a better effect, regular pumping is essential.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The second way which is suggested so that you can make the size of one's penis bigger is by consuming some penis enhancement pills. It is actually a means is done as the support on the first way to increase penis. When you are accomplishing the pumping process when you are consuming the penis development pills regularly, it will of course be faster that you see the result with the whole process which you have been doing. Now you do  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hlcmJhbGZvcm1lbi5jb20vaW5mby1uZW9zaXpleGwucGhw" target="_blank"&gt;;how to enlarge penis&lt;/a&gt;;  without undergoing any penis surgery which seems to be too scary to do. After the result can be seen, it is sure that you will able to gain more attention for any beautiful woman who becomes your sex partner..		</conversation>	</conversations></author>