<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="15c6583b31327ac5a123f8aff80a3256">			There are some people that are just more comfortable taking a shower rather than taking a bath. Walk in tubs are a great option for those who suffer from limited physical movement, but there is also the option of installing a walk in shower to provide essentially the same safety and ease of accessibility.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;In the last decade more and more homes were built with bathtub/shower combinations, but with the rise in the retiring baby boomer generation, these obsolete accommodations are beginning to disappear and being replaced with newer and safer alternatives.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;The most notable feature of a walk in shower is that they sit flush with the floor of your bathroom. This eliminates the hazard of having to step up into the shower enclosure and thus removes the fear and anxiety of tripping or falling and risking injury.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;These showers can be installed in any existing bathroom and come in a extensive variety of shapes and sizes and with an ample selection of accessories to enhance the safety and enjoyment of showering. There are many options in just choosing the type of showerhead to be installed, from a hand held showerhead, pulsating/massaging showerheads, rain showerheads, or multiple heads. An additional option with many of these showers is a shower valve with scald protection that can be set to a maximum temperature to protect against possible scalding. Many of these showers can be outfitted with comfortable seats for anyone that has difficulty with standing in a shower for any length of time, some can even be purchased with padded seats for additional comfort.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;These walk in showers can be something as simple as a chrome enclosed area with sliding glass doors to something as elegant as a &quot;wet room&quot; with steam shower capabilities. Your imagination or your budget is the only constraints when deciding how you want to design your own personal walk in shower.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;If you are dealing with the reality of physical limitations or if you have a loved one that is dealing with this situation a walk in shower is definitely an option that can be explored. Additionally, if you are a caregiver and the stress and strain of caring for the needs of an individual is making life rather difficult, this is an option that can be considered.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;As everyone ages it becomes increasingly important to be able to attend to their own personal and very private hygiene, with the introduction of walk in showers and walk in bathtubs more people dealing with the reality of limited physical capabilities, will be able to sustain their ability to remain in their homes and live with dignity and independence.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nationwide-mobility.co.uk%2Fwalk-in-baths%2Fsimplicity-walk-in-bath.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bwalk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nationwide-mobility.co.uk/walk-in-baths/simplicity-walk-in-bath.php&quot;&gt;;walk&lt;/a&gt;; in baths&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nationwide-mobility.co.uk%2Fultimate-walk-in-shower-bath.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bwalk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nationwide-mobility.co.uk/ultimate-walk-in-shower-bath.php&quot;&gt;;walk&lt;/a&gt;; in shower&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e8f99c640234f33d6767c0c9fbf08ceb">			Taking a nice warm bath can be very soothing, but for people with mobility related problems, a relaxing bath can be very stressful and dangerous. Having the proper safety equipment at home for an elderly or a disabled person is very important to make them feel secure and give them some independence. A bath tub chair lift can allow them to once again enjoy the comfort of a warm bath.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Bathroom: Hazardous for those with Mobility Problems
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Whether it involves bathing in the tub or taking a shower, bathroom is a dangerous place for those who are physically challenged.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Because it is low to the ground, entering and exiting the bathtub is difficult. You have to lean on the wall and the tub edges so you can sit on it and stand once you are done bathing. Those who refuse to use the bathtub take showers instead, which is also dangerous and can result to fall. The tub floor is very slippery that when you fall, serious injury is possible. Besides the bathtub, the shiny floors, water, and electrical appliances in the bathroom add to the hazards.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Bath Lifts: Practical Solutions for Bathroom Hazards
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Even if you hire someone to take care of your elder or disabled relative, investing in a bath lift is very helpful.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Bath lifts are medical equipment for the home used to lower and raise an individual into and from the bathtub. These specially designed seats fit into a standard bathtub with no drilling, screwing, or remodeling necessary. Easily movable, you can bring this with you when visiting relatives or going on vacation.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Users can experience again a comfortable bath using Aquatec Beluga Bath Tub Chair Lift. It has a comfortable seating surface and a reclining backrest for additional comfort. This practical lift chair for bathtubs allows your elders to get in and out of the tub easily and painlessly. This scissor-style device has a durable frame that can lower you to 2.5 inches from the bottom of the tub.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;The machine is run by lithium-ion rechargeable batteries. The batteries can lift the user up to 22 times before it becomes discharged. Getting stuck will not be a problem in case it runs out of power; it will lower the user only if it recognizes that it has enough power to lift the user once he or she is finished bathing. The reclining backrest gives comfort and allows for easy hair rinsing to the user.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Since almost all models of bathtub chair lifts need not screwing or drilling, powerful suction cups are included in the design to secure the chair to the tub's floor.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;You can choose from several models. If your tub is smaller, or if the person who will use the chair is heavier, there are options available for you.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nationwide-mobility.co.uk%2Fmermaid-walk-in-bath.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bbathing"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nationwide-mobility.co.uk/mermaid-walk-in-bath.php&quot;&gt;;bathing&lt;/a&gt;; aids&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nationwide-mobility.co.uk%2Fwalk-in-baths%2Fsimplicity-walk-in-bath.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bmobility"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nationwide-mobility.co.uk/walk-in-baths/simplicity-walk-in-bath.php&quot;&gt;;mobility&lt;/a&gt;; bath&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="c8b40ffebd68c2b9fdac0b5380304b91">			A standard tub that is installed for disabled individuals is going to naturally include a walk-in bath bench on the inside. As a matter of fact, this is one piece of equipment that any walk in tub is sure to include. On the other hand, not all of us are able to install a new bathtub in order to provide for those in our household who are dealing with limited mobility. At times, we may need to install some kind of bath transfer bench, either retrofitted to our existing tub or perhaps one that will just help them to transfer into the bathtub much easier. Here are some options that are available in a simple walkin bath bench, and some other items to consider.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;If you're going to install a new walk in bathtub, the bench should be included as a standard piece of equipment. At times, it will be to the side of the door, which many people find convenient, because it is easy to make the transfer from the floor area to the bench. At other times, however, the bench may be straight away inside of the door and this is generally the case whenever you are installing the bathtub that is a rather tight fit. In this second type of bench configuration, the door will generally swing out but when it is to the side, it may swing in.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;If you are retrofitting an existing bathtub with some type of a bath transfer bench, this is also something that may take a little bit of consideration as well. Many bath seats easily fit over an existing tub enclosure and can provide you with a convenient place to sit, as well as making the transfer into the tub area a little bit easier. There are also some swinging benches which are available that can help you to transfer into the bathtub effortlessly.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Of course, the bench may not be all that is necessary in order to make this room as safe as possible. After all, many slip and fall accidents occur within the bathroom and you would want to ensure that your stability was safeguarded at all times. This can often be done with wall-mounted grab bars, either stationary or perhaps on hinges. By having these grab bars available, you help to ensure that everybody who has to use the tub is going to be stable when making the transfer, as well as helping them to get up and down off of the bench.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;Don't simply choose the first walk in bath bench that you see when it is included in one of these tubs. As a matter of fact, it helps to look at all of your options ahead of time in order to ensure that you are getting exactly what you need. A bath transfer bench, for example, is often a convenient item whenever you are not going to install a new tub into the area. A regular bench, however, can provide you with stability and peace of mind whenever using the tub in an area of the home that can be rather hazardous.
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nationwide-mobility.co.uk%2Fwalk-in-baths%2Fsimplicity-walk-in-bath.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bwalk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nationwide-mobility.co.uk/walk-in-baths/simplicity-walk-in-bath.php&quot;&gt;;walk&lt;/a&gt;; in bath tub&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nationwide-mobility.co.uk%2Fwalk-in-baths%2Fsimplicity-walk-in-bath.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bwalk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nationwide-mobility.co.uk/walk-in-baths/simplicity-walk-in-bath.php&quot;&gt;;walk&lt;/a&gt;; in baths&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>