<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="44051b1e94da953126f7871b83bb2000">			&lt;strong&gt;;Learn How to Relax Easily&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Stress is a huge concern at the moment. People are worried about their jobs, their future and their assets. Sleep challenges, irritability and feeling down are more common than ever before. While many seek solace in medication, others are investigating natural healing methods as a means of self empowerment.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Reiki therapy could be the answer you have been looking for&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you could do with more energy, would like to relax more and sleep better then Reiki could be the solution for you. Reiki is being used in mainstream medicine and by the corporate world to reduce stress and promote a sense of well being.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Why Reiki has such a broad appeal&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reiki is a gentle and non invasive form of energy therapy. There is no removal of clothing in Reiki. Reiki healing is non manipulative, involving a sequence of hand positions on or above the body.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;How can I experience this energy?&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The two ways to experience Reiki are to have a Reiki treatment from a Reiki practitioner or to learn how to do Reiki for you by attending a &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tL3JlaWtpMS1jb3Vyc2UtaW4tZHVibGlu" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki 1 course&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Is Reiki difficult to learn?&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The beauty of Reiki is that it is very easy to learn and very easy to give to yourself after the two day Reiki class. Reiki is something that everyone can learn how to do.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Do I have to believe in Reiki for it to work?&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is not necessary to know anything about Reiki, or to have a strong belief about whether it will work to see results after giving you Reiki. Sceptical people often remark on great benefits following Reiki treatments.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;What is Involved in learning Reiki&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reiki is taught over two days.During the two days, you are taught how to give yourself Reiki and you are also shown how you could give friends and family Reiki chair or table treatments.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Upcoming Reiki 1 training in Dublin with former nurse Angela Gorman&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Stillorgan Park Hotel, 26th and 27th of May&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Angela has been teaching Reiki in Ireland since 1996. She has a very practical approach. She presents the information in an easy to understand and captivating way. Angela is dedicated to high standards of Reiki training and co-founded Reiki Federation Ireland.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Limited Time Special Discount on Angela’s upcoming Reiki course on the 26th and 27th May
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A Reiki 1 course with Angela is normally € 250.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a limited time your investment is only €175.&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those who book also receive a bonus gift of Angela’s CD Ultimate Reiki, along with one Free Entry Ticket to one of Angela’s Reiki Get-Togethers in 2012 Angela gives everyone who attends a Reiki course manual and a Reiki certificate at the end of day 2.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;For more information on Angela’s upcoming course click on the link below:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tL3JlaWtpLTEtY291cnNlLWluLWR1Ymxpbi1zcGVjaWFsLWRpc2NvdW50" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thehealingpages.com%2Freiki-1-course-in-dublin-special-discount"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.thehealingpages.com/reiki-1-course-in-dublin-special-discount&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tL3JlaWtpLTEtY291cnNlLXRvLXJlbGF4LWFuZC1yZWR1Y2Utc3RyZXNz" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki 1 courses in Dublin&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;, &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki classes in Dublin&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f1f5b773309353335e102476caa4e4af">			Reiki therapy is often remarked upon for the benefits sceptics receive following Reiki treatments.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reiki energy is not driven by conscious thought. It is directed by the deeper mind, the subconscious aspect of a person.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you breathe or when your heart beats, are you thinking about it? Are you controlling these important functions with your conscious mind? It is ironic perhaps that most adults assume we need to be thinking in order for things to happen. Yet, when it comes to important matters like breathing and blood flow, a part of our nervous system operating below conscious thought is in control.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;During Reiki treatments, the practitioner is like a conduit through which the Reiki energy flows. This energy is not the practitioner’s personal energy. &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tL2FkdmFuY2VkLXByYWN0aXRpb25lcg__" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki practitioners&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;; have been taught how to facilitate the flow of free energy which surrounds all life. In essence Reiki practitioners are just vessels for this energy.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the Reiki practitioner places their hands on the client’s body, the client is now in receipt of the energy. It flows exactly where it need to flow, being directed by the subconscious mind of the client. The flow of Reiki energy and where it goes is not directed by the practitioner.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reiki works on unconscious patients who are not consciously aware. Reiki has also been used in operating rooms during surgery, when patients are under the influence of anaesthesia.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reiki was used in the operating room of the &lt;strong&gt;;Columbia Presbyterian Medical Center in New York City&lt;/strong&gt;;. The New York Times magazine reported about the use of Reiki during open-heart surgeries and heart transplantations performed by Dr. Mehmet Oz. None of the 11 heart patients treated with Reiki by Reiki Master Julie Motz experienced the usual postoperative depression, the bypass patients had no postoperative pain or leg weakness; and the transplant patients experienced no organ rejection.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reiki also works effectively on animals who have no conscious belief system about Reiki. They appear to have a deep understanding about what healing energy can do for them.
&lt;br /&gt;;When a person attends a Reiki treatment it is understandable that there may be doubts about the effectiveness of Reiki and some sceptical thoughts regarding potential results. The good news is that a client can be sceptical and report benefits afterwards. A deep acceptance for change or a healing is what enhances the Reiki session.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Likewise, a person who states consciously that they believe in Reiki, may be the very person who on a deeper level has a resistance to change. This resistance will inhibit the effectiveness of a &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tL3RoZS1yZWlraS10cmVhdG1lbnQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki treatment&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;;as Reiki energy always flows according to the deep acceptance levels of the client.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In my own personal experience of giving Reiki treatments, I can say that people always get from Reiki energy what they need in the moment. We all have free will and Reiki moves according to its unique rhythm.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;For more information on Reiki visit:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thehealingpages.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.thehealingpages.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tL3JlaWtpLWhlYWxpbmctdGhlcmFweS1vbi1zY2VwdGljcw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki Therapy on Sceptics in Ireland&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;, &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVoZWFsaW5ncGFnZXMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Reiki Treatments in Ireland&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>