<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e11fe17c499c6ec409aba1c4e21fabe8">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZXN0bGVzc2xlZ3NndWlkZS5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Restless leg Syndrome&lt;/a&gt;; or RLS is a dysfunction that occurs in primarily adults of middle age or older. It brings about a need in individuals to move their legs to stop the uncomfortable sensations that occur. The effects of restless leg Syndrome can range from minor to chronic and the cause is hard to establish in most patients. pressure is known to make the symptoms worse, as does withdrawal from sedatives and use of certain medicines like neuroleptics, lithium, lime scale channel blockers, and medicines that contain caffeine. Restless leg syndrome can make it difficult to sleep, sit still while traveling, or any activity which requires you to sit for long periods of time. The urge to move your legs is preceded by discomfort, but walking and shifting the legs generally relieves the uncomfortable feelings overall. The disruption of rest patterns brought about by RLS can cause symptomatic difficulties together with anxiety, depression, daytime drowsiness, States of confusion, and slower ability to think productively. Restless leg Affliction is passed down by family members frequently, but an actual hereditary link or abnormality has not been identified. There are no current tests that can establish restless leg Predicament in individuals, although iron inadequacies perhaps a common symptom to look for in patients. Treatment is geared towards techniques or medicines that help lessen stress in the Muscle groups. Low doses of narcotics, pramipexole, or ropinirole can be effectively used to control RLS symptoms in some people. If sleep is being disrupted, the doctor may prescribe drugs that assist with getting proper rest for some patients. Additionally the use of therapeutic massage, warm baths, and low effect stretching exercises may helpful in combating the symptoms of restless leg Malady. Although uncomfortable, restless leg Affliction is not dangerous, life threatening, nor is it a sign of anything more significant for individuals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For More Info:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZXN0bGVzc2xlZ3NndWlkZS5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;; Restless Legs Syndrome &lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>