<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="95598bb3adc581428765243723231d50">			You should Wheaton, IL consult a metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof contractor to ask them whether you require a permit because even if they don't know off hand they will certainly know the correct people to contact. The closing paragraph of the technical bulletin states that, it may, in some cases, be prudent to consider lightning protection. Having the old shingles in Wheaton, IL removed and replaced with several layers will work out to be slightly more expensive but laying more shingles down on existing shingles can look untidy if the original layer are damaged in any way. The best bet really is to have all existing shingles removed and new ones added in their place in Wheaton, IL. It is fine to have three layers of shingle codes but you should check this is the case with your local building permit people and you should make sure that your metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof and the rest of the structure have the strength to cope with the extra weight. In Wheaton, IL some areas it may be necessary to obtain a permit to re-shingle your metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof at all, but without the required permit your new metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof is not legitimate. It Wheaton, IL really is important that you make sure you know how many layers of metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof are allowed on your roof. A metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof contractor will know exactly how many layers of metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof are allowed in your area for your building but it is normal that you will be permitted up to three layers of shingles. Finding out how many layers of metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof are allowed is only the first step in having extra metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof added or replaced on your metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof in Wheaton, IL. Once you have discovered how many layers of metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof are allowed the next decision you should make is whether you will have the existing shingles completely removed to make way for two or three new layers or whether you will have another layer of shingles placed on top of the existing layer. A in Wheaton, IL lightning protection system provides for a continuous conductor from earth to sky so that the electrical charge is furnished an obvious path through which to flow, thereby reducing the risk to resistive construction materials and human life. Metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof do not attract lightning. The consequence of a lightning strike on a structure can be minimized if materials are electrically conductive, Wheaton, IL thus minimizing fire and explosion damage to the building and occupants. Because metal roof, shingle roof, tile roof, flat roof, and cedar shake roof is both an electrical conductor, and a noncombustible material, the risks associated with its use and behavior during a lightning event make it the most desirable construction material available.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D_Tb4Q2DYU18"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_Tb4Q2DYU18&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>