<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2a41edc673ade1f5d92d7948250b0107">			The Do’s When Using a Baby Carrier&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always remember at all times to check the seams, buckles and straps before using the baby carrier. There is a built in pockets in the carriers for your keys, coins and etc. so put them there not where your baby is. Baby carriers will only provide a small amount of protection from sun so put some sun care lotion or powder for your baby. Forever attend to your babies at all times in the carrier in a carrier. Babies are sometimes left sitting in frame backpacks, which can topple over when bumped or when the baby moves. This is the cause of a large subset of baby carrier accidents. Some carriers can also be used as harnesses for a supermarket trolley, to tie a child to a chair and for other purposes. Always ensure that a carrier is not a five point harness, and that the piece of furniture you attach your child to might not be inherently steady.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Don’ts When Using a Baby Carrier&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do not put pointless item that can only add a great weight inside the carrier. Do not put your car keys, wallets, coin purse, handkerchiefs can become hazards when these things will go around and end up near your baby's face or poke into fragile flesh. Also don’t cook with heat, or handle hot liquids, while wearing your baby on your front or hip. If your baby is on your back, be careful. Do not let the tail of your sling hanging because long tails can catch fire on gas stoves and fires. They can also get caught in doors. Don't use a baby carrier while you're in a moving car. Your baby can easily be thrown from your arms and a carrier provides a baby with no protection whatsoever. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Learn more about baby slings and carriers at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.babyslingsandcarriers.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.babyslingsandcarriers.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;; where you can find out all about baby carriers backpacks and how you can purchase the good quality!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.babyslingsandcarriers.co.uk%2Fbaby-back-carriers%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.babyslingsandcarriers.co.uk/baby-back-carriers/&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.babyslingsandcarriers.co.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.babyslingsandcarriers.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>