<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e6ec836efafa09b9db07e7dddbef9190">			How to Save Time and Money Generating Leads&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We all like saving time and money on things that need to be done but no one likes to do. This article shows you how to do this on b2b lead generation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wouldn't it be nice to have sales leads line up at the door waiting their turn at the close without any effort on your part? Sound too good to be true? Perhaps it is, but we may have the next best thing. Read on.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How much does your sales leads generation cost? How much time does it take to acquire each lead? As you already know, business to business lead generation isn't cheap or easy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Qualify Your Leads&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And not all leads are created equal. What are you doing about qualified lead generation? Lead qualification, if you're not already doing it, may be the single most critical factor in improving your pipeline. And lead scoring may well be the most important method for achieving this.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lead scoring takes a look not only at lead-supplied information about company size, market segment and lead title, but also takes a look at lead behavior. Do they visit the website numerous times? What links do they click? Do they click on links in emails? Do they reply to emails? In short, do they behave like a hot lead?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What do you do with hot leads? Of course, you give them a first class ticket to sales. But what do you do with all of the warm and cold leads? Does your sales team struggle with these? Does this group become a bottomless pit of effort with little or no return on your investment?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Properly segregated, warm and cold leads can be nurtured until they become hot. That's where you need a nurturing team to take care of this. Let your sales force concentrate on closing the hot leads.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lead Generation Outsourcing&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While lead qualification and lead scoring are great moves to make in your lead generation programs, outsourcing the entire operation may save you far more time and money in the long run. Think about it. Technology lead generation isn't easy. Handing this off to a team of experts can relieve your staff of that critical, but painful chore. That leaves you to concentrate on what your in-house team does best.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a number of lead generating companies to choose from. Such lead generation services frequently offer a wide variety of services, from turnkey b2b lead generation to event promotion services, b2b sales outsourcing and sales management consulting. You owe it to your company to check out the possibilities and to assess which set of services would best suit your situation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dhbGxpbnNpZGUuY29tL3Bvc3QtNTIyMjYyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;lead-generation-company07&lt;/a&gt;;, [url=]lead-generation-companies80[/url], &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aWtpLmNvbS9lbi9lbWlsLW1ja2lubmV5LTExKzQ0Nzc5Ni9wb3N0L2xlYWQtZ2VuZXJhdGlvbi1jb21wYW55NTMrMTMxMTY5NDQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;lead-generation-companies03&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>