<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="9ad9d20596067c1816585d7c9509a74e">			There are many different types of surface protection tape. You can get glass protective film, carpet protection tape and rolls of low tack protection tapes; with each protecting surfaces from different types of dirt or damage. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Glass protective film will protect windows, mirrors, cupboards, work tops, window frames and metals; and carpet protection tape will protect your carpets. They are low-adhesive, easy to use and serve a multitude or purposes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Why not use to:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;DIY&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1.	Protect glass when painting or varnishing window frames, mirrors or photo frames.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2.	Protect carpets when painting. Dust sheets allow paint to seep through and are a trip hazard. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3.	Or use specialist wooden surface protection tapes to protect wooden floorings.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4.	Keep kitchen work surfaces free from paint and scratches when decorating.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5.	Protect surfaces from construction debris.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6.	Protect surfaces from tools and ladder scratches.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7.	Protect from water damage if plumbing could result in a flood.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8.	Prevent scratches when fitting a picture frame or stainless steel fittings.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Pets&lt;/strong&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9.	Protect carpets from pet hair.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10.	Keep floorings free from spillages made my pets.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;11.	Prevent your pet from making a mess of its eating area. Use flooring protective tapes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;12.	Protect floorings when training toilet training your pet.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Moving house&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;13.	Prevent moving furniture and boxes from scratching surfaces and flooring.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;14.	Protect furniture and possessions from getting scratched in the move.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;15.	Stop the removal men from dirtying your floorings and carpets.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;16.	Seal boxes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;17.	Pack small or easily lost non-breakable items. Wrap them all together in a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdGlja3lwcm9kdWN0cy5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;glass protective film&lt;/a&gt;; before packing them away. The films are transparent or translucent so you will be able to see what’s inside easily and it will prevent them getting lost in big boxes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;18.	Prevent spillages at a moving in party.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Everyday&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;19.	Stop carpets or furnishings from fading with UV protective tapes. If you have a skylight or conservatory this could be particularly useful.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;20.	Keep floorings and windows free from pen marks caused by children.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;21.	Protect tables from spillages at a children’s party
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;22.	Prevent tables from getting marks on them from children’s art materials.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;23.	Use to cheaply laminate paper to make place mats - get children to design their own for fun mealtimes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;24.	Keep carpets dirt-free in snowy or muddy weather.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;25.	Protect wooden flooring from muddy or snowy weather.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;26.	Keep kitchen surfaces clean when helping your children to cook.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;27.	Reduce the sun’s glare or heat through conservatory windows.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;28.	Add colour to plain glass.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;29.	Increase privacy.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;30.	 Make cut-out window stickers using coloured glass protective films.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;31.	Prevent windows from shattering when removing or in extreme weather. Use shatter-resisting glass protection.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Outdoors&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;32.	 Protect your car’s alloys or windows from paint or wax. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;33.	Protect garage surfaces from damage from tools.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;34.	Prevent people from getting splinters on benches. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;35.	No anti-freeze left for the morning? Simply use stick on window surface protection tape.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zdGlja3lwcm9kdWN0cy5jby51ay9nbGFzcy1wcm90ZWN0aW9uLXRhcGUtLS1yZXZlcnNlLXdvdW5kLS0tZnJlZS11ay1kZWxpdmVyeS05NzQtcC5hc3A_" target="_blank"&gt;;Surface protection tapes&lt;/a&gt;; have a huge variety of uses. Glass protection film, carpet protection tape and other protective tapes come in a wide range of types, each with many various purposes. It is therefore always handy to have some surface protection tape in your home, just in case.		</conversation>		<conversation id="edc8dfd1d0f3d6ba44bf7f6ca0fe47c2">			Job websites can dramatically vary. Some job platforms will only advertise jobs in a particular area, others will specialise in a particular job sector or only advertise certain job positions and some will simply cram in as many job vacancies as they possibly can, making it very difficult for those looking for a particular career. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When searching for a job in a particular field such as sales, its a good idea to select a job platform that specialises in your desired area. Recruitment agencies are often a good option as they have the ability to do all the hard work of searching and applying for you. Simply by informing your local recruitment agency of all your experience and qualifications could result in an interview for your ideal job within just a couple of days. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Alternatively, recruitment agencies also have all the latest vacancies posted on their website, allowing you to search for your ideal job and let the agency know when you find something youre interested in. Job fields such as sales, have a wide variety of jobs to choose from, therefore its advisable to choose a specialist recruitment agency to avoid being constantly bombarded with emails and phone calls, informing you of jobs that are of no interest to you. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recruitment agencies also offer both permanent and temporary positions. Perhaps you have just finished school or university and are looking for something temporary whilst you continue to search for your desired career. You may find that you enjoy your temporary position and wish to take on your role permanently or take on further training in the field. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On the other hand, perhaps you are looking for a career change. Recruitment agencies can help you discover the ideal career that matches your personality and skills. Many people are stuck in jobs they no longer enjoy, unaware that they have the ability and experience to begin a new and exciting career.  For example, you could have a large amount of knowledge and experience in advertising and marketing, therefore you may find that you would enjoy media &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3JlY3J1aXRtZW50YWdlbmN5LmNvbS9SZXNvdXJjZXMvUmVzb3VyY2VDYXQuYXNweD91aWQ9Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;;sales work&lt;/a&gt;;. With the constant increase in technology, there are hundreds of media sales jobs available. For example, you could be working in digital radio, for a satellite television channel, or perhaps for a company that streams audio and video on the internet.Alternatively, you may have experience in retail and find that a position in retail sales would really suit your personality. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recruitment agencies can be equally as useful for employers. When advertising a particular vacancy on a job website, you will find yourself having to waste hours of time and energy trawling through applications and CVs, attempting to find candidates suitable for interview.  A recruitment agency will conduct these time consuming tasks for you, presenting you with the best few candidates to choose from, saving you valuable time management and also reducing advertising costs. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With many recruitment agencies, employers also have the option to put staff on a trial period, testing out their abilities and enabling them to discover if theyre the right candidate for the position.  An agency will also take care of all matters related to the candidates salary and any tax issues that may arise.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Looking for your ideal job or staff doesnt need to be a difficult task. When searching for your new staff member or career, make sure your local specialist recruitment agency is your first port of call. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxlc3JlY3J1aXRtZW50YWdlbmN5LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Sales Recruitment Agency&lt;/a&gt;; is an online job platform targeted at the sales industry. For those looking for a career in sales they can help you find your ideal job. Sales Recruitment Agency can also help employers find the candidate that perfectly fits their requirements. Visit their website today to search for jobs in sales or advertise your latest vacancy.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>