<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="909682083bed64044495e019216a5ff6">			It doesn't have to be difficult to travel affordably. Booking a cheap international flight is very possible with enough time and research. In fact, if you are smart and really look, it is almost harder to find expensive deals than affordable deals. So how do you get these flights? Where should you begin your search? To get the best deal possible, what should you be doing? Here are some ways you can save money when you travel internationally.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be flexible. If you can, be flexible with where you fly from. The drive is worth it becuase you are likely to save money. You are most likely to save hundreds of dollars if you can remain flexible even for a short time. It is often cheaper to take short connector flights on small planes in rural areas into a larger airport. In order to gain your business these smaller airports can often offer great deals. Don't be closed minded about about where you fly from. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;See if you can find cheaper flights online. Watch for &amp;quot;web only&amp;quot; deals online. All you need to do is look around. The most popular web travel portals are Expedia, Travelocity and Priceline but there are others out there. Some of the smaller portals will give the best deals because they are trying to get more people to trust them. Be bold when seeking better deals. The amount of time you dedicate to finding the best deal could mean a better deal for you at a greater savings.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you see the price of your ticket going down after you've already purchased yours all you need to do is contact the airline for a refund. So many people can get cheap international flights just by asking for a refund so that they end up paying the same price as other people do. If they won't refund, threaten to cancel and repurchase. There are many discounts if you just ask for them. Being too scared to ask for the best rate is how many people end up losing money. Finding cheap international flights does not have to be difficult. Once you learn where to look and what to look for, finding affordable international flights can be easy. Remember, there are always things you can do to save money while traveling. Things like not checking your luggage and flying standby are ways to save money while traveling. The key to getting the best deal that you can possibly get is to be patient and willing to do the work. Without doing the work, you will almost certainly pay too much for your travel plans. You won't be able to fully enjoy your vacation if you drain your bank account to get there.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb21wYXJldGhlbWFya2V0aG9saWRheXMub3JnLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;compare the market&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="4fa69a9894d2ea553ac60386b572f5bc">			If you think that it is hard to track your money on any sort of regular basis, managing a budget can help. Life is always becoming more complicated and it isn't hard to lose track of all of your various expenses and purchases. You can regain control of your finances and money by using the budgeting tips you are about to read.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Petrol (gas) can be a problematic drain upon your budget as the cost of gas is always rising even for the most fuel efficient vehicles. The best way to lower how much you spend at the gas pump is to drive less and, believe it or not, it's easier than it sounds. If you make a lot of trips to the store for just one or two things, you are wasting time and gas that could be used on just one trip for many things. Try going shopping just once a week to cut down on all of those extra trips. Rather than driving back and forth from work by yourself, carpool or use a different kind of transportation. In terms of the shorter distances you need to traverse, why not walk or ride a bike? At least a few dollars every week can be saved if you actually think about your transportation options. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you set up your budget make sure you spend some time thinking about what things in your life are actually necessities and which you can go without. When you have kids for example, you need to clothe them but you don't need to clothe them in expensive designer clothing. Every person needs to eat but you do not need to go out to a restaurant three times a week. You might need a vehicle but you don't need to buy the most expensive make or model to go to work or run a few errands. This does not mean, though, that you can't have any luxuries at all. It's just a good idea to figure out which things you can reduce or get rid of as well as to think of how valuable they really are to you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One type of expense that drains the budgets of many people with them hardly realizing it is the kind of item you buy at convenience stores, delis and cafes. In particular, beverages such as coffee (especially expensive designer drinks) and bottled water. If you have a coffee maker at home, you can save a lot by making coffee yourself and carrying it in a mug or thermos. Another money saver is buying a water filter for your sinks so that you don't have to purchase bottled water at the store. It's possible to save as much as a hundred dollars in your budget every month by cutting down on buying coffee and bottled water outside of the home. To sum up, it is harder to manage money than it often looks. When you begin to pay attention, you might see that money slips easily away from you. This is the reason it is so vital that you keep a budget. The budgeting tips we've looked at in this article can help you do this, so you can gain control of your finances.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy40M3RoaW5ncy5jb20vZW50cmllcy92aWV3LzU1MTY0ODM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Ways to Travel Internationally for Less&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>