<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="4f6d9b521c27a06930ac1c29a88caa9b">			 christian louboutin: &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Is no exaggeration to say that the past five thousand years of human history, our planet is the gradual process of urbanization. Today, the pace of urbanization, more and more quickly. If a hundred years ago overlooking the Earth from orbit, we will only see the population of more than 16 million lights flashing together the region, including Shanghai and Beijing. Now, the space shuttle Atlantis astronauts were able to see more than 450 million people of the city. These cities is the increasing urbanization of the world's economy, government, culture and technology center.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; humans in 2007, crossed a huge threshold. In that year, the first time in human history, the urban population accounted for more than half of the total population. By 2050, urban population will reach 70% of the total population. This means that each year the Earth will increase seven to New York.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; for the unprecedented process of urbanization, we should be proud of. It embodies our economic and social development, for China and other developing countries in particular. However, urbanization also the infrastructure of the Earth brought great pressure. This sense of urgency, every insight have a profound experience.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the last 10 years, this sense of urgency to the more strongly, I believe we all know the root of the problem, and that is globalization. In the 21st century, a series of problems can be traced to the macro trends of globalization: global climate change, and the environment surrounding the energy and geopolitical issues; global food and drug supply chain vulnerability; to 9.11 as the representative of the event security issues; the financial crisis follow-up to the global spread of highly effect. These facts remind us that in the current economic, technological, and social life, we are linked, but not enough simply to contact each other.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; world will continue to become increasingly Moreover, there is a trend now beginning, and although the distance to achieve a process, but the significance and potential of this trend is very significant: the world is becoming more and more wisdom.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the so-called New smart is gradually integrated into the actual operation of the world - such as R &amp;amp; D, manufacturing, purchase and sale of physical goods systems and processes, implementation services, systems and processes, personnel flow, currency, oil, water, electricity and the flow of resources billions of people in work and life can be described as all-encompassing.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; wisdom the world is running into the road &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; First of all, our world is increasingly perceived to measure perception of what we call.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; 60 years ago come up transistors, the basic components of the digital age. Today, the number of transistors per capita almost 10 billion, but the cost of one ten-millionth cents each. People over four billion mobile phone users, the number of global production of RFID tags 300 million.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; these chips, sensors and devices become increasingly sophisticated, the cost is getting lower and lower, so the first time we can put them to the global large-scale systems are natural and man-made, real-time awareness, drive business development and social progress.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Second, our increasingly interconnected world, we call conjunction of things.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the number of Internet users worldwide will soon reach 20 million. But this is only the tip of the iceberg. In the matter of the world together, the various systems and objects to each other&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; computing power than is now being applied to the computer. In fact, the computing power virtually everywhere - any person, any object, any process or any services, the institutions of any size - can be perceived and digital networking. Imagine a trillion interconnected and each object can be perceived prospects - vehicles, appliances, camera head, roads, pipelines, and even applied to medicine and animal husbandry. Think about what all this information generated by interaction, it would be unprecedented.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Third, everything is more intelligent, we call it intelligent.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; new computing model can control a large number of end-user devices, sensors, actuators, and they are linked to the strong background system. Complemented by an advanced supercomputer, such as computing power, and with the&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; this information and can be translated into action to improve systems, processes and infrastructure efficiency, productivity and speed of response - in short, to make the system more intelligent.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; City: system system &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; All of these changes will be concentrated in the city presented. Let us think of today's cities are running critical systems: &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; look at the traffic. Projections indicate that a large number, whether developed or developing cities, traffic congestion will be consumed 1% of GDP to 3%. Expenditure is already high, and the future will continue to rise. Emerging markets - such as China, India and ASEAN countries, cities, vehicles share soared. If this ratio reaches the level of OECD countries, that is, 75-90 percent of the vehicles share, what would happen? For the transportation infrastructure will generate how much pressure?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; energy, electricity and water as well. Most cities in the global emission of carbon dioxide, water accounts for the city 60% of its water. With the urbanization level, city leaders have continued to ensure that the city water and energy supplies - while maintaining environmental sustainability? Think about: Asian Cities residents, over 50% of people do not drink water on the straight.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; health care: As the population grows, the city's financial sustainability of the health care system gradually to the limit. But there are similarities in the provision of urban level of medical treatment, the costs significantly less than other cities. How they do this?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Education: In developed countries, according to an OECD survey, 1995 to 2004, education costs rose 42%. Most of the cost of education in developing countries is still very low, but this situation will not last long. Public expenditure on primary education has been insufficient to meet demand. UNESCO believes that education spending in developing countries accounted for an average of less than 6% of national income. The future of this spending will only rise.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Public Safety: Safety is a key element of quality of urban life, but also the city to create jobs, attract investment and talent of the important conditions. Good news is that public safety is no longer bound to save the day. New York and other cities are using advanced numerical analysis and other means to make the crime rate plummeted at an unprecedented rate.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; public services: an efficient government services to citizens and businesses are extremely important. It is estimated that administrative costs decreased by 25% - such as reducing time to fill in a form, means that spending the equivalent of saving 1.5% of GDP.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; and, above all, education, safety, health, and create an attractive and efficient business environment to ensure the smooth transportation and pedestrian flow, etc., has become the global economic downturn more challenging.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; challenges, we also see hope - new models have emerged. This new model brings all new options, whether business, government or community, can be thinking of a new response to it.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; First, we need to size up the situation. The special needs of the global attention to China's development. World Expo 2010 and Shanghai should become a global city and the country's development a shot in the arm.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Second, we should invest in the future. At such moments they wander too short-sighted not before, and we can not always remedy the situation, should take precautions. If you are a corporate leader, you can not rely solely on reducing costs and streamlining operations. You need to have long-term vision for the next big growth opportunity to prepare. If you are the leaders in government, you must advance the layout for the future. Even if you are a non-governmental organization leaders ... ... or the leadership of a local community, you also need to think, is we live and work in the emergence of these new global model of our society and everyday life would be in place species affected.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; around the world if protectionist trade policies to deal with the economic downturn, it will be a serious mistake. Protectionism is back to the past, and not linked to a physical and intelligent in the future. City is a major distribution center for global trade, protectionism will only bring disastrous effects to the city. This is not a political system or ideology on the concept. This is our world in which the current historic moment, the moment the next step will be to decide how to invest, how to build the world's future.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; this time will not stand still, then will separate the winners and losers. Here, we have witnessed in Shanghai is vigorously promoting the strategy to achieve victory.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; for all of us, the good news is that we already have the technical and political potential to the city become more intelligent, more prosperous, to achieve greater development.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; visionary leaders are paving the road of wisdom &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Obviously, the leader of the long-term vision is to seize the opportunity, take action. Let's look at some of the ongoing practice: &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; energy field: Malta is an island, it is establishing the world's first national intelligence network, while monitoring their own water systems. In China, State Grid Corporation launched a ten-strong smart grid project.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; in the financial sector: The Indian Bank Grameen Koota microfinance banks with open-source platform for accurate records of almost real time information, so can predict capital needs, expanding micro-credit operations, insurance, number of customers and other banks function; by the ability of banks to absorb the number of low-income customers from 7 million to 35 million development.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the medical field: Guangdong Hospital of electronic medical records system to build intelligent fusion of traditional Chinese medicine and Western medicine treatment, so the system can handle, whether Chinese or Western medicine in medical terminology, different formats, medical terminology or language into a single standardized medical records. As a result, the hospital between the various headquarters, between headquarters and four branches, all the key information can be shared complex - improved patient care, diagnosis and treatment. Next, the hospital will be able to use in-depth analysis, the forefront of global medical research field.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Transportation: Global cities are investing heavily in all the wisdom of building traffic. Intelligent transportation card system makes the Singapore Land Transport Authority to design the optimal routes and schedules to reduce traffic congestion and enhance the attractiveness of public transport - and the toll evasion rate decreased by 80%, and land transport authority performance more than doubled, to achieve a daily fare transactions reached 20 million times. In China, IBM Innovation Center in establishing a global railway, the introduction of global industry leaders and university researchers, working together the wisdom of building the railway system.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the field of education: the Ministry of Education launched the open source Since July 2006, there have been over 780,000 Chinese students and teachers using the platform.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; water resources management: IBM is helping the Japanese Fukuoka District Water Authority, for the eight cities in Japan multiuser provide more water and improve water quality.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; list goes on - the wisdom of the South African oil development is being deployed in Vietnam and Thailand being the wisdom of the food items, and the wisdom of China Taiwan tax system is under construction.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; leadership is the key &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the key to achieve wisdom, not the technology but leadership. For the wisdom in building the city generated in the process for managers and leadership challenges, I want to say four.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; First, we must create standards. Of course, we all know the importance of standards. We not only establishing technical standards, but also to establish new global standards for trade policy, intellectual property standards and so on. But when we the city as a Standards related to the system here in the various interfaces. In the system, the interface compatibility is critical, not to be able to build systems with the object heap. To build a real system requires more than just information transfer. We need energy systems in the transport system and standardized interface between the education system and the standard interface between the health care system, in water conservancy, transportation, commerce, public safety and government services to interface between systems.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;, of course, any system of standardization also has a limit. In particular the key elements of a human system, even more so. However, if we are to build a truly intelligent city, it is necessary to improve the standardization of the interface.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Secondly, whether an organization, a city or a community, must encourage more open and more creative, rather than hinder the openness and innovation. For cities, it is especially important because the city is the birthplace of the most important innovation. IBM Institute for Business Value has just completed an excellent study reveals the city for new economic growth and progress in the community to prove that the city is a melting pot of human experience and creativity.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; In fact, the real focus of future urban design lies in the release of human creativity. We can do this through many ways: open collaboration, skills development, improvement of urban quality of life, and so on.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Third, building intelligent city, some policies will have a major impact: &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; London, Chicago, Incheon Free Economic Zone and other places of the camera, so police and other emergency response departments to obtain faster and more accurate warning information to save lives. But some people expressed nervousness. Who have all this data? How do they deal with these data? Can I trust them? Data safe? There are other similar security concerns. Now, many companies and governments to bring the infrastructure for the wisdom of the competitiveness and economic and environmental development advantages rejoice - the wisdom of the grid infrastructure, including the wisdom, the wisdom of the railway, the wisdom of the drainage system, construction of wisdom . However, this mean that our critical infrastructure security and reliability as fragile as a web page?&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; the entire community on these important issues for serious consideration of all relevant parties. We need to build not only the technical and business systems. We must build to represent the various aspects of social structure.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Therefore, we must strengthen the collaboration.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; This is not just a set of similar public-private sector collaboration program. The program has more than one direction, a number of stakeholders, and is truly global. I have mentioned these systems, no single entity or decision-making is the responsibility of parties. They are related to industry,&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapchristianlouboutine.com%2Fchristian-louboutin-lady-peep-150mm-p-129.html%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cheapchristianlouboutine.com/christian-louboutin-lady-peep-150mm-p-129.html&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;;Christian Louboutin Lady Peep 150mm&lt;/a&gt;;, government and community, involving the whole community. This will require new collaborative model. For example, IBM, Northeastern University, Shenyang City, and work together to establish a life and work to create a healthy environment.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Finally, the urgent need for collaboration lies in the establishment of new leadership.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; our traditional view of leadership is that leaders should have a Superman-like vision and the will, the leader should be able to predict the future, the prospects and dangers of commanding, convincing or inspired followers. The current reality is complex, the world is built on top of each system a set of systems, in such circumstances the traditional way of leadership no longer apply.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; more cases, the leaders must attach great importance to the collection of information, need to focus on these multi-level eco-system message. Leaders will be more to exert influence to manage. In such a dynamic and complex environment, leaders must understand the reality, and guide development. We need to build inclusive, collaborative and transparent management system architecture.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; build a wisdom of the Earth &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; urbanization can be said to have symbolic significance on the planet one of the major development, a development that is so important, that . The city of bright light, the operation of our way to shape the world and our way of life, provide a bright future.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; I, as a member of the human am hopeful that we will ultimately win.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; most importantly, the key to real change happens and preconditions already have now: people want change. Whether in the board of directors, in the Cabinet Office, or in the restaurant dinner table, people around the world are yearning for a new way.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; However, this moment of opportunity will not last forever. Looking back at the past, when the change opportunities are fleeting, when all return to&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; gap in age, for people who have the courage and vision,&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapchristianlouboutine.com%2Fchristian-louboutin-rolando-zip-120mm-p-122.html%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cheapchristianlouboutine.com/christian-louboutin-rolando-zip-120mm-p-122.html&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;;Christian Louboutin Rolando Zip 120mm&lt;/a&gt;;, it is opportunity. Remember, in the coming years, in this arena, compete with the emerging, some of the companies, industries and cities will come to the fore. At this stage, a group of leaders will emerge. Success is not to survive the storm, but to change the rules of the game.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; very clear is that the world will continue to become smaller, more flat, more wisdom. We are entering the era of global integration, we are entering a wise economic, social and intellectual wisdom of the Earth's age. If we seize the opportunity to act quickly, we will seize the promise of the future. The timing of action in the present. Site of action in our city. Mode of action is collaboration.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Let us work together.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;; Forward this article to a micro-blog in the latest telecommunications developments, see SAN microblogging User Reviews welcome comment Login: Password: Bo also sent to the micro-fast up new users&lt;/td&gt;;&lt;/tr&gt;;&lt;/table&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/div&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;div id=&quot;comment_94123&quot; class=&quot;cm&quot;&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/div&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>