<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="133a0df00caec09e9fd4a3f5caba49b9">			Thankfully a lot of things which you can do to lower  the amount of heating that you use require no cost.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The simplest and most direct method of lowering your heating bills  is to cut down the room  thermostat by 1 degree You might not expect it and probably wont even  notice the difference within the temperature but this may easily lower home heating bills by 10% per year.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You are able to greatly reduce the energy your current boiler  uses by as much as 40 % by getting an effective thermostat and thermostatic radiator valves. You can easily buy a thermostat and thermostatic radiator valves on the web .We would usually advise a thermostat  get installed using a Gas Safe Registered heating system engineer.&lt;br /&gt;;Central  Heating Leeds are always happy to fit TRVs for their customers and fit them as standard on any new installations. If you've  got a room which is  not being utilized much like a second toilet or a utility room or not being  utilized at all then switch off the radiators in that room. If a room in your  home is not used frequently why heat it?.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ehow.com%2Fhow_4529977_choose-plumber.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ehow.com/how_4529977_choose-plumber.html&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Put your central heating boiler on timer. Switching off the boiler once the heating is no longer needed (i.e. when ever no one’s home) is an effective means of saving energy and cash.Different rooms require  different temperatures. This can not be accomplished using just one thermostat. So fit  thermostatic radiator valves TRVs to the individual radiators in your  family home and improve the versatility to select the  temperatures that you want.A lot of the warmth in a  home is lost through the windows and drawing the  blinds tends to make a huge difference.Reach for a pullover instead of expecting to wear shorts and a t-shirt month in month out. Remember 1 degree Centigrade  decrease in heating can easily reduce heating  system costs by 10%.If your  central heating boiler is more than 10 years old then unquestionably you would profit if it were  upgraded. New energy efficient condensing boilers could  certainly cut down energy consumption by a 1/3rd.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Manage the  hot water temperature. Your hot water thermostat needn’t be more  than 60 centigrade (140 Fahrenheit). Any higher and you'll just be  mixing in cold water to reduce it down again to a comfy temperature to be utilised.&lt;br /&gt;;Getting the central heating boiler serviced  regularly adds dramatically to its efficiency. Energy bills are decreased because after  servicing it will perform more effectively and it'll be considerably less likely to breakdown. It is well worth contemplating a service  contract for older boilers.A shower uses far less  water and fuel than a bath . Make your showers not as long and less hot for  more health and wealth benefits!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Insulate warm water tanks and  pipes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fit cavity wall and attic space insulation. There are often funds obtainable  making these a very affordable choice. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.CentralHeatingPlumbers-LeedsPlumbers.co.ukSludge"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.CentralHeatingPlumbers-LeedsPlumbers.co.ukSludge&lt;/a&gt;; collects in radiators over time. If you've ever utilized  the bleed key and the water comes out black or grey then you certainly have a sludge problem and even though  you may cant see it yet its happening. Sludge lessens the efficiency  of the radiators by as much as Fifteen percent . A power flush will clean out the sludge and return the radiators to optimum  efficiency. Ensure that you are running your system with a  rust inhibitor. This is added to the water within the system so it helps prevent the corrosion that is the cause of the sludge build up inside the radiators. The inhibitor will also help the pump to perform better.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Radiators are a more energy-efficient method of home heating  your house as opposed to a real coal or log fire. As lovely as it's to enjoy a nice real fire in your home, a lot of the heat goes out in the chimney so energy wise it’s more  efficient to use your home heating system.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When ever the radiator is not working  appropriately and appears to get colder towards the top and hot at the bottom then more than  likely there's air within the radiator, and the radiator needs bleeding. You will need a bleeding key available from hardware stores. It's best to make certain the system is turned off anytime you are performing it		</conversation>	</conversations></author>