<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="10">		<conversation id="2e2c7f49ca05689f41687d3bf43871a1">			A donkey and a chicken are out in a field when the donkey falls down a hole....the chicken races over and jumps into the farmers bmw, ties a rope to the front and pulls him out. 
&lt;br /&gt;;The next week they're out in the field and the chicken falls down a hole! He tells the donkey to run and get the bmw but instead the donkey walks over to the hole and drops his cock in, and the chicken climbs out.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Moral of the story: when ur hung like a donkey u dont need a bmw to pull a chick!!		</conversation>		<conversation id="cf51794826f039999e0b5dfdba7b62b0">			A couple went into a field where they used to make love.......
&lt;br /&gt;;Overcome wit excitement at the memories, she leans against the fence, their passion takesover.....
&lt;br /&gt;;Afterwards the man says 'u never used to get so excited'
&lt;br /&gt;;She replies 'the fuckin fence never used to be electric!'		</conversation>		<conversation id="816f6220f0e49e814f19716bda5ea8fd">			Larry was visited by God......
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;God said 'to get into heavenu must giv up beer, smokin and sex'
&lt;br /&gt;;God said he'd be back in 2 months.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;God came back and Larry said that he had given up the beer and smokin.
&lt;br /&gt;;God asked about sex.
&lt;br /&gt;;Larry said he did his best but last week he saw his wife bent over the freezer and took her there and then!
&lt;br /&gt;;God said 'ah Jesus Larry they wont be happy in heaven'.
&lt;br /&gt;;Larry said 'they weren't to happy in tesco either'		</conversation>		<conversation id="bed02d5a9c7c9f6d7ac6cecf0373e17a">			A nun gets on a train, skinhead in front of her eatin a bag of prawns, he starts spittin the heads at her, so she throws them out of the window and pulls the emergency cord. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Skinhead says 'you'll get fined £50 for that u stupid old slut'
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nun replies 'when i cry rape and they smell ur fingers you'll get 10 years u cunt!		</conversation>		<conversation id="ae8858a8651d891e014e7c1259624fa7">			two men are walking round the airport because they cant find their wives. They bump into each other and the first man says..
&lt;br /&gt;;'can you help? I've lost my wife'
&lt;br /&gt;;The second man replies 'i can't find mine either, what does ur wife look like?'
&lt;br /&gt;;First man says 'she's 6ft, blonde hair, big tits, wearing a mini skirt and a boob tube. what does ur wife look like?' 
&lt;br /&gt;;The second man replies 'F**K her, we'll look for urs!!!'		</conversation>		<conversation id="1bdc48b398eef4ebcfb6ae8f56f27102">			Paddy pulls alongside a lorry, 'oi driver yer losin ur load!'
&lt;br /&gt;;Driver says 'fuck off'.
&lt;br /&gt;;5 miles further along 'oi yer losin ur load'.
&lt;br /&gt;;'Will u fuck off'.
&lt;br /&gt;;5 miles further along paddy yells 'I'm not jokin honest yer losin ur load'
&lt;br /&gt;;The driver says 'will u go away u thick irish twat i am grittin the road!'
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;jus gettin goin!!!!!!!!		</conversation>		<conversation id="fa8305f7c64eae42f77db17bcea01f5d">			One day a woman decides she wants bigger boobs without surgery.....so finds a doctor who says its all about mind over matter!!
&lt;br /&gt;;Dr Whatmough tells her to say 'scooby dooby dooby i want big boobies' every day and watch the results.
&lt;br /&gt;;The woman goes away and religously says 'scooby dooby dooby i want big boobies' every day.
&lt;br /&gt;;One day on the way to work the woman realizes that she had forgotten to say it, so when she get to her seat she says 'scooby dooby dooby i want big boobies'
&lt;br /&gt;;The man sat behind her says 'have u been to see dr whatmough?'
&lt;br /&gt;;'Yes' the woman replies 'how did u know that?'
&lt;br /&gt;;He says 'hickory dickory dock'		</conversation>		<conversation id="8b02c2af345a0f42f567924496b97c0">			Husband was admiring his naked body in the mirror, says to wife 'look at that, 10 stone of pure dynamite'.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wife replies 'fuckin shame about the 2 inch fuse!'		</conversation>		<conversation id="fd3bcad0279319c7da0a7daabd6438b3">			The nerves r really startin to kick in now......and i'm startin to think i really am mad!
&lt;br /&gt;;In less than 3 weeks time i will find myself on holiday (yes abroard for the first time in 10 yrs) wit my so called best friend! Yes the BITCH (sorry if that seems really bitter of me) who decided she wanted my bf!
&lt;br /&gt;;When the thought of sun, sea and sand should make me all happy and get me excited......i'm feelin nothin but dread!
&lt;br /&gt;;I'm not a violent,callous,bitter or twisted person.......its jus she treated like a fool! But u know wot they revenge is sweet and i'm sure if i get that one glance from her her direction.........a bitch slap would be most appropriate given the circumstance.
&lt;br /&gt;;Well i'll let u no the outcome soon enough.........so watch this space!!!
&lt;br /&gt;;Chelle &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="dca44d7d38aa62cb02a390db26b65f25">			Three naked men sat in a sauna.
&lt;br /&gt;;An American, a Japanese and an Irishman, they hear a beep sound, the american touches his arm and says 'thats my pager, i have a microchip under my skin'
&lt;br /&gt;;Next a phone rings and the jap lifts his palm to his ear and says 'i have a microchip in my hand'
&lt;br /&gt;;The irishman feeling very lowtech went to the loo and came back withtoilet paper hanging from his arse he says 'oh jaysus would you look at that, i'm getting a fax through!!'
&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/laugh.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>