<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="5ef0ee0db38e4631c057ad68b5a7bec3">			It has often been hypothesized that violence seems to rise in densely populated areas.  In his book, Malcolm Gladwell points out the observation that has been made to support this hypothesis:  when you pack too many species, or people, in one area or small space, there is a rising probability of them becoming aggressive with one another.  Walking down any street in a city, you have a bigger chance of experiencing a violent act than in one that doesn’t, even though it is possible to see it anywhere in the world, including rural places.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Can we work together to find a solution to this problem?  In many violent episodes, people agree that they would do anything in their power to protect themselves and their loved ones from violent individuals.  If someone feels as if they are threatened, they could also fight against someone using violent force in retaliation.  Does this kind of attitude really make any positive change?  Or does violence - no matter from what side it is coming - perpetuate violence?  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are the type of person who stands for non-violence and believes in it, you probably have a great amount of moral fiber and you stand for the things you believe in.  A corporation called NXIVM is dedicated to building ethics.  You can find one of the company’s centers in New York City, where its’ founder, &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.whomyouknow.com%2F2010%2F07%2Fmovers-and-shakers-sara-bronfman.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSara"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.whomyouknow.com/2010/07/movers-and-shakers-sara-bronfman.html&quot;&gt;;Sara&lt;/a&gt;; Bronfman&lt;/a&gt;; has set it up.  Since this is a big city, we can see the results of ethics as they play out in everyday life in regards to violence.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Is there a positive affect from moral fiber diffused in some of the people who live in this populated city location?  If you’re unsure of what ethics is, you can equate it to your intuition.  They’re the moral code by which an individual lives his or her life.  If a person’s ethics are not absolutely defined, a person might find themselves at odds often about what they will or won’t decide to do.  There is no doubt that a person who has good moral fiber will be able to almost always make a decision easily and usually without hesitation. The strong points of the article here can be accessed at &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.worldethicalfoundations.org%2Fsara_bronfman.php%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSara"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.worldethicalfoundations.org/sara_bronfman.php&quot;&gt;;Sara&lt;/a&gt;; Bronfman programs&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e49dc1aceeb07d3196ab6e5181a269c8">			Could we work as a unit to find a solution to this problem?  If you talk to a person who lives in these types of situations, you will probably hear the same statement: they would all protect and fight against a violent situation.  Some people might even as far as returning the violence - that is, they would strike back.  Can someone utilize violence in these situations and it create a positive impact?  Or does violence - no matter from what side it is derived - perpetuate violence?  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are the type of person who advocates non-violence and believes in it, you probably have a great amount of moral fiber and you stand for the things you believe in.  If you are interested in obtaining a great  understanding of personal ethics, you should research a company called NXIVM.  You can find one of the organization’s centers in New York City, where its’ creator, &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.clarebronfman.com%2Fblog%2Ftag%2Fsara-bronfman%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSara"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.clarebronfman.com/blog/tag/sara-bronfman/&quot;&gt;;Sara&lt;/a&gt;; Bronfman&lt;/a&gt;; has set it up.  For apparent reasons, it seems like a great place to test the concept of ethics and violence.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The question is, how can ethics assuredly affect violence -- even in the middle of an already violent society?  If you’re unsure of what ethics is, you can equate it to your intuition.  You can see in the way a person lives if they have good morals or otherwise.  You need to stand with what you believe in when it applies to your moral beliefs or you won’t be able to make decisive choices that could determine  your life.  If their ethical code is strong, it is likely that this person will have an idea of how to handle challenging situations as they occur.  They are more likely to be consistent and feel a sense of surety about their decision.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Violence is an issue that many people have a hard time swallowing.  Injuring someone or stealing from someone is something most of us wouldn’t even conceive.  If you have a good solid ethical background, the thought of hurting someone, letting alone killing them, would never even cross our minds.  How is  this achievable?  Were we made to avoid violence at all costs?  Will we see positive effects on the way we feel about the subject of violence if we build better ethics?  If people have been raised with an objective view of violence, is there a way to teach them something different?  If we all strive towards building these block for better ethics, we will more than likely see a difference.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The strong points of the article here can be accessed at &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.whomyouknow.com%2F2010%2F07%2Fmovers-and-shakers-sara-bronfman.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3BSara"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.whomyouknow.com/2010/07/movers-and-shakers-sara-bronfman.html&quot;&gt;;Sara&lt;/a&gt;; Bronfman programs&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>