<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="6">		<conversation id="f69fecb1cc05ea1862bde62ba6cfbe5d">			People come, then go. A song plays, then ends. You take a bath, then you get dirty again. You eat, then you get hungry again.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You lose someone good, then someone else comes along and you realize that he/she's better.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You fall down, and you get back up because staying down on the cold floor isn't really an option.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is the ugly truth of life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's like a game of snake and ladders.
&lt;br /&gt;;We just have to keep going.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes we get a boost up, sometimes we're forced to go back a few squares.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes someone else reaches first, or surpasses you.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some of us move faster, some of us prefer going slow and steady.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But you will never be out of the game itself.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Just keep rolling the dice &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; It'll never show zero.		</conversation>		<conversation id="237efc4ddaee72cc150bffe75b10767f">			I've seen castles made out of SAND,
&lt;br /&gt;;Met people who believe destiny is engraved on the palms of their HAND.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I've seen people change their FAITH,
&lt;br /&gt;;Experienced love changing into HATE.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I've seen people grow younger with AGE,
&lt;br /&gt;;and a bird who wouldn't fly out of Open CAGE.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I've seen love being sold for MONEY,
&lt;br /&gt;;People devastated inside, but outside they are FUNNY
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I've seen the Unicorn fall in Love with the TOAD,
&lt;br /&gt;;People who owned half the city now hit the ROAD.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I've learnt to expect the UNEXPECTED,
&lt;br /&gt;;Perfection doesn't exist, we are all DEFECTED.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Everyone cries, some just hide their TEARS,
&lt;br /&gt;;Coal turns into Diamond after thousand YEARS.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For someone, you are Just One in a MILLION,
&lt;br /&gt;;and
&lt;br /&gt;;For others, you are another nobody in BILLION.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b72ac60fb091566748340dc06dfb205e">			it's like this..
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;you have to wear the nicest jeans, or the cutest purse, or say the newest thing so that it catches on. You have to be skinny, you have to buy this, wear this, say that, be on his side, her side, be neutral, have white teeth, have straight teeth, your hair can't be frizzy, and you can't wear that because it just doesn't 'work' anymore. You have to go to parties, be friends with everyone, trust no one, pose like this, smile like that, tilt you head this way, and put your hand on your hip, because that's how it is. And let me just say, f*** all of that.		</conversation>		<conversation id="c18b54650cb18b1e74cbf2243421348b">			1. People who point at their wrist asking for the time... I know where my watch is pal, where the hell is yours? Do I point at my crotch when I ask where the toilet is?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. People who are willing to get off their a** to search the entire room for the TV remote because they refuse to walk to the TV and change the channel manually.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. When people say &quot;Oh you just want to have your cake and eat it too&quot;. Damn Right! What good is cake if you can't eat it?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. When people say &quot;it's always the last place you look&quot;. Of course it is. Why the hell would you keep looking after you've found it? Do people do this? Who and where are they?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. When people say while watching a film, &quot;did ya see that?&quot; No Loser, I paid $12 to come to the cinema and stare at the damn floor!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. People who ask &quot;Can I ask you a question?&quot;... Didn't give me a choice there, did ya sunshine?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. When something is 'new and improved'. Which is it? If it's new, then there has never been anything before it. If it's an improvement, then there must have been something before it, couldn't be new.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. When people say &quot;life is short&quot;. What the hell??? Life is the longest damn thing anyone ever does!!! What can you do thats longer?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. When you are waiting for the bus and someone asks &quot;Has the bus come yet?&quot; If the bus came, would I be standing here???		</conversation>		<conversation id="6ce87d827a6abc204160810db6006640">			No relationship is perfect, ever. There are always some ways you have to bend, to compromise, to give something up in order to gain something greater. If u are not up to it, u will end up alone. Try to blend in ppl!		</conversation>		<conversation id="7447d651bc81c060d303a3aaa91476ad">			Along with our life is sacrifice,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Along with love is letting go,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Valuable memories must be displace,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For our lives to be peaceful and in disperse.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ive been thinking of our past right now,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wondering what went wrong ,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Isn't me,whom you cannot accept?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Or the truth in you .that you often feel.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ive been missing your nose and eyes,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I also miss your nice smile.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I miss your hug's and kisses,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That i know, will always be the sweetest.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I just thought about it last night,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;when the moon and the stars are bright,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That we have the feelings alike ,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The days when were not yet apart.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I really just don't know what to say,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Its really blown my heart away.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Every time that i saw you I pray,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That you'll forgive me more one day.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I know that it hurts a lot,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But the truth is.,..your still in my heart.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That it's hard to let go and forget,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;''i'm SO SORRY'' that what i want you to get.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Time will come, i know will do,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The healing's of our heart's will process trough,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;like the birds in the sky that flew,
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sadly....but free to go any where without you.....		</conversation>	</conversations></author>