<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="54cd06603663823b2b36b641bb171314">			Parents are often devastated when they find out that their child is autistic. It isn't easy to accept that your child is different and has problems. However, research is ongoing and today it's much easier to discover the resources you need to help you raise your autistic child. A case in point is the fact that schools must now accommodate all students with special needs, and this includes children who are autistic. There's no doubt that you will have more difficulties than parents whose child is not autistic, but you will find a lot of help and support along the way.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fortitude is one of the main requirements of a parent with an autistic child. Autistic children usually need lots of repetition in order to understand something. When coaching a youngster with autism to learn a duty or task; you must repeat yourself time and again. The child needs to feel a great sense of approval when they do something right. Some autistic children have additional issues you need to deal with, like being touchy about physical contact or eye contact. Such issues can be difficult for parents to get used to, but you just have to accept whatever traits your child has and work around them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the first things you must learn - to make life easier - is what kinds of external stimuli sets off your child. Lights, music, odors, sounds, motion are all items that could cause a bad reaction. Temper tantrums can be brought on by any one of these stimuli to which your child is adverse. Or they may simply cease to respond and withdraw from the external world. While some autistic kids are hypersensitive, others are are less sensitive than normal, so they may ignore something right in front of them. It's important for you to note the reactions from your child to these external stimuli such as - motion, smells, light, and someone's tone of voice. Once you have figured out what upsets your child you can take steps to eliminate that irritant from their environment. By learning how your child responds to such stimuli, you can prevent many problems and learn better ways of communicating with him or her. Communicating together with your child about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.quality-clean.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.quality-clean.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  or any other topic may be effortless when you are working with your autistic child.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Over time, most medical conditions have had continued research that is constantly renewing the information they have available; this applies to autism as well. Mothers even took the rap for autism some time ago; they claimed that autism was possibly caused by a mother, not being lovable enough. People viewed the mothers of autistic children as lacking in affection and thus produced the various symptoms. But that ancient and rather crude belief has been completely abandoned. As far as we have come on a medical level, we are not a lot closer to fully knowing the reasons for the ailment. A slight war has been waged among the experts, some opt for the older remedies and then there are those with the new-fangled angles on procedures. The field of research is essentially wide open to consider possible genetic or environmental causes or even a combination. Unfortunately, there is no basic, fundamental answer as to the specific cause; it may not be that easily explained.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are a parent with an autistic child, you must learn how to develop patience and understanding when trying to instruct your children. Consistency is the key - by working with your autistic children on a regular basis, you can help improve them over time dramatically.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Articles:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21098659%2Fsome-points-to-remember-for-parents-of-an-autistic-child"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21098659/some-points-to-remember-for-parents-of-an-autistic-child&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogster.com%2Fmortonjimcknig%2Fadvice-the-parents-of-an-autistic-child-should-bear-in-mind"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.blogster.com/mortonjimcknig/advice-the-parents-of-an-autistic-child-should-bear-in-mind&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="c53cb77d639f7674ab3ec4290ecb8d72">			A very low calorie diet is just one type out of the many different meal plans out there. Ideally you shouldn't start one of these diets without consulting a medical professional for some guidance because these diets restrict your calorie intake to levels that are severely low. While doctors will sometimes recommend them to patients who need to lose weight quickly, they're not safe for everyone. We shall be looking at some of the things related to very low calorie diets in this article.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The main advantage to very low calorie diets is that they can help obese patients who are suffering from weight-related medical conditions lose weight quickly. It's possible to shed fives pounds per week on this type of diet, which equals twenty over a month. This can be very beneficial, sometimes even life saving for people who may have hypertension, diabetes, heart disease and high cholesterol. The guidance of a doctor for this type of weight loss is very important, especially so if you are already getting treatment for a health condition. It's essential that you work with your doctor to create a plan that'll maintain your weight loss for the months to come.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To ensure that you stay within the limit of your calories, most very low calorie diets will have some sort of formula that's prepared, however there are some diets that severely restrict your calories which are natural. One option is a raw foods diet, where you eat only foods that are uncooked and unprocessed. A strict raw foods diet will normally be very low in calories as you will not be eating any high calorie processed foods. Normally a raw foods diet will be made up of fruits, nuts, sprouts and vegetables, however it's possible to make your own versions of raw foods like bread by simply using a dehydrator. Lots of people find it rather difficult to stay on track with this kind of diet because eating most everyday foods is forbidden, however this is considered to be healthy. Even if you don't want to make your diet 100% raw, you may want to incorporate more raw foods into your very low calorie diet. So if you're searching out to shed &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.quality-clean.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.quality-clean.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  weight then see to it that you are not ignoring the basics.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A very low calorie diet, called the Cambridge Diet, was produced in England back in the 1970s. On this diet you're given pre-packaged foods, which have carefully calculated amounts of nutrients that you require, as well as keeping your calorie consumption low. They're usually in the form of soups, meal bars and shakes. This diet does have some disadvantages, even though people have been successful with it and it has been around for a while. You have to drink lots of water to avoid dehydration, and you can only do very low intensity exercise while on this diet. People also may find that they get tired of eating nothing but packaged meals. You should ask your doctor if the Cambridge Diet is safe for you before you go on it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Very low calorie diets can help with losing weight in the short term, however the benefits in the long term are questionable. For obese people who are under a doctor's supervision, such diets may be appropriate. But for other people it's important that you are careful when it comes to the essential nutrients that are required by your body. After all, in addition to losing weight you want to stay healthy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Links:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21130104%2Fthe-important-facts-surrounding-very-low-calorie-diets"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21130104/the-important-facts-surrounding-very-low-calorie-diets&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/dinoblackburn/blog/blogid=4654172" target="_blank"&gt;;http://en.pan.netcom/dinoblackburn/blog/blogid=...&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FSome-Of-The-Good-And-Bad-Points-Of-Very-Low-Calorie-Diets%2F03EFBFFFF0243D4180008015ACB85"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://community.atom.com/Post/Some-Of-The-Good-And-Bad-Points-Of-Very-Low-Calorie-Diets/03EFBFFFF0243D4180008015ACB85&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>