<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c575814593564b396c486d7932179dfc">			Travel Machu Picchu Peru
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CUSCO CITY + ADVENTURE (A WALKING TO LARES) AND MACHUPICCHU 6D/5N
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is a program that combines the traditional and the adventure, you will appreciate the architecture of the cityof the inca Cusco, the temple of the Sun Koricancha, our majestic Cathedral and its archeological groups nearby, Sacsayhuaman, Q’enqo, Pukapukara, Tambomachay, you will enjoy of a trip of adventure to Lares, at the north of  Cusco where we will visit medicinal warm waters to be able to take a bath in them and maybe to cure of any pain, we will visit towns of weaving craftmen that keep their customs and traditions, the road is moderated and finally we will arrive to Machupicchu, gorgeous work of inca architecture, the circuit is full of natural attractions that grant the visitor a single sensation of adventue in direct contact with nature.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Travel Machu Picchu Peru DESCRIPTION
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 1 : ARRIVAL TO CUSCO AND VISIT TO THE CITY
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Transfer to the hotel selected, interview with the professional guide of trip. Free time for resting and becoming acclimated to the height. At the afternoon tour in the city of Cusco, visiting the Main Square, the Cathedral and the Temple dof the Sun or Qorikancha; then , we directo towards Saqsayhuaman (the Real House of the Sun ). Inside this great complex there are located other archeological complexes as, Q’enqo (center of astronomica observation); templededicated to the earth, Pukapukara (military center, administrative and of watching), its function was to control the Inca Road. Tambomachay (Temple of the Water and Baths of the Inca), that was a center of cult and workship to the water. Then return to its hostage. Overnight. Travel Machu Picchu Peru
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 2 : CUSCO – LARES – HUACAHUASI.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We leave from Cusco 6:00am to then after 4 hours arrive to the spring falls Lares where we will enjoy of this marvelous place following we will take lunch over here y at the afternoon we will walk an average of three hours up to the community of Huacahuasi at 3600masl.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 3 : HUACAHUASI – ARORAY – MANTANAY.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Huacahuasi is a traditional town that still keeps its techniques of crops as well as also is typical its textiles; they produce throws, caps and other crafts. After visiting this small town, we ascend to the highest the Abra Del Puma (1416.1 m.asl.), after descending an hour approximately we will be able to watch the lagoons of Aroray and Mantanay. Finally we will camp near this lagoon.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 4 : MANTANAY - YANAHUARA – OLLANTAYTAMBO – AGUAS CALIENTES
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After a recomforting breakfast, we will start our walk for descending towards the Sacred Valley of the Incas, the place denominated Yanahuara where the transport for Ollantaytambo will be waiting us and for taking the train to Aguas Calientes to be able to spend the night in a hotel, reserved for the group.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 5 : AGUAS CALIENTES-MACHUPICCHU /AGUAS CALIENTE – CUSCO.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We will leave early by bus to explore the precolumbian city of Machupicchu guided tour for two hours, afterwards free time and then take the bus for going down to the population of Aguas Calientes and then return to the imperial city of Cusco by train. Travel Machu Picchu Peru
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 6 : FAREWELL
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After the breakfast in the hotel, we will transfer to the train station or bus one so that the customer continue with its trip over our country
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WHAT DOES IT INCLUDE
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Transfers  3 nighs hosting in a hotel . ( 2 in Cusco , 1 in Aguas calientes) ; 2 nights in Camping Tour of the city (transport and guiding + entrances) 1st. day. Walking of adventure to Lares + Machupicchu ( the service includes transportation, feeding everyday of the walking , camping equipment, bilingual guide, personnel for support, horses for the luggage in the walk, , cooker, entrances to Machupicchu, Bus for up and down to Machupicchu, round trip by train to Ollantaytambo, Transport for returning to Cusco ) Permanent assistance
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;WHAT DOES NOT INCLUDE
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Breakfast the day of arrival, lunch and dinner second and fifth day Taxes IGV 19%
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nystravelexpeditions.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nystravelexpeditions.com/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>