<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="8">		<conversation id="5f414bbcec72ff7c15badb28ff244d90">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jazzyhandbags.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.jazzyhandbags.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;JazzyHandBags.com offers high quality, affordable Juicy Couture Handbags &amp; Purses that are perfect for you, your friends, and loved ones. With JazzyHandBags.com’s one-stop shopping, superior quality Juicy Couture Handbags &amp; Purses at incredible prices, you are sure to find exactly what you are looking for and much more. Our Juicy Couture Handbags &amp; Purses make great gifts. If you have questions about our product or would like us to suggest an Juicy Couture Handbags &amp; Purses, please contact us. We are dedicated to your satisfaction and hope you’ll make JazzyHandBags.com your online shop for Juicy Couture Handbags &amp; Purses.		</conversation>		<conversation id="58f63ef3178575ac0db01933e631981b">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.fanboystatus.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.fanboystatus.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;This internet site is the result of a phrase commonly used. So we thought, hey, why don’t we build something around that ? And here we are. Almost everyone is to some degree a fanboy, I personally have become an Apple fanboy, Web fanboy, Adobe fanboy, you get the point. Now when it comes to cars, it becomes a whole new style of fanboy. And most of the car fanboys are fierce !		</conversation>		<conversation id="628b1c144e6312d2bc0d0afd8f77d158">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.donnasaccountingservice.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.donnasaccountingservice.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;I prepare federal and state tax returns in Lenexa Kansas and I also do bookkeeping and accounting services. I am a Kansas Notary Public.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d9433c823f8b60cb587364bca6991dbd">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jewelry-treasurechest.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.jewelry-treasurechest.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Jewelry Treasure Chest offers Discounted &amp; Bargain of fine Quality Jewelry Products, from rings, pendants, watches, earrings, bracelets and more. We provide FREE Jewelry Polishing Wipes for any items. You can find treasure jewelries from our category of prices to fit everyone's budget		</conversation>		<conversation id="bde84078cb734f1f732d7d0507665f42">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.qualitycurtainhardware.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.qualitycurtainhardware.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Specializing in curtain rods, drapery rods, drapery hardware, traverse rods, motorized traverse and flexible track systems. Free Shipping on orders over $100.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ee97cba7f8d837da06592632d1fdb8f4">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thecommercialhotelchester.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.thecommercialhotelchester.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Hotel Restaurant and Bar in Chester - The Commerical. A place to drink, dine, dance, and relax in the heart of Chester.		</conversation>		<conversation id="88014e1237105fbc32e31a23fab94c71">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ovuquick.de"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ovuquick.de&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;sehr schöne und informative Website zu Themen wie Ovulationstest, Fruchtbare Tage Ovulationstest, Schwanger werden Ovulationstest.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d757e077db835e3f78c8634dbd9a4ae6">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.sunpacksupply.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.sunpacksupply.com&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Pharmacy Vials and Supplies medical marijuana best value high quality selection service value.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>