<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ffb3bb9c92ae82bfb3dc5189ccb17ffd">			Using leverage and placing ads in lots of places such as free classifieds may also help get your vehicle available. Note that some of these steps may be of more use for some than others, but ideally these should help anybody that is going for a quick sale and/or optimum price. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First impressions are extremely key to getting an interested buyer. The appearance of an car can do considerably to make it appealing and more valuable. Now of course not every vehicle priced $1000 or less will likely be a concourse winner, but there are several things you're able to do for a vehicle whatever the kind of condition it's in. First, when is the last time you washed your vehicle? A full detail definitely isn't worth the time it takes to do and there are some blemishes, dings, dents, and damage that people just cannot avoid. However taking a while to wash the vehicle and do a good vacuum, maybe use some wax/shine products might go a seriously great distance towards getting a sale faster. There are tons of vehicles out there that could have probably sold much higher/faster if the seller spent a little time making it cleaner. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Will there ever be another way I can handle the debt, such as acquiring a part-time job etc.? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Must really need this many other car or whatever right now? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Can I raise funds some other way? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the answer is no therefore you definitely still need to sell your car fast, then you have to act as if somebody desperate to sell the idea, in order to distribute it. It kind of works in reverse. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I cover this in the fair bit of detail in my book - The ninety Minute Car Salesman. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There's no real way to sell it fast for a great price other than doing the standard actions properly. There is not a such thing as a quick fix. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take a look at your situation honestly and then determine what it is about it that you're not facing and you will soon see a answer. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I hope this helps. Yes sometimes life is tough. But sell your vehicle like you have constantly in the world and you should sell it faster and find a good price. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Tip 1 - Pick your time. &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; If you may possibly help it, don't sell your car after Christmas, when no one has any money. Take into consideration holiday periods: will the people be in town and away. Sometimes this can work in your favour because if people not at work they've already more time to look for cars, and they are generally cashed up with nothing to do. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On your reverse side, when clients are busy working, they don't have the time to do a whole lot of car shopping, which tend to make negotiating easier. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additionally for this reason, if you get a buyer in the future on a week-night, it's unlikely he can compare yours to other cars - that can sometimes work in ones favour. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Idea 2 - First Impacts are everything &lt;/b&gt;; Exactly are going on a date - first impressions are everything. Get all the rubbish and junk from it. Deodorize it. Wash the idea, clean it. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Tip 3 - For the reason that good boy scout tells. Be prepared. &lt;/b&gt;; Get their paperwork in order. Get the spare keys. You don't want to be rushing around at the last minute, just when the buyer is preparing to go for it. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Nhc2hmb3JjYXJzc2FuZGllZ28uY2FzaGZvcmNhcnNxdWljay5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Cash for Cars San Diego&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>