<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a01f9c1f946f6a327e5bfb812ef7eab1">			This quite possibly works for vehicles. This loan is called car title loans.&lt;br /&gt;;This loan was designed to give easy financial usage of individuals who need an immediate budget. Interest rates are flexible and can get negotiated, which is also a bonus to the borrower so that finances are managed in the flexible way and loaned amounts can be repaid on schedule. Car title loans can also be availed by any individual regardless of their credit standing. Of those with good, bad or unknown consumer credit standings can avail such loan because of the fact a property of value is being used as a security. Moreover, this loan is not just limited to car brands, lending firms also accept different titles like boats, jet skis, trucks and any other vehicles that can be used as collateral.&lt;br /&gt;;Loans such as this can be availed to help lending firms, banks and other financial companies. Some have even websites wherein you can fill up a pre-approval form and submit it online and also the company would contact the applicant once the application has been approved. All that needs to become done is to bring the title to the firmâ??s office and sign some papers and also the cash being borrowed is usually released.&lt;br /&gt;;Car title loans are very effective if financial assistance should be applied immediately. Whatâ??s great about this loan is that individual keeps the property that have been set as collateral. Additionally, the payment terms are convenient for individuals so that they would have great flexibleness on managing their financial resources.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the financial slowdown attack the financial markets, lending firms became tough on their rules when it comes to borrowing money. This eventually became a problem to those people who are cash-strapped because they can't easily access a financial resource due to the strict code being implemented through the lending firms. They want to filter out individuals who bad credit, minimizing their risks on people who default on their funds. Some lending firms get created a loan package that can be accessed by anyone providing they can prove that they will pay their loans in due time. This loan could also be used to rebuild an individualâ??s credit rating if the individual received a bad rating in the past by borrowing a certain amount of money and paying your debt in due time.&lt;br /&gt;;Guaranteed loans have been with us the financial market for quite a while now and a good search inside internet would reveal that there are lots of financial firms who offer this loan package that's suited for your need and at the same time, you can apply online and get approved in a short time of time as long as being the requirements to secure this loan are met.&lt;br /&gt;;For a summary, this loan is about:&lt;br /&gt;;â?¢	Easy access to some sort of financial resource to cash-strapped people.&lt;br /&gt;;â?¢	This loan can be employed by anyone providing they can provide a proof of steady income source.&lt;br /&gt;;â?¢	A loan that is high risk to lending firms thatâ??s why you will find there's high interest rate if the borrowed amount is not necessarily paid in due time.&lt;br /&gt;;â?¢	Short term loans which are useful to repair a bad credit rating and can be applied in the internet if the lending firm has a website.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aWtpLmNvbS9lbi9yaWNreS1icmFuY2gtMisxMTY2OTA2L3Bvc3QvQ2FyLVRpdGxlLUxvYW5zKzE0NDU0MTEy" target="_blank"&gt;;Car Title Loans&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="91dd1e15dd0a0635e16776335a5021a8">			But it's so widely ignored just by payday lenders -- and also the cops, and consumer protection authorities -- as to be a sick joke.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So today, Ottawa is allowing the provinces to set higher caps -- in effect, to legalize long-standing practices. In Manitoba (that &quot;tough on lenders&quot; province), it's $17 per $100 on loans that average only a couple of weeks, while Nova Scotia (that softies) is providing $31. Nobody knows what B. C. will settle on, but I'm hoping it'll be at least only Manitoba's.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But vehicle-title funds? Ottawa hasn't given the provinces approval to set new caps for or to regulate these, so there's virtually no new law coming. And, as far as I'm able to tell, there's no action with either police forces and the provincial Business Practices and Consumer Protection Authority so that these kinds of lenders are complying along with the law.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vehicle-title loans should not be confused with the old-fashioned car loans that just about everyone has taken out at a few point. Some payday lenders may make such loans, but they're often done by companies with the own store-fronts, and the 20 members of the Canadian Payday Lenders Association have agreed to not do any financial loans secured by chattels, which include cars.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vehicle-title loans go only to those who already own a car or truck. They're usually limited to a smallish fraction of this vehicle's real worth. And they're vastly more expensive than conventional car loans -- especially if the borrower defaults.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Amount Mounteer, a lawyer along with the Vancouver firm of Hordo and Bennett, which is involved in class-action suits against both pay day loan companies and vehicle-title loan companies, gave me a crash course in how they can work.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A loans clerk points out that your vehicle is usually secure a loan, he says, but the papers signed through the borrower actually sell the car to the lender for the price of the loan -- $2, 000 while on an $18, 000 car, inside example Mounteer cited. Than the lender takes $500 off the top, so the customer gets only $1, 500. 9 per cent a year, which is under the Criminal Rule cap.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the customer defaults, Mounteer told everyone, the company can seize the vehicle and sell it. But, because it bases its legal claim on already owning your car, it doesn't have to return to the borrower every amount it gets in excess of the money owed. To make sure you could lose, in their example, an $18, 000 car -- additionally however much you refunded before defaulting -- to cover a loan that get only $1, 500 in your pocket.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are some other variations of how businesses rationalize the hefty up-front charge. A reader e-mailed me a copy of agreement with a corporation that charged him $1, 200 &quot;to arrange credit for the Borrower&quot; associated with just $6, 200. So the borrower got to get just $5, 000 in his pocket (secured by the $28, 000 car), and was obligated to settle nearly $8, 500 in 12 monthly payments -- or he'll lose the vehicle.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In one of Mounteer's payday loan suits, the B. C. And there's no excuse for continuing to take a seat on their thumbs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JhcnJ5dGhvbWFzMTEyOS5wb3N0ZXJvdXMuY29tL2Nhci10aXRsZS1sb2Fucy0xODY3NA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Car Title Loans&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>