<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="15d76a0814e4ab13f9f03152340f8571">			The speaker system can be thought of in two parts: the channel amplifier and the physical speaker units.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Car amplifiers power the speakers in your car stereo system to provide crisp sound quality at high volumes. Each speaker requires one channel of amplification. This means a 4-channel amplifier, will support four speakers.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;And choice of speakers is not limited either. With a range of options for your basic stereo speakers [2-channel], you can supplement the high note quality using a tweeter and the low bass notes with a sub-woofer. This gives you a standard 4-channel sound system that will rival your home audio system.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Adding to a basic car stereo option typically involves adding subwoofers, amplifiers and crossovers to tailor the output sound to personal tastes.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;This does not mean the result is the boorish, obnoxious bass boom boxing that invades the entire neighbourhood. A subwoofer adds quality and purity to music.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;For details of specifications on each part of your &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fcar-computer-1006%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/car-computer-1006/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Car Computer&quot;&gt;;Car Computer&lt;/a&gt;; system, see Go-Reviews.com &amp;#8211; Car Electronics Section&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;The main factors in selecting car speakers are:&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;ul&gt;; &lt;li&gt;;Design or Speaker Type&lt;/li&gt;; &lt;li&gt;;Technical Specifications&lt;/li&gt;; &lt;li&gt;;Fitting &amp;amp; Mounting&lt;/li&gt;; &lt;/ul&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Speaker design is about the combination of sound drivers for midrange, subwoofer and tweeter. Depending upon the combination, the set is known as a two-way, three-way or four-way speaker system.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fcar-speaker-313%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/car-speaker-313/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Car Speaker&quot;&gt;;Car Speaker&lt;/a&gt;; specifications are similar to home audio speakers; the main difference in technical specification to compensate for the lower power outputs of car stereo receivers.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;The speaker technical specifications include sensitivity, frequency response, signal to noise ratio, power handling and impedance. We will look at these specification in more detail in subsequent articles.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;The fittings and mountings are selected depending upon where you choose to position the speakers. Car audio speakers are either: top mounted or bottom mounted. Clearance depth is most important when installing new speakers in a non-factory speaker location. So check all of your &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fhot%2Fp-power-inverter.html%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/hot/p-power-inverter.html&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Power Inverter&quot;&gt;;Power Inverter&lt;/a&gt;; carefully before purchase.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;With such a range of combinations available the Internet provides a valuable resource in car electronics reviews. Sites like Go-Reviews.com seek out reviews and consolidate the recommendations to give you a quick reference buying guide.&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="181918849de2f1a31b864daa46a5b4e1">			When searching for a used car, one of the most important factors to consider is whether the car you are looking for really is worth its tag price. Even though the car may look like quite a deal, it is possible that you are being ripped off. Here are a few tips to help you make that decision when considering used cars.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;1. Do A Little Research&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;When you find a used &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fcar-computer-1006%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/car-computer-1006/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Car Computer&quot;&gt;;Car Computer&lt;/a&gt;; that catches your fancy make sure you do research on that car. Find out how much that car costs if it were brand new. You should also look into whether the car is still in production and if its &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fplastic-parts-478%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/plastic-parts-478/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Plastic Parts&quot;&gt;;Plastic Parts&lt;/a&gt;; are still available. You could also try a little shop hopping to compare used car prices among cars of the same value and same age.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;If a car?s price is too low, that should send you into a state of alarm. It is possible that the car is much more trouble than it is worth.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;If it is too expensive, you may want to ask why that is so.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;2. The Older The Car The Cheaper Is Should Become&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Brand new cars typically lose up to 30% in their value in 3 years, and by the time the car is 5 years old, it may have lost up to 65%. If you know the car?s original price, you may want to use this rule of the thumb for your estimation.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;3. Use A Third-Party Information Service&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Car Fax is a good way to find out about used &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fcar_accessories_303%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/car_accessories_303/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Car Accessories&quot;&gt;;Car Accessories&lt;/a&gt;; histories. They offer a service that will give you a detailed history of the car you are interested in. The information included will typically include accident history and insurance data.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Kelly Blue Book is one of the most comprehensive used car value listings around. It would be a good idea to take a peek into their services for an updated list of hundreds and hundreds of used car values.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;4. Take A Mechanic With You&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;A car?s value is also directly related to its running condition. If you are not that well versed in mechanics and cars, you may want to take a mechanic along so that he or she can evaluate whether the car really is worth the used dealer?s tag price.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Some used car dealers will offer cars that are defective and try to hawk them by sweetening the deal. Beware of these kinds of car dealers.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Try to look for a reputable dealer. The past experience of your acquaintances will be very valuable in evaluating a car dealership.&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="1f3bf79c874b2a082d474144203c15ec">			The &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fpower-steering-pump-556%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/power-steering-pump-556/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Power Steering Pump&quot;&gt;;Power Steering Pump&lt;/a&gt;; is a mechanism applied in many vehicles to help the van&amp;#8217;s controller to manage the car while in motion. Power steering is meant to help the person controlling the van by deploying some power to a part of the engine especially when negotiating bends, corners and/or turns, sharp or not sharp. The steering pump contains many fundamentals that help the driver to feel and experience a smooth drive. Such items mounted on this part of the car engine include; fluids cover plates for suction passage, and discharge purposes; a rotor which is located in the cam chamber and has vanes which can be slid.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;Many companies manufacturing vehicles have changed into a more manual means of controlling the car. Many cars that rely on the front wheel drive are being produced. This has made the cars to be heavier and hence the need implement manual drive. Therefore, creation of the power assisted cars. There are two types of this mechanism. The system can either be an electronic system or a hydraulic one; though some companies also manufacture cars in-built with a combination of the two.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;In the hydraulic systems, the car engine is supported by the steering pump when the van is moving and/or trying to shift direction from one and to another end. The assist only comes when the driver is trying to turn the &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Fsteering-wheel-501%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/steering-wheel-501/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Steering Wheel&quot;&gt;;Steering Wheel&lt;/a&gt;; during a turn. When the two are compared and contrasted, one will find that electric option is more efficient than the other one. This is because in the electric system, the electric motor needs only to supply help or support when the wheel is turned while in the hydraulic mechanism, the drain must keep on running. Since there is use of hydraulic power fluid, it therefore causes environmental and health hazard from the leakage. This makes the electronic system a better choice for pollution free societies.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;For a vehicle to move from one point to another, it must be controlled or driven. The engine of the car is what applies all the mechanism it needs in order for it to move. The power steering pump is one of the elements of the engine in most cars. It is attached on the engine using belts and winches.&lt;/p&gt;; &lt;p&gt;;The hydraulic &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gasgoo.com%2Fauto-products%2Flubrication-system-443%2F%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.gasgoo.com/auto-products/lubrication-system-443/&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; title=&quot;Lubrication System&quot;&gt;;Lubrication System&lt;/a&gt;; is the most commonly used. The steering pump as implemented here has a fin-like item that is used to guide the hydraulic fluid through the main passages. It therefore must be able to regulate the pressure by increasing or reducing the pressure and force depending on the status of the car at the moment. At a resting position, the system produces a lot of pressure than when in motion. This is because the van&amp;#8217;s speed monitors the pressure produced. That is, the higher the speed the more the production of fluid. This employs the use of a rotary control device which is present on the power steering pump for the purpose of detecting the force applied on the wheels.&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>