<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="191de1a919aea6a84308877f5d0e5ee4">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGx3YWxscGFwZXJzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;wall walpaper&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Installing your mural &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To hang up any mural, assistance may be required if you are not comfortable taking the chance yourself. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wallpaper murals allow you to create something very creative on all the walls of your home; like you could have the walls in your daughters room look like the inside of a castle, or the walls inside your sons room wearing his favorite cars on a wallpaper mural. Wallpaper murals are certainly not just floral, colorful and pretty anymore; these days you may by almost anything for a wallpaper mural. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rub on wall transfers are also a great type involving mural for the walls in your home. All you do is actually stick the transfer sheet to your wall, apply the design just by smoothing the sheet with an application tool (An issue firm and flat). Then once it can be all smoothed out relating to the wall and there are generally no lumps, bumps, or even air bubbles, simply peel off the sheet and the picture is in the wall! People will think you have the hidden talent of artist as it will look hand-painted! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Stencil walls murals are great if you would like to do all the effort yourself. You can either purchase the stencil on its own, or if you have none of your own equipment, there are mural stencil kits available that contain all you need to create that lovely look. The kit includes the stencils, paints, brushes and whatever else you need. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The paint by number murals is exhilarating for a kid's room, to develop that look a kid will enjoy. Most of these kits come with a pattern transfer sheet and as soon as you transfer the sheet to your wall, you may make use of the color guide to fill in the pattern, or you can be even more creative and use your imagination and colors to develop your own hand colored wall mural. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wall murals are there to get rid of that boring feeling in your home and create more of a &quot;home&quot; feeling. By personalizing ones walls, you will feel more at home. And it is even better when it is your own designs! &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Ceramic wall murals may be used as decorative accessories, to lend a distinctive taste and style to a room. Ceramic wall murals include art pieces created from clay and porcelain. They brighten plain walls and enhance the room with a restored freshness and energy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ceramic walls murals are essentially tiles, which can be hand painted and display exotic patterns and designs. The tiles used are water resistant and glazed ceramic tiles. The tiles used can be of different colors which include, light yellow ochre, cream, ivory, sea green, darkness blue and terracotta. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ceramic wall murals differ in dimensions, shape and design. In the matter of big murals, the tiles are generally cut into pieces. Then the pieces are individually designed to fit within the measurement of the wall. Some of theses murals get borders. They can use to enhance the beauty in the outdoors and indoors as well. These are used just by many interior decorators to consider liveliness and beauty on the designs. The ceramic wall murals are a form of architecture, used in the decoration of many ancient buildings. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ceramic wall murals present an advantage over the background murals, in the sense that they can be easily cleaned. The colors don't fade away. They are glazed and treated at a temperature that seals their colors.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f2924ef710a079459dde0293aad89582">			.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbGx3YWxscGFwZXJzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;wall murals&lt;/a&gt;;Wall murals date oh no- prehistoric times when they were simple drawings found within caves. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Hanging your mural &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To hang up any mural, assistance may be required if you are not comfortable taking second hand smoke yourself. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A large micro fiber sectional sofa within a curved pattern was situated just far enough faraway from the TV (about the middle of the room), so that the surround sound speakers on all 4 corners with the room could be heard with peak precision. With oak bookshelves and two oak tables with matching chairs and curtains in multi-colored earth tones, the one thing left to say has been... &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Yes, this room boasts a beautiful wall mural. This mural can be an artist's rendition of downtown city with skyscrapers superimposed on the other. This time the designs are magnificent shades with browns, golds, maroons, ebony, yellow, gray and white. This is modern urban art tastefully done. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So now they ask me to go by them into the kitchen area. Here the cabinets are oak in the honey finish. All the counter surfaces are granite in a medium brown. The walls above that counters are mosaic mural tiles that picture fresh fruit platters and wine containers. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The dining room table and chairs are made of mahogany with a finish near to the same finish of this cabinets. There is a stainless island counter during the kitchen with a small sink and a cutting board inserted into the top next to this sink. Above the island is a chandelier hanging pot rack. This lighted pot tray also illuminates the island counter to shed light when preparing meals. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Did My partner and i mention the mural relating to the far wall of your kitchen? Now this is stunning and I will explain why. First, just to make sure you know, the name about this colorful mural is Courtyard View. This is an artist's rendition of an tropical sea shore view on the cobblestone courtyard with luxurious foliage. Absolutely amazing potted flowers 100 % beautiful deep colored shades of red, pink and deep red line the courtyard leading to a white linen tablecloth covered round table and seat. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sitting in the middle of the table is a wine and a pitcher associated with fruit punch. In between the lavish potted flowers are generally lush green leaf plants lining the way down the courtyard. In the distant background can be a palm tree shoreline with mountains rising straight from the sea. Wow, does this mural make a striking impression when you enter the kitchen. Need I say much more? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;From the kitchen, Jake and Diane lead me back to the stairway by entry entrance and we all head upstairs to Sarah's master bedroom. This bedroom is just about all done up in colors of lavender and red. The bed is a white wood framed canopy bed which has a white lace canopy that's lavender fringe around the whole outer edge. The curtains relating to the windows match the wide lace canopy. The dresser, night stands and hutch are typically finished in antique white-colored. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guess precisely what is on the wall opposite the bed? Did We hear you say wall mural? You are correct again. This time the wall mural is considered Unicorn Garden. This truly is a heavenly scene. I hope my description comes near to the awesome beauty of that mural. I'll do my best.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>