<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="db152e917604420677a96ab9698c750e">			Travelling costs are mounting  every year, and today even the well-seasoned and cost careful budget traveller is feeling the pinch in his pockets. When looking to plan a holiday, accommodation prices are often the biggest worry. Yet accommodation in Malta is increasingly favoured towards inexpensive travel.&lt;br /&gt;;Budget means that travellers have more cash to spend on these areas of the holiday that they really enjoy, such as going out to wine and dine, indulging in activities such as water sports, badger-carting, and other family activities.Inexpensive accommodation can vary, from small hostels and aparthotels to three-star or less hotels, yet finding the right deal can often take time.&lt;br /&gt;;It is always advisable to do your research. Looking online is everyone’s preferred method, but can often leave travellers wrongly advised. Check how recent the photos are, give the hotel a call, look for travel reviews...there are many sources out there to guide just such an occasion, and if successful, a fantastic vacation awaits.&lt;br /&gt;;One of the finest examples of budget accommodation here in Malta is the new Hotel Valentina, a charming Boutique hotel comprising of just under a hundred rooms. Its quality prices more than make up for its charm, and its facilities may be less numerous than in a luxury five-star hotel, but the service and personality of the hotel far exceeds expectations. Welcomed into the sophisticated blend of Mediterranean ambience and contemporary, Hotel Valentina is nestled in the modern night life town of St. Julian’s.&lt;br /&gt;;This charming hotel keeps all of its promises for the traveller hoping to cut costs on Malta accommodation, settling its guests in luxury guestrooms with all necessary facilities, from air conditioning to a safe, mini bar and telephone, without the excessive prices. Cleaning service and towels are provided daily together with shower gel and soap on arrival, and friendly and {knowledgeable|helpful|hospitable) staff are always happy to assist the guests in a professional manner, creating an ambience of comfort with a Mediterranean touch.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob3RlbHZhbGVudGluYS5jb20vZW4vYWJvdXQvbG9jYXRpb24_" target="_blank"&gt;;Accommodation Malta&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="7a4bd259e45367eaea5b47ce237e4794">			Travel costs are mounting  year on year, and today even the well-seasoned and cost careful budget traveller is feeling the pinch in his pockets. When looking to plan a holiday, accommodation costs are often the biggest issue. Yet accommodation in Malta is increasingly marketed towards inexpensive travel.&lt;br /&gt;;Cheaper accommodation in Malta means that travellers have more cash to spend on these areas of the holiday that they really enjoy, such as going out to wine and dine, indulging in activities such as water sports, go-carting, and other family events.Cheap accommodation can vary, from small hostels and aparthotels to three-star or less hotels, yet finding the right deal can often take time.&lt;br /&gt;;It is always advisable to do your research. Looking on the internet is everyone’s preferred method, but can often leave travellers disappointed. Check how recent the images are, give the hotel a call, look for travel reviews...there are many resources out there to guide just such an occasion, and if successful, a fantastic vacation awaits.&lt;br /&gt;;One of the finest examples of cheap accommodation here in Malta is the new Hotel Valentina, a charming Boutique hotel comprising of just under a hundred rooms. Its quality costs more than make up for its charm, and its facilities may be less numerous than in a luxury five-star hotel, but the service and personality of the hotel far exceeds expectations. Welcomed into the sophisticated blend of Mediterranean ambience and modern flair, Hotel Valentina is nestled in the modern night life town of St. Julian’s.&lt;br /&gt;;This charming hotel keeps all of its promises for the holidaymaker looking to cut costs on Malta accommodation, settling its guests in stylish rooms with all necessary facilities, from air conditioning to a safe, mini fridge and telephone, without the luxury prices. Cleaning service and towels are provided daily together with shower gel and soap on arrival, and friendly and {knowledgeable|helpful|hospitable) staff are always happy to assist the guests in a professional manner, creating an environment of comfort with a Mediterranean touch.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob3RlbHZhbGVudGluYS5jb20vZW4vYWJvdXQvYWJvdXR1cw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>