<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="8ecc60501c723a529162c2bdb3d8f47f">			&lt;P&gt;The &quot;;Idol Gives Back&quot;; charity concert held by American Idol will continue its charity activities. 4 Things You Must Keep in Mind About &lt;A title=&quot;;ed hardy&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.edhardysaleuk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bed"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.edhardysaleuk.com/&quot;;&gt;ed&lt;/a&gt; hardy&lt;/A&gt; As a program which will be broadcasted during eighth-final in American Idol one season.A documentary film that records the moderator of [American Idol&quot;;, three jurors, and some idol stars visiting poor areas will be screened in the [Idol Gives Back&quot;; concert, and the money for charity will be raised through the activity at that evening.How to Protect the Picture of &lt;A title=&quot;;parker pens&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.parkerpenshop.co.uk%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bparker"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.parkerpenshop.co.uk&quot;;&gt;parker&lt;/a&gt; pens&lt;/A&gt; ?&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;It is determined that the 2010 Idol Gives Back chatity vocal concert will be held on 21th April. &lt;A title=&quot;;ed hardy&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.edhardyclothes.uk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bed"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.edhardyclothes.uk.com/&quot;;&gt;ed&lt;/a&gt; hardy&lt;/A&gt; In StuttgartMoney raised by the activity mainly is donated to Malaria No More, Save The Children and United Nations Foundation.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;This is the third time American Idol hosts Idol Gives Back charity concert.&quot;;This is our opportunity to reach out and support the people of America and around the world who need our compassion and generosity to improve their lives.It is our pride that American Idol supports the charity cause.&quot;; Simon Fuller, the producer of American Idol said.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Since the first time on stage of [Idol Gives Back&quot;; in 2007 more than 1.4 million USD of charity money has been raised successively through the charity concert.By then, American president Obama, the winner of 2009 Noble Peace Prize, will attend the concert as an invited guest.By then, the 2009 Nobel Peace Prize laureate, the American President Obama will present as the honored guest.&lt;/P&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="fa87abd37b5b1b0813d7ef243d881cd8">			&lt;P&gt;On Feburuary 16,2007, just retired UN Secretary General Annan held a charity dinner in a manor of Texas in order to raise money for needy children in Africa and invited to the dinner were all wealthy businessmen and celebrities. What's the Best Gift Ideas This Year? Must-Have &lt;A title=&quot;;parker fountain pens&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.parkerpenshop.co.uk%2Ffountain%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bparker"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.parkerpenshop.co.uk/fountain&quot;;&gt;parker&lt;/a&gt; fountain pens&lt;/A&gt; ! Not long before the banquet began, an old woman came to the entrance of manor with a girl; the girl held a porcelain pot which looked very delicacy.To Criticize the Reasons of the Popularity of &lt;A title=&quot;;ed hardy&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.edhardys.uk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bed"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.edhardys.uk.com/&quot;;&gt;ed&lt;/a&gt; hardy&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Anthony who kept the security in the estate at the entrance stopped them. &quot;;Welcome, please show me the invitations, thank you.&quot;; Anthony said. &quot;;Invitation, I'm sorry, we have not received an invitation and she wants to come, I come with her.&quot;;The old woman said to Anthony stroking the girl's head. [I`m very sorry, except workers, you can not be in without invitation cards.&quot;; Anthony said. [Why? Is this place holding a charity banquet? We come to show our heart, is this impossible?&quot;;How I Use Evernote to Organize Everything (25) &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;The old woman said with a solemn expression on her face &quot;;my sweety litttle Lucy decides to donate all her money from her saving box when she is aware that there will be hold a charity banquet for children in Africa and she wants to do something for them&quot;;. Anthony explained: Yes, there will be a charity dinner here, people invited to attend are all very important persons, they will contribute generously to the children of Africa. Anthony came to a halt and said again,&quot;;I'm glad you have come here with love. But, I think this occasion is not suitable for you to go in.&quot;; [Uncle, Charity is not the money, is the heart!&quot;;The silent little girl Lucy asked Anthony. She made Anthony shocked.[I know that the invited people are very rich. They will take out a lot of money, I don`t have that much money, and this is all that I have. If I can`t come in, please bring this in for me!&quot;; After she said that the little girl Lucy handed the piggy bank Anthony.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Anthony, not knowing whether to accept it or not, heard someone's voice. &quot;;You don't need an invitation. Kid you are right, charity means the donation of kindness instead of money. You can go in, all the people with kindness can go in.&quot;; The speaker was an old man. He was smiling, standing beside the little Lucy. Then, he bowed to small Lucy and said a few words. Then straightened and took an invitation to Anthony: &quot;;Can I bring her in?&quot;; After checking the invitation, Anthony saluted to the old man. &quot;;Of course, Mr Warren Buffet.&quot;;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;The leading role of the charity dinner that day was not the proponent Annan, not Buffett who donated three million U.S. dollars, not Bill Gates who donate 8 million U.S. Dollars, but little Lucy who donated only 30 U.S. dollars and 25 cents. And the slogan of the dinner has become such a word: &quot;;Charity is not money, but it is the heart.&quot;; The next day, the major U.S media have resorted to these words as a title report on the charity dinner. Seeing the reports, many common Americans said that they would donate for those African poor children.&lt;/P&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="429ab574f7d9e10a986c0be28aad5c42">			&lt;P&gt;According to Reuters, in prison, Roman Polansky said he intended to finish the movie The Ghost in jail in the hope that he would attend Berlin International Film Festival with this movie next February. What's the Best Gift Ideas This Year? Must-Have &lt;A title=&quot;;parker fountain pens&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.parkerpenshop.co.uk%2Ffountain%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bparker"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.parkerpenshop.co.uk/fountain&quot;;&gt;parker&lt;/a&gt; fountain pens&lt;/A&gt; !&lt;A title=&quot;;parker fountain pens&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.parkerpenshop.co.uk%2Ffountain%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bparker"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.parkerpenshop.co.uk/fountain&quot;;&gt;parker&lt;/a&gt; fountain pens&lt;/A&gt; Trend You Should Not Disremember&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;According to Robert Harris the screenwriter of the film &quot;;gunmen&quot;; said: &quot;;Polanski hopes to complete the new film timely before the Film Festival in Berlin.&quot;; &quot;; I think even if he can not call in the cell, he still can convey his thoughts to the outside world.&quot;; &quot;;How do people think this film is another matter. I don't know how the future will the film be in the condition of the director's present state, there is nothing worse than the negative publicity.&quot;; He added. Polanski who is 76-year-old was arrested last month in Zurich, the director of &quot;;Chinatown&quot;; was charged with a number of charges because he bed with a 13-year-old girl in 1997. He fled out of the US in 1978 and has spent most of his time in France. He has dual nationalities of France and Poland.Trend Alert! Jessica Alba in &lt;A title=&quot;;ed hardy&quot;; href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.edhardyclothes.uk.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bed"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.edhardyclothes.uk.com/&quot;;&gt;ed&lt;/a&gt; hardy&lt;/A&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Gunman is Polanski's latest work, starred by Pierce Brosnan and Ivan McGregor. This political horror film tells a story between the former British prime minister and a gunman. The hero former British prime minister is said to have surprisingly a lot in common with Tony Blare, so the political will and movie background are to become the focus people are concerned about.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;P&gt;Harris also said that when Polanski was arrested, the director has completed the work of the film clips. He is now issuing orders in the prison and giving instruction on film incidental music. &quot;;It will be a nightmare if the director is still in the prison on the day of exhibition of film. But we will deal with the situation well. I am sure he eagers the success of the film since he has benn working on it for two years.&quot;; Polanski was the winner of both the Golden Palm in Cannes International Film Festival and Best Director in Oscar. However, he didn't attend the Oscar Award Ceremony in the U.S.&lt;/P&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>