<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b531002599022d8d65a0c2f0dca4d82d">			I didn't want to become an object of ridicule among my friends who mostly were either skinny or had lean muscle.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obviously, I'd never entertain the idea of having surgery to get rid of male breasts or chest fat. For me to cure gynecomastia I only had one option: natural cures without any surgery! &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gynecomastiareview.org%2Fgynexin_for_breast_reduction.php"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.gynecomastiareview.org/gynexin_for_breast_reduction.php&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gynecomastia is in basic terms, male breasts or excessive chest fat on a man. Many of these men can actually look like transsexuals or women from a distance and find it difficult to talk about their loose breasts and fat chest. In the film &quot;;Fight Club&quot;; you may recall a character with huge male breasts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;While exercise is a very positive initiative, it can appear to make male breasts actually bigger, instead of smaller and tighter. And this is the last thing you need!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How is this possible?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What happens during exercise is that the muscle you are building actually builds under the layers of soft flesh or chest fat, causing your chest to expand outwards. The exercises that build muscle don't always reduce the chest fat, and so your chest may still be fairly wobbly and unsightly even after building up your chest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We'll discuss how to cure Gynecomastia naturally soon, but first of all it's important you know what is the cause of your male breasts situation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How did you start getting male breasts and chest fat in the first place? I researched this myself because the last thing I needed was for my chest fat to come back after all the effort I'd spent toning my chest and losing weight.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Beer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Beer drinkers are very often (not always) rounder, have softer bodies and occasionally have male breasts. Now I used to think that it was a myth about beer making you fat and soft, as I always managed to keep more or less in shape and would drink beer 3 times per week at least and sometimes quite a lot of it. But now I realize that after a while, that was one of the main reasons I eventually found myself with too much chest fat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The hops in beer do actually encourage estrogen production in your body. As estrogen is a female hormone, developing male breasts to some extent can be expected.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Foods&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Too much of some types of food and not enough of other kinds of food can lead to lower testosterone levels and high estrogen levels in a man.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you consider that women are advised to eat foods such as tofu, soy protein powder, soy milk and tempeh when they are pregnant (to boost female hormones) it becomes pretty obvious you should avoid these foods!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Chemicals&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Bad old chemicals in plastics are being pumped out in huge volume every single day all over the world. Some of these plastics are estrogen mimicking, which means that they can actually induce estrogen production in your body. Some of these can also be found in cleaning detergents.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Lack of activity&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Physically inactive men who rarely exercise may also have male breasts from the fat deposits that build up over time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How To Cure Gynecomastia Naturally Without Surgery&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Improve Diet And Drinking Habits&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is quite easy for you to do, although you might not like doing it! You'll have to stop drinking beer, preferably completely to cure gynecomastia. Don't replace beer with other alcohol either; heavy drinking can knock your T levels right down and make your body soft again. Stick to red wine preferably and keep your limits low.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As for food, avoid the estrogenic foods mentioned above and eat more cauliflower, cabbage and sprouts. Whether you like or hate these, they help keep estrogen levels nice and low for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lifestyle&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need a lifestyle which avoids contact with plastics, chemicals and cleaning detergents if you can.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Drink filtered water instead of bottled water. Avoid packaged and processed food. Eat organic food and include more vegetables (broccoli, cauliflower, cabbage) and lean meat. Take a look at all detergents in your house and see if you can reduce your exposure to them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.gynecomastiareview.org%2Fgynexin_for_breast_reduction.php"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.gynecomastiareview.org/gynexin_for_breast_reduction.php&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>