<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="dfb33399123f4c0a39ee55454616ba64">			The colour with the lens sunglasses&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The sun glasses &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cheapsunglasses-outlet.org"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cheapsunglasses-outlet.org&lt;/a&gt;;   greatest lens is dark brown colour of colour, grey and put on green department, allow us see, all types of colour to fasten the protective effect!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1: darkish brown department of dark brown lens can absorb the light of purple, blue, virtually 100% in the ultraviolet absorption and infrared. Downy tonal, allow the eyes are less likely to become drained. It is extremely very good protection lens.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2 grey department: can fully absorbed infrared, ultraviolet ray, and most and will not change the scenery of the authentic colour. Gentle nature will be the colour quite popular lens choice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3 green fasten: and gray department can take up exactly the same glasses all solitary infrared and 99% of ultraviolet ray of mild green, red, can also be blocked, but occasionally the colour of the scenery in via green had been changed right after lens. But since green cool and refreshing feeling, deliver an individual relaxed to eye safety is good, as well as the sun eyeglasses lens is really a wonderful option.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4: red series of red of ultraviolet and infrared lens cut off the impact and three sorts of comparison, is decrease, some wavelengths short mild barrier home is much better. Pink color, gentle lens to some wearer talking, psychological help higher compared to the impact of essentially.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5 yellow fastens: yellow fastens lens can take in ultraviolet mild and 100% of the majority of the blue light, absorb blue light, see after the scene will be far more clear, so we can locate, hunting and shooting, wearing yellow lens when filter is very typical oh!!!!!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sunglasses of the different Uses&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sunglasses to press utility can typically be divided into the mirror, mild colour sunglasses and also the special use sunglasses three classes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The so-called shading, just as its title implies is always to be the mirror, with people in the sunshine by adjusting the pupil measurement normally to alter the flux, when mild intensity as opposed to human eye modify capacity, will cause harm to the human eye. So in outdoor activity places, especially within the summer time, a lot of people are employed to block the sun shading mirror, so that you can lessen the tiredness in the eyes caused by regulation or light from the harm the stimulus.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mild color to the sun block sunglasses function as opposed to mirror, but its wealthy colours, suitable for all kinds of gown collocation with use, have really strong adornment impact. Light colour sunglasses simply because its rich colors, designs, received the favour of fashionable youthful gens, ladies to their favor is my lifestyle. The unique use sunglasses have quite strong keep out the operate from the sun, utilized for seashore, skiing, climb watch for the light through the sun is powerful discipline, its ultraviolet efficiency indicators are substantial request.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>