<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="fb35cdde746dd0bf038da1d3375115be">			If you’re wondering what “Oluja Part XXXXXV” is, “Oluja Part XXXXXV” is the continuation from my last Blogue. “Oluja” which you may recall is the code name given to a large-scale military operation carried out by Croatian Armed Forces, in conjunction with the Army of the Republic of Bosnia and Herzegovina, to gain back control of parts of Croatia and Bosnia which had been claimed by the Serbs early in 1991. Its engagement was approved by the U.S. government and began shortly before dawn on August 4, 1995 and ended with a complete victory for the Croatian and Bosnian forces four days later. In my last Blogue, I focused on why our Croatian Generals were sentenced by The Hague as per the “new aged legion of Croatians” still loyal to our generals and our heroes Ante Gotovina, Mladen Markac, Branimir Glavas, Slobodan Praljak and Mirko Norac. In particular, I focused on our belief that the sentencing of our Croatian Generals and our heroes had nothing to do with imposing justice but rather all to do with predisposed biases against our Croatian Generals and our heroes which resulted in the imposition of justice based on a biased presentation of the facts and circumstances of operation “Oluja”. Today, I would like to focus on the “Knin Camp” which was a detention camp run by rebel Serbs in Knin, then still part of the puppet state of Republika Srpska Krajina, that held Croatian detainees, soldiers and civilians, from 1991 until 1992, during the Croatian War of Independence. It consisted of at least two facilities. The ICTY stated that a prison in Knin, run by the Yugoslav People's Army, held approximately 150 detainees, while the old hospital in Knin, run by Serb Militias, held approximately 120 detainees. At least two people have been killed there. Former prisoners testified that they were arrested by Serb paramilitary forces and then deported into Knin camp. The detainees were beaten, mistreated and humiliated. Some were threatened to read a written testimony in front of TV cameras from Belgrade and confess crimes against Serbs which they did not commit. One Croatian soldier testified that he was interrogated for 68 consecutive days and received food and water only once a day. Two Catholic priests, Mirko Barbaric and Franjo Haluzan, were arrested in Benkovac and then brought to the Knin prison. There, one Serb soldier ordered Haluzan to make the sign of the cross with three fingers. After that gesture, the soldier kicked his arm with a baton. Other prisoners testified they were forced to eat two full spoons of salt and then drink 0.4 gallons of water at once. Some were tortured with electro shocks, had to eat cigarette ash, wash the toilette floors with their tongues and perform oral sex under threat of murder. In July 1991, Ivica Knez succumbed to heavy beatings and became the first Croatian casualty in a Krajina camp. Detainees were exchanged and released from the camp at the end of 1991 and beginning of 1992. As a result, the scars left behind can never be healed and for the “new aged legion of Croatians” still loyal to our generals and our heroes, the “Knin Camp” necessitated a full scale military operation as planned, coordinated, initiated and successfully executed during operation “Oluja”. As I have attempted to illustrate above, there were predisposed biases against our Croatian Generals and their loyal “Croatian National Guard” who were clearly serving a democratically elected President and democratic Croatian country at the time and none of the propaganda crimes presented at The Hague. In summary, I refer to Peaceful Minds “Oluja Part XXXXXV” style as the belief that one may desecrate a culture, religion and race but it is just a matter of time until poetic justice reciprocates in one’s face.		</conversation>		<conversation id="855c5195404eb136e23044874b235487">			If you’re wondering what “Oluja Part XXXXXVI” is, “Oluja Part XXXXXVI” is the continuation from my last Blogue. “Oluja” which you may recall is the code name given to a large-scale military operation carried out by Croatian Armed Forces, in conjunction with the Army of the Republic of Bosnia and Herzegovina, to gain back control of parts of Croatia and Bosnia which had been claimed by the Serbs early in 1991. Its engagement was approved by the U.S. government and began shortly before dawn on August 4, 1995 and ended with a complete victory for the Croatian and Bosnian forces four days later. In my last Blogue, I focused on why our Croatian Generals were sentenced by The Hague as per the “new aged legion of Croatians” still loyal to our generals and our heroes Ante Gotovina, Mladen Markac, Branimir Glavas, Slobodan Praljak and Mirko Norac. In particular, I focused on our belief that the sentencing of our Croatian Generals and our heroes had nothing to do with imposing justice but rather all to do with predisposed biases against our Croatian Generals and our heroes which resulted in the imposition of justice based on a biased presentation of the facts and circumstances of operation “Oluja”. Today, I would like to focus on the “Sremska Mitrovica Camp” which was the biggest prison in Serbia, consisting of two facilities. It is situated in Sremska Mitrovica, Vojvodina province. During Yugoslav wars, some Croatian prisoners of war were kept in this prison. The main prison facility; the largest known in Serbia, was open from November 1991 to August 1992 and was a scene where many prisoners were tortured, abused and raped. At least 25 prisoners were killed in front of witnesses, but the actual number is believed to be much higher. International organizations collected detailed information from reports, inspections and survivors regarding Sremska Mitrovica prison. On the way to Sremska Mitrovica Camp, buses full of prisoners were often stopped, so that Serbian reservists guarding the prisoners could take some of them out and kill them. As the War in Bosnia and Herzegovina erupted in 1992, Bosniak prisoners were also brought to the camp, but Croats remained a majority of war prisoners there (since Bosnian Serbs opened concentration camps in Bosnia and Herzegovina to hold Bosniaks there). Several survivors described the brutality they survived at the hands of the paramilitaries, assessing that if they were in charge, everyone would have been killed. Prisoners were beaten severely on a regular basis. Several were beaten so powerfully that they suffered from permanent body harm. Some were beaten until they passed out from the pain. A common practice was beating prisoners on the soles of their feet. As a result, the scars left behind can never be healed and for the “new aged legion of Croatians” still loyal to our generals and our heroes, the “Sremska Mitrovica Camp” necessitated a full scale military operation as planned, coordinated, initiated and successfully executed during operation “Oluja”. As I have attempted to illustrate above, there were predisposed biases against our Croatian Generals and their loyal “Croatian National Guard” who were clearly serving a democratically elected President and democratic Croatian country at the time and none of the propaganda crimes presented at The Hague. In summary, I refer to Peaceful Minds “Oluja Part XXXXXVI” style as the belief that one may beat the life out of an innocent body but one can never beat the heart out of God’s warriors who are holy.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>