<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="5d552bba3bede93167edcf3e7cee9b4c">			Betting on horse racing is a superb sport, one that indeed can help to create a second income from betting profits. The biggest issues most amateur gamblers face when attacking the bookmakers are however, self control,belief and confidence. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Betting against the market signals or indeed what most read in the racing press is a very hard skill to master. Indeed it actually goes against human nature to take an opposite stance to the general consensus. This however is exactly what is needed to win long term when betting on horse racing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The bookmakers know that come the start of all the major race meetings, punters are queing up to part with their money. They also know that a majority of them will do so without the knowledge or indeed control to threaten their profit and loss.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As recently as August in 2011 during the York Ebor meeting this was proven in no uncertain terms when those blind punters betting on horse racing backed in short priced runners that stood no chance on the day compared to their price. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For example on day one of the Ebor meeting, both Irish runners, Seville and Await The Dawn were backed as if defeat were out of the question. Going off at restricive prices of 5/6 and 8/13 and both were beaten! Now I hate to suggest or write about incidences like this after the event, but I personally was trying to educate as many on the day to avoid backing these horses.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The same thing happened on day two, Wild Coco was a hot 11/8 favourite of a listed race, only to go down the pan and not even place!! Some horses should be favourite and others not, what you have to calculate is whether the price is fair.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These horses were vulnerable, had yet to win races at the class they were pitched in at, yet those blind amateurs betting on horse racing on the day were happy enough to literally hand over their money to the layers. They ended up with seriously burned fingers and rightly so.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The lesson here is simple. Never follow a markets opinion, always and I mean ALWAYS make your own mind up when betting on horse racing. At least even if you are wrong you can only blame yourself!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The other lesson is simple. Not every odds on shot from Ireland will be beaten, however when betting on horse racing these are golden opportunities to back against the market and take the money from losing punters.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are educated enough to know which horses to take these short price runners on with, then back your opinions against the favourites. You can also simply lay these selections on the exchanges when &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fforbettingonhorseracing.co.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://forbettingonhorseracing.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;; these days and for many, this is the simple route.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remember the next time you are watching a big race meeting and the crowd smash in to a short priced favourite, remember that virtually no horse is unbeatable, they are a rare breed. Make your own decisions and go against the grain when &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fforbettingonhorseracing.co.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://forbettingonhorseracing.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;;, it is the most satisfying feeling in the world when you get it right!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>