<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="6301debe84d4e3f8d38dae9e96e01b51">			Peace to all, I’m Julia and I do want to share something to my fellow readers. When I was still a 7th grader, I experienced a hearing difficulty. When I reached high school I was already using a hearing aid. But I’m not totally deaf; it’s just that I only hear a minimal amount of sound from my surrounding. When I started working after the graduation in college, I find it hard to travel to and from the office where I worked. That is why I decided to learn how to drive and finally obtained a driver’s license even if I have a difficulty in hearing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Only last January of 2010, I managed to have a car loan from one of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;dealership&lt;/a&gt;;  that I found online. Well I visited their office first, talked to their sales manager who was very friendly and very accommodating upon seeing that I was wearing a hearing aid. But she asks me first if I have a driver’s license, when I showed hear my license we then continue our discussion with regard to my plan to avail with their car financing program.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They offered me a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9Mw__" target="_blank"&gt;;2008 Suzuki XL7&lt;/a&gt;; . Even though it’s a used car, it’s still astonishing and beautiful. They told me that I can take their car loan program. Just with $3000 down payment, I can have the Suzuki and payable within 72-months. When my loan was approved days after, I immediately went to the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9MQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;dealership’s&lt;/a&gt;;  office and drove home with my car. Oh by the way, I put a Domestic-scale induction loop in my car to help me in my driving so that I can hear other car’s sirens or even to that of a police officer.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It’s hard at first in my part when driving because I can’t hear things around me clearly. Also it’s a little bit dangerous but as time goes by I can now drive as much as a normal driver can.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/122927727_7627540_28634295.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;*********************
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Be a CONTRIBUTOR now!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Give your TIPS, SUGGESTIONS and COMMENTS with regard to BUYING &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9NA__" target="_blank"&gt;;USED CARS&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SEND YOU ENTRIES TO: &lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=usedcars@secutires.com"&gt;;usedcars@secutires.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="6369b6ab570dc1320ba7b10200289a77">			Used car or Pre-Owned cars. The days are gone where car salesmen are offering you a car that was previously owned by a granny who’s only driving it to church or to the market every Sunday. Nowadays, even the latest model cars are now ups for grab in different &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;dealerships&lt;/a&gt;; . Not only you can get it at a lower price compared to the brand new counterpart, you can also save yourself the depreciation hit of the brand new cars.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A brand new car which costs $25,000 will approximately have a $5,000 depreciation value after 5 years of usage by the first owner. A $5,000 is already a big amount of money and can be spend to buy some accessories to your car. So I guess in my opinion that buying a used car is a wise choice.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Furthermore, dealerships lately are offering a “&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9NA__" target="_blank"&gt;;certified pre-owned car&lt;/a&gt;; ” program. A certified pre-owned car means that the used car that they are selling have gone through rigorous inspection and repairing process. Usually the certified pre-owned cars are covered by a warranty from the manufacturers. In this case, buyers of pre-owned cars can relax and can have a peace of mind that their car will still last for years.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don’t get me wrong, used cars doesn’t have that new-car smell of the brand new cars but is it worth it? I mean, the $5,000 which you will save if you buy a used car is the price for the new-car smell? Heck, I’m not paying for it. I can buy lots of car air freshener with my 5 grand. That smell is not important when buying a car. It’s just a smell for God’s sake. Nevertheless, if you’re rich and have tons of dollars at the bank then go ahead and buy yourself a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9Mw__" target="_blank"&gt;;brand new car&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/122927727_5450015_28646156.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;*************************
&lt;br /&gt;;Be a &lt;strong&gt;;CONTRIBUTOR&lt;/strong&gt;; now!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Give your TIPS, SUGGESTIONS and COMMENTS with regard to BUYING &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9NA__" target="_blank"&gt;;USED CARS&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Used car or a new one? What car suits your need? Where to look and what to look for when buying a used car? There are lots of questions that pops-up in your mind when it comes to the process of buying a car. Feel free to join us and say something or anything about your experience in buying a car. Every post or comment you make COUNTS and it would greatly help those who are confused whether to buy a used car or a new one.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SEND YOU ENTRIES TO: &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=usedcars@secutires.com"&gt;;usedcars@secutires.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="fb7dff69fe640c800356d8cb5e96ba10">			Hello everyone, I’m Virginia, a mother of 3 lovely lads. Alex, the eldest is 20, Carlo, 16, and Robert, 13. When my youngest son Robert enters High School, my husband gives him a car. It’s kinda bit old but having a car when you’re still a high school can give you a boost to your personality. But that’s not the reason why we give him a car. The main reason is that our house is a little bit far from their school. And we don’t want him to get late and even don’t want him to take a bus going home.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We went to a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;dealership&lt;/a&gt;;  nearby and agreed that a 2005 Toyota Camry is suited for my son. It may not be as luxurious as a Porsche or a BMW but it was nice and comfy enough to ride and what’s more great about the car was that it still had some few months warranty left from the original owner of the car. We don’t have enough money at that time for the down payment but fortunately the dealership that we went to has many connections with different lenders and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9Mg__" target="_blank"&gt;;financing institutions&lt;/a&gt;; . By the next few days, after we submitted our requirements, we received a call from one of their sales representatives telling us that our car loan had been approved and our &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9NA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Toyota Camry&lt;/a&gt;;  is ready for pick-up at their dealership.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/122927727_11372969_28670046.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first 2 weeks from the time we bought the car, my son seems to like the car and arrived at home early. By the third week, he started to come home late at night. Much worst on the fourth week, he came home around 2:00 AM drunk and wasted. We wonder how he managed to drive home safely. The next morning we sat with him during breakfast and told him to always be careful and don’t drink too much specially that he was driving.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After a week from the time we scolded him, he began to be a saint again. He came home early, slept early, and finished his assignments flawlessly. But 2 weeks after, we were all in shocked when he arrived at our house with blood on his head. The side mirrors of the car were missing and the headlights were all broken. Then my husband said, “Oh no, we can’t have the insurance if he’s under the influence of alcohol again”. We rushed my son at the nearest hospital to cure his wounds. Good thing that it was all just minor injuries. Another good thing was that he was not drunk or had been drinking alcohol at that time. He told us that on the way home, a group of kids with stones in their hands blocked the high way. After a few minutes, the kids started to throw stones all over the car and he got hit by one of the stones when an area of the windshield was broken.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Right there and then we reported it at the police station, called the insurance company and told them everything that happened to the car. The next morning an insurance agent came to our house, interviewed us and investigated the incident. After 2 weeks they found out that what happened to my son was really a road accident and therefore they gave the insurance money due for us. I hope my experience will give importance to the insurance available for the used cars. If a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpc3Rvbm5ldC5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwP3BfaWQ9NA__" target="_blank"&gt;;dealership&lt;/a&gt;;  can give you or can transfer the insurance from the first owner of the car then that dealership really is a trusted one.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>