<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="eeb6671ee7c1370dba465f36d6b6622e">			Buying a Ps3 headset has never been simpler, or cheaper. Let’s find out why. Today, we use headsets for everything. People have them connected thus to their phones, their computers and yes, even their games. I have a lover who wears his mobile phone headset in at all times, he looks like a berk, though. I don’t quite no why, though. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s our January buyers guide to the Ps3 headset. Its not just that we’re awesome (and we are awesome, indeed, to paraphrase The Hot Tub Time Machine “I can guarantee that”) and also that we now have a beautiful little website chock full of buying options, lowest prices and expert advice (mainly from folks that know much more than I do, which doesn’t include my friend who's no doubt sleeping through a post-Christmas DVD X Files marathon with his &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWZpbmVkaHlwZS5jb20vbWVtYmVyLzM4MjM5Lw__" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset wired&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dpbmVjb3VudHJ5d2FzaGluZ3Rvbi5jb20vY3MvbWVtYmVycy9zdGV2ZWp1YXJlejI1LmFzcHg_" target="_blank"&gt;turtle beach ps3 headset&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xpYmNvbS5vcmcvdXNlci81OTk5NDI_" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset wireless&lt;/a&gt; in - I’ll phone him and he’ll awaken screaming, thinking its a look), put simply, We’re here to help, so here goes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ear Force P11 seriously is not an earpiece, but a headset. Some people prefer a tiny, discreet earpiece (like my friend who may also marry his) whereas others, to whom sound is particularly important, enjoy the immersive feel of a full-on headset. The cans are big, the set is a bit of ungainly, but on average makes up for it with crystal-clear sound and more options than you can shake a badger at|The sound is great|The sound um...sounds good}. Hook it approximately whatever you like, and a common way you’ll mistake it for alien probe technology is that if it’s strapped in your head by Darth Vader belonging to the Planet Vulcan (second time travel movie reference one after the other! Go me!). Its not the reviews, but the cost that lets this one down. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I still visualize the Giotech EX-01 as probably the greatest earpieces, despite mixed reviews. The EX-01 is affordable, cheerful and gets the job done. Even with its angular, hard-edged design, the EX-01 is actually one of several more well-off headsets on the market today. Sure, there’s an occasional crackle documented in background, however doesn’t affect gameplay. You know very well what I like best? The Price. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Logitech’s ‘Vantage model’ represents a pleasant compromise between the two. Though it does look a little like those &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3Zpc3VhbC1icmFuZGluZy5jb20vbWVtYmVyLzMxNzY2Lw__" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53ZWFyZXJvYm90cy5uZXQvYmJzL21lbWJlci5waHA/dT0xMDA5MjY2" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset wired&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hZy5tYS9hbnRvbnJlZXZlczEyMzA_" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset wireless&lt;/a&gt; you had with your first tape-playing Walkman (assuming you’re as old as me), which, to you whipper snappers to choose from means the design is spindly, crafted from fairly cheap plastic and values being functional specially else, the product itself has garnered mostly good reviews. By way of value for money offset against performance, this will be the Ps3 headset for you|This could possibly be one of the best headset, value-wise|This can be considered the one for you}. To be honest, the difference between most of the products you’ll find is negligible but it’s really a question of non-public preference. A very powerful thing to recollect when buying a Ps3 headset is this...Oh God, they found me, I don’t know the way but they found me! Run for it, Marty!		</conversation>		<conversation id="de59a028ec792a962ce6f1a4e47a9e89">			Its never been easier to buy a Ps3 headset. Let’s find out why. Today, we use headsets for everything. People have them connected thus to their phones, their computers and yes, even their games. My friend leaves his headset in 24/7, which is probably why nobody calls him. I think he expects to use it to travel through time or something. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Here’s our January buyers guide for the Ps3 headset. Its not only that we’re awesome (and we're awesome, indeed, to paraphrase The Hot Tub Time Machine “I can guarantee that”) but in addition that we've got a wonderful little website chock full of buying options, lowest prices and expert advice (mainly from folks who know much more than I do, which doesn’t include my friend who's little question sleeping through a post-Christmas DVD X Files marathon with his &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXRraWpramlqLnR2L21lbWJlci83OTM5Mw__" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset vs turtle beach&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56ZWxkYWVsZW1lbnRzLm5ldC9tZW1iZXIvNzM5Nzk_" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset with mic&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hZy5tYS90cmV2b3JtaWxlczEyMzE_" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headsets wireless&lt;/a&gt; in - I’ll phone him and he’ll awaken screaming, thinking its a look), put simply, We’re here to help, so here goes. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Turtle Beach’s Ear Force P11 is a headset as opposed to an earpiece. Most audiophiles prefer headsets. The cans are big, the set is a bit of ungainly, but on average makes up for it with crystal-clear sound and much more options than you are able to shake a badger at|The sound is great|The sound um...sounds good}. Its compatible with nearly everything, and the only way you’ll mistake it for alien probe technology is if it’s strapped in your head by Darth Vader belonging to the Planet Vulcan (second time travel movie reference in a row! Go me!). The reviews are almost unanimously positive, but the £40 price tag lets this one down somewhat. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Flying the flag for buying an earpiece, despite a design that produces it appear to be it’s presupposed to be used in some sacred Klingon rite and also a generally mixed set of reviews, the Giotech EX-01 Ps3 headset is the most impressive around. The EX-01 is cheap, cheerful and gets the job done. Even with its angular, hard-edged design, the EX-01 is actually one of the more comfortable headsets that you can buy today. Yes, the EX-01 does emit a coffee crackle when its working, but some users found this reassuring. So, the EX-01 is by no means without its flaws, but at the purchase price it’s asking, There's no doubt that it’s worth a go. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Logitech’s ‘Vantage model’ represents a pleasant compromise between the two. Though it does look a bit like those &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hY21ld2lyZS5jb20vbWVtYmVyLzI4NDE2Lw__" target="_blank"&gt;click here&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50cmlwcGVybWFwLmNvbS91c2VyL2ZvcnVtL2FjY291bnQucGhwP3U9MTQ4MDQy" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset with mic&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53b3cuc2kvZm9ydW0vaW5kZXgucGhwP2FjdGlvbj1wcm9maWxlO3U9MTE4MTA3" target="_blank"&gt;ps3 headset vs turtle beach&lt;/a&gt; you had together with your first tape-playing Walkman (assuming you’re as old as me), which, for you whipper snappers at hand means the look is spindly, made from fairly cheap plastic and values being functional in particular else, the product itself has garnered mostly good reviews. In terms of value for money offset against performance, this will be the Ps3 headset for you|This could possibly be the most effective headset, value-wise|This may just be one for you}. Its a question of taste. A very powerful thing to remember when buying a Ps3 headset is this...Oh God, they found me, I don’t know how but they found me! Run for it, Marty!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>