<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="aa7d23e1be54610fde1842b68677c221">			I absolutely believe that the #1 backyard training aid that any player could ever hope to have is a batting cage and a pitching machine...even if the pitching machine needs to be budgeted at a later date.The reason this is so important has to do with how ballplayers are built, how they improve fastest, and where their enjoyment of the game is derived.If You Can Hit.They Will Find a Place to Play You!Most players say that hitting is the most fun part of the game.As coaches, we know that hitting the ball hard and consistent are the best we can hope for from our player&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ields. But as the game has grown in popularity and travel ball becomes bigger, some very creative inventors have filled in the gaps.For those families with limited backyard space and budget please take a look at some of these creative and more inexpensive options that we are now able to offer. The Portable Batting Cage Kit with L ScreenThis cage allows for tremendous flexibility in that it can be purchased in 50, 60 or 70 foot lengths with three choices of net strength that will fit any budget or age player.Even the shipping charge is reduced due to your needing to purchase the cage legs at a local Home Depot, Lowe's or similar.  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waXRjaGluZ21hY2hpbmVzdXNhLmNvbS9oZWF0ZXItcG93ZXItYWxsZXktbGl0ZS1iYXNlYmFsbC1tdWx0aS1mdW5jdGlvbi8_" target="_blank"&gt;;heater baseball pitching machine&lt;/a&gt;; Re-caulk around the windows and doors at least once a year, please be sure and remove the old caulking first.  6. Make sure your exterior doors are properly aligned in order to minimize gaps and air leaks.  7. Try microwave cooking rather than the oven, you won't be heating up the house at all.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The actual machine has a one inch tubular steel frame with a quick fold design for convenient storage. Another inexpensive option is the Heater Crusher Curve Mini Lite Ball Pitching Machine that is offered for as low as $99, offering a small design with complete functionality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is absolutely a simple project, with no cutting or special tools required. Total installation time is 1+ hour right out of the box!New for 2008Our Backyard Batting &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waXRjaGluZ21hY2hpbmVzdXNhLmNvbS9oZWF0ZXItcG93ZXItYWxsZXktbGl0ZS1iYXNlYmFsbC1tdWx0aS1mdW5jdGlvbi8_" target="_blank"&gt;;heater baseball pitching machine&lt;/a&gt;; Use 2&quot;; less water when taking a bath.  6. Use a lower water level setting in the washing machine for small loads.  7. When hand washing dishes, do not just let the faucet run for rinsing. If you have a double sink, then fill one with clean water to rinse with.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are shopping for a low price but more functionality, you can opt for the Heater Starting Pitcher Lite Pitching Machine with Ball Feeder, which offers a complete set up that pitches soft lite balls at 40 miles per hour. This machine offers great training in hitting fastballs and inside and outside breaking balls. The machine weighs about 12.3 lbs offering a versatile and light weight machine to be taken anywhere for your personal practice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Related Articles - pitching machine, heater pitching machine, efficient pitching machine, ball pitching machine,		</conversation>	</conversations></author>