<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="2b878f886d2186380380fb6bc09729be">			The restriction, still, is that all the bundled interfaces must be configured with matching speed and duplex settings, and each ends of each link should be configured as either a Layer two or Layer 3 interface.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If an individual link inside an EtherChannel bundle fails, site visitors previously carried more than the failed link is carried more than the remaining hyperlinks inside the EtherChannel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An EtherChannel might be configured in one of these two dynamic modes:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Port Aggregation Protocol (PAgP) can be a Cisco proprietary protocol used to automate the logical aggregation of Ethernet switch ports. This indicates PAgP can only be employed among Cisco switches.&lt;br /&gt;;    Link Aggregation Manage Protocol (LACP) is an sector normal protocol designed to automate the logical aggregation ethernet ports. Also know by its IEEE designation 802.3ad LACP isn't tied to any particular vendor.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Port Aggregation Protocol (PAgP)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As we've currently discussed, PAgP packets are sent among EtherChannel capable ports to facilitate the negotiation needed for the productive creation of a channel. When PAgP sees matched Ethernet hyperlinks, it is going to group the links into an EtherChannel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PAgP utilizes 3 modes of operation:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Autoplaces an interface into a passive negotiating state, which means that the interface will respond to PAgP packets it receives but it won't initiate PAgP packet negotiation. This setting minimizes the transmission of PAgP packets and will be the default on devices like Catalyst 3560.&lt;br /&gt;;    Desirableplaces an interface into an active negotiating state, meaning that the interface will get started negotiations with other interfaces by sending PAgP packets.&lt;br /&gt;;    Onforces the interface to channel with out PAgP. With all the on mode, a usable EtherChannel exists only when an interface group within the on mode is connected to one more interface group in the on mode. This really is known as static aggregation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Link Aggregation Manage Protocol (LACP)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LACP performs the precise similar function as the Cisco proprietary PAgP nevertheless it does it by sending LACP packets to its peer. Since LACP is an IEEE standard, it can be employed to facilitate EtherChannels in mixed vendor environments.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LACP, like PAgP, has 3 modes of operation:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Passive The switch will not initiate the channel, but does respond to incoming LACP packets. When a peer initiates negotiation (by sending out an LACP packet) which we receive and reply to, eventually forming the aggregation channel with the peer. This can be equivalent to the auto mode in PAgP.&lt;br /&gt;;    ActiveWe are willing to form an aggregate link and can actively seek to start the negotiation. The link aggregate will likely be formed if the other end is running in LACP active or passive mode. This can be similar to the desirable mode of PAgP.&lt;br /&gt;;    OnA link aggregation is forced to be formed without any LACP negotiation. In other words, the switch will neither send the LACP packet nor method any incoming LACP packet. This can be related towards the on state for PAgP. Once more, this really is known as static aggregation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Forming an EtherChannel&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Based on the information we've been presented thus far, it can be apparent that there must be distinct modes on every single end of a link to let an EtherChannel to form. We are able to see below exactly what mode combinations in every single Aggregation Protocol will trigger the formation of a channel-group:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LACP&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PAgP&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Active&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Passive&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Desirable&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Auto&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Active&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CYesC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CYesC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Desirable&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CYesC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CYesC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Passive&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CYesC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CNoC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Auto&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CYesC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CNoC&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Where ever we see a worth of CYesC we understand that an EtherChannel will form based on the mode from the distant finish.&lt;br /&gt;;Static EtherChannels&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are several benefits to using dynamic aggregation protocols over static configuration of EtherChannels. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS9jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9uL01DU0EtMjAwMy00Ni5odG1sLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;MCSA 2003 exam&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS9jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9uL0NDTlAtNTkuaHRtbC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;CCNP certification&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS92ZW5kb3IvTWljcm9zb2Z0LTEuaHRtbC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Microsoft certification&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="a96c15b0539a35c51f98340e67caea09">			In close second comes their ability to operate at Layer 2 or Layer three from the OSI model, and also the fact that all Cisco switches have the capability to assistance them. There's a lot of inner working on the subject of these aggregate hyperlinks, and we're to going to explore all of them, including link control protocols, configuration, and troubleshooting.&lt;br /&gt;;Link Aggregation Protocols&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As mentioned earlier, EtherChannel basically aggregates person Ethernet hyperlinks into a single logical link that provides bandwidth up to 1600 Mbps, within the case of Rapid Ethernet, or 16 Gbps when Gigabit interfaces are employed to make the logical link. The restriction, however, is the fact that all of the bundled interfaces should be configured with matching speed and duplex settings, and each ends of each and every link should be configured as either a Layer two or Layer 3 interface.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If an individual link within an EtherChannel bundle fails, targeted traffic previously carried over the failed link is carried over the remaining links inside the EtherChannel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An EtherChannel is often configured in one of these two dynamic modes:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Port Aggregation Protocol (PAgP) is known as a Cisco proprietary protocol utilized to automate the logical aggregation of Ethernet switch ports. This means PAgP can only be made use of in between Cisco switches.&lt;br /&gt;;    Link Aggregation Control Protocol (LACP) is an sector regular protocol created to automate the logical aggregation ethernet ports. Also know by its IEEE designation 802.3ad LACP is just not tied to any distinct vendor.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Port Aggregation Protocol (PAgP)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As we have currently discussed, PAgP packets are sent in between EtherChannel capable ports to facilitate the negotiation needed for the profitable creation of a channel. When PAgP sees matched Ethernet links, it will group the hyperlinks into an EtherChannel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;PAgP uses 3 modes of operation:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Autoplaces an interface into a passive negotiating state, meaning that the interface will respond to PAgP packets it receives however it won't initiate PAgP packet negotiation. This setting minimizes the transmission of PAgP packets and will be the default on devices like Catalyst 3560.&lt;br /&gt;;    Desirableplaces an interface into an active negotiating state, which means that the interface will commence negotiations with other interfaces by sending PAgP packets.&lt;br /&gt;;    Onforces the interface to channel devoid of PAgP. With all the on mode, a usable EtherChannel exists only when an interface group in the on mode is connected to a different interface group in the on mode. This can be known as static aggregation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Link Aggregation Control Protocol (LACP)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LACP performs the exact identical function as the Cisco proprietary PAgP nevertheless it does it by sending LACP packets to its peer. Because LACP is an IEEE normal, it could be put to use to facilitate EtherChannels in mixed vendor environments.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;LACP, like PAgP, has 3 modes of operation:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Passive The switch doesn't initiate the channel, but does respond to incoming LACP packets. When a peer initiates negotiation (by sending out an LACP packet) which we receive and reply to, eventually forming the aggregation channel with the peer. This is equivalent for the auto mode in PAgP.&lt;br /&gt;;    ActiveWe are prepared to form an aggregate link and can actively seek to begin the negotiation. The link aggregate will likely be formed if the other finish is operating in LACP active or passive mode. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS92ZW5kb3IvTWljcm9zb2Z0LTEuaHRtbC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Microsoft certification&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS92ZW5kb3IvQ2lzY28tMy5odG1sLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Cisco certification&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS9jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9uL0NDTlAtNTkuaHRtbC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;CCNP certification&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>