<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="558ee8ec1a742371c9c1039da80e6181">			The iPad 2 has been featured a lot in the news, so many of us are aware that it is out. Apple releases always create a good deal of buzz. Is this as a result of Apple's product line being great or merely buzzt from their hardcore fan base? Coming from someone who is unbiased, I'd say it's a bit of the two. Twelve months separate the launching dates of the iPad and now the iPad 2. The question that comes into most people's minds is 'is it worth getting the new iPad?', and that is the question I will endeavor to answer in this mini-review.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first thing to note with the iPad 2 is the diminution in in terms of size. The iPad 2 is slimmer by approximately a third of the original although the screen dimensions continue to be unaltered. At just 600 grams, the iPad 2 is not as heavy. Not heavy at all. If you handle the iPad and the new iPad 2, the change in design can be felt. Don't think a slimmer and lighter design means the performance is affected, because boy oh boy would you be inaccurate...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The iPad 2 has faster speeds than the first one. For one, Apple touts that its graphics processor is nine times quicker than the initial iPad. If that is accurate, it is a huge stride forward. The reasoning behind this is because of new cameras and what is necessary for games. In addition, the switch from an A4 to an A5 chip would mean that Apple has a quick processor inside. The A5 chip has a dual core processor and it does make a difference to the speed of the new iPad. No matter what I was using, I could tell that it was zippier. If I use the various media on the first model and then the newer iPad, the better load speed time is noticeable.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now, onto the recent addition of the cameras; not only one, but two cameras are on the iPad 2. You will find these set at both the rear and the front side. The original iPad did not have cameras at all, so this is a major feature if you're bothered about having a camera on your device. One camera takes 720p HD and the other camera isn't as wonderful. Video calling and fun photos are now feasible with the new iPad with the add-on of FaceTime and Photobooth. The back camera, when making use of FaceTime on the iPad, exposes where you are as opposed to the front camera that allows you to see each other.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In sum, I would personally advise upgrading from the original iPad to the iPad 2 if you have the money, however if you're not interested in slightly faster loading times then don't bother. While the upgrades are an improvement, it's nothing significant, apart from possibly the camera which is a brand new addition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more content articles on  check out our webpage.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>