<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fb6d7e52c1cf1bc293df682d00efa01b">			Electonic Mail. we cannot manage without it. Pretty much everyone that I know uses email for communication. It’s amazing how we take email for granted today, and think how much we would miss it. We would be using the phone a lot more to communicate AND we would have to give the postman more excersize. Motorcycle and bicycle couriers would be a lot bussier across the globe and in general, lgetting things done, as well as communication would be generally slower.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;when you give it thought life would be harder. I work for a technology company that places big orders. In this role I have to send large order confirmations in writing so imagine having to live without email. Yes, you could send a faxsimilie, but then you are sending 20 to 30 emails a day at least then everyone in the department would need a fax machine!! A massive que would appear in front of every fax machine that’s for sure.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Email is a brilliant invention when you sit and give it some thought, it’s a simple concept well executed and its not oftern you experience any issues. Of course you will always get spam, but without spam we would need anti-spam solutions would we? You could say the same about Anti-virus software…………&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So what is the future for email? Is there any way it can be advanced or improved? Well speech recognition is starting to become much improved and more reliable now so I can see that being used a lot more, the only thing is that it may get a bit confusing in a business environment  (a room of 7 or more people reciting emails may get a bit much)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For business, the new kid on the block is hosted exchange which uses the cloud (aka cloud computing). Cloud solutions are going to get very popular over the next four years and they are now at the point where they are reliable and secure enough to be implemented in the office.  advantage of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hostedcomputers.co.uk%2Fhosted-exchange"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hostedcomputers.co.uk/hosted-exchange&lt;/a&gt;;  is the cost. It does everything that an in-house email server would, but it does it from a cloud network, meaning that you don’t have the cost of an exchange server.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recently, I have seen the cost of Hosted exchange drop massively.  There are some vendors now offering the service at £5.99 per user and I have no idea how they can offer it at that price. However it is great value for money and I can whole heartedly recommend it to anyone that needs a reliable email solution. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many things we take for granted. Phones, the internet and email. Just imagine what life would be like without them?		</conversation>	</conversations></author>