<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3519b22ecbd6c67f8986ec8a88149d6a">			Injuries or disabilities that resulted from an accident may not be evident shortly after the incident happened. Some injuries will take time to develop and will manifest its symptoms and effects much later. This kind of injury often occurs when the cause of the accident is a toxic substance. In law, such accident is known as a toxic tort. 
&lt;br /&gt;;What is a toxic tort?
&lt;br /&gt;;Toxic torts are claims for harm caused by a person’s exposure to noxious substance. These substances may have been inhaled, absorbed, ingested or injected.
&lt;br /&gt;;Who can victims sue for injuries and health problems?
&lt;br /&gt;;The person responsible for the injury is hard to point out. However, this type of case may be brought against people who had a link to the chemical. So that will be the manufacturer, supplier or distributor of the toxic chemical, manufacturer of the machine that exposed the toxins, owner of the building or site where the toxins came from, company that stored the chemicals, and the manufacturer of the safety equipment used by the workers who handled the toxins. 
&lt;br /&gt;;What types of injuries are caused by toxic chemicals?
&lt;br /&gt;;A large number of chemicals may cause cancer to those exposed to it. Exposure to asbestos may result lung cancer and mesothelioma, vinyl chloride may cause angiosarcoma of the liver, and benzene can cause leukemia. Solvent is also known to have caused birth defects.
&lt;br /&gt;;The respiratory system is also vulnerable to toxic injury. Reactive airway disease, bronchitis, pneumonia, and pulmonary fibrosis are just some of the respiratory diseases that may endanger a person. 
&lt;br /&gt;;How can these injuries arise?
&lt;br /&gt;;The following are some of the ways of how toxic injuries are obtained:
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Occupational exposure: Workers who are exposed to high levels of toxins even for a short period of time may develop health problems later on.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Pharmaceutical drugs: Drugs may cause unintended side effects to people who often take it. Prozac and Zoloft, both known antidepressants, have been subjects of toxic torts before.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Consumer products: Products like pesticides can cause unintended illnesses when high levels of it are inhaled.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Environment: Health problems may also arise if toxic molds that are sometimes found at homes are inhaled, or if people accidentally drank contaminated water.
&lt;br /&gt;;How does one proceed with a toxic tort Claim?
&lt;br /&gt;;The victim should choose a good personal injury lawyer who specializes in toxic torts. He will be able to help prove the negligence of the people responsible for the injury. Workers who have been inflicted with an illness for working on a highly toxic factory may also opt to file a class action suit against their employer.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>