<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f1abeb29a2ca9d34e99e9d1662a79430">			Payday loans are useful cash advances for anyone who can pay the cash back on time. By applying for a payday loan you may  get approved within a few hours. Payday loans are suitable for making an unexpected bill payment , going on a short holiday or buying something that you may find necessary but don’t have the money to pay for immediately. The instant and flexible process of getting a payday loan is what makes this type of personal loan unique.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those above eighteen years of age with a steady monthly salary and a checking account are eligible for a payday loan. Even those with a bad credit history are guaranteed to be successful when applying for a poor credit payday loan. Due to the competitive market you should find a lender that offers you a decent loan rate and an approval that will take a maximum of 72 hours. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The money is deposited into your bank account in a few hours or days, making access to the money very easy. Internet lenders are a good source to start with and the possiblility of comparing payday loan rates comes in handy &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are regretably a certain level of disadvantages that are associated with payday loans and payday loan lenders still have a reputation as being aggressive lenders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those in debt are advised not to use a payday loan as a debt consolidation loan because they will find themselves more in debt. Borrowers should pay utmost caution when dealing with internet lenders due to fraud issues and reading the fine print is paramount.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you do not have a permanent job or salary you will not get a payday loan no matter how much you plead with the loan provider. If you don’t have a checking account you can’t write a check meaning you cannot secure the loan and the lender will not complete your loan application. If you need a cash advance but don’t qualify for a payday loan for any reason, ask friends and family to lend you the funds.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A payday lender only lends small amounts of money therefore, asking your close family shouldn’t be too difficult. If you haven’t managed to get the funds you need, consider applying for an unsecured personal loan instead.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Taking payday loans frequently is certainly not a positive indicator and it echos your bad fiscal management skills or even your expensive way of life. Pay day loans are intended for emergencies and not as a way of life. Before getting payday financial loans, exercise all other options available to you for the cash advance. Numerous employers provide a cash advance to their staff members to fulfill their urgent commitments. However, a loan is a loan and curbing your own expenses is the best option. “Cut your coat according to your cloth” is a good ancient proverb and is still applicable today.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In summary, pay day loans might be a viable option if you require money and need them rapidly. You still should be careful who you are working with to obtain your loan. If you don't need money right away, there is probably a better much better and altogether much easier solution for you and your relatives or family.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.paydayloansforyou.co.uk%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.paydayloansforyou.co.uk/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="64ef974a7f8d957f40bf894f4e8c7213">			Examples may include vets bills, car repairs, unexpected telephone bills or even urgent utility bills that appear each quarter instead of each month.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As individuals with low incomes have to prepay for things like electric and gas, these individuals can often find them selves with no lighting or heating if they have no money for their key meter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Families with young children can sometimes access a line of credit from the social who are unwilling to let a family with young children sit around in their homes with no electric.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For single people with less of a social safety net they are often trapped and forced into a doomed spiral of exploitation from unscrupulous lenders.  Imagine the following scenario.  Dave is a trainee plumber on a minimum wage.  He was out of work for 6 months and defaulted on his bank credit card, his full status bank account went past his agreed borrowing limit and the bank closed it and sold on the debt to a debt collector.  He was pulled up by the police while driving his car with two bald tyres.  The police officer was unimpressed with his attitude towards him and ordered a recovery truck to tow his car away.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dave was stuck with no car to get to work and no money to get it out of the impounded facility and buy the new.  The daily charges for storage were mounting up.  His friend he drank with told him to go on the internet and look for a no credit check pay day loan so he could sort out his travel problems.  His bad credit would be no issue as there was no credit check.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dave was open-minded and happy that someone [would|could] be willing to offer him credit and he went on the internet to apply.  After a certain amount of scanning and faxing documents to the loans company £350 arrived in his bank, enough for his new tyres and the removal truck and storage charges.  Everything went well until his payday when the payday loans company removed £437.50 from his bank account.  He was able to pay his rent for his bed-sit, put some diesel in his van and then he was back to his zero bank balance. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After a friend of his expressed his anger with Dave continually smoking his cigarettes and using his phone credit, Dave decided he was sick of having no money.  Dave made a quick phone  call and the payday loans company were all too willing and able to lend him £500.  Glad for their &quot;help&quot; Dave was able to have a few nights out and buy his own cigarettes.  His payday came round again and £625 was removed from his bank account.  Also, a couple of months ago he was foolish enough to give his visa debit card details to the debt collector that had [purchased|bought] the debt from his previous bank.  The debt collector caught his bank account at just the right time to empty the remaining cash.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dave sat alone in his bed-sit with no money trying to work out how two bald tyres could have cost him £350 and a ludicrous £275 in interest and charges.&lt;br /&gt;;The sad and unfortunate moral of the story is using lines of credit from lenders who charge rates of interest in the 1000's of percent is seldom the solution to any problem.  Giving out records of your employer and access to your bank account is something that no one should ever do. It is not good to do this and can lead to identity theft and all sorts of unpleasant things could happen as a result.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.paydayloansforyou.co.uk%2FNo_credit_check_furnature_shop_electricals_on_weekly_payments.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.paydayloansforyou.co.uk/No_credit_check_furnature_shop_electricals_on_weekly_payments.htm&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>