<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b07e4a61032563a40f87d6d6c683bf6">			Quid Pro Quo Love-making Harassment &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Quid pro player quo sexual harassment occurs when staff is offered to be retained in his/her occupation or be promoted frequently for sexual favors. With a student, the offer should be to help receive a good grade or a favorable recommendation in change for sexual favors. The person who commits quid pro quo sexual harassment can be a person with power to influence the victim's career or educational situation being a supervisor, manager or a teacher in the case of a student. An example would be when a manager suggests that staff goes out with him using a date or asks for any neck or back rub every so often in exchange for retaining her post or get promoted. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In this sexual harassment, it isn't important if the victim gave in or agrees to your offer. It is enough that the harasser floats or makes the offer plus the victim is not prohibited from filing a claim if he or she later on changes his mind. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;II. Hostile Environment Sexual Harassment &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hostile work place sexual harassment, on one other hand, occurs when some sort of co-worker, manager or supervisor with the work place makes uncomfortable sexual advances which inhibits work performance or makes an intimidating, hostile or offensive work environment, or learning environment in the matter of students. The sexual harassing conduct may be verbal, non-verbal, visual or simply physical. Example of a verbal harassing conduct is when one makes a sexual comment upto a person's clothing, anatomy and also looks. In cases of non-verbal sexually harassing conduct an instance would be leering, gazing or glaring at a friend or relative. Visual sexually harassing conduct on the other hand could be displaying sexually suggestive calendars, photographs, posters or cartoons at work. Physically harassing conduct is when someone provides massage around the neck or shoulders and also the victim did not look for it and regards that as offensive. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In any such sexual harassment, even the employer is likely if he has knowledge or should know about the sexual harassment perpetrated on among the list of employees and the job either does nothing about this or even faulted the victim for the happening of the sexually getting out of hand conduct. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In both cases, it would be to the best interest for the victim to secure the services of a lawyer immediately to protect the victim's rights. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;A bona fide occupational qualification (or maybe a BFOQ) is a characteristic any particular one employers are allowed to consider when hiring and firing employees. These characteristics will, in other circumstances, be looked at discriminatory; however, due for the nature of certain employment, legislature has made a few exceptions. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What creates a BFOQ? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Characteristics which are considered &quot;bona fide occupational qualifications&quot; add some following: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Age &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Gender &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Nationality &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o	Religion &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You have to keep in mind that an employer is only allowed to discriminate based on these characteristics within the next deemed it &quot;reasonably necessary&quot; in order for an employee to perform principle duties of the job for which they are applying. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Types of a Legitimate BFOQ &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With regard to clarification purposes, here is a list of examples for each type of bona fide occupational extent. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdmVydGFlbXBsb3ltZW50bGF3eWVycy5jb20vYXZlcnRhLWVtcGxveW1lbnQtbGF3eWVycy1nYXJkZW5pbmctbGVhdmUv" target="_blank"&gt;;Averta&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdmVydGFlbXBsb3ltZW50bGF3eWVycy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Averta&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdmVydGFlbXBsb3ltZW50bGF3eWVycy5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcnkvYXZlcnRhLWVtcGxveW1lbnQtbGF3eWVycy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Averta&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>