<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="8f809d68d28daed0098b5f99a2d597df">			It’s every person’s wish to achieve the maximum comfort level in their homes. The first thing you’ll probably think when asked how to improve or maintain comfort levels in your home is your air conditioner. These days you can’t really live without some type of air conditioning and heating unit/units in your home; it’s hazardous to your health. One company that works to make sure your family is  comfortable is Goodman Air Conditioning and Heating, due to the quality of their systems.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Decades of Quality Heating and Cooling&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Goodman Air Conditioning and Heating systems have been providing quality air conditioning solutions since 1982. Founded by Harold Goodman, an air conditioning contractor, this company still strives to provide affordable and dependable air conditioning and heating solutions to families with his original vision in mind. Today they produce a full line of air conditioning and heating products including air conditioning systems, heat pump systems, gas furnaces, packages air conditioners and heat pumps; air filtration, purification, and ventilation systems, air handlers, controls and thermostats, and coils. Best of all, they offer some of the industry’s most competitive standards and warranties on all of their products.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dedicated to Both the Environment and You&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Providing energy efficient air conditioning and heating solutions as well as environmentally friendly ones is just as important to Goodman Air Conditioning as it is to you. Many homeowners now strive to utilize more energy efficient and environmentally friendly appliances and systems, and Goodman Air Conditioning strives to provide just that in all of their products. In addition to providing energy efficient and environmentally friendly units they still also provide units that are dependable and affordable, meaning you don’t have to sacrifice quality or cost-effectiveness.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more information on how to install a Goodman Air Conditioning and Heating system, visit  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.edscomfortsolutions.com%2Fair-filtration-products.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.edscomfortsolutions.com/air-filtration-products.aspx&lt;/a&gt;; .		</conversation>	</conversations></author>