<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="287ae8c795e727e7225aa366217d86e6">			CCNA is the second level certification in the Cisco career certification process; this course includes the basic aspect of Local Area Network (LAN) such as installation, configuration, operation, and troubleshooting of mid-size route and switched networks, also including implementation and authentication of connections to remote sites in a Wide Area Network (WAN). 
&lt;br /&gt;;CCNP Certification acknowledges networking professionals’ ability in planning, implementation, verification and troubleshooting of LAN and WAN. CCNP certified professionals also work closely with experts on highly developed networking security, voice, wireless and video solutions.
&lt;br /&gt;;Both CCNA and &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9ua2V5LmNvbS9DaXNjby1DZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9uLVRyYWluaW5nL0NDREEucGhw" target="_blank"&gt;;CCDA Certification Training&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;; are generally offered to networking professionals having at least 1 year of practical experience in networking.
&lt;br /&gt;;In order to cope with the dynamic changing taking place in IT industry and Cisco, one has to understand what new courses or subjects are being added to the current Cisco certifications. For example, the new course outline of the CCNA certification includes the use of protocol frame relay. When you start studying for Cisco CCNA or CCNP certifications you have to keep in mind that you have to learn a lot of things. These exams are accepted worldwide and you may have to include those topics into your study that are often ignored. For example, one of the commonly overlooked topics is Frame Relay, the encapsulation type. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Frame Relay is currently the most used technology for voice and data by using encapsulation methods between LANs and over a WAN. In an established network Frame Relay is often fixed and you don’t change it frequently. It’s a hidden path for end users and a sudden change in those paths may result an end to you job but still it’s an important part of networking. 
&lt;br /&gt;;The DCE (Distributed Computing Environment) and DTE (Data terminal equipment) work only if they share same type of LMI (Local Management Interface), however the two end points o the VC network i.e. DTEs (Data terminal equipments) should also share the same value. While setting up a network the initial value of the frame relay encapsulation if often the Cisco default property but if required it can also be changed according to the industry-standards of IETF (Internet Engineering Task Force) as shown below. However if you are using a router that is not from Cisco line of products then it’s a requirement that you use frame relay encapsulation value as provided by IETF. Remember the default value of the Cisco is not included in the in the Cisco IOS (Cisco Internetwork Operating System) help section so you have to memorize it.
&lt;br /&gt;;R1(config)#int s0
&lt;br /&gt;;R1(config-if)#encap frame ?
&lt;br /&gt;;ietf Use RFC1490/RFC2427 encapsulation
&lt;br /&gt;;R1 (config-if) #encap frame ietf
&lt;br /&gt;;While establishing a new network you may use a physical network and some hosts. Some of these hosts may require Cisco encapsulation while others work with IETF encapsulation, what would you do then? The simplest answer is that you can use each type of encapsulation on the basis of PVC (permanent virtual circuit). You can use one encapsulation on interface and other different encapsulations can be included in the appropriate map statement. In the example below you see that all PVCS are using the default Cisco encapsulation but PVC 115. The map statement for frame shows how PVC 115 has been specified using IETF.
&lt;br /&gt;;R1 (config) #int s0/0
&lt;br /&gt;;R1 (config-if) #encap frame
&lt;br /&gt;;R1 (config-if) #frame map ip 172.12.123.3 123 broadcast
&lt;br /&gt;;R1 (config-if) #frame map ip 172.12.123.2 122 ietf broadcast
&lt;br /&gt;;The above show frame map clearly shows us that the mapping to DLCI 123 is by using default Cisco encapsulation, and DLCI 122 is using IETF.
&lt;br /&gt;;R1#show frame map
&lt;br /&gt;;Serial0 (up): ip 172.12.123.3 dlci 123(0x7B, 0x1CB0), static broadcast, CISCO, status defined, active
&lt;br /&gt;;Serial0 (up): ip 172.12.123.2 dlci 122(0x7B, 0x1CB0), static broadcast, ietf, status defined, active
&lt;br /&gt;;Keep in mind that Cisco encapsulation is default and all other PVCs can use Cisco only if you specify them as IETF is the frame mapping statement.  There is also the option to make the complete network to use IETF encapsulation by suing an IETF command. If you want to make successful completion of your &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9ua2V5LmNvbS9DaXNjby5waHA_" target="_blank"&gt;;Cisco certification&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;; or you are going to setup a large-scale corporate network then it’s important for you to learn many other things which are out of the box.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2e8f38e842cac103402271bec1af9e0c">			Microsoft has just announced a new generation of Microsoft Certifications; they unavoidably made one stop for a short time remembering how all started and evolved throughout history with over ten years of certifications so far. ‘Ten’ gives the impression of a determined number in the new generation of certification provided by the leading Internet Company. Microsoft has announced the new certification of MCA (Microsoft Certified Architect) as well; it also has offered the Microsoft training practical exam, which is graded by a board of examiners. MCA needs at least ten years experience in IT, and three years of practical experience as a network architect to submit an application. With this situation, just a very few IT professionals are willing to go for MCA certification.
&lt;br /&gt;;Though, Microsoft always keeps on reviewing all &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9ua2V5LmNvbS9NaWNyb3NvZnQucGhw" target="_blank"&gt;;Microsoft Certifications&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;; available since the early days when those certifications were designed to fulfill the requirements of companies and hiring managers for customer support in the office. Majority of the old certifications are under review and at the same time, some of the new certifications are also going through some important twists, such as the MCDBA (Microsoft Certified Database Administrator) on Microsoft SQL Server 2000, which candidates are required to pass three core exams and one elective exam to get the certification.
&lt;br /&gt;;On the other hand, some other certifications, such as the acclaimed MCSE Certification and MCSE training that everybody loves are on the brink of the past. At the same time, a series of specialization exams and IP Professional certification tracks take its place with a new approach to qualify as a Microsoft Certified Systems Engineer.
&lt;br /&gt;;Majority of the new Microsoft Certifications are made of three series and four credentials, providing a simpler Microsoft training, and more targeted framework for IT managers so as to certify core technical skills, architectural skills and professional skills, as true professionals in the IT industry. The structure of the new certifications of Microsoft would have the ability of assuring a more flexible, relevant, and cost-effective approach to showcase IT professionals’ skills and, according to them, such structure would be completely implemented with the next Windows server/client version. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Some time ago, Microsoft certifications and Microsoft training were not as specific and targeted the way they are now. The trainings and certifications reflect the detail of what an IT certified professional could do. Certifications were just an important ingredient of a learning process; it was not initially planned to prove expertise to those who wanted to measure your technical skills. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Now, Microsoft has planned widespread support for those IT professional holding old certifications, making easier the transition to the new generation of certifications. If it is MCPD training or &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0aWZpY2F0aW9ua2V5LmNvbS9NaWNyb3NvZnQtQ2VydGlmaWNhdGlvbi1UcmFpbmluZy9NQ1BELnBocA__" target="_blank"&gt;;MCPD Certification&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;; or any of the new Microsoft certifications that might impact your career, you should be responsive to these changes in Microsoft training, because update your qualifications is a must in the competitive and challenging world of IT.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>