<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="9d08b6ad268d7555c6f432ddbd24506e">			Chicago, Arlington Residence, Sunday October 23,2005, 6:thirty am&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following completely discovering the Pullman Historic District, we determined to look at Chinatown, on the list of a lot of ethnic neighbourhoods that Chicago has to supply. The weather had turned from cool and grey using the occasional peek of sunshine to dim, rainy and chilly, so as an alternative to walking around we determined to have an early supper in a Chinatown restaurant called the Lobster King.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Both my friend Linda and I'd ordered vegetarian dishes, but immediately after using our purchase the waiter returned and &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2lhbGFpcm1heHByb3NzaG9wLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;Air Max&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; knowledgeable us that he was gonna cost us $2 added for each dish considering that veggies are much more expensive throughout the winter season months. I made the decision to get a look at their takeout menu and saw that exactly the same reduced price tag was detailed on the takeout menu as on the main menu. As a result I put ahead an argument that if each the dine-in and also the take-out menu are stating the same low price for each dishes, I would not consent with getting charged an additional $2 for every single dish depending on a verbal announcement. Either modify the menu to include the greater cost or cost the costs which are shown on each menus. I am not usually a hard, picky guest in any hospitality establishment, but to try to cost $2 far more to get a dish which is detailed at a decrease cost on each menus did not seem a proper business follow to me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The waiter / manager finally agreed to cost us the costs outlined around the menu, as well as the meals was indeed delicious. Right after discovering the Chicago Cultural Heart and the Historic Pullman District we had gotten really hungry and we truly loved our early dinner.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Following reviving ourselves we hopped around the subway because we wished to take a look at Little Italy. So we received on the Blue Line and were told to exit in the UIC (University of Illinois) Campus and stroll southwards. By that time it absolutely was raining and it was a rather inhospitable clammy day. We really never finished up finding Tiny Italy, but walked about for around 40 minutes within the rain and following this exercise of futility we made a decision to go after our evening ideas: to attend a reside performance at 2nd City, Chicago's well-known comedy venue.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So we took the subway again downtown to Jackson and we waited for your Purple Line until we realized this line only runs throughout rush hour on weekdays. So we inquired which line we had to take and we identified out the Brown Line (to Kimball) would just take us to Second Metropolis. At that level we recognized that we had also been waiting on the wrong facet with the platform. I guess in the Loop el-trains only operate in one direction and we had currently been wondering why we had seen 3 brown line trains go by around the other aspect from the system, but none of them had arrived on our aspect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I would say we spent a great 45 minutes waiting on the wrong aspect from the system till we finally had enough and went downstairs to ask a CTA worker who directed us onto the right system. Inside the rainy clammy climate this was not the most exciting portion of our journey, but we managed to entertain ourselves with lots of insider jokes inside our original Austrian dialects.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Finally we caught a brown line practice and made our way as much as North Wells Street, into the Outdated Town Neighbourhood, residence from the 2nd Metropolis Comedy Club. Because 1959 2nd City has established alone as a Chicago landmark as well as a nationwide treasure. This theatre has launched the careers of this kind of comic geniuses as John Belushi, Mike Myers, Bill Murray, Gilda Radner, and other people a lot more. It offers nightly comedy shows, too as a variety of other programs and solutions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The theatre has two main levels, each of which had been marketed out yesterday, so we headed up onto the 4th floor in the developing which homes Donny's Skybox Studio Theatre which is affiliated with 2nd Town. This theatre attributes an eclectic blend of university student productions at the same time as other alternative exhibits and at $10.00 per person, the tickets had been a steal.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Outreach &amp; Diversity Program produces two to three unique shows every single year that happen to be performed at Second City's studio theatre, Donny's Skybox, on the fourth ground of Piper's Alley. At least one of these productions is an authentic revue written and performed by the Outreach &amp; Diversity ensemble, a group of African American, Latino or Asian actors cast by way of annual auditions.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We bought tickets for the 9 pm show: &quot;;Six Degrees of Reparation&quot;;, a hip comedy revue featuring improv, authentic material and 2nd Town classic scenes with an urban multicultural twist which was place on by 6 young comedians which included 5 black and 1 oriental performers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The display presented lots of bodily comedy plus a range of different sketches. On the list of funniest ones was a sketch entitled &quot;;Osama bin Laden could be anywhere&quot;;, where among the female comedians donned a big black beard and kept popping up in different everyday situations. The &quot;;superior Asian girl&quot;; sketch played with a, B, C (Asian, Black, Caucasian) stereotypes and demonstrated how we all have pre-conceived notions of 1 another. In the &quot;;Black Black Awards&quot;; sketch the troupe produced fun of popular celebrities such &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5vZmZpY2lhbGFpcm1heHByb3NzaG9wLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;Air Max&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; as Whitney Houston, Maya Angelou and even Martha Stewart.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among the most poignant sketches was set in an imaginary Office Depot store, where the black and Asian store employees were giving extremely shoddy and unfriendly service to various customers. In the end, the young black shopkeeper explained that having a wage of $6.50 an hour, following all her costs (food, rent, bus passes, doing her nails, etc.), she was $189 within the hole, and at that value a smile would not be included in the service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;We both enjoyed the reside performance of these gifted comedians immensely as we each love reside theatre and comedy performances. As far as culture is concerned, Chicago has something to provide to everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nicely, today is our last day here in Chicago, along with the weather is forecast to become quite chilly having a 60% chance of rain. Fortunately Chicago has a lot of indoor venues to choose from so I'm sure we won't get bored.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>