<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="34c7e2eb18738933013e298ebecefa1e">			The features that strongly make way to the security attributes of VPN and the major elements include the firewall protection, the encryption, and the passwords. This provides assistance in creation of a secured tunnel joining the office server to your system. The Virtual Private Network also has great utility in the countries, which practice Internet censorship. Let's take the instance of China, which has more Internet users than the entire US population. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;iframe width=400 height=400 src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FQUnnRisJZio%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/embed/QUnnRisJZio&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; frameborder=&quot;;0&quot;; allowfullscreen&gt;;&lt;/iframe&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A virtual private network (VPN) can either be a remote access or site-to-site network - whatever the case, you'll need specific software and hardware to build a VPN. For instance, you may need a desktop software client for each remote user, dedicated hardware (a concentrator or secure PIX firewall), a dedicated server for dial-up, a network access server for use by a service provider for remote users to access VPN, and a network and policy management center. There is no single way to put together a VPN, which is why most companies come up with a solution for their own needs. Most VPNs, however, make use of Cisco VPN technology simply because it is the most widely used equipment for networking in the world. So what are some of the hardware components you will need, in addition to VPN software One component is called a concentrator. This piece of equipment is good for remote access, with encryption and authentication techniques that are quite advanced. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is more sophisticated data encryption technology such as SSL but it can't be used everywhere. But VPN is free from any such restriction amp offers more flexibility while trying to meet the company's data sharing requirement. The VPN or the Virtual Private Network is a service is an option that has gained immense popularity all over the world. The Windows VPN service provider offer an alternative to a dedicated personal network connection for the different corporate offices across the globe. Actually, VPN is a private network built upon the Internet network having public access. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A virtual private network (VPN) can either be a remote access or site-to-site network - whatever the case, you'll need specific software and hardware to build a VPN. For instance, you may need a desktop software client for each remote user, dedicated hardware (a concentrator or secure PIX firewall), a dedicated server for dial-up, a network access server for use by a service provider for remote users to access VPN, and a network and policy management center. There is no single way to put together a VPN, which is why most companies come up with a solution for their own needs. Most VPNs, however, make use of Cisco VPN technology simply because it is the most widely used equipment for networking in the world. So what are some of the hardware components you will need, in addition to VPN software One component is called a concentrator. This piece of equipment is good for remote access, with encryption and authentication techniques that are quite advanced. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;History is witness that when office communication was needed intranets came to the rescue which had password protected features as their security for office work force only. Now a day big corporations are setting up their own VPN to put up with the dire need of constant connectivity with remote employees or work spaces. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dvcmxkdnBuLm5ldC92cG4tc2VydmljZS9kZWRpY2F0ZWQtdnBuLXNlcnZpY2U_" target="_blank"&gt;;Dedicated VPN IP&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>