<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b9cc91ca594e20afe2e438085442e272">			Decks have become important components of the modern home, especially when it comes to remodel or bringing in a new home addition. Many homeowners are expanding their homes to add an outdoor living space - a healthy way to avoid cabin fever even in the colder months of fall and winter. Traditional deck design is going right out the window as well since homeowners are pushing the limits on the materials and designs to spice up their home design with customer deck builders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to building a spa deck, deck builders often recommend using wood as the best material of choice primarily because of cost but also because it delivers on many of the same benefits as other more costly materials. Tile looks great, but it should only be used in frost-free climates. Stone looks amazing when used around a spa or hot tub but depending on the product and method of installation by deck builders it can cost as much as $80 per square foot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Homeowners will frequently request the more expensive tile and stone for its non-slip surface, hoping to build a safe environment around their spa. While this is great forward thinking, there are additives you can put in solid stain that will actually give your deck a non-slip surface and it's easy for deck builders to do. With spaced joints, stained wood is adequately slip-resistant for any outdoor spa environment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Keeping Your Outdoor Space Private&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's not uncommon for homeowners to install privacy fences around a pool area, and the same can be done when you work with deck builders on a custom spa deck. Privacy screens are a great addition and they also offer some measure of utility for the hot tub deck as well. Not only can you as a homeowner gain privacy and passive screening from neighboring homes but the right deck screen can shelter you from the sun. If you want privacy in your spa area, try not to close it off completely. Use plants and lathe to avoid that &quot;boxed in&quot; feeling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Common Hot Tub Decks from Deck Builders&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While you certainly want your deck to be unique on your home, deck builders will work with you to recommend the most appropriate design for your home and your landscape. The standard design for hot tub decks and other spa areas is a 12x12 minimum set aside for the hot tub. Beyond that, the size of the deck is a matter of preference and available space. Try to embellish on the design a bit so it's comfortable; add benches, garden pots or have your deck builder add a custom pergola over the top.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your deck doesn't have to be a drab space - when you want to create a spa environment you can step away from the traditional and branch into either formal or architectural design to fit your personal style and home design. Many homeowners enjoy adding the pergola to their outdoor living space, which can give the deck &quot;vertical interest&quot;. It also makes it easy to increase privacy and &quot;seclusive&quot; comfort. Whatever your choice, you can work with deck builders in your area to fit the right style to your preferences and design dreams.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3djb3N0LWJ1aWxkZXJzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;low cost builders&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="786a88cd8ed25daa2da58b560ac85fbf">			Decks have become important components of the modern home, especially when it comes to remodel or bringing in a new home addition. Many homeowners are expanding their homes to add an outdoor living space - a healthy way to avoid cabin fever even in the colder months of fall and winter. Traditional deck design is going right out the window as well since homeowners are pushing the limits on the materials and designs to spice up their home design with customer deck builders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to building a spa deck, deck builders often recommend using wood as the best material of choice primarily because of cost but also because it delivers on many of the same benefits as other more costly materials. Tile looks great, but it should only be used in frost-free climates. Stone looks amazing when used around a spa or hot tub but depending on the product and method of installation by deck builders it can cost as much as $80 per square foot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Homeowners will frequently request the more expensive tile and stone for its non-slip surface, hoping to build a safe environment around their spa. While this is great forward thinking, there are additives you can put in solid stain that will actually give your deck a non-slip surface and it's easy for deck builders to do. With spaced joints, stained wood is adequately slip-resistant for any outdoor spa environment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Keeping Your Outdoor Space Private&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's not uncommon for homeowners to install privacy fences around a pool area, and the same can be done when you work with deck builders on a custom spa deck. Privacy screens are a great addition and they also offer some measure of utility for the hot tub deck as well. Not only can you as a homeowner gain privacy and passive screening from neighboring homes but the right deck screen can shelter you from the sun. If you want privacy in your spa area, try not to close it off completely. Use plants and lathe to avoid that &quot;boxed in&quot; feeling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Common Hot Tub Decks from Deck Builders&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While you certainly want your deck to be unique on your home, deck builders will work with you to recommend the most appropriate design for your home and your landscape. The standard design for hot tub decks and other spa areas is a 12x12 minimum set aside for the hot tub. Beyond that, the size of the deck is a matter of preference and available space. Try to embellish on the design a bit so it's comfortable; add benches, garden pots or have your deck builder add a custom pergola over the top.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your deck doesn't have to be a drab space - when you want to create a spa environment you can step away from the traditional and branch into either formal or architectural design to fit your personal style and home design. Many homeowners enjoy adding the pergola to their outdoor living space, which can give the deck &quot;vertical interest&quot;. It also makes it easy to increase privacy and &quot;seclusive&quot; comfort. Whatever your choice, you can work with deck builders in your area to fit the right style to your preferences and design dreams.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3djb3N0LWJ1aWxkZXJzLmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;low cost builders&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>