<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f943e01a507384081982ea40f68e68fa">			With the annual event of the Wimbledon Lawn Tennis Association well under way, it is time to get out those strawberries and cream. All over Essex catering companies are busy picking and delivering the sweetest, best sized strawberries to serve up a feast on   Centre Court. As Andy Murray plays   Wimbledon, our Number One tennis champion, you can rest assured that the crowds are going to be flowing as thickly and fast as the strawberries and cream are, making their way speedily to secure their seats at the finals!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The finest &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.collinscatering.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.collinscatering.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;; can be reached if you click up on the weblink. This is a company with the professionalism and expertise to under take small to large scale events in their area, and they do so at very competitve prices.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;London catering focuses very much upon the feasts of summer. Essex really is the only way when it comes to catering for big crowds of friends, families or visitors to an exceptional outdoor event. Strawberries, sprinkled with a dusting of sugar and served with double cream, strawberries with clotted cream, strawberries with ice cream and for additional indulgence strawberries dipped in chocolate  , served with cream and meringues.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Catering the Essex way means using only the greatest and locally sourced ingredients where possible. London caterers recognise the organic, homegrown quality of produce from Essex for catering requirements and ingredients from England are utilized in some of the finest catering in London restaurants.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;London catering is renowned for its talented chefs and this is some thing that professional caterers based in London and Essex are trained to deliver to the highest standard.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whether it is for a summer tea party on the lawn with the big screen on Henman Hill in SW19 watching the tennis, or perhaps a marquee based event in Essex or London catering can and should continue to produce the best.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For excellent &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.collinscatering.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.collinscatering.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;; please click   the hyper link and you will be taken to a company   well trained in catering for a vast range of events. Whether large or small this company has the professionalism necessary for any event.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>