<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f8c36aad60240c42c1808b91a1789f7">			Many parents are overjoyed when they find out from the dentist that their children do not have cavities. Some kids are simply going to get cavities more than others, although your kids can avoid them by doing certain things. There are many factors that can contribute to healthy teeth, and in this article we'll be covering some of the most important ones.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some new parents are not sure when to start brushing their baby's teeth. Brushing should begin when you can see them. Teeth need to be kept clean, so you should start brushing them right away. The older your children become, the more important it is for them to brush more than once a day. Because all circumstances are not alike, the age at which your child will make this change could be slightly different from the next child. Your kids may cooperate a little better if you can keep brushing their teeth light hearted.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They would likely have fun brushing with a toothbrush that has the face of a fantasy character on it. Electric toothbrushes are a really popular way to perk your kids' interest in brushing their teeth. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New challenges will always arise as your children continue to grow older overtime. Most kids will not brush or floss their teeth. Usually, they're too lazy to do so. There are many dangers to smoking, yet most teenagers will ignore these dangers and smoke causing more hygiene problems. One way to get them to stop to remind them that will make their teeth yellow. This is much more effective than telling them it might kill them one day. A mouthguard is also a necessary tool to use for your teenager, especially if they play sports. Teenagers will forget about many things, prompting you to remind them constantly about these issues. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teWVtZXJnZW5jeWRlbnRpc3RsYXN2ZWdhcy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;Click here for an Emergency Dentist Las Vegas&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Healthy teeth can also be achieved by taking the correct nutritional supplements. While you should try to see that your kids get most of their nutrition from their diet, sometimes additional supplements may be needed. Calcium and Vitamin D are both essential for healthy teeth and bones. Although traditionally parents used to provide these mainly with milk products, not all kids can tolerate a diet that's high in dairy products. Parents sometimes believe that vitamin supplementation is much more efficient. Another product that may be helpful for dental health is cod liver oil, which is high in Vitamin D3. Vitamin supplements with cod liver oil are probably the best way to go since kids will probably not want to take it because of the way it tastes. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Oral hygiene is basically a routine; therefore the younger your children are when they learn it, the more benefits they will reap. When your kids regularly brush and floss their teeth, along with a proper diet; they will be ensured of better teeth down the road. If you keep the above tips in mind, your children will have a head start when it comes to their dental health.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;More Related Articles:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9oZXNmb3Q0MDUvcG9zdHMvODk4Mjg2L0Vhc3krTWV0aG9kcytZb3UrQ2FuK0FwcGx5K1RvZGF5K1RvK0dldCtHbG93aW5nK0FuZCtTb2xpZCtUZWV0aA__" target="_blank"&gt;;The Importance of Standard Care for Your Teeth&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS9lcm1uZXI5MjMvYmxvZy8yMDEyLzAzLzIwL2hlcmJhbC13YXlzLXRvLWNhcmUtZm9yLXlvdXItdGVldGg/Zmlyc3Rwb3N0PVk_" target="_blank"&gt;;Healthy Therapies Are The Preferred Techniques To Protect Your Teeth And Gums&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>