<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e483121e8d7be91cf0c528503b9d2a23">			Going to the dentist is really important.  Going to the dental practitioner is one of those things that many of us do not like to do but which we know we need to.  One all too frequent reason that people avoid going to the dental office may be the worry that the dental practitioner will reprimand them regarding the condition of their teeth. A very good dentist will never scold, but will educate you about exactly what should be done in the future, as well as about how to take good care of your teeth better. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The dentist will look at all of your teeth and look at your gum line to ensure they're strong and healthy.  The dentist will also look into the way your top and bottom teeth come together.  The dental professional will study your X-rays (searching for cavities and other problems) and ask if you might have questions about your teeth. Dental x-rays  are not dangerous and will be performed at regular intervals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those who have cosmetic issues that ought to be handled, there are numerous solutions a dentist can offer.  Dental veneers (typically known as porcelain veneers or dental porcelain laminates) are wafer-thin, custom-made covers of tooth-colored materials made to cover the front surface of teeth to improve the way you look. Dental veneers can be made from porcelain or from resin composite materials.  Dental implants are necessary when you lose a tooth.  Dental   implants are an attractive option for patients who may have lost one or more teeth, can't chew or smile comfortably, or are not happy with dentures. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Teeth bleaching | Whitening, also referred to as “teeth bleaching” can easily brighten and whiten your teeth from discoloration and / or staining.  Teeth cleanings remove debris that build up on the teeth, irritate the gum area and cause decay.  Teeth whitening is perfect for patients who have healthy, unrestored teeth (no fillings) as well as healthy gums who would like a brighter smile.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tooth decay and children no longer have to go hand in hand. A pediatric dentist can help prepare the parents so that they may begin to maintain a effective preventative regimen at home. The dental professional will certainly be most concerned with all aspects regarding preventive care. Your dentist will introduce your child to the office and show them the equipment in a non-scary way. As early as 1 year of age your dentist will be able to add value to the health of your baby’s teeth by checking that their teeth are cutting through properly and are correctly spaced as well as that there are no problems with your baby’s gums.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Standard visits to the dentist will ensure that the teeth are cleaned, a topical fluoride is given and that cavities are kept in check. In many cases this is the only treatment you will need for many years at a time, as keeping your teeth clean is half the battle in keeping your teeth and mouth healthy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ilovecats.org.tw%2Fforum2%2Findex.php%3Faction%3Dprofile%3Bu%3D42848"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ilovecats.org.tw/forum2/index.php?action=profile;u=42848&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhrodiscuss.info%2Findex.php%3Faction%3Dprofile%3Bu%3D113893"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://hrodiscuss.info/index.php?action=profile;u=113893&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="d572d261c13a8434cf713a72540f1b68">			Going to the dentist is extremely important.  Going to the dental practitioner is certainly one of those things that we don't like to do but that we realize we should.  One all too frequent reason that folks avoid visiting the dental office may be the fear that the dentist will scold them about the condition of their teeth. A very good dentist is not going to scold, but will probably inform you about exactly what should be done in the future, and about how to take good care of your teeth much better. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The dental practitioner will look at all of your teeth and check your gum area to make sure they're strong and healthy.  The dentist also will check the way your top and bottom teeth work together.  The dentist will analyze your X-rays (looking for tooth decay and other problems) and ask if you might have any questions concerning your teeth. Dental x-rays  are not dangerous and will be carried out at regular intervals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you have cosmetic issues that need to be dealt with, there are many solutions the dentist can provide.  Dental veneers (generally known as porcelain veneers or dental porcelain laminates) tend to be wafer-thin, custom-made covers of tooth-colored materials designed to cover the front surface of teeth to improve the way you look. Dental veneers can be produced from porcelain or from resin composite materials.  Dental implants are necessary if you lose a tooth.  Dental   implants are an attractive option for patients who may have lost one or more teeth, can't chew or smile comfortably, or are not happy with dentures. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Teeth bleaching | Whitening, often known as “teeth bleaching” can easily brighten and whiten your teeth from yellowing and / or staining.  Teeth cleanings remove debris that build up on the teeth, aggravate the gum area and cause decay.  Teeth bleaching is suitable for individuals who have healthy, unrestored teeth (no fillings) and healthy gums who would like a brighter smile.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tooth decay and children no longer need to go hand in hand. The pediatric dentist will help prepare the parents so that they may begin to maintain a beneficial preventive regimen at home. Your dental practitioner will be most concerned with all elements regarding preventive care. Your dental professional will introduce your child to the office and show them the equipment in a non-scary way. As early as just one year of age your dentist will be able to add value to the health of your baby’s teeth by checking that their teeth are cutting through properly and are correctly spaced and that there are no problems with your baby’s gum area.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Regular visits to the dentist can ensure that the teeth are cleaned, a topical fluoride is given and that cavities are kept in check. In many cases this can be the only treatment you'll need for many years at a time, as keeping your teeth clean can be half the battle in keeping your teeth and mouth healthy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.moviemaker.com%2Fmember%2F264320%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.moviemaker.com/member/264320/&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.project-reason.org%2Fmember%2F359691%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.project-reason.org/member/359691/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>