<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="eae050a1448cbc52176e04e962fb9a67">			&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/148328673_1331139_32457186.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We just previewed the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLWZjLXN0LXBhdWxp" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk High St Pauli&lt;/a&gt;;  , and here we feature the Nike x FC St. Pauli – Dunk High Premium, which is a collaboration which has been talked about for months, but it isn’t till now that the shoes are actually hitting retailers, with a set release date of May 30, 2008. They feature a black leather upper, as well as ostrich leather on the Nike swoosh. They also feature a variety of logos and images, including a skull and bones on the quarter panels.The High is limited to 500 pairs and the Low 250 pairs worldwide, but will only be released in European countries. 
&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLWZjLXN0LXBhdWxp" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike St Pauli Dunk High&lt;/a&gt;;   comes in a Black/Black-Medium Grey Colorway. Classic shape made of black smooth leather suede and mesh. Features nice woven laces, mixing the colors that are also represented on the sneakers. Nice and fresh with the ostrich detailing. Under the innersole you will find the Zoom Air unit for extra comfort. Each pair comes exclusive with a St. Pauli Patch!It is something for all the soccer fans among you. Nike got together with German soccer club FC St. Pauli from Hamburg. The club has somewhat of a special standing in German soccer, not necessarily because of its performance, but because of its rebel character. That is also clearly translated into the Dunk Pack that they have worked with Nike on. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;nike dunks&lt;/a&gt;;  ? Nike's most popular skateboarding shoe?has all the high quality design features that Nike offers. Nike Dunk SB’s have been available for over many years now, and come in over 65 different color variations and styles now. Since the Dunk's evolution into a skateboarding shoe, the letters `SB` have been added to signify their link to Skateboarding. It’s apprehensive at first about Nike Dunk Hi Premium “FC St. Pauli, people like the way they've gone about it.
&lt;br /&gt;;Partnering up with German Soccer Club from Hamburg FC St. Pauli, Nike released a package of sneakers commemorating the club consisting of the Dunk High and Low. The Nike Dunk High FC St. Pauli features a black and white palette made up of a variety of materials including a mesh toebox, ostrich leather swoosh and suede heel panel. Lastly, an enlarged skull and crossed bones is printed on the midsection, which is the logo of FC. St. Pauli. Both sneakers from the package released in 2008 exclusively in Europe limited to only 500 pairs. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Black, black-medium grey colorway combine to form this &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLWZjLXN0LXBhdWxp" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike St Pauli Shoes&lt;/a&gt;;  . Classic shape are made of black smooth leather suede and mesh. Features on nice woven laces, mixed colors, this model also represented on the Nike Dunk High's. Nice and fresh with the ostrich detailing. Under the innersole, you will find the Zoom Air unit for extra comfort. Each pair comes exclusive with a St. Pauli Patch!It is something for all the soccer fans to get one Nike Dunk High's. 
&lt;br /&gt;;This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk High&lt;/a&gt;;   Premium comes in a Black/Black-Medium Grey Colorway. Classic shape made of black smooth leather suede and mesh. Features nice woven laces, mixing the colors that are also represented on the sneakers. Nice and fresh with the ostrich detailing. Under the innersole you will find the Zoom Air unit for extra comfort. Each pair comes exclusive with a St. Pauli Patch!It is something for all the soccer fans among you. Nike got together with German soccer club FC St. Pauli from Hamburg. The club has somewhat of a special standing in German soccer, not necessarily because of its performance, but because of its rebel character. That is also clearly translated into the Dunk Pack that they have worked with Nike on.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We Also Recommend : 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk SB Low CL Urban Haze 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Channel Zero x Revive Customs 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High SB Send Help Edition (black white blue reef) 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Premium Osaka dotonbori Vivid Blueblack-Red-White 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Premium Santana Edition(Black / Black / Glacier Ice) 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Premium SB Dinosaur Jr		</conversation>		<conversation id="a0e9aef722f7645781ec005283e7f31f">			&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/148328673_13384134_32473917.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;collect-shoes.com currently has this rather uninspired pair of Boba Fett &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstc2I_" target="_blank"&gt;;nike dunk SB&lt;/a&gt;;   sneakers for $99.99. I guess the dark army/team red color scheme is reminiscent of Boba Fett's armor, but where are the hidden rocket launchers, grappling hooks or throwing knives? It makes me wonder if this is just a quick licensing cash grab by Lucasfilm, but does that really seem like something they'd do?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here we feature some detailed pictures of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWJvYmEtZmV0dC1kYXJrLWFybXktdGVhbS1yZWQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;nike dunks Boba Fett&lt;/a&gt;;   which are part of Nike SB’s October 2008 collection. They are inspired by the Star Wars collection, and the fictional character who is actually a bounty killer hired by the Galactic Empire and Jabba the Hutt to track down and capture Han Solo and Chewbacca. This isn’t the first time that Nike has turned to the Star Wars series for inspiration, as they released a pair of Storm Trooper Dunks a few years back. They feature a leather / nubuck construction, along with bright yellow and red accents. You can find them now at BNYC Online.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWJvYmEtZmV0dC1kYXJrLWFybXktdGVhbS1yZWQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;nike Boba Fett dunk high&lt;/a&gt;;   have an interesting story behind them. They are inspired by the Star Wars collection, and the fictional character who is actually a bounty killer hired by the Galactic Empire and Jabba the Hutt to track down and capture Han Solo and Chewbacca. This isn’t the first time that Nike has turned to the Star Wars series for inspiration, as they released a pair of Storm Trooper Dunks a few years back. They feature a leather / nubuck construction, along with bright yellow and red accents.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As reported a few months ago, Nike will be releasing this grey/black/yellow/red Nike SB Dunk High, nicknamed the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb2xsZWN0LXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1wcmVtaXVtLXNiLWJvYmEtZmV0dC1kYXJrLWFybXktdGVhbS1yZWQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;Boba Fett nike shoes&lt;/a&gt;;   . This isn’t the first time Nike has turned to the Star Wars for inspiration, a few years back the “Storm Trooper” Dunks were sold exclusively at Foot Action. However, these are rumored to be a little harder to get your hands on like the “Gold Rail” SB Dunks as seen in a previous post. Look for these to drop at selected SB retailers next month. Via Vapors.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We Also Recommend : 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Premium SB Goodfellas Mafia Edition 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Premium SB Mork and Mindy 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High Premium SB Paul Urich - Skeleton Rainbow Edition 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunks Low Pro Sb Flavio Samelo Brasil Exclusive 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk Mid Pro SB - Batman (Midnight Fog Black) 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk Mid SB - Premium SB light bone/black (Crew Collection)		</conversation>	</conversations></author>