<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3176e73fdbc092b9e60470fcd2b9ecb6">			&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm8.static.flickr.com%2F7101%2F7344270526_2b08247f86.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://farm8.static.flickr.com/7101/7344270526_2b08247f86.jpg&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;264&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;;We have all seen little old ladies and men using canes and hearing aids. But this isn't the norm. Much of the assumptions made about old age are based on myth. Many older people are living full and happy lives. Keep these tips in mind as you get older.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Go see your doctor regularly for check ups and get tested when asked. If you stay on top of it, you will find out early what is wrong and take care of it immediately. The quicker you take care of any problems, the better you will be able manage it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try a resveratrol supplement. Clinical studies being done on resveratrol and the positive effects it has on aging are showing great results. There is a compound called Resveratrol that is found in nuts and grapes, creating these benefits as well. The Japanese knotweed contains resveratol and is often used to make supplements. Additionally, it can be extracted from Senna quiquangulata roots.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Visit your GP for a routine physical at least once a year. Being examined on a regular basis will let your doctor catch any potential health problems and deal with them before they become too serious. Treatment is available for many conditions, including cancers, and it is usually more successful if the disease is caught in its early stages.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Eat a healthy, balanced diet. Eat fresh fruit and veggies to have a diet that is low in fat and sugar. A well-balanced, healthy diet improves the body as well as the mind. Your health depends on the fuels you put in your tank, so give your body high-test fuel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try to focus on making others happy in every situation. If you will make those around you happy, it will make you a happier person. Happiness is something that doesn't cost a penny, and yet it's one of the greatest gifts you can give and receive.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try not to think about the numbers in your age. You age is not too important because you may feel much younger. If you feel old, then you are old. You can be young at heart regardless of your chronological age. Try not to let your age have a negative affect on the way you feel. Focus on the positive aspects of aging, not the numbers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Through the course of your life, your house begins to feel like a safe place. Take the time to turn your home into a comfortable refuge, so that you know you have a place of rest if the rigors of the outside world have been too much for you. It is comforting to know that your home is always there for you as a place of peace and relaxation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Being healthy and in shape can help you avoid the negative attributes of old age including weight gain, certain diseases, energy loss, and memory loss. Give your body what it needs by way of a healthy diet and regular exercise, and you will see and feel the results.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be a positive presence! Taking that sunny disposition and spreading it around makes the world a better place and makes you feel better as well. Happiness is priceless. It doesn't cost a penny.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Apply what you have learned from this article to help other as well as yourself age gracefully. Keep learning, keep trying to stay young - many people are enjoying a quality of life that was previously unheard of well into their old age! &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NoYXVuc2NoYW1pbmcxNjEucG9zdGVyb3VzLmNvbS9pbmZvcm1hdGlvbi1vbi10aGUtbmlrb24tY29vbHBpeC1sMjUtZGlnaXRhbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;a website&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibG9nc3Rlci5jb20vbWFyZ2VyZXRrcmVuemtlNi9wbGFubmluZy15b3VyLW5ldy1saXR0bGUtb25lcy1iZWQtcm9vbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;a website&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>