<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="51037ae07448af85230e79e1ad7410ea">			Many people are proud owners of an iPhone, but do not know all the tricks and tips on using it to its fullest potential. Fortunately, articles just like this one abound online, allowing users to understand their iPhone better. To see if this is the phone for you, keep reading!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you value your privacy greatly, then you should probably use Siri a little less. Voice prompts spoken to Siri are recorded by Apple and then stored on their internal server. This helps them develop speech recognition programs, although it is important to understand that you may be recorded.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mdXR1cmlzdGljc21hcmtldGluZy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;futuristicsmarketing.com&lt;/a&gt;;For those who use their iPhone to view the weather, you can alternate between current conditions and the six-day forecast by swiping either left or right. Tap anywhere on the weather bar within the Notifications screen to easily access the Weather app.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you've been reading a lengthy article and want to get back to the page's top, you don't need to waste your time scrolling. Just tap on the status bar in the grey area on top of the screen and you will go back to the beginning of the website or article.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Safari and mail applications are widely used by iPhone owners, but many are not aware of how to save images with these apps. When you see a picture you want to save to your phone, just tap and hold on the image. A box pops up after this period of time prompting you to save any image on your iPhone.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Current weather conditions are available to iPhone users through the weather app. A lot of people don't know that when you click on local weather, you can get an breakdown for every hour in the next 12 hours' weather. You can also ask Siri for the weather over the next few hours, and it will give a breakdown of that too.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The iPhone's calendar function is great for organizing your life. Enhanced speed and efficiency can be achieved by directly entering events instead of using the &quot;+&quot; function. While you are viewing your calendar via the day, tap any hour and hold down. This will create a new entry on the time you chose. The quicker you can schedule things, the less time you'll have to waste on it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can use the settings to make the iPhone visually indicate when you have an incoming call or message. You can make the flash from the camera blink when you are getting a call. Just access the settings menu, then to &quot;general&quot; and next to &quot;accessibility.&quot; Then turn on the alert feature titled LED Flash.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Deleting unwanted email has never been easier. Simply highlight the message by dragging your finger across the message and hitting the delete button that comes up.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYWdib29rLmNvbS9ibG9ncy8xODUzNjc2" target="_blank"&gt;;Your Best Chance For A Successful Article Marketing Campaign Contained Below&lt;/a&gt;;The iPhone is one of the most popular devices on the market today. This device grants access to thousands of features, shortcuts, apps and tools that are perfectly suited to school, work, family and social events. This article just provided you with some of the things you can do to get the most out of your iPhone. By using these tips, you will find more fun and fascination in your iPhone than you imagined.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>