<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b67aa29b47786b2a5c1a43009a855509">			These articles get circulated far and wide and it would be to your benefit to get them out there. After you publish a certain amount, you get recognition from the article directory which gets you more views and attention. Article submission goes far beyond just posting. Writing an article analysis is just the same as writing any other type of essay, the only difference is that your own skills of analyzing papers will be included when writing an article analysis.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First, try to examine the article as a whole and establish the author's purpose, audience and subject. Why did the author write this article? Does it give some kind of information, methods, or is it political? Usually you will find the purpose of an article in the first few paragraphs. Authors will state their objectives in the first part and will try to explain what is the use of their article or how will it be beneficial to the reader.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Next, try to determine who the audience for this paper is. Is it for scholarly publishing? Is it for the scientists or is it for the public? It is important to know who the audience is so you can determine how to address the article, whether it is academic or for general readership.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Third, what is the subject? What is the article about? What is the author's argument? What is the author's point? You should be able to determine the subject in the first few paragraphs and also in the title. Sometimes some articles contain an abstract and this also gives a summary of what the article is all about. Check also the sources of the author. Is it derived from books, journals, interviews or surveys? From the sources of the author, you will be able to determine what the author is trying to talk about.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After you have determined these important pieces of information, you can summarize the article in a short paragraph, noting the important points of the article. Summarize the author's main points.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can now go to the body of the article. You may want to divide the parts of the body into segments based on your analysis. You will find in the body the evidence that the author used to support his argument. State your own opinion on the author's argument and find information in the article to support your opinion. Write your own reaction to the paper, your comments and how well did the author present his evidence. Was the evidence able to support his argument? What is the strength of the case? Is it persuasive enough to the readers? How convincing is the article?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will also find in the body the points of view of the writer. Check out which are positive and negative and write down your own analysis of what you perceive about the author's point of view. You may also write down other opposing ideas regarding the subject. Remember to keep summaries short and always write an article analysis with your own words and opinions that have been formed in your mind while reading the article.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Please don't forget to visit here online writing community for reading,writing and submitting articles.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4xMjNtaW5zaWRhLnNlL3dhbGxhY2VzYW50bzkyMi84MTAwMTM4NQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;How to Outsource - Writing a Solid Project Description Before Posting it Online&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NjZWF0aGxpbmVlbnRzeXhhbmcuamlnc3kuY29tL2VudHJpZXMvZ2VuZXJhbC9Ib3ctVG8tQmVjb21lLUFuLU91dHNvdXJjZS1BZ2VudC0tLU5vLUZlZXMtUmVxdWlyZWQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;How to Write an Article to Make a lot of Money&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="d8f40d74197da7a6980432bda334cf9b">			Doing this will alert Google to the theme of your article as well as to link the article to the keywords in which you'd like to target.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- You must also use the keywords in the first paragraph and preferably in the last few sentences of the article body. This will further cement in Google's mind the relevancy of the keywords to the article.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Further to that you also want to use the keywords around 1% of the time throughout the article. You do not want to use the keywords much more than that as Google will suspect you are trying to 'keyword stuff' the article and will de-index or 'sandbox' you accordingly.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I hope this little tips on how to write an article analysis will help show you how to lead the way and be at the top of Google for your related niches and blogs in no time!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Please don't forget to visit online business community for free and quality article marketing news and information.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Knowing how to write and article and submit it to the directories is a key to internet and blogging success. There are some basic tenants and rules to go by so that your articles get accepted and later ranked by search engines like Google. Lets break it down to the various pieces.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. The title must contain your chosen niche keyword. Keywords can be chosen using the Google AdWords keyword tool. Look for high search volume with light competition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choose category in your niche or field. ie-home based business/network marketing&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The article summary or teaser should contain the keyword once and summarizes what the article is about in a paragraph or two at most.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. The body of your article must be a minimum of 400 words. Be careful not to make them too lengthy or people may not read it. That is because people like articles that are easy to read.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the article body, use bullet points or numbers to summarize the major points. It is easy on the eye to look at bullet points thus it is easier for the reader to see your content.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Place your keyword twice in the article body. If you put it in too many times, the article publisher may reject publishing it. That will just slow you down with revisions.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do not place links into the article body (some directories allow them, but others do not), but DO place a link or two in the resource box. This is where you lead your reader to more information on the subject or offer them a free gift.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Do not sell your business opportunity in the article, but keep your article focused on content. You can write a review on your business opportunity, but keep it informational only and don't make it a sales pitch. Remember to come across as an authority on the topic rather than a salesperson.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Choose a few keywords. People often think that more is better, but we want specificity in our niche so be specific in your keyword choices. Put the niche keyword and your name to brand yourself.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is good to spread it around, but EzineArticles is the leader and widely recognized. I would start there and build up your reputation. You can combine your blog and SEO with articles to create backlinks which may put your article onto page one of Google searches.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hcnRpY2xlbWFya2V0aW5naG93dG8uY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;how to make a lot of money&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>