<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fab6d574bcafe81b8a0f6e2b68d2c92d">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxrYW50YXl0cmVrdG91ci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Salkantay Trek &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxrYW50YXl0cmVrdG91ci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Salkantay Trek &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;, has been owned and operated by Cusquenian People, for the past ten years. Arnol has many years of experience in the outdoor industry in Peru. Arnol started out in the outdoor industry travelling the country representing two well know Peru outdoor equipment manufacturers and then moved into the retail sector. Arnold has passed his expert knowledge and training on to his staff who are all involved in using the equipment they sell in the outdoors.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxrYW50YXl0cmVrdG91ci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Salkantay Trek &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; Description:
&lt;br /&gt;This trekking expedition is one of the most pictures trips offered in Cusco region which will take you close of the sacred Salkantay snow peak (6,271 meters / 20569ft), one of the highest and most stunning in the Peruvian Andes, passing through Quechua communities and lesser-known Inca ruins, to finally reach Aguas Calientes on the fourth day. The impressive Sacred Inca city of Machupicchu is visited on the last day of the program. This itinerary is an interesting alternative for those not having found spaces on the Inca Trail trek to Machupicchu. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxrYW50YXl0cmVrdG91ci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Salkantay Trek &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; Itinerary:
&lt;br /&gt;DAY 01 : CUSCO - MOLLEPATA - SORAYPAMPA 
&lt;br /&gt;We leave Cusco very early, passing villages like Izcuchaca and Limatambo and then after 3 hours we arrive in Mollepata. After a light breakfast we start our long but slow walk till the sector of Silca where the lunch is waiting for us. After a short break we continue our walk in beautiful landscapes till Soraypampa, where we spend our first night.
&lt;br /&gt;DAY 02 : SORAYPAMPA - CHALLWAY 
&lt;br /&gt;Today, nature will change drastically from dry sceneries to snowy peaks and tropical areas. After a nutritious breakfast, we will start the most difficult part of the trek. We will start the hike around 7:00 in the morning. We will hike to a place called Pampas Salkantay, then go toward the left side of the snowy peaks of Umantay located next to the Apu Salkantay. At midday, we will be on the highest point ( 4600 meters above sea level). We will appreciate spectacular views of the mountains and the imposing snowy peaks of the Salkantay (6264 meters above sea level) which is known as the second highest point of the Cusco region. Around 1:00 p.m., we will have our lunch, in the area called Huayracmachay. After a trek of approximately 3 hours, we will arrive to our camp in Challway (2920 meters above sea level). Around 7:00p.m., we will recuperate from the trek and eat dinner.
&lt;br /&gt;DAY 03 : CHALLWAY - HIDROELECTRICA - AGUAS CALIENTES 
&lt;br /&gt;Around 5:00a.m., we will start our trek and we will enjoy the beautiful sunrise. We will walk for about 5 hours toward Playa Sahuayaco and during this period; we will observe a town called Collpabamba, also called the “Forest Cloudy Brow” where waterfalls, fruit-bearing trees, varied flora, and birds can be observed. salcantay pass river crossingIf we are lucky, we will be able to observe the famous bird called the “Cock of the Rocks'. Once at Playa Sahuayaco, we will take a local bus to drive us to the hydroelectric train station. At around 1:30p.m., we will have our lunch at the hydroelectric. At 3:20p.m., we will take a train from the hydroelectric to the town of Aguas Calientes (2000 meters above sea level). Here, you have the option of going to the thermal hot springs. We will have dinner at 7:00p.m. and accommodation at the hotel or hostel of your choice.
&lt;br /&gt;DAY 04: AGUAS CALIENTES - MACHU PICCHU - CUSCO 
&lt;br /&gt;This day we go by bus or walking to Machupicchu where our guide tells us in three hours about the times and history of Incas, when we have the opportunity to appreciate Machupicchu in all its splendor. In the afternoon we return to Aguas Calientes to take a train. Then, in Ollantaytambo we change to a bus which takes us to Cusco.  
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxrYW50YXl0cmVrdG91ci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Salkantay Trek &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; What is Included:
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Official English speaking guide (two guides for groups over 8 persons)
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Entrance to Machu Picchu
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Transfer from Cusco to Mollepata Village by private or shared tourist bus
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Return train ticket from Aguas Calientes to Ollantaytambo
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Bus tickets round trip from Aguas Calientes village to Machu Picchu
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Horses to carry food and camping equipment and your personal items (6kilos)
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. 4 capacity tent (four season tent) - 2 persons per tent with plenty space for backpacks
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. A Roll pad mattress
&lt;br /&gt;•	
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Bags for your items from the company for 3 days
&lt;br /&gt;•	
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. All meals on the trail (3 breakfast - 3 lunches - 3 dinners)
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Teatime everyday (coffee, tea, popcorn, cookies)
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Water supply (boiled) after every dinner or breakfast
&lt;br /&gt;•	
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. First aid kit and oxygen bottle for any participant and our camp staff
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Vegetarian food available on request .Vegetarian food
&lt;br /&gt;•	&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zYWxrYW50YXl0cmVrdG91ci5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;Salkantay Trek &lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt; What is not Included:
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Breakfast on the first day and last day lunch
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Visit to the hot springs in Aguas Calientes: a relaxing way to end-up the 4-day trek while you’re awaiting the return train to Cusco, only 10 minutes from the village center, entrance fee is US$ 1,50. Towels can be hired in Aguas Calientes.
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Tips: please beware that our agency staff is well paid so please feel free to tip or not according to your wish.
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Alcoholics drinks
&lt;br /&gt;•	*. Personal clothing for trek and clothes rain.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.salkantaytrektour.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.salkantaytrektour.com&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>