<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d25fcdfa22d8da7e7fa09ff130968754">			Limited Numbers Of Photographers At All Lessons.&lt;br /&gt;;As a way to optimize the training opportunity, each delegate is guaranteed private one-to-one shooting time with every model for each ‘look'. You're a part of the team for the time that you are on the courses. Delegates integrate fully with the models, stylist and hair and make up artist and discover first hand from Bruce and his squad what performs, what doesn't and exactly why.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Discover The Secrets Of Lighting For Location Fashion.&lt;br /&gt;;Learn how the photos you have seen in numerous publications are produced, when you learn how Bruce lights his amazing location or studio wedding pictures, then apply it yourself during the class! Before you reserve your fashion nude photography course, have a look at the Former Students Feedback And Images, where every image was shot by delegates during Bruce Smith Photography Lessons.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Professional Team.&lt;br /&gt;;Bruce exclusively selects working professionals to become a part of his team. This assures that the wardrobe stylists and make up artists are creating appropriate and dazzling ‘looks' that help to make the basic people photographs which will go in to your portfolio be right UP TO DATE One 2 One pictures..&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Agency Standard Professional Models.&lt;br /&gt;;You'll be photographing with Bruce's choice of agency level professional glamour models, selected for their appearance and their ability to work with photographers. When you have never captured pics of a professional model in the past, this will certainly give you an insight to a totally new arena of creativity.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Crucial Insights Tips And Hints.&lt;br /&gt;;The Bruce Smith Photography Academy Lessons will give you a foundation from which to actively pursue glamour photography as a vocation. The photography lessons contain essential insights, tips and techniques that will inspire you to develop your own skills and style as a baby photographer - so you too can capture the glamour, dynamism, and sophistication of the model portfolio photography industry.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To Become The Best You Need To Be Taught By The Best.&lt;br /&gt;;Students receive a professional experience because we only use the best team members, models and facilities for these courses. YOU will be taught by a seasoned professional with 35 years experience shooting for high calibre nude clients all over the world.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Combining The Important Elements.&lt;br /&gt;;During these photography classes, Bruce demonstrates and explains to you all of the key information, from setting up the perfect lighting set ups for freelance or preparing to shoot on location. Working with agency standard professional beauty models. Post-production and photoshop for portraiture skills and how to break into this amazing industry. Helping you to compete within the fashion portrait photography business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will get a unique opportunity to combine all of these elements to produce your own fashion nude photographs for your portfolio during these photography courses. To achieve amazing fashion portrait pictures you need to be able to communicate, direct and be in control of your shoot. All of which you will learn during a Bruce Smith Academy Location Fashion Photography Course, and all of these skills I teach and help you to refine so you are at the start of developing your own unique style of photography.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xlYXJuZGlnaXRhbHBob3RvZ3JhcGh5bm93LmNvbS9mYXNoaW9uLXBob3RvZ3JhcGh5LXR1dG9yaWFscy1saXR0bGUtZ2Vtcy0x" target="_blank"&gt;;senior photography courses&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xlYXJuZGlnaXRhbHBob3RvZ3JhcGh5bm93LmNvbS9mYXNoaW9uLXBob3RvZ3JhcGh5LXR1dG9yaWFscy1saXR0bGUtZ2Vtcy0z" target="_blank"&gt;;beauty photography courses&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xlYXJuZGlnaXRhbHBob3RvZ3JhcGh5bm93LmNvbS9mYXNoaW9uLXBob3RvZ3JhcGh5LXR1dG9yaWFscy1saXR0bGUtZ2Vtcy0y" target="_blank"&gt;;portrait photography courses&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="bb1985a946013bb019f5ca30f5f569ff">			Limited Numbers Of Photographers For All Courses.&lt;br /&gt;;In order to optimize this training opportunity, each delegate is assured private one-to-one shooting time with each model for every ‘look'. You're part of the team for the time you are on your lessons. Delegates assimilate fully with the models, stylist and hair and make up artist and find out first hand from Bruce and his squad what performs, what won't and why.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Discover The Secrets Of Lighting For Senior Portrait.&lt;br /&gt;;Discover how the photos you have often seen in numerous mags are accomplished, when you learn the way Bruce lights his amazing location or studio wedding pictures, then practice it yourself through the course! When you book your model portfolio photography lessons, have a look at the Former Students Feedback And Images, where each and every image was taken by delegates during Bruce Smith Photography Lessons.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Professional Team.&lt;br /&gt;;Bruce only selects working professionals to become part of his team. This ensures that the wardrobe stylists and make up artists are coming up with relevant and dazzling ‘looks' that help to make the basic people photographs that will go in to your profile be right UP TO DATE Glamour images..&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Agency Standard Professional Models.&lt;br /&gt;;You will be photographing with Bruce's choice of agency level professional freelance models, selected for their look as well as their capacity to work with photographers. When you have never photographed a professional model in the past, it will provide you with an insight to a whole new arena of creative imagination.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Crucial Insights Tips And Hints.&lt;br /&gt;;The Bruce Smith Photography Academy Lessons will give you a foundation from which to actively pursue basic people photography as a vocation. The photography classes contain essential insights, tips and techniques that will inspire you to develop your own skills and style as a studio photographer - so you too can capture the glamour, dynamism, and sophistication of the beauty photography industry.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To Become The Best You Need To Be Taught By The Best.&lt;br /&gt;;Students receive a professional experience because we only use the best team members, models and facilities for these classes. YOU will be taught by a seasoned professional with 35 years experience shooting for high calibre beauty clients all over the world.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Combining The Important Elements.&lt;br /&gt;;During these photography classes, Bruce demonstrates and explains to you all of the key information, from setting up the perfect lighting set ups for senior portrait or preparing to shoot on location. Working with agency standard professional nude models. Post-production and photoshop for creative skills and how to break into this amazing industry. Helping you to compete within the one 2 one photography business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will get a unique opportunity to combine all of these elements to produce your own portrait images for your portfolio during these photography classes. To achieve amazing beauty pictures you need to be able to communicate, direct and be in control of your shoot. All of which you will learn during a Bruce Smith Academy Artistic Photography Lesson, and all of these skills I teach and help you to refine so you are at the start of developing your own unique style of photography.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xlYXJuZGlnaXRhbHBob3RvZ3JhcGh5bm93LmNvbS9mYXNoaW9uLXBob3RvZ3JhcGh5LXR1dG9yaWFscy1saXR0bGUtZ2Vtcy0x" target="_blank"&gt;;beauty photography courses&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xlYXJuZGlnaXRhbHBob3RvZ3JhcGh5bm93LmNvbS9mYXNoaW9uLXBob3RvZ3JhcGh5LXR1dG9yaWFscy1saXR0bGUtZ2Vtcy0y" target="_blank"&gt;;senior photography courses&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xlYXJuZGlnaXRhbHBob3RvZ3JhcGh5bm93LmNvbS9mYXNoaW9uLXBob3RvZ3JhcGh5LXR1dG9yaWFscy1saXR0bGUtZ2Vtcy0z" target="_blank"&gt;;portrait photography courses&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>