<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f62728ee4f50b0b1a776eb9a908301fb">			The &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbosehometheaterreview.com%2FBoseV10HomeTheaterReview%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BBose"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://bosehometheaterreview.com/BoseV10HomeTheaterReview/&quot;&gt;;Bose&lt;/a&gt;; Lifestyle V10 Home Theater&lt;/a&gt;; has very small &quot;cube speakers&quot; and over at Bose they've always specialised in tiny audio gear, and they've made it their mission to use that, as their biggest selling point... it's their forte so to speak.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you imagine Bose Wireless speakers imagine them being about the same dimensions of the furry dice that used to hold from every truckers rear view mirror...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That is how small these things are, we're talking small...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Small enough to sit on a book shelf... small enough, to make using the term astounding, without having tofeel bad for over stating my point.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In a nutshell these little speakers are completely brilliant, and the Bose Lifestyle V10 Home Theater Review favourite feature of all!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Yes, there are many Audio fans concerned with issues such as connectivity and Bose do that at a level most home theatre manufacturers just can't even hold a candle to, but I'm talking about me and people like me here, your &quot;average&quot; user.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having a mess of spaghetti-like wires hanging out of the rear of everything you own, gaming machines, video, blue ray system, radio, desktop computer systems and so forth, is a total nightmare and with these Bose systems we're talking about wi-fi cube speakers and the entire home theatre system itself. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I stay in a small area and this makes all of the difference as I would be endlessly tripping over cable if it we're not for this one feature. My wireless cube speakers for example, &quot;snuggle down&quot; behind stuff on a shelf (and one potted plant that appears to just love Joni Mitchel) and they always create that spooky impact when visitors suddenly want to know where on earth the sound is coming from.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Astounding, is just about right, where these little Bose cube wireless speakers are concerned. You get five of them with the Bose V10, so you can get an all round surround sound, fully HDMI ready of course...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What else would you expect from Bose Home Theater?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Particularly good when connecting to other gear (HDMI connectivity is what I might call perfect, and gives fine quality sound so you can get the best from blue ray players and games machines alike) and as you'd expect the system already has all of the connections you'd ever want inbuilt, so it is so simple as putting the plug into the socket to get the best sound you could possibly imagine.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Visit the if you want to learn extra in depth reviews. You'll find some great consumer comments not all of them agree with me though, however I just do not see the sense in paying out huge mountains of cash for The Most expensive Home Theater System. That's simply pure stupidity.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbosehometheaterreview.com%2FBoseV10HomeTheaterReview%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BBose"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://bosehometheaterreview.com/BoseV10HomeTheaterReview/&quot;&gt;;Bose&lt;/a&gt;; Lifestyle V10 Home Theater&lt;/a&gt;;  is expensive, yes, it would be foolish to say otherwise, but this mid range priced outfit will get you more than you'll get with most of the more expensive systems		</conversation>		<conversation id="e596284bd096c4d63b2db62a9927a0b4">			&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cannonreviews.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3BCanon"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cannonreviews.com/&quot;&gt;;Canon&lt;/a&gt;; SD880is Powershot&lt;/a&gt;; Digital Elph you'll find that it is only one digital digital camera in a range of &quot;Canon powershot&quot; models. There are several like the Sd880, which is a slightly older, and one of the  models that we'll see in use for some time to come.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The rationale it is &quot;here to stay&quot; is simply that it is one of those digital cameras that gets the job carried out and will get it carried out well... In the Canon SD880 Powershot Review you'll notice that it scores very extremely well in all categories. I am giving it 5 out of 5 in all but one category. Check to see which on the review itself...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The 10-megapixel PowerShot SD880 IS Digital Elph is the new follow-up to the SD870, and is a wonderfully updated model of a camera that everyone just fell in love with..
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Easily capable of producing an outstanding quality of shot for a digital camera of its size, you'd be forgiven for reckoning that you all of a sudden developed a magical touch. In your very first shots you may no doubt discover Canon SD880 powershot an instantaneous improvement. I personally was amazed by it's performance...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;(Fact is, I like anything that makes me look good!)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are minor weaknesses, as you will see on the Canon SD880 review sales page, however this is an excellent point-and-shoot camera, which for it's price, outshines the competitors easily.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is dimensions are good too...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To start with there's an amazingly visable display screen on the Canon SD880  which takes up virtually the entire back of the digital camera! The display itself is nice and brilliant, and crystal clear. Which means that even the on sunniest of days, you can still have the ability to get a clear view of your shots. Something that many other producers really fall fowl on.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6.3 ounces in weight it's nice and light. At 3.7 inches wide by 2.2 inches high by just 0.9 inch deep, it will slip comfortably in your coat pocket with ease. There are a great deal of smaller cameras on the market than the SD880, but I reckon, if it slips right into a coat pocket, it's small enough.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In comparison with the previous version, the old SD870 IS, the more updated SD880 IS has the very latest release of of Canon's image-processing engine, Digic 4 taking it from eight megapixels to an amazingly clear 10, which suggests if you would like, you can get enormous prints with none of the normal loss of clarity.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It additionally now provides you a number of extra &quot;scene&quot; modes. It's 4x f28-58 28-112mm lens is one of the highlights of the camera. You're getting a wide angle lense!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is a nice touch that Canon have used here.. and so good to have, particularly on a digital camera  that isn't a DSLR... A camera as small as this one? That is extremely good. You are additionally getting a better zoom than on the SD870, and a dramatically improved video function, as Canon SD880 Powershot is now using the H.264 codec an upgrade to the previous Motion JPEG. Motion JPEG was good, but the H.264 codec makes a real noticeable difference. Enough to warrant a special point out in my book.
&lt;br /&gt;;When you decide to &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cannonreviews.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bbuy"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cannonreviews.com/&quot;&gt;;buy&lt;/a&gt;; Canon SD880 Powershot&lt;/a&gt;; you'll find it was worth getting.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>