<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="39fbfca0ef4312cc5189faffc6afaee9">			Having your skin tags removed would mean experiencing a lot of pain. Now getting rid of them can be done easily and with less pain. It is important for you to know &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZW1vdmVza2ludGFncy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;how to remove skin tags&lt;/a&gt;. Before moving on to different skin tag removal methods, make sure first if it has to be removed. Will it cause harm to the body, if it remains there forever? The answer is an emphatic 'No'. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Others are led to believe that skin tags are cancerous. These are all false statements. Skin tags do not have any connection with the term 'cancer'. This is not worth worrying. Therefore, there are no pressing medical justifications to remove skin tags. The main reason why it is removed by people is due to the fact that it affects their physical beauty. Of course, given the choice between unblemished, flawless skin and one with warts and skin tags, you would prefer the former.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is beauty-related more than health-related that tags are subjected to various treatments to remove them. Thus the amount of money that you wish to spend need not be so high. You can choose between surgical procedures and natural treatments. Home remedies are also known to be quite effective. It's also all right, if you decide that you don't really need any treatment at all.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There's no need to subject yourself to surgery, if you've come to terms with having a skin tag anyway. Using dental floss or a string to remove skin tags requires a lot of care and caution. You have to tie only the lower region or the narrow base of the skin tag. If you tie the wrong region or if you apply too much of force, this might lead to the problem of excessive bleeding. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Freezing can also help pinch off the skin tags. Nitrogen is liquid in the freezing method. Since you will be handling chemicals, make sure to wear gloves. Burning the skin tags is also considered to be a wonderful option. This is tried out by many people. Burning will be done using the electric cautery.  
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you want the simplest method, use scissors. But this procedure can be a little painful. You can have anesthesia when using this method.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may not need &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pbnN0aXR1dGUtc2hvdC5jb20vYW5lc3RoZXNpYV9hbmRfc3VyZ2VyeS5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;anesthesia&lt;/a&gt; if the skin tags are small, anyway. Doctors would suggest anesthetics when dealing with larger skin tags. Lidocaine will be injected, before removing the skin tags. Another option is topical anesthesia. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Betacaine cream will be used or LXM 5 % percent cream will be used. The methods on removing skin tags will greatly benefit the people whose skin tags are in visible parts of their body.		</conversation>		<conversation id="cf555d82d5d3ed128f2de94b930bc24e">			Having your skin tags removed would mean experiencing a lot of pain. Now getting rid of them can be done easily and with less pain. Everyone should know &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZW1vdmVza2ludGFncy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;how to get rid of skin tags&lt;/a&gt;. But before you go about learning different ways to remove skin tags, ask yourself first; 'Does it have to be removed?' Will it cause harm to the body, if it remains there forever? The answer to that question is no. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some people have the fear that the skin tags can lead to cancer. There is no truth in those statements. Skin tags are in no way connected to cancer. You need not be worried about this. Hence, there are no medical reasons for you to remove skin tags. People have skin tags removed for the simple reason that they ruin attractiveness or beauty. There is no contest when choosing between tag-riddled skin and skin that is unmarred with any imperfection.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you decide to have treatment like freezing the tag or burning skin tags, it is purely for beauty-related reasons and not due to health concerns. Thus the amount of money that you wish to spend need not be so high. You can choose between surgical procedures and natural treatments. Some home remedies also seem to be highly effective. It's also all right, if you decide that you don't really need any treatment at all.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have accepted having skin tags and you're all right with it, there's no need to undergo any surgery. Using dental floss or a string to remove skin tags requires a lot of care and caution. You have to tie only the lower region or the narrow base of the skin tag. If you tie the wrong region or if you apply too much of force, this might lead to the problem of excessive bleeding. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The skin tags can also be pinched off the skin by freezing it. Nitrogen is liquid in the freezing method. If chemicals are involved, be sure to wear gloves. Burning the skin tags is also considered to be a wonderful option. It has been tried by many people. An electric cautery is used in this process.  
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scissors are still the simplest skin tag remover. But this procedure can be a little painful. It is done either using anesthetic or without it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If the skin tag to be removed is very small, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ubG0ubmloLmdvdi9tZWRsaW5lcGx1cy9hbmVzdGhlc2lhLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;anesthesia&lt;/a&gt; may be too much. Doctors would suggest anesthetics when dealing with larger skin tags. You will be given a dose of Licodaine before the skin tags are removed. You can also opt for topical anesthesia. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The recommended ones are Betacaine and LXM 5% cream. The methods on removing skin tags will greatly benefit the people whose skin tags are in visible parts of their body.&lt;object width="336" height="295"&gt;&lt;param name="movie" value="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4629693"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name="wmode" value="window"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;param name="allowFullScreen" value="true"&gt;&lt;/param&gt;&lt;embed src="http://en.pan.netcom/go/widget/videoID=en-4629693" type="application/x-shockwave-flash" allowFullScreen="true" wmode="window" width="336" height="295"&gt;&lt;/embed&gt;&lt;/object&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e30068f7b0ae1847959b2c291c4c404c">			We all aspire to maintain our bodies and keep them in great shape and good health. If things do not go the way we want to, then the problems start coming in. Even the deceptively normal hormonal changes could bring about a break out of unwanted skin problems such as moles and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZW1vdmVza2ludGFncy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;skin tag&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The medical name for what we casually refer to as skin tags is acrochordon. You may also have come across it in your readings as cutaneous papilloma. When you observe the skin tags, you can just a flabby fold of fat, which is held by the stalk. This stalk is referred to as the peduncle. It is very noticeable and distinctive with how soft it is when touched. You can immediately tell it is a skin tag with this telling feature. It is what sets skin tags apart from other types of skin problems. But they all differ in shape, structure and size from person to person. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Alarm is the first reaction of people who see skin tags appearing on their body for the first time. But there is no reason to panic. They are actually normal for some women during pregnancy. The changes that will be brought about by changes in one's hormone levels could be in the organs or could be in the surface of their skin. Seeing the changes clearly with your own eyes will only make you worry even more. If it does not cause you any inconveniences or pain, a doctor's appointment need not be set. Being informed is never a bad thing, so you would be better off knowing about the details of these changes in your body. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Similarly, when you ponder over the cause of the formation of skin tags, you will find that the trapping of collagen result in skin tags. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VuLndpa2lwZWRpYS5vcmcvd2lraS9Db2xsYWdlbg__" target="_blank"&gt;Collagen&lt;/a&gt;is only one of the many important layers of proteins and elements under the skin. When a group of collagen and the bunch of blood vessels are piled up over one another, they get trapped within the dermal surface. Skin tags then start to form. Try observing certain infections and you will see their causes and effects being interconnected in some way. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you know that simple rubbing of one skin layer over another can lead to skin tag formation? Tight clothes, when donned, can also highly encourage the contact of one layer of skin with another. There will be excessive friction between these two layers. Soon, skin tags will appear.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/179139242_8162448_49521704.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;There are also several other risk factors associated with skin tag development. Skin tags become even more possible for those who take too much steroids. Those who are affected by the human papilloma virus may also suffer from this problem. Unless there is bleeding or you are experiencing pain from your skin tags, there is no need to go to a doctor. If the skin tag does not change in size or dimension, then you are safe. It is not cancerous. Skin tags are also frequently seen among people with diabetes.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>