<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="da5a6477641ef9d01872ea645dc47548">			It was once merely a dream, envisioned as a thriving township just above the Intracoastal Waterway from the blossoming metropolis that is Myrtle Beach, South Carolina. A dream no much more, Carolina Forest is a real possibility... and it is getting better everyday.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL015cnRsZUJlYWNoSG9tZUxpc3RpbmdzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Mertle Beach SC Home Listings&lt;/a&gt;; area has been one of the fastest growing in the country. The city is a very popular tourist destination as people come from all over the country to enjoy the beaches, shopping, and golfing opportunities.  The warm weather typically attracts people nine months out of the year. Check out: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL015cnRsZUJlYWNoSG9tZUxpc3RpbmdzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Myrtle Beach Home Listings&lt;/a&gt;; for more info.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Beginning as forestry area for International Paper Corporation, Carolina Forest was master planned being the foremost suburban community over the Grand Strand. With its location adjacent to the Intracoastal Waterway, and all this potential growth, the planners ensured that &quot;green spaces&quot; could be preserved, and the natural splendor that defines the Carolina shoreline remains.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Carolina Forest continues to flourish, and its residents already enjoy the conveniences of major shopping centers, banks, a post office in addition to fire station, as well as housing and condominium communities having an experienced caterer to every style, taste, and budget. Brand new schools, numerous churches of a variety of faiths, a major hospital, colleges and universities, as well as convenient highways and thoroughfares are simply minutes from your home.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Located just 10 minutes towards beautiful beaches of the Grand Strand, the Carolina Forest Township offers its residents the close proximity to entertainment settings, shows, and nightlife Myrtle Beach provides, while tucked away within many acres of parks interlaced together with hiking trails. The preservation of this environment is paramount to the lifestyle Myrtle Beach, Carolina Forest, and the Grand Strand offers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As Myrtle Beach has become the world's premier golf destination, Carolina Forest itself houses half a dozen golfing courses - all ready to accept the public. Each offering its own challenging features and beautiful views, the golf enthusiast will without a doubt enjoy mastering each one... and then venturing just a couple miles in either course to experience any of greater than a hundred courses close by.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And there is additional is to come. A new retail complicated, the Carolina Forest Towne Heart, will be located just off the Grissom Parkway Bridge, at the intersection associated with Carolina Forest Boulevard. A Carolina Forest hospital is already under construction! Initial proposals for the Towne Centre included rooms for medical and dental care offices, various shops and shops, restaurants and branch campuses for colleges - it will have very little you cannot find in Carolina Natrual enviroment!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Be the first to avail before someone else does! &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL015cnRsZUJlYWNoSG9tZUxpc3RpbmdzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Myrtle Beach SC Home Listings&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>