<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="333271b14ef211e67573eb1e5675cf10">			The Navman MY60T GPS is considered a versatile global position system, so lets take a close look at that today. You will come across the normal standard and expected features as well as solid engineering. But an important aspect to consider when you are in the market for a new GPS is to think of what you want it for. The way that you think you will use it the most is something you need to consider as well. GPS units can be used for both driving and walking around a city as well as for hiking. That is a common design trend, building devices that are small enough for many scenarios. Anymore, it does seem that both local as well as long-distance driving can both be accommodated by a good quality GPS.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The location where you are going to use the GPS is something that needs to be taken into consideration. There are parts of the world that are in vast remote areas which haven't been mapped into the GPS database, although the users in most of the countries won't find that an issue. The GPS will probably not work as well in that kind of remote area. One such country in which that is a real concern is Australia due to the large expansive areas that are truly remote. Of course you will see the major and other primary routes on the MY60T. There won't be much else to see though since the local secondary routes haven't been mapped.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Smart Route is a software that comes from SUNA Predictive and is part of the MY Drive application that is on this particular GPS unit. The database that is used is copyrighted, however, it is used by most GPS devices to access traffic data. Over time, this information will get better and better. GPS units work off of this historical norm to find new routes; if it is too confusing, the traffic situation you are in may not be resolvable. But that is impossible to predict just like accidents and anything else are by and large impossible to predict.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are good and bad aspects related to the Navman MY60T. While we have generally talked about the solid features in this unit, one possible drawback for some users is the lack of Bluetooth capability. This particular issue is not that problematic because most people have their own Bluetooth unit and would not have to use the one on the GPS. In the end, you just need to pick a GPS unit that has features that are to your liking. If you're considering getting a new GPS, make sure it has everything that you are looking for.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This GPS unit, the Navman MY60T, is a great unit for almost everyone. One thing that this GPS unit may have difficulty in doing is choosing different routes if the main one is unavailable. Due to its tendency to use primary routes, this could be a drawback for those living in large urban areas trying to navigate with the Navman MY60T. So when it comes to getting a worthy GPS unit, ensure you're keeping in mind  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vidaddict.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.vidaddict.com&lt;/a&gt;; .&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Resources:		</conversation>	</conversations></author>