<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ddd9c4ddad29e944d1c384a9dc0735bc">			[nickname]htpp://&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.romanticlivesshop.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.romanticlivesshop.com&lt;/a&gt;[/nickname]
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;More Weight, More Risk
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consider one study of 115,000 female American nurses, who were followed for 16 years. The study found that when adults gain even 11 to 18 pounds, it results in a higher risk of heart disease. This study, published in The New England Journal of Medicine of September 14, 1995, indicated that one third of cancer deaths and one half of cardiovascular deaths were due to overweight. According to a report in The Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA) of May 22/29, 1996, &quot;;78% of hypertension in men and 65% in women can be directly attributable to obesity.&quot;; The American Cancer Society says that those who are &quot;;significantly overweight&quot;; (40 percent or more above ideal weight) &quot;;have a higher cancer risk.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But it's not just putting on extra weight that is a danger; the distribution of body fat also affects the risk of disease. Those who carry excess fat in the abdomen are actually at higher risk than those who carry more weight in their hips and thighs. Fat in the stomach area is associated with increased risk of diabetes, heart disease, breast cancer, and uterine cancer.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Similarly, overweight youths suffer from high blood pressure, elevated cholesterol levels, and prediabetic conditions. And they often become obese adults. The New York Times, using data published in the British medical journal The Lancet, reported that &quot;;people who were fat as children died earlier and suffered far more diseases at far younger ages than the general public.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;New Weight Guidelines
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The U.S. government, convinced of a serious weight crisis, toughened its recommended weight guidelines in 1995. (See the box.) The updated guidelines identify &quot;;healthy weight,&quot;; &quot;;moderate overweight,&quot;; and &quot;;severe overweight.&quot;; The guidelines apply to both adult men and women, irrespective of age.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The 1990 guidelines made allowance for middle-body growth in middle age, often called middle-age spread. The new guidelines do not make this allowance, since indications are that adults should not gain weight over time.# Thus, a person who was formerly considered of normal weight may now find himself in the overweight category. For example, a five-foot-six-inch [168 cm] person between the ages of 35 and 65 who weighed 165 pounds [75 kg] would have been within the healthy weight range under the 1990 guidelines. But under the new guidelines, he or she would be ten pounds [5 kg] overweight!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Quick show slimming tea will also help you to loose weight&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3d3cucm9tYW50aWNsaXZlc3Nob3AuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;Quick show slimming tea&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>