<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="885bb94ae9f637ae1b5510e3a12eb3f5">			Music has always been a large part of the world as it has shaped and changed many lives. Everyday we listen to music and use it in many different forms. It has become an integrated part of our world. Rap beats are just one part of that large world, but a large part it is as history has shown.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A rap beat is the rhythm that keeps the whole song flowing. Especially in the early artists, this often came from inspiration taken from a much unexpected type of music. Many artists looked to the real instrumental talent and knowledge that came with classical music. That is why it is commonly believed that this genre of music is more closely linked to classical than most genres in existence today. In fact, many artists will still opt for real instruments over the recently popular soundboard-style of music creation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the 1970's in South Bronx, rap began to start, as it was used at several block parties to promote a festive anti-violent atmosphere. The music was developed by many artist that brought their cultural roots into the music as well as styles that were unique to that group. Rap beats began to develop more as it started to spread of out New York to the rest of the nation, then the world..&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The culture behind this genre of music knows just how much work goes into this part of a song, and takes it very seriously. That is why many of the older rappers have not been forgotten. Magazines, shows, etc. Have been attributed to this part of a rap song by black culture.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many of the sub genres created by rap beats have opened the door to rivals such as the east and west coast. The dynamic nature of the music has helped to make it adaptable over time and with many audiences. The diversity of rap is its strength and has allowed it to adapt to the changing markets.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As a musician you need to understand this if you want to get a good start on your career. There's a lot of work to be done, in fact there's a ton, and using the wrong rap beats from the start can sabotage your career before it even gets started.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZWF0czRsZWdlbmRzLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Rap Beats Online&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>