<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d28f890f740c0c1d5dfcb93bfdcf917f">			It is green gem of Kings,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnLw__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Outlet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; not a green lets  a person's eyes so enjoyable. Emerald, the most beautiful, rich and gaudy, most  noble, let a person cannot imagine the green.
&lt;br /&gt;Emerald is very old gem, through it can  connect the ancient civilization. Its name comes from the ancient Persian  zumurud, meaning is green gems. Legend 6000 years ago, ancient Babylon someone to sacrifice it in before the  statue.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktbmVja2xhY2VzLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Necklaces&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Later zumurud evolution into Latin smaragdus, and EChuan for esmeraude,  emeraude, and eventually into English of now emeralde. Apparently  &amp;quot;emerald&amp;quot; just transliteration, and her grandmother had nothing to do  with. The long history of emeralds, given it noble and various legends.
&lt;br /&gt;It is the earliest known history can be  traced back to ancient Egypt, and in 1500 BC and even more have early for it  consumes slave life. 16 centuries ago, Egypt is what is known as the only  emerald origin. 16 century until the middle of the Spanish,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktYnJhY2VsZXRzLWMtNC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Bracelets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; in South America found a large charming emerald. As early as  in 1521, when Mexico Spanish aggression, plunder of the emerald record. Rich  color to the emerald Spanish king, also fallen Europe of the nobility, time to  wear nobility of South America emerald  jewelry. To europeans, emeralds represents the eternal love and beauty. Eternal  love and beauty is noble, magnificent, and even after the queen also can only,  it is to belong to the goddess of pride. South America's gaudy green, in Europe the royal family has the beautiful fruit, European  royal family survived emerald jewelry, still give contemporary designer  inexhaustible inspiration. In ancient Rome,  emeralds is love and beauty of the goddess Venus color. Her green will with  sunny days and cloudy subtly change, like goddess full of clever eyes, always a  vivid and the rich and gaudy soft light.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktZWFycmluZ3MtYy04Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Earrings&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Love, beauty and joy of life,  emeralds, with a kind of color represents the best things that life, let a  person never tired of.
&lt;br /&gt;In another forks in the road, east of  emerald have another kind of know. In many centuries ago, India's sacred  scriptures-vedic interpretation of it cured characteristics: &amp;quot;emerald can  give the wearer bring good luck&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;enhanced life welfare&amp;quot;, it  is no wonder that the great king and queen India India has the most beautiful  of the treasure of the emerald. In 1695, a giant emerald was found,  217.80-carat,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktY2hhcm1zLWMtNi5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Charms&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; about 10 cm high.  It carved side prayers and the other side carved the splendor of the flowers  figure adorn. The legendary emerald in September 28, Christie's London an anonymous buyer  to $220 million on leave. Emerald respected since ancient times, one of the  most famous emerald is often museum. The New    York museum of natural history has displayed a belong  to India Jehangir emperor's pure emerald cup. But next to display  &amp;quot;Patricia&amp;quot;, one of the world's largest Columbia emerald original  rock, its hefts 632 carat. Bogota bank also collect five very precious emerald  the original stone, weight between 220 to 1796 carats between, and these bright  emerald is part of the Treasury belongs to Iran, and used to decorate the queen  before pilar crown of the law. According to records, Iran's royal family has  the world's largest emerald treasures, and has thousands of piece of color  beautiful, more than 50-carat emerald. The pahlavi crown had a about 100 carats  a 65 carats and three pieces of 14 carat gorgeous color emerald. In the throne  set have 21 piece of heavy 35 to 90 carat, 4 piece of heavy 100 to 170 carats  and a piece of about 225 carats of emerald,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktY3VmZmxpbmtzLWMtNy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Cufflinks&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; this shows Iran to the royal  emerald treasure.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f4d94f7b9e02114f49914f005d928bd6">			Looking at the 150th anniversary and for  its Cartier the serpents in emerald necklace design,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnLw__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany and Co Outlet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; let a person think of  cleopatra Clifford's Petra.  The snake is YaoYe type and full of the senses, and two stars huge water  droplets form with green deduce acme of the emerald leng yan. Eternity serpents  senior jewelry antique necklace to different region amorous feelings to explain  forever, forever is mysterious and let people full of desire, just had the  ancient egyptians to eternal persistent. Do not break dignified and elegant  European royal, Cartier in the use of the emerald has always go further. Cartier  is good at will Oriental amorous feelings into their design, as early as 1920  design a series of India  amorous feelings emerald jewelry. Europe type of diamond cut set into India  style decorative pattern, India amorous feelings of the emerald bracelets let  people do not know where you are.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktc2V0cy1jLTIuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Sets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Carving a lotus pattern of the emerald pearl  and pendants, dotted with natural pearl emerald bead string long necklace, in  in emeralds exquisitely carve patterns or designs on woodwork, all sorts of  Oriental amorous feelings let a person see the grandmother of trance green  jade. Clever is the integration of, let Cartier in the design of the emerald  jewelry on its own, the most suitable for like different region amorous  feelings.
&lt;br /&gt;Careful attention to highlight the gem  bulgari of colour and shapes formed contrast, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL3RpZmZhbnktc2V0cy1uZXctYy0xMy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Set Diamond&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; so sometimes to precious or color  gem in special basis to cutting, make its shape can be the perfect with inlays.  This money to give priority to the stone emerald necklace gold, in designer of  the interpretation of wonderful artical excelling nature, let bulgari than the  traditional jewelry with more rich color range,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL290aGVyLXRpZmZhbnktb3RoZXItdGlmZmFueS1icmFjZWxldHMtYy0xOV8yMS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Bracelet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; including violet color, red and  green and other distinctive color.
&lt;br /&gt;This is London's  Bond Street,  the world advanced jewelry sanctuary, it exists to let Paris Vend me and New York's Fifth Avenue is  coquettish, less. London  native Graff here to set up their own palace, advanced customization jewelry  this absolute luxury items,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL290aGVyLXRpZmZhbnktb3RoZXItdGlmZmFueS1yaW5ncy1jLTE5XzIyLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Ring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and let all the people here are can enjoy the queen  level of honor. Graff1899 years Harcourtr of imperial crown design in now is  still a stunning display, diamond stretched out a beautiful Mosaic branches,  elegant and noble elegant emeralds, I'm afraid even queen Victoria will be its  beauty tracks. Now comes the serenity of the emerald Graff Tranquil Green  series jewelry, flashing but have of cold tone is high. Advanced customization  of the unique and high quality,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55YW5kY29vdXRsZXR1c2Eub3JnL290aGVyLXRpZmZhbnktb3RoZXItdGlmZmFueS1lYXJyaW5ncy1jLTE5XzIzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiffany Earring&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; let Graff gourmet jewelry pronoun, many royalty  and the super rich and famous are Graff customers.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>