<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e6971cdd0febe62c5160cccba851b0f1">			It is a big business, the one that stops your snoring, or do they? Many of these products simply treat the symptom of a larger underlying cause without really addressing the problem behind it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snoring is caused when our breathing is restricted during sleep. The repertory system close to the throat vibrates as the air passes through it. This produces the sound that our loved ones hear as they try to sleep. There are many things that can cause your snoring, and each of them needs to be treated in its own unique way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snoring is just the bodies response to another problem. It can be brought about by things like allergies, excessive weight or perhaps drinking. Treating the symptoms is only a temporary measure. If you want to cure your snoring then you will need to treat the cause.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snoring should not be left unchecked. It may seem harmless enough to those of us who have the problem but it actually keeps you from getting a good nights sleep. Are you often tired during the day or do you wake up in the morning feeling groggy for a long period of time? This is probably because your snoring is not allowing you to get the sleep that you really need.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It could be that the snoring that we experience is a sign of a very serious problem, sleep apnea. Sleep apnea is characterized by our skipping breaths during sleep. These missed breaths, known as apnea, keep us from getting the sound sleep that we need. For those of us that suffer from this problem it can happen many times during the night and we are not aware of it. This problem can be so serious that it can even cause our death.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fortunately there are natural stop snoring remedies out there that will not only help us to stop snoring, it will help to remove the cause behind the symptom and allow us to get a good nights sleep, once and for all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best cure for snoring really depends on what is causing you to snore in the first place. Each of us is different in this respect, and it can take a little time to find exactly the right solution for you. If you have tried some snoring cures but have not been successful yet, here are a few suggestions for other things you might consider:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Are you overweight or out of shape? Carrying extra weight can cause the tissues in your throat to become flabby, which can create the blockages in your air passages that lead to snoring. The best snoring remedies are also the healthiest! Consider a healthy weight loss plan, along with exercise that can strengthen your throat muscles. Some great throat exercises can be found in The Stop Snoring Exercise Program, by Christian Goodman.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Are you all stuffed up? A cold or allergy can cause nasal congestion, which makes it harder for you to breathe. This is another thing that can cause snoring. If this is the case for you, try a decongestant, or nasal strips that will help clear your air passages so that you can breathe more easily. These types of snoring cures are meant to be for temporary conditions, and may not help if you have an ongoing problem.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Be patient, and you will succeed!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fthebestsnoringremedies.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://thebestsnoringremedies.com&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>