<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a3bd676ffbc760aa012f16b90856e0b0">			You may use wall art to highlight your contemporary tastes or even old world traditional values. Paintings are very versatile and will look good with current, minimalist, contemporary or quite possibly traditional furniture. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choosing the right artwork can be an issue, so we've provided some tips that you make the task of selecting a canvas easier for people: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Size - Large canvas paintings look very impressive and awesome, but hanging a canvas that's too large for your room, wall space and complementing furniture could make your room look unbalanced. Don't get paintings that are too large and risk overwhelming everyone in the room with an over-sized canvas. Paintings that are too small as well be detrimental to your designing efforts and will look out-of-place and dwarfed amongst large furniture. Take proportions first before buying your canvas wall art. if you are hanging artwork above some sort of couch, make sure that the canvas is not wider that along your sofa. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;two. Color - When you see at an art gallery, exhibit or on an online art store, it may look striking and attractive. Be aware though that will ones you hang it on the wall amongst your own furniture, it may not look as attractive since it used too. Take note of the colors in your room in your home, the color of your drapes and upholstery or carpet. Get a painting that is not of the same colour as your wall but something similar to other decor pieces in the room. A beautiful painting will look bad if the colors relating to the canvas will clash with your room's color theme. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Eyeglass frames - Traditionally, paintings were always presented when used as wall art in a home. These days, more and more people prefer to hang canvas wall art without a frame. There is nothing bad with hanging frame-less art providing they are stretched with gallery wrapped canvas. These types of canvas are streamlined and show clean and presentable without frames. It also adds a very artistic and bohemian turn to a room. It's a sensible way to save on your walls decor because frames can get pretty expensive. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Personality - Make your choice of artwork a personal decision. If you personally enjoy looking at a particular painting, you will enjoy seeing it everyday in your house. It is also an extension to your character and personality. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Mood- Artwork can change or influence people's moods in the room. bright red, red, gold or yellow canvas walls art will cheer up people in the room. Paintings that have dominant colors of blue and green will make the viewer feel calm and calm. Find out types of mood you want to project inside your room, whether the canvas will hang inside your living room or rooms. Neutral earth colors can make one feel balanced, nor calm nor too excited. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Photographs are an integral part of life. Thanks to picture taking, people can document every aspect of their life. These days, it is common to have friends who post photos of their wedding, vacation, new little ones, etc. on a web site or photo sharing internet site. Photography has certainly appreciated the digital age. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZ21lbnRvci5jb20vM2QtYW5pbWF0aW9uLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;3d animation&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>