<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c35167c2b95d3694b8319077847b183f">			'As a result of I watch what I eat, I eat higher than they do, and I take better care of myself because of my diabetes. In twenty years, I betcha I'll be in a lot better shape than they'll be in!'&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'Bingo! You've got acquired it, Jared! While most people see diabetes as a very unfavourable value and have unfavourable expectations about it, you worth it as an experience that makes you self-discipline yourself so that you take better care of your physique, and you'll be better off in the long run for it!'&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'Truly, now that I think about it, it is paying off in the quick-run, too, Mr. 'But I guess there IS a sort of silver lining to the entire thing. I get to see my dad extra, y'know. He schedules time each week with me so he can come over and take me out and do issues with me.'&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'I see. You are referring to the saying that, Every darkish cloud has a silver lining. Some other silver linings-good things that occurred after the sad divorce that did not occur along with your dad earlier than the divorce, when he was living at residence?'&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'Well, yeah. He takes me more locations, and he buys me extra stuff. Now that I give it some thought, he even offers me extra money than he ever did earlier than!' Pamela was grinning faintly, now.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'You're heading in the right direction, Pam. Now you have identified the positives about divorce-the reverse of the damaging worth expectations, that everybody sees divorce as just completely bad. As you said, there's actually a silver lining in it for you because you get to see your dad extra, he takes you extra locations, he buys extra issues for you, and he even offers you more cash than he ever gave you before the divorce.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'Sounds such as you've probably received a lot of details to assist your thesis that, Divorce is not so bad, after all-no less than not in your experience. Now use that very same technique of looking for silver linings with some other detrimental values in your life, and you'll have plenty of materials for all the essays you have to write after your trigger-and-impact paper on divorce.'&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;'Thanks, Mr. Drew. I perceive the assignment rather a lot higher, now. See you at school!' Pamela stood up from her chair and walked away, smiling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After those two interviews, I questioned why they had been in a position to 'get it' at school and 'get it' when speaking with me, but not by themselves. The 2 books plus software for the first ebook can be found at his website, at Amazon.com, and at ThoughttOffice.com.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;His NewView strategies are being efficiently taught in elementary, middle college, and high school classes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For additional info, see the various endorsements of his books and software program on the Testimonials page of his website, as well as the a number of Reviews on Amazon.com.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Upcoming books planned by Drew embrace The Secret DNA of Writing Promoting, The Secret DNA of Analyzing Novels, The Secret DNA of Faculty Writing, with Lesson Plans, The Secret DNA of Shakespeare's Plays, The Secret DNA of Communication, The Secret DNA of Training and Teaching, The Secret DNA of Hemingway's Writing, The Secret DNA of Introductions and Conclusions, The Secret DNA of Topic Sentences and Paragraph Growth, and lots of more to come back in the Secret DNA series.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lc3NheXNtYXJrZXQuY29tL3NhbXBsZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Essays Market&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>