<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="32e264a748a1e3106ee729330191a5d">			Taking the time to perform thorough research on asking for testimonials before you attempt doing it is definitely a smart move. Let's take a look at one thing very many people give little attention to - target market knowledge. There are very many reasons why you should perform effective research on your audience. The competitive edge will be much sharper and in your favor with the knowledge you will gain. Never think it is your market who has to do the work to understand you; but rather it is just the opposite. Your readers will never get to a point where they will fulfill your most desired response if they cannot relate to it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Testimonials are powerful because they represent social proof, but the newer online businesses often have a tough time with this issue. Yes, there are a collection of methods that have proven to work well with getting that social proof on your site. Oh there are definitely right and wrong ways to approach this task; so do continue reading.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Think about using the case study approach because they can be much more valuable than a testimonial if it is well-executed. If you do not have any testimonials at all, then we suggest you seriously take a look at this if you can perform one in your market or niche. It's not just a few lines of positive feedback, but an actual experience recounted by the customer when using the product. Be sure to let it all hang out because the willingness to reveal the negative aspects can actually work in your favor. Businesses of all sizes use the case study strategy and method because it is effective as a marketing device. You should have a fairly good idea about how well your product performs, and so all you need to do is contact your customers. Getting testimonials can be ethically achieved, and so you really need to stay clear of making statements of any kind that amount to soliciting a direct testimonial. It is a smart idea to engage your audience as much as possible, and asking them to provide you with their thoughts about the product or buying experience is nothing but feedback to you. Some businesses make a small mention about feedback on their Contact page, but it should be more than just a brief mention. Sure, make this a little higher profile without making the visitor think this is super important to you even if it is.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of course all your testimonials will come from a cross section of demographics, and that is important for potential customers to realize. It's important that the testimonials come from similar people, facing the same kind of problems because that's how you'll get others to connect to them. People seem to trust those testimonials more strongly which they can relate to, so make sure you're not collecting testimonials from anyone and everyone but rather someone who has actually bought and used your product. If you are open to trying new marketing/advertising ideas, then seriously consider anything new you come across because new ideas are everywhere. We have received a lot of feedback from users of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZW8tc2VydmljZXMtd2ViLWRlc2lnbi5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcnkvc2VvLWV4cGVydHMtc2VvLWV4cGVydC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;SEO expert London&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZW8tc2VydmljZXMtd2ViLWRlc2lnbi5jb20vY2F0ZWdvcnkvc2VvLXNlcnZpY2VzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;; SEO Services London&lt;/a&gt;;, and if it great and gives excellent results when applied in the right way. There is a lot to consider when you are contemplating all new promotional activities. When you look at major corporations, they are constantly working to add new products, markets and overall growth. So in order to do that, what you have to do is scale-up what you are doing and also add new methods. It is not necessary for you to know everything, but it is critical to know what exists so you can consider it, if necessary. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will discover that once you have a good collection of terrific testimonials, your conversions will improve.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We understand very well that getting great client feedback is nothing new within the world of internet marketing and business. You never want to find your self in a situation with your business that causes you to have a narrow view of the marketing world. Jog your brain, clear out the cobwebs and try to use a creative approach with these methods in what you are doing now. Nothing beats experience, and that is the power of testing and giving something an honest shot. Do not forget the one thing we always like to beat to death, and that is getting sufficient amounts of relevant information so you can use a method with intelligence. After you feel you have enough info to try it out, then you know what needs to be done. Obviously you are the only person in the position to make the call about those matters.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>