<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b4543b9862bfbb275a780c3b1b277221">			It's no secret that will London is jam packed full of office space. From designers to financial institutions and from media enterprises to charities, everyone is keen to position their headquarters in the administrative centre and for good purpose. London commercial property is much like no where else in the world when it comes to quality and style. While London office space might always be in demand, it's far from beautiful.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rent London commercial the property market and you'll probably find yourself staring out over the bleak city streets or over tiny because old and unattractive tube stations which might be hanging around. Whatever your view out of your capital location; it's unlikely to be inspiring and will undoubtedly look much like dull in both summer and winter weather. But there are locations around London which might be far from uninspiring. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWFyY2hvZmZpY2VzcGFjZS5jb20vdWsvb2ZmaWNlLXNwYWNlL21heWZhaXItc2VydmljZWQtb2ZmaWNlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;office space mayfair&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWFyY2hvZmZpY2VzcGFjZS5jb20vdWsvb2ZmaWNlLXNwYWNlL2tpbmdzLWNyb3NzLXNlcnZpY2VkLW9mZmljZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;office space kings cross&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWFyY2hvZmZpY2VzcGFjZS5jb20vdWsvb2ZmaWNlLXNwYWNlL29sZC1zdHJlZXQtc2VydmljZWQtb2ZmaWNlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;office space old street&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;London has plenty of green spaces like parks which needn't you need to be reserved for summer picnics. There's lots of commercial properties that can now be rented overlooking one of the capital's many parks. Leasing workplace in a great location like this is convenient for clients and also the beautiful surroundings should be an aid to inspire creativity.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;SW1 workplace can be taken out overlooking St James' Playground, while W2 offices may be taken out which get fantastic views of London's Hyde Park. Other key green spaces with prominent office complexes nearby include Regent's Recreation area, Battersea Park and Green Park. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWFyY2hvZmZpY2VzcGFjZS5jb20vdWsvb2ZmaWNlLXNwYWNlL3ZpY3RvcmlhLXNlcnZpY2VkLW9mZmljZXMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;office space victoria&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWFyY2hvZmZpY2VzcGFjZS5jb20vdWsvb2ZmaWNlLXNwYWNlL2NhbmFyeS13aGFyZi1zZXJ2aWNlZC1vZmZpY2VzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;office space canary wharf&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zZWFyY2hvZmZpY2VzcGFjZS5jb20vdWsvb2ZmaWNlLXNwYWNlL0tlbnNpbmd0b24tc2VydmljZWQtb2ZmaWNlcy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;office space kensington&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Key advantages to leasing office space near parks include great scenery, easy access and a place to entertain people. The green spaces offer a great environment for staff to look at their lunch break and gives them the opportunity to get away from the stressful office natural environment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So next time you're considering renting workplace in London why not consider a venue near one of the capital's many parks? Affordable leasing and elegant buildings means it's now more of a popular option than ever so you might want to act quickly to ensure you don't miss out!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>