<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="6c1c60e5042e9c4c3c34fbc001ad2770">			You are frankly a chain smoker like me. Even if I'm not holding my cigarette I want a cigarette lit on my ash tray ready for me to vape. I could say that I consume at least 2 -3 packs of cigarettes each day .&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Especially when I'm in front of a computer writing my blogs or articles about anything under the sun, I want to smoke to calm my mind. I don't know but there is something with smoking cigarettes and my productiveness. I am ready to think better and do more when I have a cigarette beside me.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's a good thing though that eventually I have stumbled on e-cigarettes. One of the advantages that any chain smoker like me would get from it is spending a load less than in traditional cigarettes. Even though you go with the most costly brand of e-cigarettes I will assure you and conclude that in the long run you are still spending fewer bucks on this.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first brand that I used is KR808D-1, it will definitely five you the worth for your cash and you can vape all you want without caring about the costs. At the same time if you're hunting for that rich and traditional taste of your old cigarette KR8 is able to give you precisely that. The best part about this cigarette is that you're able to enjoy the flavour and at the same time you aren't taking in the bad elements of a traditional cigarette. You aren't in a position to miss out in any fashion on the flavour of your good old cigarette.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Smokers desire things graceful and  easy. This is exactly how KR808D is designed. You will be smoking with easy elegance. You are definitely a smart consumer when you get this e-cigarette. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fkr808d.org%2F10-reasons-kr808d-1-great-start-4-vapers%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://kr808d.org/10-reasons-kr808d-1-great-start-4-vapers/&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fkr808d.org%2Fkr808d-kr808d-2-piece-electronic-cigarette%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://kr808d.org/kr808d-kr808d-2-piece-electronic-cigarette/&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fkr808d.org%2Fkr808d-1-design-top-brand-electronic-cigarettes%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://kr808d.org/kr808d-1-design-top-brand-electronic-cigarettes/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="72ae01a6536e7730e0e6b36c6ddfb722">			KR808D-1 is a name given to the standard base of electronic cigarette which uses a cartomizer. Shenzhen Kanger Technology Co. L.T.D. Was the 1st company to manufacture this model. KR808D measures a total 9.8cm in length. 808D has only 2 parts, a cartomizer and a battery. The cartomizer consists of a cartridge and an atomizer in one unit. The atomizer is the heating element of KR808D and s fundamentally responsible for heating up the solution in the cartridge and turning it into vapor. Cartridge is found at the end of the electronic cigarette where the filter is found in a conventional cigarette. The cartridge homes the nicotine based solution.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All about the KR808D model&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The better part of this model is that it looks exactly the same as a cigarette, but is free from a lot of harmful effects that traditional cigarettes are known to cause. The body of a cigarette smoker is hooked on nicotine. The body suffers from dreadful withdrawal syndromes if the smoker isn't given the satisfactory nicotine amount the body is used to. Withdrawal problems include headache, queasiness, dizziness etc . The KR808D model supplies the vaper with the satisfactory amount of nicotine, but minus the dangerous consequences of a traditional cigarette. Fundamentally, KR808D-1 uses nicotine filtered from tobacco using biological methodologies, which removes just about all the armful chemical that tobacco originally contains. This saves the body from a large amount of dangerous effects that traditional cigarette smokers have to be affected by. The electronic cigarettes aren't covered in under almost all of the smoking bans and therefore allow you to take nicotine drag where and when you are feeling like.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The KR808D is composed of a stainless-steel case which encloses an atomizer chamber, micro electronic circuit, a lithium ion battery and an indicator light at the end of the cigarette. The battery of the KR808D-1 has 50% bigger capacity than other electronic cigarettes making it more energy-efficient, with a lower running cost. The cartomizer cartridge is also built to last for longer and one cartridge lasts virtually so long as 20 traditional cigarettes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;KR808D was the first model with a cartomizer&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cartomizer has brought a revolution in the electronic cigarette industry and has eliminated a number of Problems that plagues the earlier electronic cigarette models. KR8 was the 1st ever model to make use of the cartomizer. Cartomizer derives its name from cartridge and atomizer. Cartridge contains the nicotine solution which is now typically flavored and atomizer heats up the solution in the cartridge converting it into vapours. The cartomizer mixed with a battery makes up the KR808D model. The KR8 cartomizers are available in 2 forms, pre filled and blank. The KR8 converts the conventional 3 piece model of electronic cigarettes to a rather more reliable two piece model and is far better than the other atomizer based cigarettes. The cartomizer is also unencumbered by any leakage Problems that earlier electronic cigarettes suffered from. 808D is certainly the ideal electronic cigarette model.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fkr808d1electroniccigarette36.wetpaint.com%2Fpage%2FVape%2BAll%2BOf%2BThe%2BWay%2BWith%2BKr808d-1%2B%252835%2529"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://kr808d1electroniccigarette36.wetpaint.com/page/Vape+All+Of+The+Way+With+Kr808d-1+%2835%29&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femmanuelfisc23.livejournal.com%2F702.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://emmanuelfisc23.livejournal.com/702.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2F.posterous.com%2FVape-All-The-Way-With-Kr808d1"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://.posterous.com/Vape-All-The-Way-With-Kr808d1&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="cfb53653fecce5999d55b73968eaa418">			KR808D1 is a common name given to the base model of the majority of the standard electronic cigarettes. Electronic cigarettes are a great craze now. Especially because they have added convenience to the entire vaping experience. Another benefit of electronic cigarettes is that they aren't a part of almost all of the smoking bans which gives the users an opportunity to take nicotine hit where and when they wish to. The electronic cigarette also doesn't cause any fire hazards. KR808D1 was first made by Shenzhen Kanger Technology Company. Ltd. And since that point has been adopted by the majority of the electronic cigarettes. The KR808D1 encloses a microelectronic circuit, a lithium ion battery, an atomizer chamber and a cartridge inside a chrome steel case. Even though the case is made out of chrome steel, the KR808D-1 appears precisely the same as a traditional cigarette, but the experience of vaping a KR808D1 is far better than smoking a traditional cigarette and is a lot less harmful.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is so great about the KR808D?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;KR808D-1 has been responsible for turning the fortunes of the whole electronic cigarette industry. Electronic cigarettes failed initially thanks to the many issues which troubled the first models including Problems like leaking, atomizer and cartridge upkeep, poor battery charge lifespan among other. KR808D-1 brought the cartomizer in the electronic cigarette market. Cartomizer is essentially a combination of a cartridge and the atomizer in one unit. Earlier the cartridge and the atomizer were separate units, which together with the battery made the electronic cigarette a 3 piece set. The cartomizer combined the cartridge and atomizer and made the electronic cigarette a 2 piece set. This made the whole vaping experience better and much more convenient. It was due to KR808D that more and more users got interested in electronic cigarettes and the whole market grew at an exceedingly good pace. KR808D1 made the maintenance process straightforward and eliminated all the issues like leaking etc . It also brought the idea of a throwaway cartomizer which could be replaced or refilled after every use.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What are the other blessings of KR8?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;KR808D1 introduced dispensable cartridges. The cartridge fundamentally houses the liquid which contains the juice. The juice is heated by the atomizer and converted into vapours. The juice also contains flavours to enhance the vaping experience and make it a great filled experience. Since the cartomizers were made disposable by the KR808D-1, it gave users the chance to try new flavours every time they vape using their electronic cigarette. The KR8 also had a much better battery life. The battery lasted 50% longer than the standard batteries plentiful in electronic cigarettes. The juice per cartomizer also lasts longer. The juice of an average KR808D-1 lasts so long as twenty traditional cigarettes. The cartomizers can be gotten in two options, pre filled with juice and blank cartomizers. Users can select the cartomizers according to their convenience. All of these advantages were offered by KR808D-1 without rocketing the dimensions of the electronic cigarette. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femmanuelfisc23.sosblog.com%2FThe-first-blog-b1%2FVape-All-The-Way-With-Kr808d1-b1-p2.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://emmanuelfisc23.sosblog.com/The-first-blog-b1/Vape-All-The-Way-With-Kr808d1-b1-p2.htm&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Femmanuelfisc23.livejournal.com%2F702.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://emmanuelfisc23.livejournal.com/702.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,		</conversation>	</conversations></author>