<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="22449cacd618876229e79eb3d1e8e93a">			Drug possession is a severe criminal charge in Texas carrying an array of punitive measures from probation to lengthy prison sentences, depending on the amount of the drug. A conviction on drug possession criminal charges may have severe implications for you because of the possibility that you could have to go to prison and pay stiff fines reaching into the thousands of dollars, along with the possibility the police may seize your car or other property.  Drug possession criminal charges will follow you with a criminal record that may also keep you from certain jobs and professional licenses. If you are charged under the possession law, it means the state has accused you of transporting or having access to a controlled substance such as marijuana,  cocaine, or Ecstasy. &lt;br /&gt;;                A drug possession conviction may perhaps result in a 6 month driver's  license suspension under Texas statutes, therefore it is a good idea to speak with an criminal defense attorney for additional details on alternatives to pleading guilty should you require the ability to drive. Police officers might charge you with drug possession should they find drugs in your pockets or anywhere else on your body, or they might charge you under a claim of &quot;constructive possession&quot;. That means the drugs were in a place that you normally control or could easily reach, that could be your car, your apartment, or the cushions of a couch where you were sitting when the authorities entered. &lt;br /&gt;;Hire the Leading Houston Criminal Lawyer! Whether you are experiencing felony drug possession charges or your minor child is fighting misdemeanor drug criminal charges for possessing a small quantity of marijuana, it is advisable to have an experienced attorney advocating for your protection under the law. Get in touch with a Houston, Texas law firm to schedule a complimentary initial consultation with  a professional, aggressive Drug Possession Defense attorney.&lt;br /&gt;;Aggressive Drug Possession Defense&lt;br /&gt;;              The  Top Houston Drug Crimes  Attorney will have a great deal of practical experience providing vigorous defense for adults and juveniles confronting criminal defense criminal charges for possession of illegal substances, that include:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Marijuana&lt;br /&gt;;                Crack cocaine&lt;br /&gt;;                Heroin&lt;br /&gt;;                Methamphetamines (meth&lt;br /&gt;;                Other unlawful drugs             A drug possession conviction may result in criminal penalties, including fines and time in jail, and other penalties, that include license suspension, damage to reputation and loss of ability to obtain student loan financing. The  Most Respected Houston Criminal Lawyer will strive to lessen or altogether avoid such drastic consequences by providing zealous defense representation.&lt;br /&gt;;              The penalties for a drug conviction may range from fines of $2,000 and 180 days in jail to fines of $50,000 and an entire lifetime in jail. The level of misdemeanor or felony charge is dependent upon the amount of drugs confiscated. For example, possession of five ounces of marijuana would lead to state felony charges with a sentence potential as high as $10,000 and two years in prison.            Drug Possesion Sentencing&lt;br /&gt;;              Judges will commonly attempt to figure out if the drugs were for personal use or drug possession for sale and distribution when sentencing. Quite often the fines are quite considerable and often the sentence includes at least random drug testing and probation if not some jail time. Drug awareness classes and community service hours are often the initial option for the majority of judges, once it has been confirmed that the drugs had been for personal use.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A skilled criminal defense attorney can help prove this, or perhaps establish that the drugs were absolutely not yours in situations where they were recovered from an automobile or residence.&lt;br /&gt;;Protect Your Legal Rights Under the Law               You have a right to remain silent and the right to an attorney - USE THEM. The Most Dedicated Houston  Criminal Defense Attorney  investigates the methods in which the evidence was obtained in order to uncover violations of your constitutional rights.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Elicited confessions and the seized drugs are quite often the only evidence creating a case against you. This may provide leverage in plea negotiations and even bring about dismissal of drug charges. Any sort of evidence which is obtained in violation of your rights is inadmissible in the courtroom - meaning the evidence cannot be used in a case against you. If a confession was acquired unlawfully or unlawful drugs were seized with an invalid search warrant (illegal search and seizure), your attorney should fight to suppress the evidence. As an expert drug possession attorney, Charles Johnson knows how to mitigate damaging evidence.Will I have to go to Jail on my Drug Possession Criminal Charge?&lt;br /&gt;;              State possession law allows counties to set up diversion programs for those charged with offenses  concerning the use or possession of drugs, including marijuana. And, judges are required to give probation, or community supervision, in some drug possession court cases.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The state health code also requires any county with a populace in excess of 200,000 to establish a drug court program to send some drug offenders to treatment rather than prison.     The punishment primarily depends on the amount of drugs concerned and your prior conviction history, but it is very possible you may not have to serve time for a drug possession conviction if it is your initial offense for a somewhat small amount./p&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;              The Texas Code of Criminal Procedure makes community supervision and mandatory drug treatment programs a sentencing requirement for people found guilty of possessing:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Less than 5 units of drugs including LSD.&lt;br /&gt;;Less than 1 gram of drugs such as cocaine or meth.&lt;br /&gt;;Less than 1 gram of drugs including Ecstasy (MMDA) or PCP.&lt;br /&gt;;Less than one pound of marijuana.      &lt;br /&gt;;              Nonetheless, the judge does not have to sentence you to probation in the event you have been convicted of a prior felony, or in the event you have violated an earlier probation sentence. In those court cases, it is up to the judge whether you go to prison or receive probation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If your attorney can show the officers  didn't have probable cause, your consent, or a search warrant, your attorney may perhaps be able to challenge the legality of the search that turned up those drugs and get the evidence suppressed, keeping the state from making its case against you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To achieve that, the prosecutor must show that law enforcement found the drugs on you or in your control subsequent to a legal search. The judge also can sentence you to serve three to six months in jail prior to starting probation. But don't forget, the state  must first prove  the criminal charge of drug possession before you can be sentenced. Remember to get in touch with your lawyer for a no charge consultation regarding your Texas drug possession charge, and your lawyer will walk you through the information and facts of your case, and your  most effective legal defense solutions. As you can see, drug possession court cases get challenging very quickly.&lt;br /&gt;;Hire The Very Best Houston Drug Possession Defense Lawyer:&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.houstonlawyer.com%2Fdrugoffenses.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.houstonlawyer.com/drugoffenses.html&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.houstonlawyer.com%2Fdrugcharges.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.houstonlawyer.com/drugcharges.html&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.houstonlawyer.com%2Fdrugsales.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.houstonlawyer.com/drugsales.html&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;              If you are fighting misdemeanor or felony drug possession criminal charges following a drug arrest in Texas, protect your liberties and future.  Contact the Best Houston drug crime defense attorney to schedule a no cost preliminary consultation. Frequently a first charge on Drug Possession charges may be dropped down to a disorderly conduct, resulting in less substantial penalties that usually don't include time in jail. Furthermore, the Most Dedicated Houston Attorney could possibly even be able to have the criminal charges dropped in situation where you had been merely within the vicinity where the drugs were located. &lt;br /&gt;;                              A professional criminal defense attorney can certainly negotiate these kinds of arrangements to stop you from having a drug related charge on your record.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>