<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="10d7b167da54809b1dcf78844d3c0065">			For example, if a stalker is entering a woman's home, the hidden spy camera can record the activity when she is gone. There are cameras that will record only when there are changes in the room, or others that will record at all times through a home computer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Women's self defense is much more reliable if self defense weapons are available. Getting the best ones depends on knowing the market and choosing wisely. It is important for women to know their own habits and preferences before buying women's self defense products.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Police departments all over the world use them. Military forces throughout the world use them too. Millions of civilians around the world use them as well. Why shouldn't you? What are we talking about?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We are taking about the array of non-lethal weapons like stun guns, tasers, pepper sprays, et. al. of course.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These self defense products give the users a viable alternative to a deadly outcome in any kind of a confrontation. In the case of police, over 11,000 U.S. police agencies have come to the conclusion that the taser for example gives them one more alternative in the continuum of force response to a legal and lawful order.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the case of individuals who choose a non-lethal self defense product they have made a conscious decision to avoid the use of deadly force and at least like the police give themselves one more alternative to it. Some do it for religious reasons some for other reasons but no matter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The fact is that no matter what the reason for using these products to protect and defend themselves from the bad guys that would do them harm-the products WORK.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Their purpose is simple: to allow the victim to escape a potentially deadly situation and seek help. They all perform this function very well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A short spritz of OC pepper spray in an assailant's eyes may give you up to 15-20 minutes to get away. A 2 second shot from a stun gun will incapacitate an assailant for 5-10 minutes. The taser has nearly 100% stopping power and will allow you plenty of time to seek help.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The point is they all work at doing their job with non lethal results. Non-lethal self defense products have become the choice for millions of citizens and military and police agencies around the world.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I've spent so many hours in hospitals and doctors offices in the last 10 years I feel like I know most nurses in the country. What I didn't know is the potential danger that nurses are in on a day-to-day basis in performing their job. For example, did you know that the international Association for Healthcare Security and Safety reports that almost two thirds of all healthcare facilities are in areas that are average or above-average in violent crime risk?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is common knowledge that hospitals are understaffed. This causes increased stress for this staff, which treats drug and alcohol abusers in emergency rooms on a daily basis. This places them at risk for increased assaults, beatings, shootings, and even rapes and stabbings. Take some steps to protect your self in a hospital setting with the best self defense products for nurses.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NoYW5lcG90dGVyNTEyLnNvdXAuaW8vcG9zdC8yMzY0MjY2NzMvc2VsZi1kZWZlbnNlLXByb2R1Y3Rz" target="_blank"&gt;;Self Defense Products - Best Defense Against Dog Bites&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NvbW11bml0eS5hdG9tLmNvbS9Qb3N0L1NlbGYtRGVmZW5zZS1Qcm9kdWN0cy1mb3ItV29tZW4tLVRoZS1CZXN0LVRocmVlLzAzRUZCRkZGRjAyNkFGNkQ0MDAwODAxOEY5M0Yz" target="_blank"&gt;;self defense products for women&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NoYW5lcG90dGVyNTEyLm91dGlsYmxvZy5jb20vVGhlLWZpcnN0LWJsb2ctYjEvc2VsZi1kZWZlbnNlLXByb2R1Y3RzLWIxLXAyLmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Consumer's Guide To Four Popular Self-Defense Products&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>