<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c76340f5edba39044595a9d5018256f7">			Love is a slow kiss good night. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's anticipation.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is a solitary tear falling from a waterfall of sheer bliss.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is a shoulder to cry on.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's patience.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is a smile that never falters.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is gentle passion, and fierce lust.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is a flower that never dies.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's consideration. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is saying the perfect phrase to make a solemn embrace dissolve into giggles. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is your own name being called out by your soul mate in the heat of passion.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's desire.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is peace of mind.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's abandonment. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is seeing what your lover really looks like for the first time. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's truth. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is knowing in your heart you will never again be alone.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is knowing what time it is and not caring. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's joy. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is that simple gesture that means the world.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is an Angel that kisses your cheek.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is the arms around you tightening their embrace. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's ecstasy. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is seeing a new side of a person you thought you knew. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's renewal. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is everything and all things.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is telling a person if you have to leave, you will let them sleep, and being told they would rather be woken.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's tenderness. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is waking up to find the subject of the dream you were having asleep on your shoulder. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's where fantasy meets reality. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is being there to wake your lover. Slowly. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is forever.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's sensuousness. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is two people only taking up a third of a queen-sized bed. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's closeness.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is ever-lasting and transcends all boundaries.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's trust. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is saying good-bye and knowing you will be back by mutual consent. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's faith. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is a heart beating, or a heart stopping.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is hearing the weather forecast for a winter storm and wishing you could spend it in bed with your lover. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's loneliness. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is stories that will never be told.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Love is a slow kiss good night.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>