<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f350384d67c082fb215f5ac62e246f2">			The Lightning Rod is the strongest stun pen readily available available, yet at 6 inches long and about an inch thick it is actually simple to conceal and manage. It has two bright LED lights to serve as a flashlight for nighttime safety. It features a protective safety cap and on/off safety switch to stop accidental discharge. Rechargeable batteries are included and installed. The unit comes using a holster with belt loop and recharging cord for uncomplicated recharging. The dimensions are six and one-half inches x three-quarter inches&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is suggested that you simply have your stun gun out and prepared when walking thru a prospective unsafe region such as a parking lot or though walking your dog. Make a habit of it. Stun guns are get in touch with devices and do not shoot something out of it. The top points of contact will be the upper hip, beneath the rib cage or the upper shoulders. This can be due to there getting nerve centers at those points, on the other hand the stun gun will perform when touched at any point in the body. As a rule of thumb - aim for any area on the torso. Hold the stun gun against the assailant so long as is necessary to incapicitate them and permit you to escape. (1-5 seconds depending on voltage)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It functions by disrupting the message the brain sends for the voluntary muscles. Simply touching an attacker using a stun pen for 3 to 5 seconds will deliver a high voltage shock causing loss of balance and muscle control, confusion, and disorientation bringing him to his knees and producing him incapable of further aggressive activity. Full recovery takes about five to ten minutes and there's no permanent harm. Functions a safety switch to stop accidental discharge and contains a absolutely free case. Demands two 'AAA' batteries. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Please note: to obtain 200,000 volts into a stun gun this modest causes it to function slightly differently than our other models. When pushing the trigger there's no visible arc (spark). To fire the unit you have to hold the trigger down for a second to charge the capacitors. An orange light will come on indicating it is ready for use. When the unit is charged and you don't use it to defend yourself you must touch the prongs to a metal object in order to safely discharge it.&lt;br /&gt;;With the new Stun Pen your defense remains unknown as defeat befalls your attacker. Who'd think that a supposed flashlight withheld such a shocking surprise? &lt;br /&gt;;Packing a potent jolt of 1,200,000 Volts, it can be by far the most potent pen kind stun gun out there. When fired, the stun pen produces an intimidating electrical sound because the bright electric surrent pulsates across the prime of the unit. This stun gun is ensured to protect you together with the combined effort of each the sound as well as the general impact with the volts running through the assailants body. But, it can assist to protect you in more than one particular way. &lt;br /&gt;;In addition to being a effective amazing device, this stun pen has a hassle-free built-in LED flashlight. Its ulterior function adds to the valuable impact that the stun pen has for its user. Not just will it provide you security with the expertise that you can defend yourself, the stun pen will give you light and guidance when you need to have it. &lt;br /&gt;;As well as providing you protection, that you are protected by the precautions taken inside the designing of the stun pen. 3 levels of safety deterrant had been built in to avoid any incidents of accidental discharge. First, the safety cap have to be removed. Then, the safety switch need to be inside the &quot;on&quot; position which will result in a red LED warning light to come on. The final amount of safety precautions calls for the trigger button to become pressed down. With all of these added safety increments your welfare is at its peak!&lt;br /&gt;;This pen stun gun comes with built-in  rechargeable battery which eliminates the must acquire or replace the batteries and comes with Free of charge intergrated charger.  Every unit also comes with a Free Nylon holster with belt loop attachment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2tpdGNoZW5hcnQtaXN0LmNvbS8yMDEyLzA0LzEyL3N0dW4tcGVuLXN0dW4tcGVuLXBlbi1zdHVuLWd1bi0zLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;stun pen, stun pen, pen stun gun&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="1aa37362cd6ed5e3a445428093b3636">			The Lightning Rod is the strongest stun pen offered on the market, but at six inches lengthy and about an inch thick it really is easy to conceal and deal with. It has two bright LED lights to serve as a flashlight for nighttime safety. It has a protective safety cap and on/off safety switch to avoid accidental discharge. Rechargeable batteries are included and installed. The unit comes using a holster with belt loop and recharging cord for easy recharging. The dimensions are six and one-half inches x three-quarter inches&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is actually recommended that you simply have your stun gun out and prepared when walking thru a prospective risky area including a parking lot or whilst walking your dog. Make a habit of it. Stun guns are speak to devices and do not shoot something out of it. The most beneficial points of contact could be the upper hip, below the rib cage or the upper shoulders. This can be on account of there getting nerve centers at those points, on the other hand the stun gun will operate when touched at any point from the body. As a rule of thumb - aim for any region on the torso. Hold the stun gun against the assailant as long as is essential to incapicitate them and allow you to escape. (1-5 seconds according to voltage)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It operates by disrupting the message the brain sends for the voluntary muscles. Just touching an attacker with a stun pen for 3 to five seconds will deliver a high voltage shock causing loss of balance and muscle manage, confusion, and disorientation bringing him to his knees and producing him incapable of additional aggressive activity. Full recovery takes about 5 to ten minutes and there's no permanent harm. Capabilities a safety switch to prevent accidental discharge and contains a no cost case. Needs two 'AAA' batteries. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Please note: to get 200,000 volts into a stun gun this smaller causes it to function a bit differently than our other models. When pushing the trigger there's no visible arc (spark). To fire the unit it's essential to hold the trigger down for a second to charge the capacitors. An orange light will come on indicating it can be ready for use. When the unit is charged and you do not use it to safeguard oneself you should touch the prongs to a metal object in an effort to safely discharge it.&lt;br /&gt;;Together with the new Stun Pen your defense remains unknown as defeat befalls your attacker. Who'd think that a supposed flashlight withheld such a shocking surprise? &lt;br /&gt;;Packing a potent jolt of 1,200,000 Volts, it's probably the most potent pen kind stun gun offered. When fired, the stun pen produces an intimidating electrical sound because the bright electric surrent pulsates across the prime from the unit. This stun gun is ensured to shield you using the combined work of each the sound and the general influence of the volts operating via the assailants body. But, it may help to protect you in greater than one way. &lt;br /&gt;;As well as getting a potent beautiful device, this stun pen features a hassle-free built-in LED flashlight. Its ulterior function adds for the beneficial effect that the stun pen has for its user. Not simply will it supply you security with all the information that you can defend oneself, the stun pen will present you light and guidance whenever you have to have it. &lt;br /&gt;;As well as offering you protection, you might be protected by the precautions taken inside the designing of the stun pen. 3 levels of safety deterrant had been built in to prevent any incidents of accidental discharge. 1st, the safety cap need to be removed. Then, the safety switch must be inside the &quot;on&quot; position which will lead to a red LED warning light to come on. The final amount of safety precautions demands the trigger button to become pressed down. With all of these added safety increments your welfare is at its peak!&lt;br /&gt;;This pen stun gun comes with built-in  rechargeable battery which eliminates the really need to purchase or replace the batteries and comes with Totally free intergrated charger.  Each and every unit also comes with a Cost-free Nylon holster with belt loop attachment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5taWdlbnRlLmNvbS95b3VyX3BhZ2UvYmxvZy92aWV3X3Bvc3RpbmcuaHRtbD9waWQ9MjM0NjExNCZhbXA7cHJvZmlsZV9pZD03MTk4ODAyJmFtcDtwcm9maWxlX25hbWU9YmFydG9uY2hlcnJ5MTEmYW1wO3VzZXJfaWQ9NzE5ODgwMiZhbXA7dXNlcm5hbWU9YmFydG9uY2hlcnJ5MTE_" target="_blank"&gt;;stun pen, stun pen, pen stun gun&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>