<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="168a9432ec39d16bdc5b3057c2d9e050">			So if you have out of date or a corrupt driver, the only way to fix this issue is to update the driver to the latest version.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To get the latest version of the printer drivers from the HP website follow these steps:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Go to the HP website&lt;br /&gt;;Go to Support &amp; Drivers&lt;br /&gt;;Under &quot;;Enter a product name/number&quot;; put your model and press &quot;;Search.&quot;; If you're not sure what model your printer is HP has a handy page for finding your printer model here: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fh10025.www1.hp.com%2Fewfrf%2Fwc%2FfindModel%3Flc%3Den%26amp%3Bdlc%3Den%26amp%3Bcc%3Dus"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://h10025.www1.hp.com/ewfrf/wc/findModel?lc=en&amp;dlc=en&amp;cc=us&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Select the printer on the list that matches yours&lt;br /&gt;;Select your operating system&lt;br /&gt;;Download the drivers to a place you will remember&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To update the drivers:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Click Start&lt;br /&gt;;Click Control Panel&lt;br /&gt;;Click on System and Security, Under System go to Device Manager&lt;br /&gt;;Here look around some, your printer may be under Imaging Devices&lt;br /&gt;;Double click the printer&lt;br /&gt;;Click on the Driver tab&lt;br /&gt;;Click the Update Driver button&lt;br /&gt;;Browse to where you saved the files&lt;br /&gt;;Install the files&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of course there is now software on the market that makes updating hp printer drivers and keeping them updated simple. The software is called driver update software, and what it does is scan your computer for the current version of drivers in use, then scans the Internet for the latest drivers, then installs the latest version of the drivers available. Thus, making updating drivers manually a thing of the past.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Today, discount printer color cartridges are available online and people can opt for them instead of expensive ones and save money. Online stores are flooded with such cartridges. When you buy a printer, you make a one-time investment. Daily usage of the printer can lead to issues like running out of ink and the need for refilling or getting new cartridges.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's a known fact that laser printer ink cartridges, color cartridges, and other printer accessories require you to shell out quite a number of dollars. However, if you search the internet, you can find several sites which offer printer color cartridges at a discount!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Discount Printer Color Cartridges&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sites like Combo Ink and others provide attractive discounts on printer cartridges. The fact that they are inexpensive does not mean that they are mediocre in quality. These printer accessories rank the highest in terms of performance and quality standards. Whether you have a printer from Samsung, Dell, HP, Epson, or any other reputed company, the cartridges from these sites provide the best replacement when your printer runs out of ink.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're skeptical about the quality of printer accessories available on discount on the internet, just try them once. You'd even stop buying them from the regular store!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Secret behind Discounts&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ever wondered how these websites manage to provide appealing discounts on printer color cartridges and other printer accessories? These online dealers purchase the cartridges directly from the manufacturers in bulk.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is no third party involved in the purchase and the volume bought is large, which enables them to get the items at a stunningly low price. Also, they sell the items only on their online stores. This means that their overheads are low too. Such a direct purchase and online selling removes the need for a shop space, which in turn, removes the cost of renting and maintaining the space, hiring staff and inventory management. This is why they can easily afford to provide you printer color cartridges at unbelievable prices.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The discounts offered and reasonable prices have made such websites popular. It's time you ordered these cartridges!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.mehleprinting.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.mehleprinting.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>