<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fb28349d4bd0b481f8db66cbb415eaa">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.globalbhutaneseliteratureorganization.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.globalbhutaneseliteratureorganization.com/&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Face Book    -      Wikipedia  -      Blog  -   Europeen(Comperative Literature
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Our Literature Today        World Literatre                  Social Netwok       
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What is Literature? Literature
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Literature is an artistic writing or body of written work. It may be imaginative or creative writing. Usually it’s a writing that is recognized for artistic quality. There are many sides to literature and many different forms in which it is introduced to us. Whether literature is to be figurative, informative or critical it has become a way in life for all humans to gather other forms of information.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Literary works are portrayals of the thinking patterns and social norms prevalent in society.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prose, poetry, drama, essays, fiction, literary works based on philosophy, art, history, religion, and culture and also scientific and legal writings are grouped under the category of literature. Creative nonfiction of the ancient times and literary journalism are also fall under literature. Certain extremely technical writings such as those on logistics and mathematics are also believed to be a part of literature. Some of the great literary works like the Bible and Indian epics like Ramayana and Mahabharata, among others, provide society with the guiding principles of life
&lt;br /&gt;;It is through reading such great literary and poetic works, that one understands life. They help a person take a closer look at the different facets of life. In many ways, it can change one's perspective towards life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Literature serves as an enormous information base. True, languages are the building blocks of literature. Literature, is definitely, much more than its literary meaning, which defines it as 'an acquaintance to letters'. It, in fact, lays the foundation of an enriched life; it adds 'life' to 'living'
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many people have accepted literature as it is the basis of all human arts....all forms of expression. Writers express the matters in artistic way in literature.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bhutanese Literature
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the context of world literature, Bhutanese Literature seemed hidden in the corner of this world and not exposed with its artistic writing. There was in need of one concrete literature organization which can give a common platform to the Bhutanese readers and writers to make renowned Bhutanese literature globally. To meet the global standard Global Bhutanese Literature Organization was formed on 5th of October 2009 with common objectives. Objectives are: promote, Protect, Conserve and bring revolution in Bhutanese Literature in this 21st century with new concept and ideas of all people.
&lt;br /&gt;;Connect Bhutanese writers all over the world,
&lt;br /&gt;;Encourage and uplift the young generation in the field of literature and education, keep Old Literature alive with respect and bring change in progressive way across the globe, encourage all people in literary field making their active participation, look the world with clear view of freedom mind in 21st century.
&lt;br /&gt;;To involve young generation and develop their potentialities in Literature and Education, and its main objectives to bring all writers and readers in a platform to share ideas and views to give a complete solution in Bhutanese literature and meet the standard of high level of Global literature
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bhutanese writers 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thousands of Bhutanese writes and readers are doing literary work every day. We (GBLO) knew the right way to preserve and promote our Bhutanese writers globally. GBLO is the right organization for all level writers. Child’s Literature, Adult literature, Elderly literature etc also comes under our literary program. It’s fully non political literary organization for all Bhutanese people. People of all ages are welcome to this organization to express their feelings, thoughts, suggestion through literary work. We believe literature is in everything if we know it rightly. GBLO also knows that literature and music are the two sides of same coin, and society as a good land of creation in literature. We are hopeful that GBLO writers will meet the standard of World Literature. We welcome all writers and readers to be committed in the development of Bhutanese literature and become the great professional writers one day across the globe and educate the people. GBLO works for the writers and readers promotion in globally through different Medias. Global Bhutanese literature Organization also works to share art in literature with world community in progressive way. GBLO publishes all kinds of literary writings, including descriptive, native, expository and persuasive works, as well as creative literary works like prose ,poetry, story, essay, plays, novel, music videos/videos related to literature etc. through website, social networks (&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bhutaneseliterature.ning.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.bhutaneseliterature.ning.com/&lt;/a&gt;; and face book – &lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=gblo_195@yahoo.com"&gt;;gblo_195@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;;), blogs, Google, YouTube, online book publishing E – website etc.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>