<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="cbec744e39d2f78fb110cd3e350c4011">			Proceeding to the Birthplace of Taoism, Taoyuan Holy City of Heming Mountain in Dayi, Sichuan for Enjoying Unique Taoist Dance - Taoism Religious Ceremonies&lt;br /&gt;;???Taoism originates from China for 1800 years till now. The person entering into religion will advocate peace of mind, have simple life, quiet and comfortable state, let everything take its course, and govern by doing nothing that goes against nature. The birthplace of Chinese Taoism – Heming Mountain is located in Dayi, Chengdu, Sichuan Province, with Qingcheng Mountain on the north, Emei Mountain on the south and Wuzhong Mountain on the west, and the foot of mountain reaches Western Sichuan Plain; it is about 70 km away from Chengdu and is famous scenic tourist area and summer resort. There is a “Taoyuan Holy City” built on the mountain, which is a site of Taoist pilgrimage in the world, and also is a blessing place of seeking Taoist fairy formula, recovery and health preserving by numerous living beings. Scenic spots includes more than 20 buildings and temples, such as Temple Gate, Yucong Square, Tai Chi Square, Crane Moo Bridge, Baiyi Avenue, Taoist Canteen, Lingzu Palace, Wenchang Palace, Hall of the Three Officials, Hall of Ancestral Celestial Master and Lord Laozi Hall.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Finfo.taoholycity.com%2Fuploads%2Fallimg%2F120428%2F1_120428150008_1.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://info.taoholycity.com/uploads/allimg/120428/1_120428150008_1.jpg&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;br /&gt;;???Row upon row of temple groups in Taoyuan Holy City&lt;br /&gt;;???Taoism religious ceremonies initially originated in original religious consciousness of ancient Chinese society; the shaman will offer sacrifices to ghosts and gods, communicate with heaven and man to seek the blessings from heaven. The people believed in Taoism think that doing religious ceremonies (chai-chiao) can seek the blessing from gods, eliminate the misfortune, accumulate good fortune and prevent the disaster. There are many names of Taoism religious ceremonies, generally if common people have the need, there is to be corresponding name of Taoist sacrificial ceremony. Common Taoism religious ceremonies include: morning and evening altar scriptures (routine ritual made in the morning and evening by Taoist priests living in the temple. The first is to cultivate perfection and nourish heart, the second is to pray for auspiciousness, the third is to strengthen the mind of Taoism, the fourth is to release the souls of dead from purgatory, and the fifth is to reflect the management of Taoist mood in the temple); Taoist zhujiang ritual (requesting the gods for visiting mandala to bless); sacrifice ritual (offering sacrifices to solitary souls and releasing the souls of dead from purgatory); birthday ritual and celebration ritual (celebrating the birthday of the founder); meeting ritual (meeting the Jade Emperor come to the world for giving blessings, avoiding disasters and prolonging life); returning ritual (a kind of ritual when the ritual is completed satisfactorily, to eliminate the sin and release all living beings from sufferings).&lt;br /&gt;;???In the temples of Taoyuan holy city, grand Taoist religious ceremonies will be held on every Dragon Boat Festival, birthday of Taoist master, Spring Festival and other traditional festivals. The religious ceremony rituals are well known both in China and abroad for their authentic and efficacious features. Taoist priests are dressed the priest frock with gold and silver thread, hold various musical instruments, sing the old tunes, dance in the mandala of temples, convey the followers’ good wishes to the gods, and pray the gods to bless for fruition. On the day of religious ceremonies, the holy city is crowded and all alive. Taoist believers and tourists from all over the world gather here together to enjoy the beautiful dance of Taoist religious ceremonies. Today, various types of religious activities have become one of the most representative characteristic cultures in Heming Mountain. In addition to holding Taoist zhujiang ritual, sacrifice ritual, meeting ritual, birthday ritual, returning ritual and other everyday religious activities, it will undertake a variety of ritual religious ceremonies, for praying the blessings and a change of luck for all followers, removing disasters and eliminating misfortunes, which attract all followers to go on a pilgrimage and pray for safety.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Finfo.taoholycity.com%2Fuploads%2Fallimg%2F110603%2F1_110603165817_1.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://info.taoholycity.com/uploads/allimg/110603/1_110603165817_1.jpg&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;br /&gt;;Unveiling ceremony of blessings in 2010 Spring Festival&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VuLnRhb2hvbHljaXR5LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Address of Taoyuan Holy City: Sanfeng Village, Dayi Heming Township, Chengdu, Sichuan, China&lt;br /&gt;;Reference website of Taoyuan Holy City: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Finfo.taoholycity.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://info.taoholycity.com/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;English website: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.taoholycity.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://en.taoholycity.com/&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Contact E-mail: &lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=service@taoholycity.com"&gt;;service@taoholycity.com&lt;/a&gt;;; &lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=billchin72@foxmail.com"&gt;;billchin72@foxmail.com&lt;/a&gt;;; &lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=Iviey@163.com"&gt;;Iviey@163.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>