<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="42d67804e15c377e84f638a2be1b8b77">			People who are serious about their body building are often subjected to intense stereotypes. The stereotype is that of people who cover their bodies in oil, grow their muscles to almost obscene proportions and then do no thing but lift half ton weights over and over again. The stereotype is not totally in error. That lifestyle is something that some body builders choose for themselves. Professional body builders, for example, earn their living by building up their muscles to outrageous proportions. Of course, that is not the only reason to take up body building. Getting healthier should be your main goal if you start body building. Body building is one of the best ways to work out. If you are new to body building, here is the approach you should take. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Similar content and details: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9naW92YW5uaWpvbmU5MjIvcG9zdHMvODM4MDE2L0JlZ2lubmVyJTI3cytHdWlkZSt0bytCb2R5K0J1aWxkaW5n" target="_blank"&gt;;Body Building For Newbies&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NsZWlkaWdkZ2VlbG9jYmEuamlnc3kuY29tL2VudHJpZXMvZ2VuZXJhbC9CdWlsZC1hLVN0cm9uZy1Cb2R5LVdpdGgtQ29uc2lzdGVudC1Cb2R5LUJ1aWxkaW5nLVdvcmtvdXRz" target="_blank"&gt;;Body Building Help and Hints&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choose a gym that is good. Body building is not something that every gym is set up to offer. Before you decide which gym to join make sure you shop around. You want to have a gym that has a body building population.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You want to also choose a gym that is brightly lit and extra clean. You should choose a gym that takes good care of its equipment (and that has equipment that is not always broken down). You also want the gym to have a good vibe to it. It is hard to take real advantage of a gym membership if you don't enjoy the time you spend there. This could cause your body building efforts to wane. Take some time to try out all of the different exercises that body builders do. You don't have to commit to certain ones yet, but trying out everything is great! Doing this will help you learn which exercises to do when you want to work certain groups of muscles. It will be easier to plan a workout and to get results when you know exactly what you need to do to each part of your body. After all, if you want to develop your triceps and biceps, you don't want to do exercises meant for your pecs or your abs. Learning what needs to be done and the best methods of doing it are steps you need to ensure that you use your time wisely and don't accidentally get hurt. Go look at these strategies on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvdy10by1idWlsZC1sZWctbXVzY2xlLndpa2lkb3QuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;how to build leg muscle&lt;/a&gt;; here...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Check in with your doctor regularly. Your doctor can help you make sure that you are getting the work out you need while still keeping your muscles in check. A doctor will be able to help you take steps to prevent causing yourself accidental harm when you work out while still making sure that the workouts are having the effect on your body that they should be having. Your doctor will not only help you identify issues as they occur, he or she will help keep them from advancing too much. At minimum, you should see a doctor when you begin your body building routine so that you can make sure that you have the correct approach to the sport. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Body building, as an activity, can be incredibly rewarding. It helps you stay healthy. It helps you get your body in shape. It can help you increase your stamina and endurance levels.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you work at the sport your strength will improve and your muscles will grow and it is very important that you consciously care for your health and your muscle tone. You will have great body building results if you take the proper steps to protect your health.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Relevant content pieces and tips:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYXN0LmZtL3VzZXIvbm9haHphbW9yYTkyMy9qb3VybmFsLzIwMTIvMDMvMTIvNWRicGxzX2JvZHlfYnVpbGRpbmdfZm9yX2JlZ2lubmVycz9zdWNjZXNzPTE_" target="_blank"&gt;;How to Engage in Body Building Training For the Best Result&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25vYWh6YW1vcmE5MjMuZG11c2ljLm5ldC9qb3VybmFsLzI1MzczMQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Simple And Effective Body Building Routines For Starters&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cueGluZy5jb20vZXZlbnRzLzMtaW1wb3J0YW50LWJvZHktYnVpbGRpbmctdGlwcy1wZW9wbGUtaWdub3JlLTg5MzIxOA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Simple And Effective Body Building Routines For Starters&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e887dffd66b25f825ed901d7a9b49341">			Body building is about more than turning yourself into the next Arnold Schwarzenegger (the 1980s Arnold, not the current, Governor of California Arnold). Most people think that body building is about growing your muscles to incredible sizes. The truth is that body building is more about building the strength of your muscles than it is about building up their appearance. It isn’t always about “getting ripped.” It is about increasing your health. If you are interested in starting a body building routine, here are some tips to help you out. Don't ever forget that in body building your health comes first and your physique comes last. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other related content and suggestions: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9naW92YW5uaWpvbmU5MjIvcG9zdHMvODM4MDE2L0JlZ2lubmVyJTI3cytHdWlkZSt0bytCb2R5K0J1aWxkaW5n" target="_blank"&gt;;Pushing Past the Body Building Stereotypes&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXluLmNvbS93YXluYmxvZy5odG1sP3djaT12aWV3ZW50cnkmYW1wO2VudHJ5X2tleT0xNjM1Njg_" target="_blank"&gt;;Body Builders Need The Right Approach&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choose a gym that you like. Not all gyms are set up for body building--some lack the right equipment. Look at several gyms before deciding which gym is right for you. You want a gym center that has regular body building clientele.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You also want to find a gym that has good lighting and is very clean. Your gym should have equipment that is well maintained and always in working order. You also want the gym to have a good vibe to it. If you don’t enjoy working out there, you won’t take full advantage of your membership. This could put a major slow down on your body building efforts. Take a little bit of time to learn how to do all of the different body building exercises that are out there. You only have to try them for now; you do not have to commit them to your routine. This will help you learn which muscles get worked on by each exercise. It will be simpler to develop a workout plan and to see results that you want to see when you know exactly which exercises and what tools to use to develop each part of your body. Give it some thought: when you go to work on your arms you don't want to actually (accidentally) be working on your posterior region! When you take the time to explore and learn you are less likely to waste your own time and hurt yourself. Go and visit these resources on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvdy10by1nZXQtYWJzLWluLWEtd2Vlay53aWtpZG90LmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;abs in a week&lt;/a&gt;; here...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Stay positive. The story of The Little Engine that Could is more than a cliché. It is an actual mindset that you can have. It could be the key to your body building success.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You need to believe in yourself. You have to keep a positive mindset or you'll just get discouraged. It is also important to note that your body will show more of a response if you stay positive. When you are happy about your situation it is easier to body build. If you hate what you're doing, you'll have a more difficult time with it. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Body building can be an incredibly rewarding activity. It can help you increase your health. It helps you keep your body in the proper shape. It increases your stamina and endurance.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is important that, as you work to get stronger and have better muscles, you take specific steps to protect your health and your muscles from deteriorating. You will see a high level of success with your body building when you take steps to protect your health.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other relevant articles or blog posts and details:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25vYWh6YW1vcmE5MjMuc291cC5pby9wb3N0LzIzODE4NzA2Ny9UaGUtRXNzZW50aWFscy1PZi1Bbi1FZmZlY3RpdmUtQm9keS1CdWlsZGluZw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Have More Success With These Body Building Tips&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpY2VwbXVzY2xldHJhaW5pbmcxMDg1LndvcmRwcmVzcy5jb20vMjAxMi8wMy8xMi9ob3ctdG8tZW5nYWdlLWluLWJvZHktYnVpbGRpbmctdHJhaW5pbmctZm9yLXRoZS1iZXN0LXJlc3VsdC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;High Performance Body Building 101&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ub3J0aGVybi1saW1pdHMuY29tL3N0b3J5LnBocD90aXRsZT10aGUtYmVzdC13YXktdG8tYmVjb21lLWEtYm9keS1idWlsZGVyLTI_" target="_blank"&gt;;Build a Strong Body With Consistent Body Building Workouts&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>