<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ca964f7298049b27287eac2de861e454">			You must beware as overdose of these pills can lead to nervousness, headache and hypertension.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brick and mortar Herbal stores will want to consider stocking Guarana Seed and&lt;b&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2d1YXJhbmFrYXBzZWxuLmluZm8_" target="_blank"&gt;;guarana capsules&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/b&gt;;, which may be purchased as wholesale guarana for the purpose of resale. There are online bulk herb suppliers who offer Guarana Seed, which is also commonly known as guarana herb, at both retail and wholesale competitive prices.&lt;br /&gt;;Guarana Seed comes from the fruit formed by the Paullinia cupana plant, which is a vining plant found in the same botanical family as the maple, and is native to Brazil and the Amazon basin. Off-white flowers of Paullinia cupana produce a fruit that is red and brown in color. Inside the fruit are the black seeds, which are of the same approximate size as coffee beans.&lt;br /&gt;;There is a unique process that goes into the making of Guarana Seed tea. First, the seeds are shelled and then washed, after which they are finely ground down into a powder. The guarana herb is then used to create a kneaded dough, which is rolled into cylindrical shapes. This is then grated, and the gratings are used for making guarana herb tea.&lt;br /&gt;;Guarana herb, as well as guarana capsules, are known for their strong stimulant effect. Guarana contains the chemical guaranine, which is a type of caffeine; guarana offers twice the amount of caffeine as is typically found in coffee beans. Because of its high caffeine content, guarana may help to reduce migraine headaches.&lt;br /&gt;;Bulk guarana finds its way into several different items. These include soft drinks as well as drinks promoting energy. Herbal tea is also made from the guarana powder. It may also be taken as guarana capsules. Guarana is especially popular in South America, where guarana is used most often as a source of caffeine.&lt;br /&gt;;An initial study of guarana has discovered other unique qualities possessed by the herb. When the herb was taken, it was found that it may help to increase memory, mood and alertness. It may also help with weight control, because early studies have shown that it may help the body recognize satiety more quickly. The herb may also offer antibacterial and antioxidant qualities. In mice it was shown to have reduced fat cells.&lt;br /&gt;;Like any herbal product, guarana should not be used diagnose, treat, cure or prevent any disease. If you believe that you are ill, you should consult with a health care provider right away.&lt;br /&gt;;Herbs such as guarana can be purchased in bulk quantities at wholesale prices. Wholesale guarana can be found from quality natural bulk herb processors online.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Guarana's use by South Yank local clans predates the discovery of Brazil. These tribes recognized its stimulant effect and used it during periods of fasting too.&lt;br /&gt;;Traditionally, the native tribes of Brazil and the surrounding nations have used guarana to treat many ailments. Included in this list are the runs, hypertension, fever, migraine, neuralgia, and dysentery. It has also been used to treat pain, overcome heat fatigue, combat early aging, detox the blood. It has been found useful to govern intestinal gas, obesity, dyspepsia, fatigue, and arteriosclerosis.&lt;br /&gt;;Guarana's effect on the central nervous system, most particularly as a stimulant, has caught the eye of many sportsmen and people who wish to lose weight. The metabolism boosting and energy manufacturing effect make this a popular supplement with those attempting to boost performance or losing weight by increased caloric burning.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2d1YXJhbmFrYXBzZWxuLmluZm8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Guarana &lt;/a&gt;;has a higher proportion of caffeine than the coffee or cacao beans.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>