<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="2b6227c91fe6d8da1ed0aa02c12ac39d">			If you still have no idea of the coming 2011 Halloween, I think you must grasp time to make Preparation. To avoid some mistake, and assist your a happy &amp; horrible Halloween ,the items I suppose below is really worth to buy, including Costumes, Masks and Face Paint. it is sure they will be the Hottest Halloween make-up of 2011
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Iterm: DIY Colored Drawing/Painting Masks with Paint Set  
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Interesting to paint your own masks
&lt;br /&gt;- Great DIY idea for painting by yourself
&lt;br /&gt;- Comes with six different color paints and painting brush
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween Cosplay Spandex Witch Costume Dress Set (2-Piece Set) 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Witch 2pcs/set included: hat + dress
&lt;br /&gt;- Great for cosplay party
&lt;br /&gt;- The dress also good for wearing at normal day
&lt;br /&gt;- Material: high quality 90% nylon + 10% spandex
&lt;br /&gt;- Color: black + yellow
&lt;br /&gt;- Free size, one size fits most 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Halloween Costume Face Paint Make Up Crayons Set 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Color: Red + green + blue + coffee
&lt;br /&gt;- Made of professional face painting crayon
&lt;br /&gt;- Easy to use 
&lt;br /&gt;- Allows paint directly to the skin
&lt;br /&gt;- Creates even scarier monster face
&lt;br /&gt;- Great for Halloween, theme party or other situations
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is sure a good chance to train or practice your creativity, and enjoy the fun of Painting your own Halloween mask, make up in Halloween face, and the customs seems for ladies, but if this is made-up dress, men also can make a try.or maybe you need more material as the different ideas in your mind,ok,check our here
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fchina-wholesale-gifts-and-party-supplies%2Fhalloween-gadgets%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/china-wholesale-gifts-and-party-supplies/halloween-gadgets/&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="faced83e7c7b059c413fd361d9ea6487">			Cute Cartoon Style USB 2.0 2*CMOS Double 1.3MP Lens 3D Webcam with Microphone&amp;3D Glasses
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fcomputers%2Fwebcams%2Fcute-cartoon-style-usb-2.0-2cmos-double-1.3mp-lens-3d-webcam-w-microphone-3d-glasses.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/computers/webcams/cute-cartoon-style-usb-2.0-2cmos-double-1.3mp-lens-3d-webcam-w-microphone-3d-glasses.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most of us learn of 3D webcam via the Worlds first 3D webcam– Minoru 3D Webcam, it reflects how users feel about the 3D image. The Minoru can be used with Windows Live Messenger, Skype, AOL instant messenger, OoVoo and other video conferencing packages. The camera can also be used to take still pictures or record 3D video for YouTube. It can also be used as a normal 2D Webcam. Today I would like to introduce a similar 3D webcam of Minoru; it is just half price of Minoru
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Specifications
&lt;br /&gt;- Color: Red
&lt;br /&gt;- High speed USB 2.0 with UVC
&lt;br /&gt;- 2 * CMOS sensors (VGA 640*480)
&lt;br /&gt;- Double 1.3MP wide angle lens
&lt;br /&gt;- 300kb~3MB image output @60fps
&lt;br /&gt;- 3D/2D mode selectable
&lt;br /&gt;- Built-in microphone
&lt;br /&gt;- USB cable length: 1.8m
&lt;br /&gt;- Support Windows XP/Vista/7
&lt;br /&gt;- Support automatic white balance &amp; exposure
&lt;br /&gt;- Your friends can see you in 3D on Skype or other messaging programs
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fcomputers%2Fwebcams%2Fcute-cartoon-style-usb-2.0-2cmos-double-1.3mp-lens-3d-webcam-w-microphone-3d-glasses.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/computers/webcams/cute-cartoon-style-usb-2.0-2cmos-double-1.3mp-lens-3d-webcam-w-microphone-3d-glasses.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;So you see from above that this Cute Cartoon Style 3D webcam features a USB 2.0 interface with an approximate 1.8m cable length. A built-in microphone allows you to chat directly over the Internet with friends and family. Special 1.3MP Lens creates a 3D effect that really brings video chatting to life! Included are four sets of 3D glasses 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;It is currently available from vkamobi.com for $49.99. it will comes with the package including 1 * 3D webcam,1 * Software CD,1 * Plastic Frame 3D glasses, 5 * Paper 3D glasses. Vkamobi provide free shipping worldwide, order today, you can pay by PayPal or via western union		</conversation>		<conversation id="155853ff0732c68c3ca3b41ef76f4dec">			Hero H400 4.3 inch Android 2.3 GPS Analog TV Wifi Touch Screen Smartphone
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fgoogle-android-phones%2Fhero-h400-wifi-gps-tv-touch-screen-smartphone.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/google-android-phones/hero-h400-wifi-gps-tv-touch-screen-smartphone.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Among thousands of China Smartphone Hero always give us surprise. Today I would like to show a new hero Smartphone –Hero H400 Android 2.3, the surprise is that price is really cheap as a new android 2.3 Smartphone.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Main Feature
&lt;br /&gt;•  Type: Smart Phone 
&lt;br /&gt;•  OS: Android 2.3 
&lt;br /&gt;•  CPU: MTK6516 460+280 MHz
&lt;br /&gt;•  512MB ROM+256MB RAM extend to 16GB max  
&lt;br /&gt;•  Quad Band: GSM850/900/1800/1900MHZ 
&lt;br /&gt;•  Dual sim cards dual standby
&lt;br /&gt;•  Dual cameras with flash light
&lt;br /&gt;•  Support GPS
&lt;br /&gt;•  Support WIFI: 802.11b/g wireless internet
&lt;br /&gt;•  supported Analog TV 
&lt;br /&gt;•  Support Java, can install applications
&lt;br /&gt;•  Games: Android and Java games
&lt;br /&gt;•  Screen: 4.3 inch high definition touch screen, QVGA, 320x240
&lt;br /&gt;•  Slide to unlock 
&lt;br /&gt;•  Dedicated Touch Keyboard
&lt;br /&gt;•  Auto horizontal function
&lt;br /&gt;•  Bluetooth A2DP 
&lt;br /&gt;•  Data transfers: USB, WiFi, U disk under the third party software, Bluetooth
&lt;br /&gt;•  FM/MP3/MP4/Bluetooth/Email function supported
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fgoogle-android-phones%2Fhero-h400-wifi-gps-tv-touch-screen-smartphone.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/google-android-phones/hero-h400-wifi-gps-tv-touch-screen-smartphone.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Obviously, Hero H400 was set with prevailing features like GPS, Analog TV, Auto horizontal function, Wireless internet and Java are all here with this new android 2.3 Smartphone. It runs on the CPU of MTK6516 460MHz+280MHZ.It supports dual SIM cards dual standby and dual cameras with flash light. Just a simple slide to unlock the phone! There is 512MB ROM, 256MB RAM, and card slot supporting memory expansion up to 16GB.for more features and function of h400,you can visit here to check
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Hero H400 is also available and hot on eBay(179.99$), but for Hero mobile, you can order from Reliable and professional China mobile phone wholesale website, likes this mobile on vkamobi, it will save u a 30$,and they provide free shipping, accept payment from PayPal or via western union.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2c4b994671fdcb3db7f99afc319ddfd6">			The Hot Five Angry Birds Introduction
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angry Birds is a video game by Rovio for the Apple iPhone, Apple iPad, Android Smartphone or other touch devices(Tablet PC). In a nutshell, the darned pigs stole the birds’ eggs, and the angry birds must take their revenge by flinging themselves (with your help) via slingshot at those darned pigs to knock down their houses and kill the pigs. To win full star and high score, now learn feature of each birds before you play the game.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fangry-birds%2F5pcs-10cm-cute-angry-birds-plush-toy-set.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/angry-birds/5pcs-10cm-cute-angry-birds-plush-toy-set.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Red Bird 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The angry bird that starts it all is red bird. He is smallish, red, and oh so angry. What you see is what you get with red bird. No tapping the screen unless there’s a smudge. Red angry bird is good for running directly into pigs though or knocking down wooden parts of the pigs’ house. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yellow Bird 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This angry bird is triangle shaped and yellow. He sails through the air with the greatest of ease, that is, till you tap the screen which speeds him up considerably. This also gives this angry bird more power to knock down the pigs’ house. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blue Bird 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Blue bird, or should I say blue birds, are useful little critters in the Angry Birds game. The blue bird starts off as one tiny blue bird, but when you tap the screen, he separates into three birds that can do triple the damage. Triple the fun. Not to the pigs of course. Ha ha, pigs. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White Bird 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White bird is one angry bird. He is fat and round and white. His best feature? With a tap of the screen, white bird drops an egg on pigs or on their house. Take that, pigs! 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Black Bird 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Black bird is a rotund fellow who is spitting mad. In fact, after you sling him at the sneaky pigs, he nestles among the pigs’ structure, turns red, then blows up. He’s that mad. And black bird does some serious damage. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.vkamobi.com%2Fangry-birds%2F5pcs-10cm-cute-angry-birds-plush-toy-set.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.vkamobi.com/angry-birds/5pcs-10cm-cute-angry-birds-plush-toy-set.html&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Angry Birds has been praised for its successful combination of addictive gameplay, comical style, and low price. And the picture I show above are angry birds plush toy set, It is great for Angry Birds fans. It is a good decoration for homes and cars.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>