<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="d17e19ef0e95ecd894bccfdece4f1981">			Tenorshare Software, the professional data recovery software provider, today announce a special Christmas surprise for Tenorshare products lovers. &lt;strong&gt;;From now to December 31, 2011, customers can get the bundle product which includes Card Data Recovery for Windows and Card Data Recovery for Mac with $39.95, which is to up to 70% discount to the original price ($19.95+$29.95=$49.8). Or get Card Data Recovery for Mac individually for $19.95, saving $10 compared to its original price.&lt;/strong&gt;; This promotion will expire on December 31, 2011. If you are interested in data recovery program and use Mac as well as Windows, This bundle is the perfect choice for it will save you a large amount of money. Visit Card Data Recovery’s Christmas sale website:&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkvY2hyaXN0bWFzLmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.card-data-recovery.com%2Fchristmas.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.card-data-recovery.com/christmas.htm&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Card Data Recovery has won good reputation among users for the easy to use interface and powerful function. It has two versions specified for Windows users and Mac users. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkuY29tL3dpbmRvd3MtZGF0YS1yZWNvdmVyeS5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;Card Data Recovery for Windows&lt;/a&gt;; runs well on Windows7/Vista/XP/Server/2008/2003/2000. It supports file system recovery for Windows FAT12/16/32, NTFS, Linux EXT2, EXT3 and Mac HFS, HFS+. You can use it to help you recover photos, video, audio, documents from Windows hard disk, external hard drive, memory card, USB drive, floppy drive, pen drive, etc. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkuY29tL21hYy1kYXRhLXJlY292ZXJ5Lmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Card Data Recovery for Mac&lt;/a&gt;; runs well under Mac OS X 10.7 lion, Mac OS X 10.3 and above, also is compatible with the latest “Snow Leopard”. It allows you simply drag and drop the program into your computer’s “Application” directory. Largely shorten installation time. Meanwhile, you can preview the deleted data including photos, audio before recovery.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;About Card Data Recovery developer&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Card Data Recovery is one of the significant products developed by Tenorshare Inc., which is the leading PC utility software supplier who is dedicated to developing excellent tools in the field of PC security and multimedia. We have developed a wide range of awarding-winning software including data recovery, PDF converter, video converter, etc. for home and business PC users worldwide. Our products have won excellent reputation among customers and we will continue to develop wonderful tools for Tenorshare products’ lovers.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Contact information&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Tenorshare Co. Ltd
&lt;br /&gt;;maggiena
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=support@card-data-recovery.com"&gt;;support@card-data-recovery.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="82e5c0faf40e6ad5d6d71da0c9b59c76">			Santa brings you omnipotent data recovery tools packed with new product Card Data Recovery for Mac as well as 60% discount on this new product. &lt;strong&gt;;From now to December 31, all customers can get Card Data Recovery for Mac with $19.95, which is 60% discount from original price ($29.95)&lt;/strong&gt;;. If you are Mac user, and in need of data recovery tool, it is really a good bat for it will save you a large amount of money. Visit Card Data Recovery for Mac’s Christmas sale website: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkuY29tL2NocmlzdG1hcy5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.card-data-recovery.com%2Fchristmas.htm"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.card-data-recovery.com/christmas.htm&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkuY29tL21hYy1kYXRhLXJlY292ZXJ5Lmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Card Data Recovery for Mac&lt;/a&gt;; can recover lost and deleted data from HFS+, HFSX file systems on Mac OS X. This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkuY29tL21hYy1kYXRhLXJlY292ZXJ5Lmh0bQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Mac data recovery&lt;/a&gt;; software supports Mac OS X 10.4.11 and above, including the latest “Snow Leopard”. Meanwhile, it is compatible with EXT2, EXT3, FAT12/16/32, NTFS file system. Therefore, you can recover photos, video, songs, documents from other storage devices like digital camera, external hard drive (Western Digital external hard drive, Seagate external hard drive, etc.), memory card, SD card, CF card, MMC, USB drive, Pen drive, etc. &lt;strong&gt;;This new product can help you get back data under the following scenario:&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;1.Accidently deleted files and they can’t be found in trash, or deleted documents with “Command + Del”;
&lt;br /&gt;;2.Emptied Trash bin without backup;
&lt;br /&gt;;3.Deleted pictures, video, songs, etc. from storage media for mistakenly formatted storage devices;
&lt;br /&gt;;4.Falsely eject USB drives, pen drive, external hard drive, etc. to cause data loss;
&lt;br /&gt;;5.Pictures lost while pulling out the memory card without switching the camera off or turning off the digital camera during a write process;
&lt;br /&gt;;6.Apple partition or catalog file is corrupted;
&lt;br /&gt;;7.A volume has been formatted/reformatted or inaccessible.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;About Card Data Recovery for Mac developer&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Card Data Recovery for Mac is one of the significant products developed by Tenorshare Inc., which is the leading PC utility software supplier who is dedicated to developing excellent tools in the field of PC security and multimedia. We have developed a wide range of awarding-winning software including data recovery, PDF converter, video converter, etc. for home and business PC users worldwide. Our products have won excellent reputation among customers and we will continue to develop wonderful tools for Tenorshare products’ lovers.		</conversation>		<conversation id="15b026789fc6da884a77596a7e86897b">			Christmas is drawing near, what present do you expect most in Christmas? Some may want to get a laptop, new gadgets or devices that they don’t have before, some are looking forward to receiving video games. Toys and dolls are favorite staff kids love most. Several weeks before Christmas, parents are busy with preparing gifts for their kids. Sometimes, It proves challenging for boys or girls may be transitioning from wanting toys or dolls into wanting more “cool” items. 
&lt;br /&gt;;So you have to take that into consideration before you go out hunting for the gift. Here are some presents and gift ideas. Hope it can ease your job and make your Christmas season merrier.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Christmas Gifts for teenage&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;For teenage girls, fashion clothes, shoes are good choice. If a teenage boy is a video game freak, then new video games can be an ideal Christmas gift. If they have already had the popular gadgets like MP3 player or iPod, iPhone, digital camera, you can gift certificates for downloads, so they can choose their own loved music. Other accessories will also be appreciated, such as &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJkLWRhdGEtcmVjb3ZlcnkuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;photo recovery software&lt;/a&gt;;, data backup tool, etc.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Christmas Gifts for Kids &lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Preparing gifts for kids is less tough compared to others. The hottest game this year: Angry Birds: Knock On Wood is an excellent choice. You can also prepare Harry Potter Toys, Personalized Christmas Rag Dolls, Laser Cosmos, Gravity-Defying Gear, VTech InnoTab Learning App Tablet, Ugg boots for little fashionistas, etc. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Christmas Gifts for parents&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Parents often don’t ask for much. Before hunting up gifts among hundreds of products, you should think of their hobbies, household needs and interests. A digital photo frames with already downloaded photos of their grandchildren or children is a good choice, or you can prepare a letter telling them all the things you are grateful for. If your parents enjoy travelling or other things like watching sports game movie or listening to Opera, then order tickets for them. May everybody in the family have a peace and happy life should be their greatest wish.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Christmas Gifts for family&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Having a complete family in celebrating the Christmas sounds really excited. Economic family Christmas presents include customized Christmas cards writing your wishes, home-made cookies, meals, decorated flashing trees, etc. Also, you can prepare a family travel if it is possible. Or just sit together and chat about the jobs, school episode, etc.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>