<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a715343ef200bed1af5ad87b698c7e82">			Could this become an olive-branch into the conspiracy theorists, or only an attempt to decrease the radical implications for the Planet X / Nibiru ideas? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The data because of NASA's wide surveys for the outer solar system is supposed to be ready by time in 2012. So somehow, we should involve some answers regarding that existence of Tyche, Planet X or Nibiru by then. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;A great author named Zecharia Sitchin a short while ago discovered and translated an old Sumerian text thinking that a there is also a tenth planet simply just outside Pluto and its name is Nibiru. Nibiru is really a Sumerian God akin to Zeus of that Greeks. He also stated that it Nibiru and Tiamat collided with each other creating the asteroid belt and therefore the minor planets which include Earth. He also explained that Nibiru would pass away our Solar Method every 3600 years &amp; it is inhabited by a &quot;Annunakis&quot; or &quot;Nephilim&quot; through the Christians. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recent studies identified that the Mayan Calendar's long count is likely to end on 12 , 21, 2012. While online, a website identified as Zetatalk revealed that this Planet Nibiru will almost certainly collide on Dec 21, 2012. In addition, they said that through April 2003, it's about to be visible plus by May 15, 2009 the planet are going to be seen by typically the naked eye on the Southern Hemisphere and even they're also claiming they may have photos and video clips as proof. Now they are really saying that this planet is behind the Direct sun light. How could a planet originating from a distant place could orbit so fast inside of a span of 6 many? They never shown any facts in any way, just illustrations of this passage of the earth. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rumors spread the fact that on May 15, 2009 Planet Nibiru will be visible around typically the southern hemisphere. But nothing taken place nor anything strange within the skies. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If our planet's permanent magnet poles are aligning towards Nibiru then why don't you consider the other exoplanets? What about Jupiter? Saturn? The sunlight? The problem while using the doomsayers are all they think about is definitely the Earth. They have altogether disregarded what would happen on the other planets. Precisely why? Because they can't find enough excuses that will feed your is situated. There have been so many photos of environment X since 2003. However , no HARD EXPLANATION. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The bottom set is all we've got to do is delay until that time of day comes. If Nibiru is actually real then many of us will die, or, then life continues. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;A recently found out planet lurking in the far most locations of the solar system is stated to be 1 of the biggest probable threats not only to the galaxy but much more importantly to our house, Earth. But what is this planet that could feasible eradicate the lives of billions of creatures right here on planet Earth? Nicely, this so-contact planet X is the prime culprit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Planet X also goes by the name planet Nibiru. We shall wait and see, but in the meanwhile, allow as get ready and be prepared all over the place and every time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjanhoover25644.webs.com%2Fapps%2Fblog%2Fshow%2F8548815-nibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://janhoover25644.webs.com/apps/blog/show/8548815-nibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21581404%2Fmayan-calendar"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21581404/mayan-calendar&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="74263acad9fa2ea60456e2010c4b7184">			Could this often be an olive-branch into the conspiracy theorists, or just an attempt to decrease the radical implications on the Planet X / Nibiru studies? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The data with NASA's wide surveys belonging to the outer solar system is supposed to be ready by a bit in 2012. So one method or another, we should have some answers regarding this existence of Tyche, Planet X or Nibiru at that time. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;An author named Zecharia Sitchin most recently discovered and translated an old Sumerian text just saying that a there's a tenth planet just outside Pluto and your name is Nibiru. Nibiru is usually a Sumerian God just like Zeus of typically the Greeks. He also stated the Nibiru and Tiamat collided jointly creating the asteroid belt and the minor planets among them Earth. He also talked about that Nibiru would spread our Solar Product every 3600 years &amp; it really is inhabited by the particular &quot;Annunakis&quot; or &quot;Nephilim&quot; with the Christians. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recent studies learned that the Mayan Calendar's long count would end on January 21, 2012. While on-line, a website termed Zetatalk revealed this Planet Nibiru is going to collide on Dec 21, 2012. And also they said that by just April 2003, it's gonna be visible together with by May 15, 2009 the planet will be seen by the naked eye on the Southern Hemisphere together with they're also claiming they've photos and shows as proof. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If Nibiru passes on the planet. Our magnetic rods will align towards the crossing planet as a consequence creating devastating results on the planet like earthquakes, massive tsunamis, solar flares &amp; the like. Earth will stop rotating for just a week which would cause every one of those destructions. While the Christian believers also believe that it is the coming of Christ and additionally called this planet &quot;Wormwood&quot; much like stated on the Revelation which a great star through the sky will can come and cause earthquakes &amp; some other sort of natural catastrophes and also the NASA is seeking to hide the truth of the matter. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some of that their statements will find terrifying but Nibiru is a hoax. Because there is absolutely no such thing as the planet Nibiru. Even so, there is a tenth planet, it's name is certainly Eris and it's located in the Kuiper Belt however is in hardly any collision course along with Earth. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Zetatalk is founded by the Alien contactee or psychic Nancy Lieder. It had been 1995 when she proposed of the fact that world would stop on 2003 from this Nibiru issue. But since 1995 up even today nothing unusual transpired. What did your woman do? Re-scheduled the particular doomsday on January 21, 2012. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Mayan Diary ended on 12 , 21, 2012 nonetheless it returns back to beginning just like your speedometer once it reaches it's highest possible then it extends back to zero! It's very similar with Gregorian Calendar (the calendar people are using) once it reaches 12 31 it starts back to Jan 1 along with the cycle goes concerning and on. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All worth mentioning photos and clips are purely misinterpreted. Most common answers are because of Lens flare &amp; Reflection in the Sun. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Earth just can't stop rotating for one week. We shall wait and see, but in the meanwhile, allow as get ready and be prepared everywhere and each and every time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fjanhoover25644.webs.com%2Fapps%2Fblog%2Fshow%2F8548815-nibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://janhoover25644.webs.com/apps/blog/show/8548815-nibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit&lt;/a&gt;; , &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fquizilla.teennick.com%2Fstories%2F21584834%2Fnibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://quizilla.teennick.com/stories/21584834/nibiru-december-21-2012-the-lies-and-deceit&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>