<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="fb454653947622c0f4bebf76380732d4">			People usually notice your smile before anything else, so you would not want stained teeth to be the first thing you worry about. You can make your teeth visibly whiter by applying many different methods. The following article provides you with further information on teeth whitening and the various products and techniques that are available, so you can determine the ones that will work best for you. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtZXJnZW5jeWRlbnRpc3RueWMyNi53b3JkcHJlc3MuY29tLzIwMTIvMDMvMTIvaW5mb3JtYXRpb24tb24taG93LXRvLXRha2UtYXBwcm9wcmlhdGUtY2FyZS1vZi15b3VyLXRlZXRoLWFuZC1ndW1zLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Click here for a fantastic Emergency Dentist article&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Certain drugs, such as tetracycline, may cause teeth to appear gray, and this kind of discoloring is very difficult to whiten. Most teeth whiten products will produce better results on yellow and brown stains. You will have to do several treatments to turn teeth that are badly stained white again.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is a lack of evidence suggesting that they are more helpful than regular toothpastes. Ask your dentist to recommend a better brand that may be more effective.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Put strawberry juice on your toothbrush and brush away discoloration. The acid from the juice softens your tooth enamel, thus enabling you to clean away much of the discoloration from your teeth. This does not cost a lot of money and will help provide you with a beautiful smile.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You should eat fibrous vegetables and fruits because they will naturally scrub your teeth. For example, cucumbers, broccoli and apples are all wonderful types that will work. You can get the maximum benefit from these foods by eating them raw and chewing them very thoroughly, so they have sufficient time to clean your teeth. As you are chewing, move the food all around your mouth to work it all over your teeth.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's time to stop smoking. If you smoke, your teeth will be discolored by the smoke itself, as well as the nicotine it carries with it. This is an incontrovertible fact.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Coffee and tea can ruin a white smile. Both of these products can discolor your teeth. If you must drink coffee, when you finish, quickly wash out your mouth with water. This will help to reduce the stains caused by these drinks, that can ruin your smile.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To whiten your teeth naturally, brush your teeth with a paste of baking soda and water. Baking soda is soft on your teeth, but it contains enough abrasive agents to remove stains. Wet your toothbrush with water and dip it in baking soda right on your toothbrush.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lower the amount of soft drinks that you consume. The color of soft drinks can cause tooth stains. Soft drinks contain other ingredients which can potentially mar your tooth enamel. This will cause stains to stick. If you consume excessive amounts of soda, your teeth will be more resistant to whitening treatments.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Switching your regular toothpaste for whitening toothpaste is a simple way to enhance the beauty of your smile. Whitening toothpaste makes your teeth whiter by scrubbing away stains with the force of friction. Over time, the stains will fade and your teeth will gradually become whiter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Think about how your life would be better if you could smile with confidence. Give the tips in this article a try, and set out on the path to a lovely smile. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VtZXJnZW5jeS1kZW50aXN0LW55YzIwLm9uc3VnYXIuY29tL1Byb3Zlbi1UZWNobmlxdWVzLUtlZXAtWW91ci1UZWV0aC1IZWFsdGh5LVN0cm9uZy0yMjA5MjExOA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Go here for a Emergency Dentist article&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;More Informative Articles:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BvZ2VvdDM3NC5vbnRoZXJvYWQudG8vc2hvdy9zaG93LW9mZi10aG9zZS1wZWFybHktd2hpdGVzLXdpdGgtdGhlc2U_" target="_blank"&gt;;Advice To Give You a Brighter Smile&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlYXZlemluZS5jb20vZXZlbnRzL2xlYXJuLXRpcHMtd2hpdGVuaW5nLXlvdXItdGVldGgtZWFzaWx5" target="_blank"&gt;;Get Whiter Teeth By Following This Advice&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>