<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="43fbc66c872fca72ca3ee56c75fb3ff7">			Recent international oil prices continue to rise, the rate of change is also continuing to rise, a new round of expected impact of increased domestic oil market, constantly pushed up the price of gasoline and diesel. Refined oil prices rose, finished fuel oil bullish enthusiastic. Of methanol gasoline and we are concerned about the shift ushered in a small spring.Last week, reporters learned from the special committee of the national alcohol fuel standards, methanol gasoline additive national standards. Preparation process is accelerated by the end of November next year, is expected to form a standard draft and submitted to the National Standards Commission. The Scope of methanol gasoline additive standard, including the M85 and above and M30 following methanol gasoline. Methanol gasoline additive preparation of national standards since its launch in 2010, has been initially identified the additives 16 quality indicators, including appearance, boiling range, the evaporation residue, mechanical impurities, moisture, pH value, sulfur content, nitrogen content, organic chlorine content, additives The dosage; initial screening of the 40 kinds of test methods, and to determine the professional testing organization.According to standard members of the special committee of the national alcohol fuel, alcohol fuel and ether clean car special committee Xi'an Test Center Director Professor Liu Shengquan, in mid-July, the National Standardization Technical Committee of alcohol fuel, alcohol fuel and ether clean car designed Authority in Hanzhong City, Shaanxi Province, organized by car methanol gasoline additive "and" car cars use methanol gasoline additive GB Third preparation meeting to discuss the method for determination of methanol in the methanol gasoline standard text framework preliminary the additive indicator set and the screening test method, and to carry out a preliminary test.		</conversation>		<conversation id="622529e86e8566b5600b940bdfb4ac45">			The methanol fuel is a low-carbon high oxygen content of the fuel, combustion does not require too much air, helps to reduce the carbon and nitrogen oxide emissions. At the same time, the use of methanol do not need to make too many changes, it does not require too much input costs of the existing automobile manufacturing system and the fuel delivery and storage system. Thus, methanol can be said is a very suitable for the development of alternative fuels. George? Aura, winner of the Nobel Prize in Chemistry even "methanol economy" is considered the most important oil and gas era across a solution pathway.Methanol fuel only need to do a small change of the internal combustion engine manufacturing system, changes production assembly process is very simple, general-purpose high traditional automotive production system. And if just a small amount of methanol mixed with gasoline, blending into the low proportion of methanol gasoline, do not even need to make any changes to the existing car can use.We do methanol car modification methanol fuel, a coal-to-methanol, another natural gas to methanol. What difference does it make? In fact, the actual production process, natural gas, methanol, slightly better than the quality of the coal-to-methanol. Steam reforming of natural gas desulfurization can be carried out transformation may not transform directly to the methanol synthesis, a process that can largely reduce the byproducts generated in the methanol synthesis process, synthesis gas quality and stability, appropriate ingredients, in the subsequent methanol fine in the distillation process is relatively easier to achieve high-quality the usual testing standards AA grade methanol; For coal-to-methanol, completely different from all aspects of production and natural gas, methanol, and coal gasification process there will be a variety of byproduct, making the gas purification and transformation will be more complex and more difficult to control, making byproducts significantly more than natural gas head methanol synthesis process, thereby affecting the methanol distillation process control, through engineering means, of course, the coal head methanol still can reach AA grade methanol, just need to consume more raw material and power costs.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a9620071463be4e4964e990ca9edbc4c">			Methanol gasoline is a new alternative to regular gasoline, dedicated to the car with a gasoline internal combustion engine locomotive fuel, belonging to low-carbon energy; denatured alcohol additive is the industrial methanol or fuel methanol with the existing GB gasoline (or components of oil) certain volume (or weight) of a new clean fuel made from a rigorous scientific process deployment, can be partially or completely replace gasoline for all types of motor vehicle gasoline internal combustion engine. Due to the different physical and chemical properties of methanol and gasoline, methanol micro corrosion properties of methanol, methanol modified car can not be directly used with the case of methanol fuel additive. Methanol fuel additive has what role? Alcohol can methanol car modification experts for everyone following specific introduction.As we all know, methanol gasoline from the base gasoline, methanol and methanol fuel additive technology lies at the heart level of technology and quality control of methanol gasoline additives, the methanol fuel additives decided to allocate the soul of methanol gasoline quality. Methanol fuel additives key role in not change the condition of the engine structure, methanol and gasoline can achieve the long-term stability. So the methanol gasoline critical core design modulation methanol fuel additives. The new generation of alcohol can methanol fuel additives biochemical extracts contained in the biological hydrogen, biological enzyme dissolved in methanol gasoline, its molecular cleavage, activation and chemical reforming the hydrocarbon molecules in the catalyst carried out under the new permutations produce more branched hydrocarbons, cycloalkanes, the formation of the the effective a multivalent carbon chain and increase the octane number. Add in alcohol can methanol fuel additive methanol gasoline burning more fully, the rapid removal of water molecules and can produce a lubricating function, the engine to reduce the coefficient of friction and increase power.In the research and development process, the methanol fuel additive alcohol can aid chemical raw materials and chemical properties and the chemical reaction process scientific optimized permutations, in different proportions and stringent deployment of technology to solve the miscibility, water stratification and micro-etch problems. The moisture content of 3% emulsifying, -40 ? for 48 hours non-hierarchical. Both "open source" and "cost-cutting" and reduce energy loss was not involved in the combustion process for successful, create conditions for full combustion fuel, to reduce energy waste, reduce exhaust pollution, to achieve the optimal design of state to address past methanol gasoline fuel is not the promotion of technical obstacles.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>