<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="1f8a8f95a0767d24c39347a9ab1ca6f5">			Going and actually talking to people about the success they have had in relationships, you will find this: Almost always, among the top three reasons cited is the ability to laugh together. The marriages who do well together are the ones where the couples have learned to laugh at life.  We do not take things to hard but learn to have fun as a couple.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People want to have a good time.  But in so many cases it can be quite costly.  So it is fun to look for things that are fun to do that are free. Give your partner the gift or being a slave for a week, including the requisite master or mistress verbiage, pulling your forelock, bowing or curtseying, and backing out of the room. This schedule can shake things up so that you both are completely entertained.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After years together, we become used to the routine. We must fight to make sure that do not let the fire grow dim but must actively work to maintain its brightness. We have become habituated to the lives together we have created.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Understand that the &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;;&gt;love&lt;/a&gt; quotes&lt;/a&gt; that are all around us are to inspire us and not to be a thing of judgment.  And, certainly, we all long for the love that we see in the &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bquotes"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://greatestlovequotes.com&quot;;&gt;quotes&lt;/a&gt; about love&lt;/a&gt;.  But that love is one which is acquired and not just handed to us.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another thing you can do is to find a TV show that you both love and do an all day marathon where you camp out on the floor together. Laughing together can be a great time so have fun searching through funny birthday cards together. Tell stories about things that happened to you before you met and reminisce about the fun times you've had since you first became an item.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Have fun with learning a new language together and make it your new language together when you go to restaurants or the mall. Why not take a cooking class together as you both learn new ways of cooking.  
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The wonder of your love is it does not require the monumental to build a relationship. Plan a visit to the fast food chain where you had your first date. Plan simple overnight visits to your favorite hotel or town and just enjoy each other's company. Meet at a museum or an art gallery for a stroll together.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Send your honey a special invitation by card or e-mail. Tell them it will be a time to remember. Prepare for the date as carefully as if it was your first meeting and be on your best behavior as you were in that delicious dance of courtship.  When your friends question why you are in such a good mood lately, just smile and tell them that your life is so special that there's no time left to be grumpy.		</conversation>		<conversation id="446f33e9e42cc9f0f577904a677e4d8c">			Learning to anticipate a date night with your spouse is an important skill. Setting up and thinking about the date can be just as much fun as the date itself. We think about what we're going to wear, where we'll go, what we'll eat, what we'll say and do. Having fun planning all the small things that can get overlooked is a great anticipation builder.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If we enter a relationship, we stop dating. We see one another, of course, much more than we did in our dating days. At the onset of living together, we still have that sense of anticipation before seeing that beloved face. The two would wait excitedly for the next time that you would meet.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The last thing we want to do is to find ourselves in just a rut. The one thing we must always be vigilant about is the fact that our love must grow bright and not grow dim with time. We must guard against our comfortable life growing boring as well.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The best thing to understand that the &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;;&gt;love&lt;/a&gt; quotes&lt;/a&gt; that we all read needs to be an inspiration and not a judgment.  And, needless to say, we all long for the love that we see in the &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://greatestlovequotes.com&quot;;&gt;love&lt;/a&gt; quote&lt;/a&gt;.  However, that type of love is one that is cultivated instead of only stumbled upon.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One great idea is to take your favorite movie and your favorite dessert and snuggle on the couch as you watch it. Search out joke sites on the Internet or spend some time at the drugstore just looking at funny greeting cards. Find time to recall funny stories together and find ways to make the other person laugh.  It is the best medicine.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Going on smaller dates together can have the same effect of a vacation just in smaller scale.  So be good about planning those small dates.  A lunch or dinner date at a special place can be something we look forward to for a long happy week. A date to go bowling, or dancing, or golfing, can be set up several days in advance. Is there a movie that you both want to see?  Get out there and see it! 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take life a little slow now and again and you will see your love blossom.  Take the bus or the train to your favorite downtown.  Do things that are spontaneous.  It is so much fun! Learn to always try and win the heart of your spouse by doing their favorite things.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Give your love a little tingle by leaving note to come to a date. Explain to them that you eagerly await them. Have fun planning out all the tiny moments of your date together.  So that when you are together with your spouse, your time together will be stress free and you are truly able to relish your mate.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f5c5b2fd0a841825e682389e000b3dc7">			Going and speaking with people about the success they have had in relationships, you will find this: Almost always, the top three reasons cited is the ability to laugh together. Every single partner has the ability to look at life's problems without being to serious about it.  They can walk with their spouse through life and just be at ease.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having fun can cost more than a few bucks. Vacations, day trips, and even going to the movies all can be spendy.  But not all fun costs money. Give your significant other the gift or being a slave for a week, including the requisite master or mistress verbiage, pulling your forelock, bowing or curtseying, and backing out of the room. The results can be very funny, especially if carried into public or in front of the kids.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The worst thing we can do is to get into a rut. We may enjoy seeing our significant other as much as ever but the exhilarating anticipation has become normalized. We must guard against our comfortable life growing boring as well.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Keep in mind that the &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatestlovequotes.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Blove"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://greatestlovequotes.com/&quot;;&gt;love&lt;/a&gt; quotes&lt;/a&gt; we all seem to know are there to show us what love can be and not to criticize our relationship.  Certainly the fact remains that we all want a love like the love in the &lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.greatestlovequotes.com%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bquotes"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.greatestlovequotes.com&quot;;&gt;quotes&lt;/a&gt; about love&lt;/a&gt;.  However, that type of love is one that is cultivated instead of only stumbled upon.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Watch television together: not the dreary news but old Seinfeld or Lucy reruns which are just as funny as when they were made. The funny thing about laughing is that it can heal relationships so find ways that you two can laugh together. Tell stories about things that happened to you before you met and reminisce about the fun times you've had since you first became an item.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The good news about the fun of vacations is that they can be reproduced on a smaller scale.  A lunch or dinner date at a special place can be something we look forward to for a long happy week. A date to go bowling, or dancing, or golfing, can be set up several days in advance. Plan on when you are going to see that special movie or attend a concert. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;An event simply needs to be special; it doesn't have to be expensive. Plan a visit to the fast food chain where you had your first date. Take visits to local hotels to see which ones have the best free hors d'oeuvre at happy hour. Find a place that has art that you can comment on and have fun talking about it.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Give your love a little tingle by leaving note to come to a date. Explain to them that you eagerly await them. Pay special care to every detail of the date so that they will thoroughly enjoy themselves.  Make it a night to remember.  And when the date time comes, relax and enjoy the fact that you are with your mate and you are both able to relax together.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>