<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="df4c6fa81a3c32e914a76f5217aabc64">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3N5aWxhbWVyaWNhLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Bench top CNC&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Autoclaves ensure superior sterilization of medical instruments by wiping out pathogens, mold spores, bacteria, yeast and protozoa. They are perfect for prototyping and for almost any light duty industrial work. Many manufacturers, both large together with small, have gone to benchtop mills for their more compact production needs. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Benchtop mills have many outstanding features which were standard or optional. They only weigh about 260 pounds to enable them to be used on almost any surface table. They often contain identical ball bearing components to those found on larger and more expensive milling machines. Their design is compact but is professional in appearance and performance. They are very accurate pieces of equipment that could be depended on to complete assigned tasks with precision and efficiency. They can perform contouring with a 3 dimensional effect and a lot of models contain their own cooling system, making them safe and secure. CNC benchtop models can be operated from a desktop computer which contains graphic-specific software. Their digital controller has specialized sensors built right into it. And, finally, most benchtop manufacturers offer limited and extended warranties and supply excellent 24-hour customer service. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many home hobbyists go with a benchtop milling machine for their small projects. With this machine, they are able to easily work with many kinds of materials such as wood, plastic, aluminum, brass together with steel. Even though benchtop machines are small, they complete big! Anyone just beginning to use milling machines will find that benchtop models are a simple way to get started. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Benchtop table saws can save you a ton of time on the job site. They're much more accurate than the hand held circular variety. If you get a good model, they stand up to a lot of use. The problem with benchtops is accuracy. So, you have to know why you're buying it, and also if there are alternatives available. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Basically, there are four types of kitchen table saws, benchtop, contractor, cabinet, and hybrid. We won't talk about hybrid saws much, here. They're basically a hybrid of a contractor saw and a cabinet saw. Sort of an concerning saw. We will talk briefly about each of additional three. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Benchtops are designed to be use a table, the floor, a tailgate of a pickup, or even the ground. They're generally lightweight for a machine tool that this. About 40 to 80 lbs. You can carry these phones the job site, cut what you need to, then put them back up. They cost as little as $150, but for a reputable saw, you're going to have to spend double that will. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A contractor saw is basically a benchtop with legs. A lot of times contractor type machines get legs and wheels. Bosch makes a really nice contractor saw where the legs fold up automatically. Very impressive! Contractor saws are generally a little larger than benchtops. The table's a small larger, and there's more room between the blade and the fence--say something like 16 inches for the benchtop saw and 25 inches for any contractor saw. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As opposed to contractor together with benchtops, cabinet saws are not at all portable. They have to be heavy to be more precise. They're made for fine woodwork, furniture, and built-in cabinetry.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>