<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="251c5b4ad82754569272782d965e18df">			3) Door to Door Or Fatal To Terminal &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You cannot assume all car shipping services will ship the car to your dwelling. Some car shipping agencies only deliver to serious cities and towns but will deposit your car within a terminal. From there, you certainly will collect your car. There are some companies that costs additional fees for shipping to your dwelling. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In every case, make sure you ask your car shipping company whether they provide door to door shipping for terminal to fatal delivery. In most cases, terminal to terminal is actually cheaper. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4) Shipping Insurance &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ensure you have sufficient insurance coverage when shipping your car. I learned a great deal, especially about ways that i can protect myself together with my cars with uninsured motorist coverages. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Helpful &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some sort of Florida car shipping company will always are categorized in Florida laws because that is their home state. They should provide a consumer with copies of everything they have to know, including any rights and responsibilities. A company should try to answer any questions that a consumer might have. Florida is vastly different from the New York that i was used to, but as a result of Florida car shipping, my cars and I made it to my new home in one piece. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Shipping a Car? Beware! Recently, a number of false car shipping and vehicle transport websites have popped up across the internet. Some of the commonest scams involve fake trucking company websites which are not a company at all, rather, a scammer wanting to attract a victim. A user will come to the website to get an auto shipping insurance quote. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The online site may often look legit and is often built to reproduce a legit auto transportation company website. The user is then returned a very reasonable auto shipping insurance quote with instructions for payment. Once the user pays the auto transport truck never turns up and the user is out their money. This form of scam, however, is with relative ease to avoid. Here are some tips on identifying a scam vehicle shipping website: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Never use a site that recommends using a wire transfer. Legit vehicle shippers NEVER require wire transfer payment. Most car shipping agencies will accepts payment methods which offer comsumer protections, such as plastic cards. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Determine if the address in the address bar matches the name in the website. If it doesn't, that's a danger sign. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Search for Errors -- grammatical problems, typos, etc. If they're present, the site is likely the effort of a hasty scammer rather then an actual company. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Find a number listed for any site and call it. The downside to bigger car carriers is a speed at which people operate. Big car carriers may pickup and go away every vehicle on the trailer for a different location. Therefore, that may be about 7 to 10 pickups and go away. The safety of your car or truck on a bigger truck is very good. However, things may happen since a big car carrier has lots of vehicles loading and unloading so the likelihood of minor damage are improved. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Smaller vehicle carriers hold 1-6 cars at a time. These carriers tend to charge more since they have less cars to move. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uYXRpb253aWRldHJhbnNwb3J0c2VydmljZXMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;car shipping&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>