<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c5e805126c4c9d03fa09275cee49e350">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb3VudGludGVsLmNvbS93aHkvcHJvZHVjdC5waHA_" target="_blank"&gt;Silestone countertops&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jaWFjb3VudGVycy5jb20vcHJvZHVjdHMva2l0Y2hlbi13b3JrdG9wcy9zaWxlc3RvbmUtY291bnRlcnRvcHMv" target="_blank"&gt;Silestone prices&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaWxlc3RvbmVwcmljZXMuY29tL2Fib3V0LXNpbGVzdG9uZS8_" target="_blank"&gt;Silestone prices&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Is it time to renovate you kitchen? Do you need to renovate everything from the granite countertops to the appliances? Maybe you have your eye on those beautiful Hearth Kitchen cabinets. Deciding to renovate is the easy part, if you know your kitchen is out-of-date.  What you might not realize is how much renovating your kitchen will impact your family. I didn’t realize how much kitchen renovations impacted my family until after the renovations were complete. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When renovating your kitchen it’s import to understand the kitchen space. Can you knock out walls? When we started renovating my kitchen, I had a consultant tell me that if we knocked out a wall we could put a breakfast bar in place of the wall.  At the time, all I was thinking about was money, but in the end, I was convinced.  By opening up your kitchen, I learned, you prevent isolation from the rest of the house and the family. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The breakfast bar with granite countertops makes for a great gathering place, whether you are entertaining or spending time with family. We were able to knock out the wall that separated the kitchen and the dining room. The dining room opens up into the living room, so now when I’m cooking I can see all the activity. Everyone gathers around the breakfast bar that I often treat as a place for a buffet. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;One of the most important things to remember before renovating is contractors. Contractors can be a nightmare, so it’s extremely important to get find the best service providers.  We called Hearth Kitchen for our kitchen renovations, and I would recommend them to everyone. I was talking to an expert, which is important when you’re getting ready to spend a large amount of money on renovations. My consultant was able to walk me through the entire renovation process. Not to mention, I was able to stay within budget, which I hear is impossible.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>