<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="91cfd9a1b2c70d724d72a8ddc8743a9e">			According to February 5th message, in a consecutive six-game road trip, the Los Angeles Lakers, the team suffered defeat, coach Mike Brown - in the fourth quarter ate two technical fouls . Saihoubulang blame his cool behavior to drag on a Lakers team - Kobe Bryant pointed out that the causes of failure, he even praised some of the team bench, their performance.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before the team began the road trip, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWxlYnJvbi05" target="_blank"&gt;;Lebron 9&lt;/a&gt;; Black Light Blue Bryant once said rebounds away the key is to lay the results of the Lakers today, precisely on the boards lost eight, they let the opponents to grab as many as 18 offensive rebounds. &quot;It's always the old problem of this season, offensive rebounds. &quot; Bryant said, &quot;They have done a very good rebounding, many secondary and even third chance to attack, we must do better on rebounds compete. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWxlYnJvbi05LWJsYWNrLWxpZ2h0LWJsdWU_" target="_blank"&gt;;Lebron 9 Black Light Blue&lt;/a&gt;;&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A poor start to the fourth quarter the Lakers team, Lebron 9 opponents wave of 14 to 0 offensive climax to widen the gap, the critical moment or Kobe Bryant shot to Glenealy 9 to stabilize the situation, but unfortunately this can not help the team comeback. &quot;We must retain patient, more calm Black Light Blue &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpcWluZy5hcnRpY2lhbi5jb20vYmxvZy8yMDEyLzAzL25pa2UtbGVicm9uLTktYmxhY2stZ3JleS13aGl0ZS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Lebron 9&lt;/a&gt;;. &quot; Bryant said of the team's fourth quarter performance, &quot;We 've gone through this situation, this time to do is to insist, must concentrate on play strike in the control of defensive rebounds well, and gave the opponents too many second-chance opportunity.&quot;		</conversation>		<conversation id="680091302a6d00b7b589d03910b7719b">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/biqingchen/photo/photoid=48671694" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/181806279_6235255_48671694.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike is coming back strong with some interesting new looks for the ladies this holiday season. This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWFpci1mb3JjZS0xPyZhbXA7c29ydD0yMGEmYW1wO3BhZ2U9Mw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Force 1&lt;/a&gt;; Low Premium features a blend of nice materials on the upper, using Metallic Zinc leather on some sections with a herringbone patterned fabric covered by a floral design on the toe box and heel. A White midsole and laces and a gum outsole add the finishing touches to this sophisticated new women's look.Air Force 1 low shoes'color way consists of metallic zinc and a herringbone toebox and heel that features embroidered black roses. White midsole and laces play the only real contrasting color seeing as how the outsole matches the zinc upper. Using white shoe tougue AF1 logo, shoe laces and midsole to contrast with gum rubber outsole for traction and durablity.
&lt;br /&gt;;The actual, Air Force one is not just a pair of shoes, it is a kind of experience, and it is still a birthplace and the connected a culture of the bridge, and the culture and make it itself survive. This Womens &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLXdtbnMtYWlyLWZvcmNlLTEtbG93LXByZW1pdW0tbWV0YWxsaWMtemluYy13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Force 1 Metallic Zinc&lt;/a&gt;; shoe comes with the very cool design idea. First the super texture leather as the vamp material then take the metallic zinc as the base color shows very Metallic Zinc, the best wonderful place is the toe box and ankle strap decorated with the nice black flowers. Also you consider the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpcWluZy5hcnRpY2lhbi5jb20vYmxvZy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Force 1 Low Futura Matte Silver&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="79e6e7fcc31d484b110ea4fa177c8136">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/biqingchen/photo/photoid=48843105" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/181806279_15628458_48843105.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;JGoods has done it again. These sneakers are the first collaboration between JGoods and NikeiD. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bms_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk&lt;/a&gt;; High is featured in a fresh water colorway with a four color swirl pattern on the toe and lace guard. The King of the Jungles are finished with a set of JGoods laces and a lion head on the heel panel drawing inspiration from the Netherlands National Football Club.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Classic Nike Dunk High design let this pair of shoes in the fashion as well as a gentle temperament of type.The Nike Dunk Men craze has only grown bigger with the limited production on many colorways.Buy nike dunk shoes for yourself,and in the times of street culture,not only the men's shoes development toward individuation.Now we have this nike dunks shoes sale, you can get a big discount price and a free shipping to most english speaking countries.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstaGlnaC1jdXN0b20tamdvb2RzLWtpbmctb2YtdGhlLWp1bmdsZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Custom Jgoods King Of The Jungles&lt;/a&gt;; features black and blue color scheme to use on the entire upper construction. The colorway design concept is so well, the blue toe box and ankle strap matches to black mid panels and collar. While on the tips is colored by blue, grey, white and black.At the same time you can consider the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpcWluZy5hcnRpY2lhbi5jb20vYmxvZy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Iphone Nike Dunks&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="48087b467138246efcd060522ab644d4">			&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/181806279_7916099_48925634.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bms_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk&lt;/a&gt;; SB Low-Pro SB De La Soul was designed by De La Soul, and the vinyl hologram used on the heel of the shoe stems from their album cover of “3 feet High and Rising“. It is part of a 2 series release, the other being the Nike Dunk High Pro SB – De La Soul (baroque brown / altitude green). The idea of constructing the shoe from part vinyl was not typically used in the industry, so it helped to make the shoe an instant hit with sneakerheads, paving the way and introducing a new method to the art of shoe designing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstc2ItbG93LXByby1zYi1kZS1sYS1zb3Vs" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk Low De La Soul&lt;/a&gt;; Edition shoe features a simple design, sporting a cement-like print on the yellow panels, along with white on the upper, sides, and heel. Adding some depth to the subtle look are muticolored letters and pattern, which are seen on the toe and heel.Buying Nike Dunk shoes just easy by get in touch with diva-shoes.com. Our Nike Dunk store supply greatest selection of Nike Dunk series, high quality and best preices. For years, we stick to our our great mission, which is to make our valued customers satisfied with both products and customer service(&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpcWluZy5hcnRpY2lhbi5jb20vYmxvZy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Apple Green Black Nike Dunk&lt;/a&gt;;).		</conversation>		<conversation id="eb54903ac4bbedca1678b374a88a0808">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/biqingchen/photo/photoid=49081067" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/181806279_7622170_49081067.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here’s the first good photo of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bms/JmFtcDtzb3J0PTIwYSZhbXA7cGFnZT0z" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk&lt;/a&gt;; Mid Pro SB “Patagonia,” release date scheduled for December of this year. As you’d expect based on that perfect palette—brown leather overlays, green textile inlays, beige suede Swoosh, pink laces—the shoe looks even better in photos than it did in the catalog. Stick around for more photos as they become available.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A few new shots of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kaXZhLXNob2VzLmNvbS9uaWtlLWR1bmstbWlkLXByby1zYi1wYXRhZ29uaWE_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike SB Dunk Mid Pro Patagonia&lt;/a&gt;;hit the internet today pitting the rustic looking sneaker against a few seasonal elements. The shoes look particularly at home amongst the outdoor backdrop with their noble green canvas upper and brown nubuck as well as metallic gold suede. Nike SB has a Dunk Mid that has a stylish, yet rugged appeal. Here are new images of the outdoor-inspired Nike Dunk Mid Pro Patagonia. Although it’s a Nike Dunk Mid the boot-like metal eyelet, earth-tone colors, and mixture of materials gives the Nike SB Dunk Mid Pro a hiking boot feel.Recommend;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zbmVha2VyZnJlYWtlci5jb20vYmlxaW5nY2hlbi8xMzM2NDYwODI1Lw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk Svsm Lebron James&lt;/a&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>