<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="bb7c015b3ea40a3c943bbf2ccfd71dd5">			This year, I joined the school Cantonese Club founded by a grade twelve student. I choose this club because I was quite interested in the Cantonese culture and I wanted to know more about it. The basic activities are the Cantonese lessons that taught us simple vocabulary and sentences. At first, I felt quite difficult because it was an entire new language, although it was related to Mandarin in some ways. I can’t even pronounce a single word well at the very beginning and it really discouraged me to continue on. However I didn’t give up at last and instead, I worked harder and put much more effort on it. As a result, my pronunciation of Cantonese became the best one in the whole the club in the end of the year. From this process, I learnt how to achieve a goal through hard working and careful planning. The experience of Cantonese Club told me that as long as I put a lot effort in the work, I can get equal payback from it.
&lt;br /&gt;;   Besides Cantonese Club, I also joined the Math Club this year because I was looking forward to taking some of those math competitions. The first thing I did was to get myself ready for the coming test. My way of preparation was to do a lot of exercises and I spent one hour a day to review for the test in the week before the upcoming test. It was a boring and long process to do those works but I still found it interesting to do. When I could exactly experience my progress in math, I felt so proud of myself. When I get a grade in the math competition, I felt a great sense of achievement. These competitions practiced my mathematic skills and my ability of focusing all my attention on one subject.
&lt;br /&gt;;   These club activities not only made my school life more colorful but also practiced my abilities. I enjoyed my life in Grand Canadian Academy with those various clubs a lot.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2e33872f21fe95e9e7b04c41b043761">			During a weekend, I went to Hello Italy and tried some Italian food with my friends. We decided to try this restaurant because it looks great on the magazine and we haven’t eaten any classical Italian food in Nanjing yet. It did take us a long time to find the restaurant since it was located on a really small street. When we reached there, it was almost afternoon. There weren’t many guests in the restaurant and the environment was quite quiet inside. I ordered pasta as my main course and we also ordered a pizza together. The chef was so quick that all the dishes we ordered were on the table within ten minutes. After finishing my meal, I found I was pretty satisfied with the pasta but not the pizza. The pizza was too thick and hard to chew easily; also the flavor of the cheese cover was too light. I prefer thinner pizza with more thick cheese. In all, I think Hello Italy is a good restaurant worth going.
&lt;br /&gt;;  On another holiday, I went to Henry’s House with my parents for lunch. We chose Henry’s House simply because it was really close to our home and we were not willing to drive for a long time to search for another restaurant. Unlike Hello Italy, the environment in Henry’s House was much noisier and there more twice guests in Henry’s House than in Hello Italy. This time I ordered one of the most popular foods in Henry’s House, the sirloin steak. The steak tasted so delicious that I finished it in a relatively much shorter time. Most steaks from restaurants in Nanjing are too hard even I ask for medium and some even taste like a piece of wood. I strongly recommend others to try this restaurant.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9b12e98ed0b8e60912aa7ca837630c53">			I am not that kind of active person and actually I am a little bit lazy so I didn’t like doing sports regularly. To live in a healthier way, I decided to get an exercise which was running with my dog for thirty minutes everyday.
&lt;br /&gt;;  I had a good start and I enjoyed running in the garden to breathe the fresh air. However I’m not that kind of person who continues on doing one thing. After a few days, I have already become tired of running every morning, especially on cold mornings. I was not even willing to move out of my bed so I just wanted to give up. When I became lazy again, my parents blamed on me and told me that I have to be persist in doing things or I won’t be successful in the future. Their words encouraged me and every morning, I started running with my dog again. Whenever I wanted to give up, I thought of those words my parents told me. Now, running has already become one of my best habits. It makes my life much healthier than before and this was my original goal for running.
&lt;br /&gt;;  I also joined badminton class to exercise my body too. I played in the school gym with my classmates. At first, my skill was so terrible that I even didn’t know how to serve a ball. In ten hits, I usually could only get three hits on the shuttlecock. I thought I was hopeless but my classmates helped me get out of this situation. They taught me how to play and urged me to practice playing badminton from time to time. With their help, my badminton skill developed quickly and I can play as well as most of them, now. From this physical activity, I learnt how to find help, when I can’t solve the problem by myself.
&lt;br /&gt;;  I also played table tennis and performed gym class this. After doing all those healthy exercises for over several months, I became not only healthier but also more confident in doing other things such as speech or presentation. Physical activities practiced both my body and my spirit. Even My bad habit of doing things lazily has been changed to doing things harder so I consider that exercise is really good for us.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>