<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="fe257e6428390ed0ddf694c5ef60ea66">			As one of the biggest contributing factor for economic development in any part of the world particularly the producers of cocoa. Cocoa as the main component for chocolates and other creamy and healthy foods the producers of it continue to produce a high quality cocoa bean. In the year 2002, according to studies the production of cocoa are very low and that’s why producers need to give the lowest price they can to consumers in order to sell their products but as they give attention to their respected farms and harvest as many cocoa the prices is now on the hot pot where they hit the global market.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For the known producers of cocoa this can be the biggest challenge for them. This country was known for their greatest production of fruits that can give a high satisfaction to their consumers, it is also where the famous Shea butter being produced. In some areas in Western Africa, the soil and land are very much abundant for nutrients to help grow a cocoa tree. Together with the location and other environmental factor that helps yield a healthy crop.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ivory Coast was the largest and biggest cocoa producer, for others who may not know they became the largest producer because they intend to produce a lot of cocoa and helps Ivory Coast in the development. The other top three aside from Ivory Coast are Ghana, Nigeria and Cameroon.  Given this volume for at least 75% of the production, cocoa that being produced in Ivory coast are commonly used in chocolate production while cocoa’s form Ghana are mostly used in Europe and its prized is consistent in quality.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As the season will hit the harvest period, the farmers will see to it that every cocoa they got is perfectly ripen and the quality of it is not only sold out in the market but also gives the expectations of every consumer that spend a wide variety of money to enjoy his cup of hot chocolate. Not only to a single consumer but also to the big companies they supply their cocoa product. As economy continues to rise the cocoa still maintains its position as one of the leading factor in economic growth.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the latest study held last 2010, a list is being shown how amazingly a cocoa production increases. As the list shows at the year 1998 to 2000 in the world market the production is 2220 and when 2010 is being reached the production increases at 2,994. The growth rate continue to increase, the prices continue the rise but with this changes in the economy the value of money needs to be increased in order to cope up the producers expectations.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign" style="text-align: right;"&gt;;Source: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xpZGl0eXRyYWRlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.soliditytrade.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.soliditytrade.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="ab3ed897ca2d383fc447043a49c0eea9">			Shea oil is widely becoming highly recommended and one of the best selling skin care products nowadays. Shea butter is used in Africa as cooking oil, contrary to other countries where it is widely used as a cosmetic ingredient.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is widely used as salve and moisturizer. Because of its anti-drying, softening and shielding effects, shea oil is an efficient ingredient in soaps, sun care products, hand creams, body massage products, anti-wrinkle creams and for hair care applications.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tama Shea oil, high in essential fatty acids, unsaponifiable (7-8%), and Vitamins A, E, and F, is efficient in providing skin with all the essential elements for good balance, elasticity and tone. It cares for the skin, especially skin repair and soothing action. It rejuvenates old cells and brings back elasticity and tone.  It easily melts at body temperature and rapidly penetrates deep down the skin without leaving a greasy feeling.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tama shea oil moisturizes dry skin, helps prevent ashy skin, chapping, rashes and tough skin especially feet and elbows. It acts as a good ingredient for hair care where 0.5-1% addition in a conditioner or using the shea oil directly to hair may help enhance gloss and moisture retention in the hair. It is also applied before swimming to protect hair against chlorine and sea salt. It prevents bed sores and ensures continued suppleness and moisture of elderly skin. It can be used as a sunscreen to prevent the UV rays from penetrating the skin. It helps aging skin tissue to firm up and protect against wrinkles and fine lines. And shea oil is recommended as base oil for massage therapy when it is blended.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Produced by Shekaf in Northern Ghana, it can be used for direct personal care usage and also serve as raw material for homemade body and personal care product manufacturers. It is obtained by fractioning shea butter to separate its liquid and solid properties while preserving all the valuable characteristics of shea butter. It maintains the integrity of the stratum corneum and helps protect the epidemis. Since shea oil has a low melting point that leads to easy creation of emulsions with no adverse crystallization, it is recommended for use in liquid formulations.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The product will be available in bulk and small bottles of 500ml. You must ensure that you are buying Shea oil from a highly regarded supplier, one that is capable of giving you original shea oil. Tama Shea produces original Shea on their online website.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xpZGl0eXRyYWRlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Source: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.soliditytrade.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.soliditytrade.com&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="b72b49871a15932b11d9794ccf4818a0">			Ever tried a natural black soap?  If not, you have missed one of the best kept skin care secrets of our time.  Imagine having your complexion that makes you want to stop and look every time you pass a mirror.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Forget about those harsh astringents and toners, soaps with coarse scrubs and high alcohol-based products.  Treat your skin with african black soap and these simple steps and you’ll be on your way to perfect skin.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Step 1: To use organic black soap for a shower or bath, wet sponge or wash cloth and rub the organic black soap on the sponge or wash cloth. Lather up with natural black soap and use shea moisturizer or shea butter to moisturize your clean lustrous skin after a shower or bath.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Step 2: Wash your face once or twice a day and use natural black soap. Or better yet, give yourself a facial with natural black soap. Prepare a small towel, dip it into some warm water, squeeze out and place the towel over your face for about 10 seconds or until the towel goes cold. Repeat several times. When you are done, wash your beautiful face with natural black soap. Don’t forget parts behind the ears, under the chin and neck and rinse with warm water. Finally, moisturize with a moisturizer. Acne, blackheads, whiteheads, pimples, blemishes, rashes, breakouts and discolorations will eventually fades away.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Step 3: Wet your hair and rub organic black soap in until it lathers. Wash hair, rinse &amp; repeat the process until hair is clean.  When you are done, use regular hair conditioner.
&lt;br /&gt;;To store unused organic black soap, place it in a cool dry area wrapped in saran wrap or in a zip lock bag or in a plastic container.  It has natural glycerin that will naturally absorb moisture from the air and become darker and softer when left exposed. Do not leave African black soap in water. If you are storing African black soap in a soap dish, make sure that the soap dish is well drained. If it is to be stored on a surface, make sure surface does not have a paddle of water.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Aside from using natural black soap for your skin, it will be an added bonus if you will avoid smokes and cigarettes. Proper nourishments will also do well for your skin which includes eating healthy and nutritious foods and minimize eating junk foods. Enough rest and sleep, for at least eight hours is very important. Prolonged sun exposure especially if you have not applied your sunscreen should also be avoided. In addition, be sure to clean your face thoroughly at night, removing every trace of makeup. This will be efficient especially with the use of African black soap.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use black soaps on your skin and not imitation soaps that have chemicals and coloring added to them. Pure black soaps are available at an international grocery store, African marketplace or online. It comes as a liquid, bar or in an unformed lump.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=Source: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.soliditytrade.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.soliditytrade.com&lt;/a&gt;;]Source: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.soliditytrade.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;www.soliditytrade.com&lt;/a&gt;;[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>