<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d410a5bb4cc540df6b26712a1d7b9555">			Dianabol (D-bol), or it's off-brand term Methandrostenolone, can be viewed as the grandaddy of most anabolic steroids, and the majority of musclemen that have chosen steroids got their initial start with D-bol. The chemical was originally designed by Dr John Ziegler and released by the Ciba Corporation in the late 1950's. Dr Ziegler designed the steroid after speaking to some Russian strength training trainers as soon as Russian bodybuilders suddenly began dominating the sport in the early 1950's. As an anabolic steroid it's chemically an offshoot of the male hormone testosterone. Because of this it offers both anabolic (muscle tissue building) and androgenic (masculinizing) properties. Since it's initial use Four decades ago, D-bol has quickly become perhaps the most preferred and sought-after substances in body building.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Methandrostenolone was very prevalent in fitness centers during the 70's. In fact several tales continue to be spoke of the tiny blue pills being sold at the main counters of the bigger bodybuilding gymnasiums. D-bol is among the most well known anabolic steroid ever developed and many expert bodybuilders, who are ready to talk, have admitted to using it in their routines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The popularity of Dianabol was ironically the main factor to its drop. Throughout the 80's, Ciba stopped the original D-bol after the Food and drug administration concluded that the beneficial purposes were small in comparison to the rampant use by athletes and the amounts that quite a few body builders had to have. But generic methandrostenolone has not been out of creation. It's reported that the Russians had become quite fond of D-bol and Russian D-bol has become one of the popular variants of the chemical on the black-market.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Evidently, D-bol, being rather androgenic will produce unwanted effects. To begin with the chemical can be very estrogenic in certain consumers. Gynecomastia (aggravation of the breast region) is generally a problem throughout use, and could happen somewhat early in the routine (specifically if the person used high dosage amounts). For this reason a lot of muscle builders add an estrogen blocker such as Nolvadex, to their cycles. Another beauty unwanted effect is water retention. This is a worry for aggressive weight lifters, as it causes a notable reduction in muscle definition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Besides gynecomastia and water retention D-bol may produce such androgenic unwanted effects as oily complexion, acne and body/facial hair growth. There is also the potential of increasing hair loss in people genetically susceptible for this condition.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although common as an off-season mass-building compound, Dianabol is not usually used in pre-contest drug cycles. This is because it heavily aromatizes to estrogen making fat loss tough. The chemical is also known to cause a large amount of water retention - another property making it unpopular as a tournament substance. To get around this serious weightlifters usually stack it with steroids such as nandrolone.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The standard dosage used by muscle builders is around 15-40mg/day (three to eight, 5 milligram capsules). Newbies do not require above 15-20mg every day because their anabolic steroid receptors have not been subjected to the drug before and will endure remarkable results using smaller doses spanning a 6-8 week interval. As an alternative an injectable for example Deca-Durabolin or Primabolan-Depot could be combined with the cycle.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dbolcycle.net"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dbolcycle.net&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>