<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b8ddc165fbf6c132c9f4750b984a321b">			Prestige RADIATORS UK specialize in all kinds of radiators to suite your BATHROOM &amp;amp;#38; KITCHEN like contemporary radiators, vertical and column radiators for sale
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Different from the classic style of heavy cast iron, Central heating radiators are now made of stainless steel or aluminium. Central heating radiators are varied from their size and shapes. Customer can choose modern types in different sizes as Quinn Radiators and Stelrad Softline Radiators are available in plenty of lengths and heights. Myson Premier and Henrad Radiators are the compact types obtainable in slim and unobtrusive appearance. Some Prorad Radiators are made according to room sizes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Modern central heating radiators are usually light weight and easily installable. They are even long lasting because of the noncorrosive material used to give them a better look and to merge with room decoration. This type of central heating radiators has low maintenance due to the use of new techniques and better designs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Buy Central heating radiators online at Prestige Radiators UK. If you have any queries, please feel free to contact our expert team on phone number 0844 884 2942 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Buy Online at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prestigeradiators.co.uk%2Fcentral-heating-radiators%2Flow-surface-temperature-lst-radiator-pack-66.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.prestigeradiators.co.uk/central-heating-radiators/low-surface-temperature-lst-radiator-pack-66.html&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Website - &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.prestigeradiators.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.prestigeradiators.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="202fce59b25ebfa0aae14bacb58ec6f0">			One of the best purchases I ever made was to buy an Electric Blanket for my bed!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the dark nights, autumnal chills and winter snaps rapidly approaching, I get a warm sense of anticipation knowing I am able to snuggle down into my bed, and have instant warmth generated from my treasured 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Electric Blanket.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Electric Blankets come in 4 separate sizes designed to fit any size of bed, single, double, king size and super king size.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The way Electric Blankets work is that they provide warmth by integrating an internal electrical heating device.  The Blanket is used over your top bed sheet and you can control the amount of heat that is generated by using the temperature control buttons. The double Electric Blankets have a choice of single or dual control, with the king size and super king size ones all having dual control. The great advantage of the dual controls are that by having controls at each side of the Blanket, you can control the temperature at each side of the bed, giving each of you the right amount of heat for your side of the bed!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are concerned about the safety issues with an Electric Blanket then don’t be!  All quality Electric Blankets now operate on a much lower voltage, normally around only 24 volts, as opposed to the older models that used to require between 110-240 volts. The modern day Electric Blanket contains an overheat protection safety feature that will automatically turn off the Blanket if it becomes too hot.  The newer quality models also come with rheostats to measure the total heat generated not only by the Blanket, but also by human body heat.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will find Electric Blankets will save you money on heating Bills as they require little electricity to operate and provide centralised heating quickly, without you having to heat up the rest of the room or the rest of the house!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An often overlooked advantage of the Electric Blanket is that it is of course portable.  You can virtually use it anywhere in the house!  If you wish to watch a movie downstairs on the sofa and would like to save a few £’s on the central heating bills, then consider investing in a second Electric Blanket!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The elderly or wheelchair- bound individuals also find them an invaluable comfort, as they can help ward off chills and give them an extra degree of warmth that able bodied people take for granted.  Many Nursing Homes and Residential Homes purchase Electric Blankets for their residents just for this reason alone.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The most popular selling versions of the quality Electric Blankets tend to be the reputable brands such as Morphy Richards, Serenity, Bliss, Dreamland and Tranquility.  There are more brands around, but as these tend to be the market leaders, then hundreds of thousands of people surely cannot be wrong!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Quite astonishingly, the remarkable growth in the Electric Blankets market has also led to some spin-off products entering the market, such as Heat Pads and Foot Warmers.  These are obviously cheaper than the full Electric Blankets, and are designed to concentrate heat in one particular area of the body and tend to be used to relieve aliments for certain parts of the body.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Consider investing in an Electric Blanket and you will find this is one of the best autumn/winter purchases you will ever make. Once tried, you will never be without one!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choose from massive range of Electric Blanket having different options like electric blanket double, Single Electric blanket, King Size Electric Blankets and lots more at Prestige Radiators, competitive rates with next day delivery.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Website - &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcmVzdGlnZXJhZGlhdG9ycy5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Buy Electric Blanket&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>