<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="f886f197a0c203f7f16a4b825087a395">			&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin&lt;/a&gt; The burly, bipolar man who held a Florida school board at gunpoint was frustrated and broke. He was a troubled ex-con with an interest in anarchy, and when his wife was fired from her teaching job and their benefits ran out, he went to the board meeting and said he was prepared to die.Clay Duke killed himself Tuesday after firing at the board members, missing them by mere inches, and exchanging a volley of gunfire with a security guard. A day later, his wife tearfully talked about the man she loved, calling the 56-year-old father a &quot;;gentle giant.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin pumps&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin pumps&lt;/a&gt; The entire shooting was captured by local television stations, and the video was posted on the Internet and broadcast on TV throughout the day. His Facebook page, which was public until late Wednesday afternoon, revealed a man who was fascinated with the movie &quot;;V for Vendetta&quot;; — which depicts the same symbol that Duke spray painted onto the wall just before he took out his gun.As board members gave television interviews about the harrowing experience, a sad and troubling portrait of Duke emerged.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin black&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin black&lt;/a&gt; He also quoted the final passage from Percy Shelley's &quot;;Masque of Anarchy&quot;;: &quot;;Rise like lions after slumber/In unvanquishable number/Shake your chains to earth, like dew/Which in sleep had fall'n on you/Ye are many-they are few.&quot;;Duke had no Facebook friends — although by Wednesday afternoon, thousands of people responded to his earlier postings, many of them critical of Tuesday's shooting. Others were more sympathetic, saying that Duke was driven to madness because of the difficult economy &lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin sandals&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin sandals&lt;/a&gt;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9c854d31d6119e13484d73908e2e9c9e">			&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin&lt;/a&gt; A senior U.S. official says embattled Ivory Coast President Laurent Gbagbo, who has refused to cede power after an election defeat, has been given a &quot;;finite amount of time&quot;; to step down or face sanctions. The comments came after the political standoff in the West African country turned violent Thursday.A senior official here says Mr.  Gbagbo has been given what amounts to an international ultimatum to step aside and that diplomats believe the incumbent president - in power for a decade - has gotten the message.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin pumps&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin pumps&lt;/a&gt; But the senior State Department official, who spoke to reporters on terms of anonymity, said there is &quot;;strong unanimity&quot;; among concerned parties including the United States, France, the African Union, and the West African regional grouping ECOWAS that he must yield.The official said Gbagbo has a finite amount of time, a matter of days he said, to make the &quot;;right decision&quot;; and that if he fails to do so the United States and others are prepared to follow-through with sanctions against him and close associates.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin black&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin black&lt;/a&gt; Crowley said a rocket-propelled grenade struck the outer perimeter of the U.S. embassy in Abidjan, causing minor damage but no injuries. He said the State Department is considering an evacuation of non-essential U.S. personnel from Ivory Coast but that no final decision had been made.The senior official who spoke here said Mr. Gbagbo would have to step down and leave the country to avoid threatened sanctions.He declined to say where he might go but said Mr. Gbagbo has &quot;;multiple homes in multiple countries&quot;; and has the &quot;;opportunity to avail himself of any one of them &lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin sandals&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin sandals&lt;/a&gt;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="af8d61c8f9e4c88f2956498c730fe329">			&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin&lt;/a&gt; When he died last year, Jeffry Picower left behind a multibillion-dollar fortune – and the complicated legacy of a life and career that won praise and engendered -suspicion.Picower was hailed for his generosity to philanthropic causes and scrutinised by regulators for his business dealings.He was a self-made billionaire known for his investment savvy. In a letter this week, Goldman Sachs described him as a “valued client” who had generated returns of more than $2bn over the past three decades. Yet he entrusted his money to two of the most notorious figures in recent Wall Street history, Bernard Madoff and Ivan Boesky.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin pumps&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin pumps&lt;/a&gt; While he sought to keep a low profile, rarely granting interviews, the spotlight would inevitably return – even in death, as his estate this week agreed to hand over $7.2bn to the victims of the Madoff Ponzi scheme.Picower first invested with Mr Madoff 35 years ago after being introduced to him by an accountant. Like Mr Madoff, not all of his dealings remained below the radar. A New York-born lawyer and accountant, he gained renown in the 1980s as the largest individual investor in Mr Boesky’s biggest arbitrage fund, according to Den of Thieves, James B Stewart’s account of the Wall Street scandals involving Mr Boesky and Michael Milken.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin black&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin black&lt;/a&gt; At the time of his death, Picower’s Goldman account held $4.5bn in unrealised gains, including $2.2bn in Apple stock. William Zabel, his lawyer, said it is not clear how much money the estate will hold after the settlement. In accordance with his will, the estate will establish a new charitable foundation, he said.Picower left $200m to his wife, $25m to his daughter and $25m to MIT’s Picower Institution for Learning and Memory. To everyone else, there remains an abundance of questions.Copyright The Financial Times Limited 2010. You may share using our article tools. Please don't cut articles from FT.com and redistribute by email or post to the web &lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin sandals&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin sandals&lt;/a&gt;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="190cf507df11e98f7caf68b411065a5f">			&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin&lt;/a&gt; United Nations Security Council efforts to calm tensions between North and South Korea were stalled as China refused to support a resolution condemning the North for a Nov. 23 attack on a South Korean-held island.China declines to join a majority of the Security Council members in condemning the North Korean attack, according to a diplomat present at the meeting who spoke with reporters on condition of anonymity. The Chinese mission to the UN didn’t respond to a telephone message requesting comment. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin pumps&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin pumps&lt;/a&gt; The North says it won’t recognize a sea boundary drawn up by U.S. officials commanding UN troops at the end of the Korean War in 1953. It says the sea around the islands belongs to the North, and has vowed massive retaliation if the South again fires into the sea around the islands. The U.S. has about 28,500 troops in South Korea.The Security Council must “help launch diplomatic activity with a view to resolving all issues of dispute between the two Korean sides by political and diplomatic means,” Russia’s ambassador to the world body, Vitaly Churkin, said in a statement late yesterday. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin black&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin black&lt;/a&gt; South Korea’s new defense minister vowed Dec. 3 that his country would reply with moves including airstrikes if North Korea makes another attack.“I will mobilize all combat capabilities available to severely punish the enemy,” Kim Kwan Jin, former chairman of the South’s Joint Chiefs of Staff, said at a confirmation hearing. “I will surely use planes. This is a matter of self- defense.”South Korean President Lee Myung Bak on Nov. 29 apologized for what he called the military’s weak response to North Korea’s Nov. 23 shelling &lt;a href=&quot;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.newchristianlouboutinshoes.com&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; title=&quot;;christian louboutin sandals&quot;;&gt;christian louboutin sandals&lt;/a&gt;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>