<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="5365befca982a752444a3fe3614b1597">			A gp locum can be a very fulfilling  career and even a  curse, based on the way you look at it. There  are some gps who wanted to switch careers, after a few months of being a gp locum. However there are many &lt;a  href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.nexopia.com%2Fusers%2Foliverbulloc622%2Fblog%2F1-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-being-a-gp-locum"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.nexopia.com/users/oliverbulloc622/blog/1-advantages-and-disadvantages-of-being-a-gp-locum&lt;/a&gt;;]gp locums[/url] who love this profession and look forward to another  satisfying day of  work.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The reality is that it depends on the  aptitude of a person and how well he/she is able to  adjust to this career.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are a gp locum, then here are a few hurdles you could face in your profession:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. You don’t have a fixed consulting room and you have to adjust  to the one you have as soon as possible otherwise there is a danger of being criticised even though the fault may not be  entirely yours.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Sometimes, there are no machines at all and the gp has to bring his own. Imagine how stressful it can  be when you are about to examine someone and the equipment doesnt work due to low or no batteries at  all. Under these circumstances, all you can do is to talk to the gp partners and make sure they know the difficulties you are facing and the steps they ought to take to help you out.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. You have to walk into an  unknown practice to see unknown patients. You dont know their  health background because the documents are missing and you have no clue  how/where to find them. For someone who is new to this profession, this situation could be an  absolute nightmare.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now, I am not saying that all &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibG9nc3Rlci5jb20vbWF5bmFycmRzODMvYWR2YW50YWdlcy1hbmQtZGlzYWR2YW50YWdlcy1vZi1iZWluZy1hLWdwLWxvY3Vt" target="_blank"&gt;;locum  gps&lt;/a&gt;; have to work in these types of situations. Now, this doesnt  mean that whatever practice you join is going to be like this. I just want you to take note of the down sides a gp locum has to face one or more times in his  profession.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But being a gp locum is not about facing  difficulties and to be able to get used to  difficult situations. There are numerous things to like about being a  locum gp and I have listed some of these here:  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. You will have the freedom to walk away from a practice if you dont like the way they work. Actually, I even know a few locum gps who decided to leave the practice  because the gp partners didnt care about the patients at all.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. In locum work you choose the exact kind of life you want to live. You could work as a gp 3 or 4 days a week and play golf  for the rest of the week. Or maybe you could work as a gp for six months and go for a world tour the rest of the year.  You get to choose.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Different practices have different procedures of working -  They have  different machines, different softwares and different ways of recording consultations. This way you get to learn a lot more and become more useful as a  gp locum.  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Being a gp locum need not be  a stressful thing. You can have a very successful and  enjoyable career as a gp locum.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>