<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="333484ed2b1beb2a13ad8a6a2fc8a829">			Melt the butter in a flame-proof casserole and lightly brown the rabbit joint capsules on both sides. Lift out the rabbit joints and set them aside. Peel and finely cut one onion and garlic clove cloves to taste. Take away the rind from the bread and roughly chop it. Fry the bacon in the butter for a few minutes add the red onion and garlic and cook for a low heat until this onion is soft. Return the Rabbit joints to the casserole, cover with a detailed fitting lid and cook on the very low heat to get a further thirty minuets. Take away the casserole from the heat and stir inside double cream. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cover again using a close fitting lid and throw the main lot into an oven preheated to about 180c. Cook for forty five minuets.. you might like to stir the casserole once or twice during the cooking period. Serve straight from the casserole (mind you don't burn the kitchen table)! Boiled potatoes and the usual green vegetables match this dish. You might want to throw a few bread croutons excessive as well. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get pleasure from. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Rabbit meat is eaten globally. Rabbits have been raised since Roman times and wild rabbits have been completely hunted since man could throw a spear. So just why is it that some countries have such a problem eating domesticated rabbit? Because you close your eyes and see that happy Easter Bunny with the bright coat and painted Easter eggs and you simply can't bear to kill and eat some of those beautiful New Zealand Whites. It is actually called the Easter Bunny Syndrome and is common in the countries of The united states particularly. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're not opposed to eating rabbit meat, raising rabbits to remain used for meat, or raising these phones be sold to some other rabbit breeders, the USDA has extensively studied and discovered that rabbit meat is most of the healthiest mean known to man. It is nominal in cholesterol and fat and may be added to most recipes that demand skinless chicken, pork, or even veal. A typical fryer dimensions rabbit is between 8 together with 10 weeks old based on the breed, and should ponder 3-5 pounds [1350-2250 grams] in weight. A well-managed doe can produce as many as three hundred pounds [150 KG] of meat a year. That can be quite a freezer stuffer for sauces, stews, BBQ, and casseroles. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before deciding to do this quest, the breeder have to do research for laws governing the raising and hurting of rabbits for food on their area. The best meat producing breeds that fare well within their temperature zone is an additional consideration because rabbits do not tolerate the heat perfectly for long periods and frequently require air conditioning. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If a person is considering a family operation to stock the fridge, they must weigh your start-up costs of bunnie farming and the roi they will see over the first year or so of production. The breeder must be ready to commit to health and safety standards and all sanitation regulations for the health of the people using this meat, and they must be aware of diseases that make a difference to rabbits that make their own meat unusable for food. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2V2ZW50cy5yb2xhbmRmcm9zdDkyNC5wb2RvbWF0aWMuY29tL2VudHJ5LzIwMTItMDMtMzBUMjFfMDJfNDgtMDdfMDA_" target="_blank"&gt;;Hunting Rifle Scopes – Great Rifle Scopes on the Market Now&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3JvbGFuZGZyb3N0OTI0Njk5Ni5ibG9nLmhyLzIwMTIvMDMvMTYzMDQ2OTc1NC9sZXVwb2xkLXZ4Mi1ncmVhdC1yaWZsZS1zY29wZXMtb24tdGhlLW1hcmtldC1ub3cuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Hunting Rifle Scopes – Best Scopes on the Market Currently&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="ce57311eb8caefbb24f1fe237f6ef5f8">			Those long hours on stand should give you an idea of the location where the squirrels are hanging or at the least some good places the location where the acorns are plentiful. Squirrels may be using that area now even if they were not early in the year. This is also a good time to reverse this scenario and use your day a field to locate some terrific stand locations for following deer season. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A comfortable fanny or backpack is important for squirrel hunting. You need enough room in your home for your calls should you use them. A thermos of hot coffee if you drink it and a book if you read. A lunch is important in cold weather if you plan to hunt for hours on end. Late season usually means not many hunters a field with deer season over the fear of ruining someone's hunt or getting shot by one of those &quot;hunters&quot; that can't discover a method to tell the difference between a ten point buck and an out of shape hillbilly tromping in the woods and smoking a swisher sweet. Anyway this is the time of year, especially on public lands that you can wander freely and discover your hunting area while providing and yours with some great game for the dinner table. If you do wander deep in the woods, far from that truck, that thermos involving coffee, lunch and a good book or magazine comes in handy as the bushytails tend to go inactive sometime in daytime and unless you plan on trekking back to the truck to wait for the evening feed then these items will make your wait even more enjoyable. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Late season usually means the breeding season is now over and squirrels usually don't travel far from home as they are nourished by the stockpile of nut products they buried in missed fall. For this reason position and stalk is usually the best way to harvest these tasty critters. Squirrels can be hard to see now because they are digging inside leaves for previously hidden nuts. Since the nuts are buried close together and in large quantities movement is kept to your minimum therefore adding on the difficulties in spotting them. You may hear a squirrel rummaging in the leaves, if they are generally dry, and even though you know so you see just ahead you just cannot notice. A good set with low power binoculars come in handy for spotting squirrels which were digging. The leaves they are moving in search of nuts tend to surround them making it even more difficult to see them. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This time of year squirrels are very skittish, as breeding subsides and searching pressure continues, sneaking up on a squirrel takes patience. Late season tactics in many cases does not include calling. The squirrels are just too close to their den and tend to bolt right to their hole in the first sight or sound of danger. There are generally times, during late season that the call may help as soon as used sparingly. If you can hear a squirrel excavating for nuts but just can't see it you can hit the distress call very gently. At this close range this doesn't take much. The desired effect would be a quick jump onto the side of the tree as it glances back at where the sound originated. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]Leupold's VX-2 Scope – Best Rifle Scopes on the Market Today[/url], &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xldXBvbGR2eDJzY29wZXM0OS53ZXRwYWludC5jb20vcGFnZS9IdW50aW5nK1JpZmxlK1Njb3BlcyslRTIlODAlOTMrR3JlYXQrUmlmbGUrU2NvcGVzK29uK3RoZStNYXJrZXQrTm93" target="_blank"&gt;;Leupold's VX-2 Scope – Great Scopes on the Market Today&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>