<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="80edfa7bdc8f4e66d2e7ae00aec8444a">			Improving the way your skin looks will do a lot for your overall appearance. Healthy skin enables you to appear younger, and it lessens the need to wear unnecessary makeup. However, if you want healthy skin, you need to care for it. Some of the information provided here will help you take great care of your skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always apply sunscreen before going outside. Even on cloudy days, there could still be harmful rays penetrating from behind the clouds. If you do not like the consistency of the sunscreen, try applying the sunscreen using a sponge meant for makeup application. Doing this aids the sunscreen's absorption into your skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can take care of your skin inside out by eating healthy. Surprisingly, foods like french fries and chocolates are not a major cause of acne. However, your diet can contribute to skin problems in other ways. You should eat foods such as fruits, whole grains, nuts and vegetables. Whole foods contain vitamins and minerals you need to get rid of bad skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do your best to take stress out of your life by taking time to relax. Skin problems are often caused by stress in your life. Work on getting rid of emotional stressors, as well as environmental ones, to clear up your skin. Having less stress in your life will be beneficial to the rest of your life too.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While many people desire a nice tan because they think it looks healthy, the tanning process is actually very damaging and has really bad side effects. Safe tanning involves self-tanning lotion, not sunbathing or sitting in tanning booths. UV exposure can come from tanning lamps as well as from the sun, and you can risk getting melanomas later on.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remove all makeup and oil from the day before you go to bed. When you wash off makeup, you also eliminate excess oil build-up and slow down the growth of harmful bacteria. Sleeping helps your skin rejuvenate.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When your skin starts to age, talk to an expert about a prescription cream. There are many anti-aging creams which are FDA-approved that will help to reduce wrinkles and fine lines on the skin. There are some people who shouldn't take them though; those include women who are nursing or pregnant, as well as those people who are on certain types of medication.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remember to protect your lips as well. Air dryness occurs more often in the cold, windy months of winter. Be sure to apply a moisturizing lip balm to your lips to prevent painful chapped or cracked lips.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avoid smoking if you want to take care of your skin. Smoking ages you really quickly and accelerates the appearance of wrinkles. Oxygen flow to your skin is cut when you smoke. This will cause your skin to have less elasticity. Smoking also promotes the formation of wrinkles around the eyes and mouth.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always use sunscreen to protect your skin from harmful UV rays. Even if the sun is not shining, you can still be taking in harmful rays. A makeup sponge can be used to even out sunscreen that's too thick and can help absorb it into your skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Moisturize your skin with a lotion containing jasmine extract. Your skin will glow when you use jasmine extract regularly. It is generously packed with antioxidants and feels very soothing. It might be more difficult to find on the store shelves than standard moisturizers. Jasmine extract can also be slightly more expensive than normal moisturizing products.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Exfoliating your skin with a loofah can help enhance your skin and get rid of dead skin cells. Removing this dead skin lightens up blemishes and other spots and gives your skin and complexion a healthy glow. That layer of dead cells gives the skin a tired and aged look. Getting rid of dead cells will make your face look far better.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Creating healthy and youthful-looking skin doesn't have to be overly time-consuming or expensive. With all the options available to you, there should be something out there that works for everyone. These tips are here to aid you in looking your best as well as keeping your wallet full of cash.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy55dXZhZGVybXN0b3JlLmNvbS95b25rYS1tLTI4Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Yonka&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>