<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="51ad2a120174de0fa1d34e55114d6efe">			Since Paul Alfille invented freecell solitaire in 1987, more and more people have been attracted and appealed in it. It is easy for many people to win the game, but once they found a strategy, they can win with even the unsolvable game. It must take a lot of time to find a perfect strategy. As the experience player with freecell solitaire, I found some very powerful strategy for the game.
&lt;br /&gt;1. &lt;strong&gt;How to move safely?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;    Firstly, consider carefully before moving the first card. You should plan several moves ahead. It is easy to be trapped if you are not conscious. Since all the moves that seems obvious are not always the best ones. There are cards that you can move at any time and no other cards depend on them. Aces are this kind of card. Thus, to win the game, you should try to move these aces at first,especially when they are buried behind several high cards. Secondly, with other kind of cards, when the cards one less in rank, of the opposite color, are already in the foundation, now you can safely move them to the foundation. Such as, if the black 7s have already been moved to that foundation, you can move safely the 8 of Diamonds. With a better freecell, when there are these kinds of safe moves, game will automatically move for you. Your duty is that only concentrate on the moves that matter, you do not have to manually make inconsequential moves.
&lt;br /&gt;2. &lt;strong&gt;The role of freecells&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;            Opening cells is the important key to win the game. So you must judicious use of them. They play a role as a temporary storage. Because when you want to move longer sequences around, they will help you to store the cards for a short time. Here is an example for more details:
&lt;br /&gt;If you have a column with 5 Hearts, Ace Spades, Ace hearts and 4 Clubs. In this case, you want to move 4 of CLubs onto the 5 Hearts. To do so, you must move 4 Clubs to a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qZXV4ZnJlZWNlbGwuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;freecell&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; then you can easily move two Aces to the foundation. Now you can know clearly the important role of free cells.
&lt;br /&gt;3. &lt;strong&gt;The importance of empty columns.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;        To win a freecell game, you should keep in mind that there is always an empty column. Since, it can help you move longer sequences around. The length of sequence you can move depends on empty columns and the number of available freecells. The empty columns can be even more useful than empty free cells. As possible, you should create an empty column. There is a move that called a &quot;;super-move&quot;; when you can move an ordered sequence of cards that is twice as long from one column to another. Only an empty column can allow you do it.
&lt;br /&gt;4. &lt;strong&gt;How to have empty columns?&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;	The important role of empty column is very clearly. The not less important factor now is how to create one.
&lt;br /&gt;	You can fast move every cards to the home cells. But you will lose easily if you do so. Because you need them when you move around lower cards of other suits. And only when they help you to make an empty column, you should move cards. Most of the first players pretend to go straight for releasing from Aces, then 2nd, 3rd, etc. Playing in this way will be easier and requires less thought. But when they play the harder game, this strategy does not promote efficiency. Then the most important strategy for all the easy and hard game are freecells and empty columns.
&lt;br /&gt;	There is no order for all these strategies. All of them must be conducted at the same time, and right after you press playing button.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>