<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="1d872c3a50ce69531dc7968dc9d770e">			&lt;em&gt;;Drew Barrymore has been a favorite of film audiences for almost three decades. Behind the camera, she is also enjoying success as a producer under her own Flower Films banner, with such hits as Never Been Kissed, Charile’s Angels and 50 First Dates. In addition to producing the films, Barrymore joined Cameron Diaz and Lucy Liu to star in both Charlie’s Angels and Charlie’s Angels: Full Throttle, which, together, grossed more than half a billion dollars worldwide.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;She has also earned praise from both critics and audiences for her performances in a wide range of comedies, most recently including the romantic comedies Music &amp; Lyrics, opposite Hugh Grant, Fever Pitch, in which she starred with Jimmy Fallon under the direction of the Farrelly brothers, and 50 First Dates, opposite Adam Sandler. Barrymore also starred in the 2007 drama Lucky You for director Curtis Hanson. Other recent films have included George Clooney’s widely acclaimed biographical satire Confessions of a Dangerous Mind, with Sam Rockwell; Penny Marshall’s Riding in Cars With Boys; Never Been Kissed, which marked Barrymore’s producing debut; Home Fries, opposite Luke Wilson; and the smash hit comedy The Wedding Singer, opposite Adam Sandler.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Barrymore made her feature film debut at the age of five in the science fiction thriller Altered States. However, it was her scene-stealing performance as the precocious Gertie in Steven Spielberg’s 1982 blockbuster E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial that catapulted the young actress to stardom. She went on to star in the thriller Firestarter and the comedy Irreconcilable Differences, for which she earned a Golden Globe nomination for Best Supporting Actress.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Her other film credits include Stephen King’s Cat’s Eye; Far From Home; Poison Ivy; Guncrazy, for which she received another Golden Globe nomination for Best Actress; Bad Girls; Herbert Ross’ Boys on the Side; Mad Love; Batman Forever; Woody Allen’s Everyone Says I Love You; and Wes Craven’s horror hit Scream, which launched a successful franchise. Barrymore next stars in and produces He’s Just Not That Into You, a comedy ensemble with Jennifer Aniston, Scarlett Johansson and Ben Affleck.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Drew most recently wrapped HBO’s Grey Gardens, co-starring Jessica Lange; based on the 1975 Maysles brothers documentary about the reclusive aunt and cousin of Jackie Kennedy who lived in a crumbling mansion in East Hampton.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This summer, Barrymore will direct her first feature film, Whip It!, starring Ellen Page for Mandate Pictures.&lt;/em&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>