<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="bd57f24319280eff1fd8c98d6449c4dd">			The introduction of Japanese Hair Straightening has been satisfied with warm welcome from the hairstyling elite of the western globe and has been and however is the most current trend for celebrities throughout the world. Let us dig deeper and unravel the strategies to &quot;Luscious Hunting Hair&quot;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Japanese Hair Straightening, which is also regarded as Thermal Reconditioning, Magic Straight, Bio Ionic Straightening and the Yuko Technique, is a lasting hair straightening approach that employs warmth to restructure the bonds in your hair so that the hair lies straight, giving you glossy, clean hair that displays gentle, radiates coloration and presents the visual appeal of silken gloss.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The best programs on the marketplace are Liscio and Yuko each of which occur from Japan. Liscio is a common choice as it normally utilised in today's salons. Yuko Yamashita is the founder of the Yuko process and was granted a patent for her system in Japan in 1995. She also opened up her initially specialised hair straightening salon in 1996 and launched her technique to the USA in 1997. Since then she has educated numerous best hairstylists on how to use her techniques and has started the YUKO Academy which offers budding hairstylists the possibility to study this most innovative talent and get their hairstyling potential to the next amount.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hairstraighteningnow.com%2Fjapanese-hair-straightening%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hairstraighteningnow.com/japanese-hair-straightening/&lt;/a&gt;;  can be utilized to almost all kinds of hair, with only one particular exception, that becoming the hair largely of African origin as the hair could fall short below the extreme warmth process. This approach will have your client in the chair for at minimum 6 hours undergoing shampooing, heating beneath intensive lamps, blowing out, flat ironed and then repetition of the identical process all over again.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This hair straightening system comes with an high priced price tag tag ranging any place from $300 - $800 which is excellent information for hairstylists, and it only calls for a re-growth touch up every six - 9 months, which is good information for your consumer as they have maintenance free glamorous and glossy seeking hair for at least 6 months, so it is a win win scenario for the two client and hairstylist.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is a 72 hour initial aftercare course of action which your customer must adhere to in purchase to absolutely benefit and get pleasure from lasting success, uncomplicated adequate guidelines like contact with water, as they will not be permitted to wash their hair for a number of days.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In closing, the YUKO Academy offer you their training in the USA, United kingdom and Japan and I would stimulate all specialist hairstylists to include this string to their bow as these  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.hairstraighteningnow.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.hairstraighteningnow.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  approaches are turning into really common and it appears to be like like it still will be for a very long time to arrive.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>