<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f52d2aa94c8af0908918e6f84c7708b1">			According to the officials of some of the hotels, their rooms remain occupied these days as tourists have started pouring in to a life of luxury and freedom in Dubai. In the current year, China has also remained a major contributor. According to resources, now Dubai properties and hotel officials have also taken steps to further enhance their services to attract Chinese tourists and investors.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Demand of Property Market&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dubai real estate officials are of the view that Dubai is seeing a constant decline in rental and sales prices and the market is becoming more tenant-friendly. The main reason behind the fall in prices is the economic downturn in the US and Europe. Most of the offices and corporate buildings are occupied by the US and Europe based companies. Now they give careful forethought and delay the leasing decisions. However, the Arab Spring has helped Dubai properties to get a boost in its prices. Currently the rental and sale prices of Dubai villas, hotels and other residential and retail market are moving towards recovery stage. But the question remains that how long this impact would last? The impact would not last long if the economical and financial conditions of the West do not improve. Real estate experts and economy analysts are of the view that more sustainable recovery is required to turn this impact into broader economic activity. They are still pessimistic about any chance of Dubai recovering in near future and are of the view that the market will take time to fully recover.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dubai has attracted many celebrities to its shores with the promise of all year around sun and Tax free status and what also attracts the rich and famous are the luxurious villas and penthouses.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dubai offers many exclusive villas but not many come as exclusive as Al Barari villas. The Al Barari concept is of very high specification villas located on the edge of the Dubailand development in the royal area of Nad Al Sheba. The villas are located in clusters around the royal nature reserve, Al Barari actually means wilderness.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Villas are designed for the high end market and feature 4 main designs of Acacia, Bromeli, Camelia and Dahlia. The whole project is very much on a botanical theme with 24 botanical gardens and 1000 species of plants brought in from 20 countries and actually grown in Al Bararis very own development.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional to the villas there will be a selection of apartments and retails outlets and complemented by a very high specification boutique hotel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Emirates Hills like Al Barari offers some of the finest villas and mansions located around the exclusive world famous Golf Course of the same name. The Villas in Emirates Hills offers palatial abodes ranging from 10,000 sq foot properties up to mammoth villas of 20-25,000 sq feet built up areas most around a number of man made lakes carved out of the desert.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If it is Beach front living you are looking for go no further than Palm Jumeirah, the man made Island located off the shores of Dubai. Here you will find exclusive Signature villa and Tip villas located on the Fronds ( Branches ) of the man Made Palm Tree. Get your little piece of paradise now&lt;br /&gt;;by investing in the Dubai property market&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2F800mag.tumblr.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://800mag.tumblr.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>