<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ec378e9ec0adfb90a1010f6dd39d229c">			And with Beyonce telling Oprah that she used this diet, this diet is getting more and more popular.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So I began my fasting in accordance with the diet, and although it was hard but I experienced 10 pounds decrease in approximately 2 weeks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here's the Do's and Dont's for master cleanse diet.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do's:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Eat raw vegetables and fruits if your hunger is unbearable.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Eat a little supply of carbohydrate twice in a week fasting. (Baked potato, brown rice, sushi)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Drink your laxative tea in the night regularly.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Drink approx 4 glasses of water everyday. You need water to make sure you don't face dehydration.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Use freshly squeezed lemon juice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Focus on cleansing your body from toxins and weight loss will come naturally.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dont's:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Drink the saltwater beverage that the diet requires you to. The reason is that the saltwater can threaten your body metabolism by forcing you to excrete more water. Laxative tea is already enough.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Undertake heavy exercise that force you to sweat a lot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Drink the lemonade two times more than you drink the water.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Mix this diet with cabbage soup diet or other fad diet.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Eat high sugary snacks during the diet.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Focus on losing weight during the fasting, you will end up starving yourself more than ever.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Eat too much after your fasting period. Adjust your eating portion gradually.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Don't do this diet for more than 2 weeks without resting.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By following the do's and dont's that I mentioned above you should be able to succeed in the master cleanse diet. And always remember that the purpose is to cleanse your body, don't worry about weight loss. It will come naturally together with the cleansing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Good luck and happy dieting!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Acai Berry needs no introduction. The weight loss benefits have been unparalleled and it seems finally we have a product which naturally burns excess calories. Following are the ways in which this wonder fruit leads to fat loss:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Regulates Metabolism - The berry causes the calorie consumption rate to naturally go up. A person consumes more calories even while sleeping. These extra calories consumed leads to sustained weight loss. Since the calories lost is excess fat burnt and not water loss. The lost weight does not come back easily. But it is very important that a healthy diet is maintained.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Suppresses Hunger - A lot of weight gained is due to the 'binge eating'. Acai provides natural energy to the body hence there is no craving for salty and sugary foods. These excess calories are avoided and there is no weight gain.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Boosts Energy- The body is not starved during the Acai diet and the energy levels remain up.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Acai berry diet works best if it's combined with natural colon cleansing foods. These are foods which are rich in fiber such as fruits, nuts and cereals. Flax seed is another excellent source of fiber and can help in colon cleansing. The foods assist the body to shed excess pounds in following way&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Helps drain harmful toxins from the body.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Remove sludge from the stomach, this alone could knock off couple of inches from the stomach area.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Improves food digestion immensely. This leads to better energy absorption and overall well being.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;o Helps reduce blood pressure and regulate cholesterol levels&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now another important property of Acai Berry and Colon Cleanse Diet is that they retain their weight loss benefits when preserved. Thus leading to very effective weight loss supplements. What is more, the antioxidants in the acai berry keeps on working days after, in limiting toxins and plaques, on and on a continuous cleansing process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dvdHByb2Jpb3RpY3MuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;colon cleansing&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>