<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="7973c409fd34dcaa1ee2d2c11443703d">			With your release of Windows 7 in late 2009 has suggested that Office 2007 did not utilize the many features of the new os. The new features with 2010 office do operate the new platform with a new set of icons to be able to be read along the task bar to help you easily switch between. It's also possible to see previews of the project to find what you are working on just by moving your cursor above the application icon. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New templates and layouts are now available in Office 2010 because whenever you would know for those who have been using 2007 a lot that you keep while using the same title pages anyone can be happy to know Microsoft Office 2010 has provided an array of new templates with improved functionality for users. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In overview Office 2010 improves on the great office suite that 2007 is and provides users more potential uses while using the integration of the menu bar across all of the suite now. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;It's a love/hate relationship. When Office 2007 ended up, you either loved it or hated it. Using Office 2010 out today, your hate may soften to accepting the product, and your love might just deepen. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The dismay within Office 2007 centered on the feel and look of the product. The introduction on the new Ribbon, which replaced the typical toolbar in Office 2003, had users grumbling. One was the familiar look that prior Office products kept. You could upgrade and also the transition was easy. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Within Office 2007, Microsoft made a huge leap into the brand-new and unknown, leaving many PC users baffled. The new Ribbon housed a permanent arrangement of command buttons and icons, organized commands as a set of tabs, each grouping relevant commands. The look and feel with the old standby was ended up. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Designed to produce the features of the applying more discoverable and accessible, the Ribbon was either loved or hated. Many gave it this quick term shot and returned to using Office 2003. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using Office 2010, Microsoft designed an exceptional product. Microsoft listened to all the challenges and grumbles of users and created a superb blend. Office 2010 is a good of Office 2003 together with Office 2007. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New Features &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;People endured will enjoy an alternative customizable Ribbon (Users can't customize the Office 2007 Ribbon) so you can organize it according for your needs. A modified Ribbon is now available in all Office environment applications, and it now comes with the &quot;File&quot; option and a new feature called &quot;Backstage See, &quot; giving easy access to task-centered functions such since printing and sharing. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get excited! Backstage view incorporates probably the most commonly used actions in a single place (no much more dialog boxes with tabs). And there's much more! You get the usual open, save and printing, and you also get several templates for new documents, print layouts and ways to share your work, all without dialog boxes together with tabs, everything is a lot more easily accessible. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional features include: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;bull; A Paste preview which lets you switch between paste options so you can make sure that work will be formatted properly&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; Role orientation tailored to employees in &quot;roles&quot; which include research and development experts, sales persons, and human resources&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; A built-in screen capture tool for convenient internet copy and paste&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; A background removal application for editing photos and clip art just a document&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; SmartArt templates and author permissions to help you create wonderful documents despite the fact that you're not an artisan&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; New copy and image editing side effects; making it easy to become the pro&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; Live collaboration functions; great for any office&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; Brand-new animations in PowerPoint 2010; insert videos directly into PowerPoint&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;bull; A Social Connector which allows users to write emails while monitoring their family, friends, and colleagues by looking at status updates and past communication history with the individual &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;World-wide-web Apps &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you happen to are just buying into the idea of &quot;Cloud Computing, &quot; Microsoft now provides a free web-based version involving its Office productivity suite, known as Office World-wide-web Apps, which started shortly before Office 2010 was already released. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NoZWFwbGljZW5zZWNvZGVzLmNvbS9taWNyb3NvZnRfb2ZmaWNlXzIwMTBfcHJvZmVzc2lvbmFsX3BsdXNfU2VyaWFsX0xpY2Vuc2VfS2V5X0NvZGUuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;office 2010 pro plus product key&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="9011e40f9934a17d8697a4fef001bdb5">			With your release of Windows 7 within late 2009 has required that Office 2007 did not utilize all of the features of the new operating system. The new features with 2010 office do make use of the new platform with a new set of icons to be able to be read along the task bar so you can easily switch between. Additionally you can see previews of the effort to find what you will be working on just just by moving your cursor above the application icon. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New templates and layouts are generally available in Office 2010 because because you would know for those who have been using 2007 a lot that you keep while using the same title pages it's simple to be happy to know that Microsoft Office 2010 has provided several new templates with increased functionality for users. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In summary Office 2010 improves to the great office suite that 2007 is and gives users more potential uses with the integration of the menu bar across all of the suite now. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;The 1402 error is quite a common problem for individuals trying to install Microsoft Office and also other programs onto their pc. This error normally shows up part way through an installation and is seen as a stopping the installation from occurring. To fix this problem, you need to instigate a few small things which will fix what may cause the issue. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The cause of the 1402 error is in fact from your PC being unable to read the registry keys that it needs to change to be able to install the program you want. The error that regularly appears will say something including &quot;Error 1402. Cannot open registry key: &lt;em&gt;; key_name &lt;/em&gt;; &quot;. They key name will normally be a long textual path to one of many obscure registry keys on your hard drive. To fix this problem, you need to help your laptop or computer access the key it needs. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The first thing you should do to refurbish this error is : if you're using Microsoft windows 98 or 2000 - to make use of the 'registry checker' facility. This is done by loading up the &quot;Run Console&quot; with CTRL + R and then typing &quot;registry checker&quot;. If the registry is intact then this aren't going to be a problem. On later versions of Windows, feel free to use a 'registry cleaner' program to perform this task. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those who have XP, Vista or Microsoft windows 7, you should first download a registry cleaner from the web and let that scan your system. It will look for almost any registry errors on your computer and then fix them, which should fix the 1402 error in the way. To use one these, you need to download a registry scanner program and let it scan your laptop or computer. It will identify most of the damaged parts of Windows and should fix them. And if one such registry errors is producing the 1402 error a quick restart after your registry scan should enable you to install Office or the program you wanted. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If that method did not work, you should use a different user bank account, or creating a brand-new user account, to install this software onto. It's often the condition that user accounts will become corrupted for whatever reason, blocking access to that registry. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]office-2010-professional-plus-keys[/url], &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWN0b3JpYWFkdm9jYXRlLmNvbS93ZWJsb2dzL2JyZXR0bmd1eWVuMjMvcG9zdC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;office-2010-pro-plus-product-key&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hcnRpY2xlc3Zpc2lvbi5jb20vYmxvZ3MvMTE1MjYvb2ZmaWNlLTIwMTAtcHJvZmVzc2lvbmFsLXBsdXMta2V5cy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;office-2010-professional-plus-keys&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>