<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="457318282fd24fa1856f02fcef3e9fde">			How about the power of social networking like Facebook and Twitter? As a consumer you are able to &quot;like&quot; or follow a favorite retailer and get price cut on deals. For instance 12 million consumers &quot;like&quot; Victoria's Secret on Facebook by March 2011. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rick Okamura (managing accomplice at Okamura Consulting) tells that social shopping is getting started. He or she mentions that Facebook offers good return on investment. However you may still find lots of retailers that have not taken this advantage yet. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Online shopping  is usually going to help lots of small niche online retailers. By way of international or cross border e-commerce, they can be now doing 10-20% of their sales outside their own country (example SousVideSupreme, Zara, Best Shop and StyleTrek). &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are nowadays ever more sites that cut with the din of so several sites and bring consumers only the info they are interested with: Dealnews, ConsumerSearch, Brad's Deals and My Shopping Genie. There are sites you may use to find coupon unique codes, and possibly to make money although shopping online. There are also a variety of websites it's possible you'll utilize to earn &quot;points&quot; or even &quot;bucks&quot;. It is possible to accrue these points and bucks and &quot;cash them in&quot; for goodies like gift cards, actual money, accessories, electronics, so on and etc . (Swag Bucks). &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An awesome advantage for consumers with online shopping is that precisely as it becomes easier to compare prices (via My Shopping Genie for instance) stores will be required to create better experiences using better sales staff and items difficult to find anywhere else. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the article from April 2011 it was eventually revealed that China banned 410 websites involved within copyright violations and counterfeiting in the first 3 months involving 2010. This can be a sign that governments are trying to interfere within legitimating online sales and turning it into safe for online buyers. China's online shopping has been booming (iResearch test). China has more than 450 million internet users, becoming the world's largest. China's internet shopping transaction volume jumped 89. several % year on 12 months. Concerning 148 million customers purchased goods or services online really. China's internet economy grew rapidly inside first quarter of 2011, mainly driven with the development of e-commerce and mobile internet. Due to this increase in online shopping, local Chinese authorities are placing more emphasis on monitoring online shops. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another example is Malaysia. Malaysians spent $739millions shopping online not too long ago according to a survey released by PayPal. Your PayPal's growth in Malaysia not too long ago was the strongest in your community Asia and India at 70%. The main percentage of online retail purchases are made on local websites. However the USA is the most popular country Malaysians bought from. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As we mentioned above, governments are generally trying to make the internet shopping safer for the purchasers. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In an article from ABC News from April this year, it is known that the White House has evolved a plan named the National Technique for Trusted Identities in Cyberspace (NSTIC) so as to fight online identity theft. The idea of this plan is to help consolidate internet logins, type of &quot;Connect&quot; for online shopping along with the government's mark of approval. The purchasers may benefit from these version of legislations but there are disadvantages to it&lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlb25saW5lc2hvcC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;online shop from china&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="a89677a8e601e57a090bd664f4d33b3b">			They should be able to tell you a small about where it came from and most importantly when it's harvested? If they is unable to, or do not want to answer this last issue, you need to get started questioning how fresh the tea may very well be? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Online shops have made the world of artisan whole leaf teas more accessible than ever before. By following the simple rules from this guide we hope that you'll be able to discover a whole world of teas from tea producers around the world. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Online direct selling is among the most most lucrative ways to make a living. As more people make the net their one-stop shop for everything they need, marketing online becomes well-known. One great thing that technology was able to provide the consumer is the chance to know that there are alternative products that are available. In the past, the only products that people are aware of are those under big companies that can pay for the creation of commercials. Since these businesses need to recuperate the money they spent on advertising, they normally offer their products with a much higher price licence plate. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Through the online market place, big and small companies are now given an equal playing field when it comes to marketing their product internet. As such, consumer can have a more practical decision in purchasing the products that they need. China products are among the best alternative in regards to electronic gadgets. China is known to manufacture electronic gadgets which might be cheap and functional. These gadgets are currently being patronized by many consumers around the world. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A number of online retailers are actually contemplating on adding these items to their line of inventory. However, their normal concern is that they cannot know how to get hold of these wholesale products to sell. Since these are China products, getting these wholesale products distribute may be difficult precisely as it will involve shipping together with importation. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Several retailers know that there's an alternative way of having these wholesale products distribute. Since they are only aware of ordering in bulk and shipping it, most of these retailers are not very attracted to paying for the costs. The new method that is gaining popularity among retailers and manufacturers is a method called the drop ship. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Drop shipping can be a method of selling that doesn't involve bulk buying. It's normally done by at first making an arrangement with the manufacturer. Get the list of the product that they are selling and offer it on the online shop. From the amount provided by the company, put a price mark-up; the purchase price difference is your gain. Be very realistic together with compare prices with other retailers offering the same product. Market it the way you market your other solutions. Once a transaction may be concluded and the buyer post the payment, order the item from the manufacturer and pay for it. Give the shipping details to your manufacturer. Once these are generally done, the manufacturer will then ship the item for your customer with your details labelled relating to the package. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3dlb25saW5lc2hvcC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;online shop 2012&lt;/a&gt;;One of your friends, knowing you like tea, has visited an online tea shop and bought you a selection of beautiful whole leaf tea from China.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>