<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="4b038f45394f7de52dba6ef6ee80cd23">			There are 4 distinct collet measurements (one/32&quot;, 1/16&quot;, 3/32&quot;, and one/8&quot;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; accessible for the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dremel8200.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dremel8200.com/&lt;/a&gt;;. The 1/8&quot; dimensions collet is typically bundled in most tool kits.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. The 8200 comes with a constructed-in &quot;hanger&quot; that you can use to hang up your rotary instrument when it is not in use. When you will need to use your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dremel8200.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dremel8200.com/&lt;/a&gt;;, just snap the hanger again in area on the human body of the rotary instrument.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Make sure that your attached accessory is in balance on your rotary device in advance of you use it. Immediately after attaching your accessory, just turn on the rotary tool and you should be in a position to tell from the feel and the sound whether or not the connected accessory is in balance. To accurate an imbalance, only loosen the collet nut, twist the accessory a small, and retighten the collet nut. Then recheck the stability by restarting the rotary device. You might need to have to carry out these measures a few of instances right until you are satisfied with the balance. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dremel8200.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dremel8200.com/&lt;/a&gt;; comes with a collet wrench.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. When employing wire brushes, by no means set the running pace of the rotary instrument at greater than 15,000 RPMs. Pieces of the wire brush may possibly arrive loose during operation and turn into embedded in your skin. In addition, when you 1st attach a wire brush to your Dremel, turn on the Dremel and permit it operate for about a moment prior to utilizing it. This 60-second warm up time period should shake free any pieces of wire on the brush that are unfastened.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. When using your device for severe grinding or when utilizing a cutoff wheel, grasp the body of the Dremel like you would maintain a fishing rod - with your thumb on top in close proximity to the OFF/ON swap, the physique of the tool resting in the palm of your hand, and the other 4 fingers securing the left side of the tool.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. Setting your rotary device at a speed higher than 15,000 RPMs when using a bristle brush, could injury the brush.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;seven. When functioning with plastic, get started your device at a small charge of pace and progressively improve the speed until finally you see the plastic commence to melt. Then cut down your tool's pace a very little. This will give you the ideal doing work speed for that piece of plastic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. If the 3 lights on the fuel gauge start off flashing &quot;off and on&quot; that suggests your rotary tool's battery has come to be also hot for use. Just flip off your instrument, get a break, and permit your tool cool down. (Note: If the three lights are flashing &quot;aspect to side&quot; or just one mild is flashing &quot;off and on&quot;, that implies that your battery requirements to be recharged.)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. Just like with most cutting equipment, certainly not turn on your Dremel with it touching the material you are heading to operate on. As a substitute, commence your Dremel and permit it attain the full velocity you arranged it for just before you start out to lower/polish/sand/grind/and so on the substance.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ten.		</conversation>		<conversation id="410b9d55c202c723ee8fd1b2ed3456a">			It will answer all your drilling, grinding, polishing and cutting needs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dremel8200.com%2F-1%2F24"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dremel8200.com/-1/24&lt;/a&gt;; 300 Series Variables-Velocity Rotary Instrument Kit is handy and so you can simply have it wherever. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dremel8200.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dremel8200.com/&lt;/a&gt;; Owner's Handbook gives four pages of suggested speed configurations relying on the material and distinct Dremel accessory tool the consumer is using.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tip #three - Use a sequence of passes with the rotary device relatively than seeking to do all the operate in one single pass. 1 of the greatest rotary resources on the sector is the Dremel 8000.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why this tool is far better:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dremel8200.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dremel8200.com/&lt;/a&gt;; is a rotary tool that appears to be like a bit like a cordless screwdriver besides the suggestion of it is distinctive. There are four distinct collet measurements (one/32&quot;, one/16&quot;, 3/32&quot;, and one/8&quot;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; accessible for the Dremel 8200. The 1/8&quot; dimensions collet is ordinarily included in most device kits.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. The 8200 arrives with a built-in &quot;hanger&quot; that you can use to hang up your rotary device when it is not in use. When you have to have to use your Dremel 8200, just snap the hanger back again in position on the entire body of the rotary instrument.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;three. Make sure that your connected accessory is in harmony on your rotary tool previous to you use it. Following attaching your accessory, just flip on the rotary instrument and you will need to be capable to tell from the sense and the sound whether the attached accessory is in harmony. To suitable an imbalance, merely loosen the collet nut, twist the accessory a tiny, and retighten the collet nut. Then recheck the balance by restarting the rotary instrument. You may well will need to conduct these techniques a couple of days until eventually you are satisfied with the stability. The Dremel 8200 arrives with a collet wrench.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;four. When working with wire brushes, certainly not arranged the operating pace of the rotary tool at greater than fifteen,000 RPMs. Items of the wire brush may perhaps arrive unfastened all through operation and become embedded in your skin. In addition, when you initially connect a wire brush to your Dremel, flip on the Dremel and allow it run for about a minute just before applying it. This 60-2nd warm up time period must shake absolutely free any items of wire on the brush that are free.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;five. When applying your instrument for significant grinding or when using a cutoff wheel, grasp the physique of the Dremel like you would hold a fishing rod - with your thumb on leading around the OFF/ON swap, the system of the tool resting in the palm of your hand, and the other four fingers securing the left aspect of the instrument.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;six. Setting your rotary tool at a pace greater than 15,000 RPMs when employing a bristle brush, may well harm the brush.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. When working with plastic, start your instrument at a low price of pace and step by step boost the velocity right up until you see the plastic start out to melt. Then cut down your tool's speed a minimal. This will give you the optimum doing work pace for that piece of plastic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>