<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3ba5730562742723c6c6283eeb78d15d">			There is a lot more learning material for players than there was four years ago.  There are scores of poker forums and strategy guides.  It is now a lot tougher to find players who will make bad moves that cost them lots of money.  With this in mind, you need to adjust to the new games, or go broke.  There are ways however that you can accomplish this which I will get into in a bit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Poker can be a very profitable game if you are skilled enough at it.  The problem is you not only need to beat the other poker players, you also have to beat the rake.  Rake is the house cut, or amount the poker site or casino takes in.  There isn't a set rake amount amongst internet poker sites.    Players are able to get some of the rake taken away sent back to them.  This is known as rakeback.  In order to get rakeback, you have to enter in an affiliate code from a rakeback provider at the time you make your account at the poker site.  These affiliates have negotiated the rakeback offer with the poker rooms and pass some of the rakeback they will get from the poker room to you.  How much rakeback you receive depends on which rakeback provider you ultimately choose.  Right now there are many options so it's smart to shop around to get the best offer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The great advantage of getting rakeback, is that it's free, as well as permanent.  Rakeback is essentially just like receiving a tax refund on each hand you participate in.  With the speed of internet poker, players can play a lot of hands per hour.  The more you play, the more you'll get back in rakeback.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Back in the early days of online poker if you wanted to get rakeback you needed to play in one of just a few poker sites.  This is not the case anymore  In order for poker sites to stay competitive these days, they must offer rakeback.  The typical amount you could expect to get from one of the main online poker websites is 33%.  In most cases websites having less players give higher rakeback.  The downsides to a lot of these sites is the fact that although you will be receiving more in rakeback, it'll be a lot more difficult to find games to play in.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Of the many poker websites on the web that offer rakeback, cake poker is the largest.   Cake poker was launched with an intuitive and simple to use software as well as a great sign-up bonus for new players.    This created a big change in the poker community and caused the site to increase in popularity.  Cake Poker's rise to glory could be ascribed to many different factors.  The main reason however was due to their rakeback offer.  If you are searching for a poker site with no shortage of players which has rakeback, then cake poker is the website.  They also offer a fairly big sign up bonus based on when and where you sign up to the website.  This sign up bonus with the great rakeback offer tends to make cake poker a solid option for virtually any poker player considering getting rakeback.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wcm9yYWtlYmFjay5uZXQvcmFrZWJhY2svY2FrZS1wb2tlci5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;cake rakeback&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>