<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="8d6da94df8e7d9bcdea822559c35ced9">			Some thousands of years ago, the Celts were in what we now know as Great Britain and France, and celebrated the new year on November 1, meaning that began with the issue from the October 31 night. But, something incomprehensible, not drunk! as is now usual (what a waste of time ...), but taking it very seriously, and priests dedicated the night to Samhain, the lord of death. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Great bonfires were lit, horses and sometimes even humans were sacrificed to ward off witches and evil spirits, it turns out that in the Celtic custom the dead returned on the night of Samhain, to seek food at the frightened villagers to who cursed and made victims of their spells if they agreed to their requests (or give me or I make a prank, which is the translation of &quot;Trick or Treat&amp;quot. 
&lt;br /&gt;;From Italy, taking the domains Celts came the Romans. But very little intellectual Pueblo pachanguero, which already had occupied the last days of October and early November with festivities called &quot;The Feast of Pomona&quot;, dedicated to the goddess of fruit trees (it was something like the celebration of the harvest or harvest) and could not leave this town &quot;barbaric&quot; the ignorant, so they thought of adapting the manner of the rule to their own, confused and then say they already had them before. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Fruits were mixed with witches and evil spirits! 
&lt;br /&gt;;The apples were very popular and soon were part of the celebrations. 
&lt;br /&gt;;When A.C. became D.C. and Christianity spread, the priests saw with disgust that there were still some stubborn who worshiped Samhain or Pomona (or both of the two, as said Rep.), and that was not correct (for Christians, of course). But when they put customers uncompromising lost, sorry ..., devotees. 
&lt;br /&gt;;They had to find a smart way to please everyone, and that's how they thought of the feast a Christian convert. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Already brought a Problemón with the timetable had been insufficient to give a day to all the saints, then, what better way to spend a single day of all saints minors (in category I guess). Thus establishing November 1st as All Saints Day, which in England (where there was a problem) is called (literal translation) as &quot;All Hallows Day&quot;, and last night was called &quot;All Hallow Even&quot; . 
&lt;br /&gt;;With the familiar contractions, so used in English, this became &quot;All Hallow E'en&quot; and finally &quot;Halloween.&quot; 
&lt;br /&gt;;By the time of the Middle Ages, some bandits took advantage of these beliefs and, after committing their crimes, were with the rumor that the spirits were to blame (who, of course, never were there to disprove). These crooks are disguised to look like devils and ghosts and make more credible his story, Hence the custom of the costumes! 
&lt;br /&gt;;Some years after this festival comes to America, brought by the pioneers, and is accepted as a tradition, integrating all the details mentioned above. It was a Catholic feast of small groups of faithful who greatly popularized with the advent of the Irish around 1840. It was they who added the &quot;Jack-o-lantern&quot; (the hollow pumpkin with a candle inside), since they had a legend of Jack (John) who was banned from entry into Heaven and Hell (no holding him ) and was walking with a lantern, which was a hollow cabbage with a burning coal inside (he had given the Devil himself!), seeking a way to enter one of the two clubs. 
&lt;br /&gt;;The Americans were more practical and used cabbage instead of a pumpkin that is easier to hollow out. 
&lt;br /&gt;;The party however did not start mass held until 1921. That year was the first Halloween parade in Minnesota and then was followed by other states. 
&lt;br /&gt;;The internationalization of Halloween was in the 80s thanks to the television series. Hits the small screen as &quot;Roseanne&quot; began to devote a chapter each year to make Halloween pumpkin smiling in a picture as well known as Coca-Cola. Today Halloween is one of the most important dates estadounidenense and Canadian holiday calendar.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/es/p/oo/123458359_11845778_36609060.jpg" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="41b9e999cd71cc0dbbe2df35783e3bff">			I do not want to disguise as anything
&lt;br /&gt;;I would maybe just a mask...		</conversation>		<conversation id="bbe893db97e0ace5491b84d619997723">			-Germany 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: German 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: hearty breakfasts are usually high-calorie 
&lt;br /&gt;;(Sausage, cheese, sausage, biscuits with honey ...) 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Euro 
&lt;br /&gt;;Singer: lale andersen 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centres: freiburg 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Australia 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: English 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Anzac Day 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: U.S. dollar 
&lt;br /&gt;;Singer: kylie monogen 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centres: Adelaide 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Spain 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Spanish 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Bullfights 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Euro 
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Carlos Acuña 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centres: Flamenco Y Toro 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Denmark 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Danish 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Respect for Others 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Danish Krone 
&lt;br /&gt;;Singer: Grethe Ingmann 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers: Palacio De Amailenborg 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-France 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: French 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: They love to cook 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Euro 
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Isabelle Adjani 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers: Torre Axis 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Greece 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Greek 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Residents' daily routine 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Euro 
&lt;br /&gt;;Singer: Sotiria Bellou 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers: Athinai 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Sweden 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Swedish 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Speak Soon 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Swedish Krona 
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Nanne Grönvall 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural centers: Stockholm 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Italy 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Italian 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: handshake And The Kiss 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Euro 
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Anna Maria Alberghetti 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers: Torino, Napoli 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Romania 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Romanian 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Son Del Tito Orthodox 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Romanian Lue 
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Ovidiu Cernauteanu 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural centers: Park Bucharest 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Portugal 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Portuguese 
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: drive on the right 
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Euro 
&lt;br /&gt;;Singer: Luciana Abreu 
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers: Universidad Salamanca		</conversation>		<conversation id="25f2f00db78a03d654cc25b9e9ad3e3a">			-Arabia
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Arabic
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Islamic Holidays
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Saudi Riyal
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Ze Cabra
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers, King Abdulaziz
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Armenia
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Armenian
&lt;br /&gt;;Customs: Powerful Tribes
&lt;br /&gt;;Are The Triumphant
&lt;br /&gt;;Currency: Armenian Dram
&lt;br /&gt;;Artist: Emmy Bejanyan
&lt;br /&gt;;Cultural Centers: Parks
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-China: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: mandarin 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : yúan 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer: wei wei 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: monte everest
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Japón: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: nihongo 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : yen 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer:Yaida Hitomi 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers:fujiyama 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Taiwan: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: Spanish 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : nuevo dólar de taiwan 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer: Susan Boyle
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: Yu Shan 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Turquía: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: turco 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : lira de turquía 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer: tarkan 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: monte ararat 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-India: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: bodo 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : rupia india 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer: Engelbert Humperdinck 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: nanda devi
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Tailandia: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: tailandés 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : baht 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer: ruj 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: doi inthanon 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Georgia: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: georgiano 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : lari 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer:Georgina Valdez Levin 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: kazbek 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-Corea Del Sur: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Language: coreano 
&lt;br /&gt;;currency : won surcoreano 
&lt;br /&gt;;singer: Yuri 
&lt;br /&gt;;cultural centers: halla-san		</conversation>	</conversations></author>