<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="75b35fde7d93de09e061eaec14271164">			Internet marketers who do a lot of affiliate marketing are learning that Twitter is a very useful tool. Twitter works so well for affiliate marketing because it's immediate and about what's happening right now. With Twitter, marketers are able to receive information and put it to work right away. Many marketers also use this as a tool for connecting with their target markets and getting ahead of the competition. Without a proper map to navigate the shortcuts and detours, it can a very long and dark road to affiliate marketing success. Many marketers looking for success have found Twitter to be the simple solution. Use these Twitter tips to find your own success as an affiliate marketer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Firstly, you should understand just how important it is to listen to those following you. Listening to your followers, really listening, is the only way to determine what they need and demand. This means you should always answer your followers' questions to the best of your abilities. When you want to grow a business, no matter what it is, you need to find out what your prospects and customers think about that business, and Twitter is great for doing this very thing. The more you can involve yourself with those people on your followers list, the more they will want to hear what you have to say. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Secondly, don't make the mistake of turning your professional Twitter account into a personal one. To put it another way, personal and professional Twitter accounts should be kept separate. You will want to make sure that your profile is never used to describe what you're doing every second of the day, such as washing your car or going to the movies. Instead, you will do better to make sure every tweet is tailored towards offering your target audience something of value. You can get away with tweeting about daily activities if you want to show people that you're a real individual and not some robot sales person. For example, if there is something humungous going on in your life, like you're getting married, feel free to share that with your Twitter followers. But you will want to keep these types of tweets to a minimum. Creating a healthy balance in your tweets is the key to success with Twitter when it's used for affiliate marketing purposes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Be sure to leverage the full potential of Twitter in your affiliate marketing efforts. In addition to using Twitter as a promotional tool it's also possible to use it to collect information as well. Be sure to follow people who are successful marketers and learn from them. Keep in mind that affiliate managers and affiliate networks also share important nuggets of information in their tweets too. The truly successful affiliate marketer is one who uses Twitter for send and receive information. Twitter is one of those tools that is very effective for any affiliate marketing business. Affiliate marketers who have the good fortune to use Twitter and similar social media tools the right way have enjoyed amazing benefits for doing so. To stay ahead of the crowd in affiliate marketing you have to get an edge; Twitter is an excellent edge to have.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3NsYXBzaG90Z2Vhci5jb20vcGl0dHNidXJnaC1wZW5ndWlucy1zbmFwYmFjaw__" target="_blank"&gt;pittsburgh penguins snapback&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>