<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="8f58c4557cac20a31ecb0611d9f51e4c">			It is important to learn this when selecting a house security camera system, because when you can avoid having to pay an extra $10-30 per month for a static IP address, then you can save a substantial amount of money in the long-run. So while you are selecting a remote viewable security camera system or DVR, be sure to ask if it will work with a dynamic IP address. Most of the systems on the market will not utilize a dynamic IP address, which is why our Alnet Systems PC-Based DVR Cards are very popular for security camera installations. This system has built-in support for the dynamic IP addresses, so that you can view your cameras remotely, without needing to pay an extra monthly fee for a internet service provider. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lastly, look at the remote viewing options that home security camera system or DVR delivers. The remote viewing potential of standalone and PC-based DVRs vary widely from basic Internet Explorer-ONLY remote viewing via the web browser, to higher PC-Client remote viewing that offer full-resolution access to your cameras, and even Home's windows Mobile PDA phone together with Windows Mobile Smartphone rural viewing, like with our Alnet Systems PC-Based home security camera systems. With your PDA phone and Smartphone remote viewing, you are even able to connect in to see your live and pre-recorded video right from your cell phone, so that next time you are on the train together with stressing out about with certainty if you shut the car port door, you can know definitely in seconds. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your choice to install home security cameras is becoming an convenient one in today's society... but ensure when you do, that you select a process that can work for your needs. Consider the costs and remote viewing capabilities while doing so, because a cheaper DVR can sometimes cost you more in web connection costs over the long run, while providing lower-quality recording while doing so. Let the remote access help you have better peace with mind, and stay more with your largest investment, your personal property. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;For those who are generally technologically challenged, like myself, hooking up any kind of equipment has always been problematic. I know My organization is not alone. So here in detail are instructions. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First things first See the Directions. I know most guys are from this basic necessity. It's a macho thing. Once we have that out of the way you are ready to help rock. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For purposes of this article we can call the place where the hidden camera is stored-the 'house'. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To get a WIRED CAMERA: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Turn on the camera by connecting the male plug from the power supply to the feminine plug from the camera labeled power. These plugs are wires coming from the back of the camera. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Connect the cameras video output to your recording device. This is performed by, connecting a RCA cable relating to the Female connector on the wires from the back of the camera labeled video and also the video input on your recording device. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. If using a VCR you may need to adjust the video feedback, see note below. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take note.&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; To set your VCR Video Input. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51a3NlY3VyaXR5c2hvcC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;cctv cameras&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="b9a05d5285761f946b93912fa45e565c">			So when you are selecting a remote viewable security camera system or DVR, make sure to ask if it will utilize a dynamic IP address. Most of the systems on the market will not work with a dynamic IP address, which is the reason our Alnet Systems PC-Based DVR Cards have grown to be very popular for security camera installations. This system has built-in support for the dynamic IP addresses, so as to view your cameras remotely, without having to pay an extra monthly fee to your internet service provider. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lastly, look at the remote viewing options that this home security camera system or DVR delivers. The remote viewing ability of standalone and PC-based DVRs vary widely from basic Internet Explorer-ONLY remote viewing through a web browser, to more advanced PC-Client remote viewing that provide full-resolution access to ones cameras, and even Microsoft windows Mobile PDA phone and Windows Mobile Smartphone rural viewing, like with our Alnet Systems PC-Based security camera systems. With your PDA phone and Smartphone remote viewing, you are even able to connect in to see your live and pre-recorded video right from your cell phone, so that next time you will be on the train together with stressing out about whether or not you shut the garage door, you can know definitely in seconds. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The choice to install home security cameras is becoming an convenient one in today's modern culture... but ensure when you need to do, that you select a pc that can work for your needs. Consider the costs and remote viewing capabilities as well, because a cheaper DVR can sometimes cost you more in web connection costs over the long run, while providing lower-quality recording while doing so. Let the remote access allow you to have better peace with mind, and stay more connected with your largest investment, your home. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;CCTV Maintenance, Camera Systems Need Repair Too &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Everyone has had something break and has had to repair it. In many cases the repair of the device can nearly exceed the money necessary a new one. The repair or replacement of the part that failed causes downtime increases costs and frustration to the owner. CCTV systems are virtually no different. CCTV maintenance reduces costs and eliminates each of those downtime and frustration. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your car or truck requires periodic preventative repair; you change the oil and filters. You follow the service recommendations in the owners' manual. This is usually periodic maintenance. The CCTV system needs periodic CCTV repair also. The mounts that the cameras and monitors are hung from ought to be inspected to insure bolts are tight and also the mount is safe. The camera housing needs to be inspected to insure that it is watertight. The fan for cooling the within the housing and the unit to heat the houses must be checked make sure that they are working correctly. A camera that will become too hot or too cold can have a shorter lifespan than one that is kept in adequate operating temperatures. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The video signal from cameras can be compromised if the cables that are exposed to the environment are not necessarily inspected periodically. The insulation over the cables can become nullified and broken allowing weather or moisture to enter the cable and change the characteristics in the cable. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51a3NlY3VyaXR5c2hvcC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;cctv&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>