<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="dae05f42f97c49d7d287e297eec680ba">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50ZW50YW5nYnVuZGEuY29tL2NhcmEtbWVtYW5kaWthbi1iYXlpLXlhbmctYmVuYXIuaHRtbCZxdW90OyB0aXRsZT0mcXVvdDtjYXJhIG1lbWFuZGlrYW4gYmF5aQ__" target="_blank"&gt;; Cara memandikan bayi&lt;/a&gt;;  sebaiknya dicermati&lt;br /&gt;;secara sebaik-baiknya karena bayi bisa menjadi amatlah licin saat basah.&lt;br /&gt;;Pengetahuan yang memadai pada waktu menyambut kelahiran bayi &lt;br /&gt;;di rumah benar-benar sangat penting &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;agar semua kegiatan bisa dilakukan dengan benar. &lt;br /&gt;;Bayi masih begitu lemah dan tergantung pada orang tua. &lt;br /&gt;;Persiapan menyambut bayi salah satunya adalah cara memandikan bayi yang benar. &lt;br /&gt;;Anda akan memperoleh beberapa langkah untuk tahap yang berbeda. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Saat bayi baru berumur beberapa hari dnegan tali pusat yang masih menempel, &lt;br /&gt;;berlanjut pada masa mereka sudah cukup kuat menahan&lt;br /&gt;;kepala lalukemudian|dan} selanjutnya proses lain pertumbuhan motorik anak.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sebagian besar para orang tua tidak melakukannyas sendiri, &lt;br /&gt;;mereka dibantu oleh tenaga ahli baik itu paramedis ataupun para tetua daerah setempat. &lt;br /&gt;;Tali pusat yang masih menempel amat berbahaya jika terluka sekalipun sangat sedikit tergores saja, &lt;br /&gt;;selain itu kulit bayi yang baru dilahirkan sangat tipis dan masih dalam masa penyesuaian &lt;br /&gt;;dengan segala sesuatu yang baru selain air dalam rahim ibunya.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ketika pada usia 15 hari, atau masa setelah putus tali pusar, &lt;br /&gt;;mereka sudah sedikit lebih tangguh.  Sang ibu bayi biasanya telah mempersiapkan diri untuk mulai menerapkan &lt;br /&gt;;bagaimana memandikan bayi yang telah dia pelajari sebelumnya.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ae4a3e82d2945d75f4cd73686b05bf59">			Internet has opened a new era of business opportunities. Each day, thousands of new customers are joining the internet. more and more corporations are adopting web as their primary sales and distribution channel. consistent with Forrester analysis -The survey of 130 U.S. firms indicates shoppers spent $76 billion shopping on-line in 2002. This represents a 48 p.c increase over 2001, and projections for 2003 likened to $100 billion, representing 4.5 % of total retail sales.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As a business you most likely understand that in order to stay competitive you need to integrate ecommerce to your present business strategy. alittle analysis will show you that there is an in depth array of technology and solutions for enterprise and web store building out there within the market. you also perceive that ecommerce sites can price you from a mere few hundred bucks to hundreds of thousand of greenbacks. a way to opt for one thing from numerous choices that may specifically suit your present need?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although, this might seem like a frightening task, to a small degree preparation will certainly assist you taking the right call in your quest for an applicable ecommerce resolution. to grasp your demand higher and create a proper ecommerce strategy, you've got to ask yourself a number of questions. Below I jotted down a number of the queries that, hopefully, can spur your imagination.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What ought to be the look of my net store?&lt;br /&gt;;Do i need a database for my product catalog?&lt;br /&gt;;How ought to the acquisition order generate on my net store?&lt;br /&gt;;Do i need to handle totally different pricing system for dealers, wholesalers and finish customers?&lt;br /&gt;;How do I bill my customers?&lt;br /&gt;;How simple am i able to build my internet store to navigate?&lt;br /&gt;;How many search options should we tend to have?&lt;br /&gt;;Can I show my customers a product comparison table?&lt;br /&gt;;What ought to be my merchant account gateway system?&lt;br /&gt;;Finally, how much ought to I invest to build my internet store?&lt;br /&gt;;If building an ecommerce site from scratch feels too overwhelming to you and you're a small business, my suggestion is - to create an online store with one amongst the suppliers like Yahoo, Bigstep, Rusbiz etc.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The web stores that you will build directly on the net have all the necessary features like shopping cart, product catalog and payment gateway as any regular ecommerce website. In most of the cases, you construct internet store online from templates and easy-to-use editor and you hardly need to grasp html or alternative script languages.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can order your net Store from Rusbiz right now.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The benefits of using a internet store that you just can build online are enormous.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Quick to build: If you have got all the materials handy, you'll be able to build an online store among on a daily basis.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Easy in use: you do not have to be compelled to be a rocket scientist to make a fully practical ecommerce website. Step by step procedures of constructing pages from templates enable anybody to form a professionally wanting web store in no time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Affordable: though, some of the providers charge commissions on your sales, as Yahoo will, in most of the cases your expenses are but US$ 100 a month to own a decent internet store.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The only disadvantage you have with this sort of internet stores is you would possibly not be ready to give the customized look and feel to the site as you plan to. Then again, once you start generating enough sales through your net store, if you must, you'll perpetually build an ecommerce site by hiring internet style firms.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are still hesitant in beginning online business using web stores i would recommend you to scan the subsequent eventual edges that you just may have from ecommerce.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Increase your sales &amp; profits&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are a brick and mortar company, on-line commerce will certainly increase your sales and with it profits.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Enhance your company image&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Today, even tiny companies understand the importance of having a website. Planned, refined and skilled web site creates positive image of the company and help building brand name.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reduce costs and save money&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If needed options are offered on the website practically all business processes are doable to hold out on the internet, which allows you to cut back overhead costs, costs incurred as a result of documentary mistakes, document processing costs, etc.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Improve customer service&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Frequently Asked queries pages, forums, Internal Messaging Service, chat lines, etc. all these features help you effectively running your customer service.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Become a worldwide player&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thanks to the reach of internet you are now not confined to a precise geographical boundary any more. you'll sell product to any place of the globe 24 hours on a daily basis.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Add sales channels&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By joining e-marketplaces and B2B exchanges you'll be able to significantly increase the number of sales channels available to you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Reduce supply chain cycle&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you automate provide chain processes through internet, you may be able to shorten the whole cycle from months to days. you may be even ready to eliminate bound phases of your offer chain process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Market merchandise and services&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are varied ways in which of getting traffics on your web site and popularize your merchandise. In fact, you'll be able to get more individuals in your internet store than it's physically attainable to accommodate in a bricks-and-mortar search.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Compete with giant corporations&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On the web you may successfully compete with the behemoths of your industry and even curve market shares out of them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Low start-up costs&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Normally, beginning a brick and mortar business requires significant cost involvement. On the web - opposite is true! to start out a business online you hardly want any major investment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No entry barrier&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you know, several businesses in globe are tightly controlled by certain groups. On the net there is no such barrier! Anybody can begin any business of his alternative.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No need to close existing sales channels&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By adopting internet as a sales channel you are doing not loose anything as your internet store solely complements existing sales conduit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are new to ecommerce world, i might advise you to go slow! first produce an idea with future and short term objectives. try implementing your set up gradually. ensure that you do not pay an excessive amount of cash on your initial ecommerce project. Remember! Over eighty percent of all software comes don't end in time at intervals the budget; and do not work as planned! source [url=] jasa pembuatan toko online[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>