<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="338362982fb57ac7170683fc74946b1e">			A ridiculously high couple of heels is a must and platforms are again! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; High boots &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Knee or thigh boots are nevertheless on trend, styled with round or even tapering toes and stated in fabrics from lace to silk. They look fantastic with jeans or paired which includes a mini-dress with patterned tights or higher knee socks. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Shoots &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This blend of shoe and boot is incredibly flattering and versatile and you can wear them with just about anything you like. 'Shoots' are available in as comfortable or complicated a style decided on way more this year and undoubtedly are a big favourite. Look out for any cut out, open bottom, strapped and cage designs, which have been seen all over the catwalks and - as with all shoes this season - don't be afraid of a bit of colour. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Lace pumps &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lace is big for 2010 and it's so really on pumps. Many these designs include a hidden platform and tend to be super-glam. However, heels like these are typically not for the faint hearted! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Platform sandals &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ultimate heels for 2010, high-heeled platform sandals have been all around the Spring/Summer catwalks. Platforms create them slightly more comfortable than straight heels nonetheless they are certainly for the true shoe lover. On the traditional, bright colours like cherry red and yellow is a most cheerful choice with regard to spring. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Mary Janes &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ideal for the office, last year's sophisticated Margaret Jane shoes will carry on and grace our feet in 2010 but there is a cheekier twist this year with the help of retro peep-toe designs. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Flat thong sandals/gladiators &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thank goodness, some easy to use versatile flats. Flat thong sandals are perfect summer wear and they are often as casual or dressy since you like. You can put them on with most outfits and in a huge variety of shades and style. Gladiators supply a more edgy look. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Converse All Star excessive tops have been around for years, and their style and appear have not changed much since 1923. When you consider of Converse footwear you probably think of the traditional canvas shoes, and although they are still available and popular today, the leather version in the converse are even most liked. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The one universal trait we found a lot of people talk about, is how comfortable they are. Some have even said that after you have worn them in slightly, you get the feeling that you don't even know you are wearing them. On top of this the, the canvas ones are also very lightweight, when compared to other sneakers, so it you don't enjoy bulky shoes then these will be right up your block. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The base of these canvas sneakers are quite flat which makes them great to use for all sorts of different activities. However, we would not recommend them for many specialist sports or pursuits like running or boarding, as they don't have a lot of foot support to help protect your feet. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additionally, for the fashion conscious of you out there, fashion stylists agree that the black &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb252ZXJzZWFsbHN0YXJzZ29lZGtvb3AuZXU_" target="_blank"&gt;;converse sneakers&lt;/a&gt;; make an awesome look with skinny jeans and can even be worn with a number of other different clothes together with outfits too.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>