<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="ecb1d8cf8a110687cfd4a037a253e8f5">			Autumn fruiting &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3dpbmdyYXNwYmVycmllc3EuY29tL2hvdy10by1wbGFudC1yYXNwYmVycnktYnVzaGVzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;how to plant raspberry bushes&lt;/a&gt; canes will not need to be cut down till late winter, until then they could be especially kept loosely tied to counteract breaking. They make superb jam. Prune summer fruiting canes to the ground in Autumn. Prune Autumn fruiting in mid-winter or how to plant raspberry bushes. Apply fertlisier in that spring. Mulch well to retain water inside soil and don't forget the watering.&lt;br /&gt;Raising RASPBERRY Facts&lt;br /&gt;How to plant raspberry bushes possess a dual usage; berries for eating and leaves with regard to tea. Raspberry leaves can be dried and used for herbal and medicinal teas. How to plant raspberry bushes contain a?substantial amount?of antioxidants which have been proven to improve your overall vascular health. There are two main types to learn when how to plant raspberry bushes: the June-bearing and the Ever-bearing varieties. June-bearing raspberries are picked inside late spring typically for around 3 to 5 weeks and produce heavily do your best. Black raspberries don't produce as much berries, some varieties will bear fruit throughout the spring and summer, while other varieties will produce once in the spring and once inside fall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When to Vegetable rasperries&lt;br /&gt;Raspberry canes grow for 2 seasons. The first year an alternative green cane, the primocane, evolves; it develops bark, then goes dormant for any winter. The cane is referred to as a floricane in it's second year; it yields fruit, then dies. That roots, however, continue to help send up new primocanes annually. Raspberry slips are usually planted in the early spring after the bottom thaws in the To the north. In the South, you can plant raspberry slips inside fall or early springtime.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Best Locations to Plant Raspberries&lt;br /&gt;Raspberries like full sun. We tried how to plant raspberry bushes these in partial shade many years ago, and they simply never grew well. Aspects with cold winters are generally preferable for June-bearing raspberries. New varieties are being developed, though, that grow well in Southern areas. Choose soil that drains well, has high organic information, and is slightly elevated if possible. To test drainage, love a 12 inch deep by 12 inch block hole and fill that with water. If the water's drained in the hole in under 3 hours, your soil drainage is actually adequate. Don't plant too close to trees, and don't plant ones berries where raspberries have been planted recently.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Soil Prep for Raspberries&lt;br /&gt;Raspberries prefer slightly acidic soil below 7. 0 pH stage. Optimally, it should be around 6. 0, and never below 5. 5. Compost and composted manure will supply most, if not all, the nutrients needed as a result of raspberries. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3dpbmdyYXNwYmVycmllc3EuY29tL2JsYWNrLXJhc3BiZXJyaWVzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;black raspberries&lt;/a&gt; in most grocery stores are picked green and artificially ripened so they really survive shipping without bruising and go longer on the shelves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most tomato varieties can be grown very well with containers, especially cherry tomato plants, grape tomatoes, roma tomatoes, and small salad tomatoes.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b8fd70662af7753d8e236201c2a37f53">			Autumn fruiting &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3dpbmdyYXNwYmVycmllc3EuY29tL2hvdy10by1wbGFudC1yYXNwYmVycnktYnVzaGVzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;how to plant raspberry bushes&lt;/a&gt; canes will not need to be cut down until such time as late winter, until then they could be especially kept loosely tied to prevent breaking. The distance between the rows should be around 5 to 8 feet. It is a good practice to &quot;;trellis&quot;; your raspberries to keep them from falling over as the canes can grow around 8 feet tall. The way we do it is to apply 4 x 4 inch posts with 36 inch 2 x 4's nailed width wise at 2 feet from the ground and 4 feet in the ground (additionally add a third horizontally bar at 6 feet off the ground whenever you). Then string wire between the horizontal 2 x 4's to keep the canes standing vertically. During the mid to late summer time, as the primocanes are how to plant raspberry bushes rapidly, you'll must ensure, every couple of days, that the canes stay inside wires as it becomes difficult to attempt to shove them back under them once they get too tall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Having the Most from Your Raspberries&lt;br /&gt;The more bees you have in your patch, the more all berries you'll harvest. Keep the place between the rows filter free by rototilling regularly or mulching. Another option is to plant a cover head. As mentioned previously, some sort of trellis system or many other supports is key to keeping your plants up and down - and production higher. It is a superior practice, in the spring before the leaves begin how to plant raspberry bushes, to prune the tops of your floricanes to 5 or 6 feet in height. One trick for getting more fruit is to cut off the primocanes at about 30 to 36 inches. This will force them to put out branches, providing more fruit production that's easy to reach as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After your fruit has been harvested, cut off most of the dying floricanes at ground level to give the primocanes as much room as possible to grow. In the spring, thin out the brand new floricanes so that just the thickest and most robust canes remain. These will produce much more fruit than leaving most of the canes in the ground. If you need to help, you can sidedress your canes with composted manure in the spring. Usually, if you've mixed in a good amount of composted manure before the initial how to plant raspberry bushes, you shouldn't need to add much.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This past gardening season we tested a liquid organic leaf spray fertilizer called Organic Backyard garden Miracle. We sprayed the majority of our garden plants with OGM. The sprayed veggies were better quality than the un-sprayed facilities, and the flavor was superior to boot - sweeter and juicier. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3dpbmdyYXNwYmVycmllc3EuY29tL2JsYWNrLXJhc3BiZXJyaWVzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;black raspberries&lt;/a&gt; in most shops are picked green and artificially ripened so they really survive shipping without bruising and last longer on the shelves.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most tomato varieties can be grown very well in containers, especially cherry tomato plants, grape tomatoes, roma tomato plants, and small salad tomato plants.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>