<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="62412b6b1b3f9d243f4e966a844f086c">			A backlink directory is a website that provides the SEO option to add backlinks to your website, and help your website get a higher ranking on web search engines. There are many different sites that act as a backlink directory. Most often, any website that acts as an online business directory offers a backlink to your website so that it can help your site increase its page ranking in major websites such as Google, MSN, Yahoo, and others.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When using a backlink directory, you can simply submit your site to search engines, and submit your site to. You can think of the World Wide Web as a super highway. Backlinks are equivalent to the many roads on that highway leading to a certain destination. In order to get as many visitors as possible to that destination, there should be several ways to travel to it. There is no difference when it comes to websites or web pages. The more paths that are available that lead to that particular website or web page will increase the amount of visitors that reach it. Many times, a lot of sites that you can submit your site to offer a backlink to your site to help aid in this.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many people use software that can help them achieve the maximum SEO (search engine optimization) advantage by providing backlinks and submitting their site automatically to top sites so that the person can achieve a higher page ranking in the system. It also sends the page link to a backlink directory, or site that gives backlinks such as business listings or artist listings, etc. Some people actually stumble upon this accidentally. Most people don't understand that by putting their weblink to their page on various websites, they achieve a maximum advantage in creating a higher page rank on the top search engines.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fpabrikbacklink.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://pabrikbacklink.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When people are submitting their websites, the way a backlink directory works, is that it holds a large directory of different sites, and then they list those sites in a directory. At the same time that they are using a basic link exchange method, they are providing a constant backlink to the person's website. Google, MSN, Yahoo, and all of the other top engines in the world operate by seeing these backlinks and see that the higher the number of backlinks, the higher the page rank it gives the site, because all those backlinks make the site look &quot;;popular&quot;; on the web for that specific keyword, phrase, or keywords. This will all increase Google ranking for any website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are a lot of programs that are offered, from SEO Elite, and other paid programs, to SEO software that is freeware. And a lot of sites that you can submit your site to for free actually backlink your site for free as well. At the same time, there are even companies, both paid, and free, that try to do their best and have people use backlinking tools and by using a specific backlink directory in order to get you the highest page ranking on the high end search engines. So be sure to find an SEO software or service like SEO Elite to bring your site to its maximum potential and increase your business standings to make your business stronger.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A lot of times, there are tools on the market that some backlink software, and SEO software such as SEO Elite, and many others use to help a business generate backlinks to optimize their page rank and make their site the number one site on all the major search engines. This is often a tool which is a backlink finder. This tool is used to get the backlinks from other pages, so that they can create backlinks of their own to compete with competitor sites.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A backlink finder works by searching for a backlink to a particular website, say, one that you are competing with or that competes with page ranking on a search engine with your website. When you use this tool, this finder actually finds all of the backlinks and what pages they are on for that company's website, and shows you the links to those pages, then allows you to use those same sites that your competitor uses, and submit your site to provide backlinks to your own website as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fpabrikbacklink.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://pabrikbacklink.com/&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;By doing this, you increase the page rank, and the visits to your page, and thus, increase your websites overall rank value. The more backlinks you have, the higher the rank. And you can use any site's backlinks that are found to submit your site to and connect a backlink to it. When you use a backlink finder to do this, you can legally use another page's backlinks, and create one of your own. By doing this, you can have more backlinks than your competitor sites even if the content of the page you are linking to is irrelevant with the content of your site or what you are selling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Many programs, and even some services that are sold online, and even some which are free, offer a backlink finder, so that you can submit your site on the internet and show the world your page. You can almost make your page come up with whatever keywords you so choose to backlink your site to. You can also use the keywords to increase the ability to find your own site, or for people to find it which will then increase Google ranking for the website.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;People in the world today don't often know how a backlink finder works, or how backlinking works, and sometimes they stumble upon the tools by themselves without even knowing it. They submit their page to various websites, and don't know that this is actually generating traffic, and backlinks to their page. That is why some companies don't even know that they are becoming an online success until it actually happens. But the key is that backlinking is the primary way that a search engine optimizes itself to find your page, and to help you generate enough web traffic that makes people go to your page, and see your product, company, service, or even your hobby, and since people are often curious when something new and important shows up, they will find out what it is, and more and more people will actually be able to backlink to your site, buy your product or service, and increase your business revenue.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>