<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="90a9cecc973208079289e275a4cc9e72">			In feeling this sense of potential loss, I knew Flagstaff’s presence in my life had grown important and indispensable to the point where I decided that I must tell people; “Yes, Arizona is my home,” for here is where I stopped longing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What made it physically impossible for me to leave Flagstaff was when I imagined my life without San Francisco Peaks, without big imaginative skies, without omnipresent sunshine or the sweet smell of pine. All of these things bring me limitless comfort, like a best friend, after a hard day’s of school and work. This comfort I appreciate most on the evenings before the sun has completely set, when I ride my bike home from work, tired in body and mind. The first few moments of my ride home I think about how tired I am and dread all of the pedaling I have to do, but then something amazing happens, I look up. When I look up I see something so much bigger than myself, I see pink clouds floating down on the mountains, getting ready for bed, or I see the blue and gray remnants of a rainstorm, whatever it is I see it readily puts life back into my mind and body.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When I lived in Philadelphia, catching a glimpse of the skyline, especially at night, would sometimes have this same rejuvenating affect on me. I found, however, that it was only excitement I felt when seeing a big city all lit up like that. Therefore, it was not a lasting feeling. Arizona’s vistas excited me at first also, but the reason its landscape has not blended into the background of my consciousness like that of Philadelphia is because Arizona’s landscape is alive. I feel a deep love for the diverse living environment that engulfs Arizona, deeper than I could ever feel for lifeless buildings or architecture.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Arizona’s landscape is not exclusively good for looking at; it also begs to be explored. The question people often ask upon learning I live in Flagstaff is, “Isn’t there anything to do up there?” I guess since there is no venue for a Red Hot Chile Peppers concert, some think Flagstaff is a small town subject to small town boredom. While I cannot say on behalf of all Arizonans, especially not the high school population, that Flagstaff is not boring; I can personally attest that Flagstaff is anything but boring. In fact, Flagstaff becomes bigger, more interesting and multifarious to me every day, especially when I go somewhere new.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For instance, imagine my shock when, after having lived and traveled around in Flagstaff for many months, I discovered a few minutes away an underground cave almost a mile long. The cave is actually a lava tube formed millions of years ago. It was produced by a lava flow that cooled from the outside in allowing the lava inside the body of the flow to remain fluid, kind of like jelly in the center of a doughnut. In effect, when the eruptions stopped and there was no more lava coming, an empty tube-like structure was left behind. Therefore, if Maya Angelo is right and every human being longs to be at home wherever they find themselves, one who finds them self in Flagstaff, Arizona is sure to be at home.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.Tryptophans.Com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.Tryptophans.Com&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.Tusayan.Us"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.Tusayan.Us&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>