<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e93fc3ddc9588d04c612d30735381acb">			Generating traffic is hard, and many people are turning to blogs as a method to get the traffic they're looking for. You're going to also find that there are people who will simply use blogs in an attempt to make money from Adsense or affiliate programs. No matter what you are using your blog for, you will realize that you'll need to still optimize your blog in order to get the traffic you're looking for. And for people who would like to understand how to optimize your blog I will be explaining this to you in the following paragraphs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The main thing you want is to get your blog pages listed in the major search engines, as this will be one of the best ways to get targeted traffic to your pages. One of the greatest ways to ensure that your pages are being indexed is by making sure that you add all the ping sites you can into your word press dashboard to make certain your pages get indexed quickly. Your best bet for finding ping sites is to just do a search on one of the various search engines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The content of your blog will also be a big thing that you have to have to be worried about and utilizing the keyword phrases in the blog in the proper places is really important. You will have to place your keyword phrase all through the content on the page you're producing. When you're starting off you will need to generate a title for your post and you will want to be sure the keyword phrase is incorporated in the title. You will in addition want to ensure that the perma-link that points to the page of your post additionally has the keyword phrase in it. For individuals that are not aware this is what you would type in to your browser.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you begin producing the content of the page itself you'll want to be sure you use your keyword phrase throughout the article without over stuffing the keyword. The best technique to make sure you are not overdoing it's to simply add the keyword phrase once in each and every paragraph that you have within the content. When doing this it is also important to position the keyword phrase within the first sentence of the first paragraph and in the last sentence of the last paragraph. There are interesting attributes we all have because we are human, and this relates very strongly to suspending initial impressions if they seem negative until you have a complete picture. Naturally, we are talking about ideals because we know most people will have difficulty possessing such an open mind. While &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldmVyeWJvZHlsb3Zlc3Jld2FyZHMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;discount here&lt;/a&gt;; has been used successfully over the years, it may not work with your model or you just do not want to take the time to test it. Only you know, in the end, what is best for your business; even though we have encouraged you to have an open mind and test.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Basically, this is all about buyer beware, and you have the responsibility to take care of your self. Just one great danger for those who believe too quickly is they usually find themselves moving from one method to the next. The thing about this is it is totally understandable for beginners to IM to have this kind of unfortunate luck. We are not worried about what we are telling you about today, but since you do not know us - then that means you have to verify everything. That is a habit worth developing because at some point along the line it will serve you very well. This is actually a wonderful way to make certain that search engines like Google understand what your article is all about.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The last thing you need to do is to take the URL for that web page and go to all the social bookmarking sites and distribute that page to as many of those internet sites as you can. The intention of this is to get one way links pointing to the page as this will additionally help with the ranking of that page. Yet another thing you're also going to find is that you will be able to get traffic straight from the website links in the bookmarking sites. If you adhere to the suggestions above you are going to realize that you will be acquiring the traffic you need and want.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Resources:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FuZHloZXNhcmdlbnQubGl2ZWpvdXJuYWwuY29tLzYyODMuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;When Adding Content To Your Blog Make Certain It Is Optimized For The Various Search Engines&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kZW1vY3JhdGFuZGNocm9uaWNsZS5jb20vYXBwcy9wYmNzLmRsbC9zZWN0aW9uP2NhdGVnb3J5PVBsdWNrUGVyc29uYSZhbXA7VT03M2JiMTM3N2YxN2E0MWQ1YmJjYjYzMzMwZDQyNWIzYiZhbXA7cGxja1BlcnNvbmFQYWdlPUJsb2dWaWV3UG9zdCZhbXA7cGxja1VzZXJJZD03M2JiMTM3N2YxN2E0MWQ1YmJjYjYzMzMwZDQyNWIzYiZhbXA7cGxja1Bvc3RJZD1CbG9nJTNhNzNiYjEzNzdmMTdhNDFkNWJiY2I2MzMzMGQ0MjViM2JQb3N0JTNhZWZjYTg3MmMtOGJjMi00YzJlLWEzNGYtNTk4OWMxM2Y0MDFhJmFtcDtwbGNrQmxvZ0l0ZW1zUGVyUGFnZT01" target="_blank"&gt;;The Various Search Engines Are Looking For Search Engine Optimized Web Pages&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]The Various Search Engines Are Looking For Search Engine Optimized Internet Pages[/url]		</conversation>		<conversation id="9528266d4db66834ad0c5d47611a5903">			Men and women are always looking for new ways for making money online. One thing you'll find is a large number of internet marketers will invest in all the new programs that come out which promise to enable them to start making more money. But if you consider it, E-books have always been a wonderful way to earn money online. And you should also realize that this is also going to be a profitable technique for some time in the future. With regards to creating and selling E-books we are going to teach you how to do that here.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In case you are selling information that folks want, you will see that men and women will end up buying it. But one thing you need to recognize is that unless you're selling information that individuals want you will find that you will not make any revenue. For the most part you will find that people will not be interested in an E-book that can teach them the fastest method to change the tires on their automobiles. But if you decide to write an E-book on how to get better gas mileage with any car, you might find that because of the price of gas, people might be willing to spend some cash on a book that will show them how to save cash on gas. With that being said, if you have reliable information, it's going to sell, but if you have worthless information you'll be wasting your time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You should also use this same theory if you intend to buy the resale rights to E-books. I am sure some of you don't really know what resale right E-books are, and just so that you know, this is something you can sell to folks time and time again when you purchase the rights. Additionally you need to bear in mind that you need to get the rights to E-books with information that people actually want.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will also need a website, this is how you're going to have the ability to have a web page to advertise your E-book. Some folks generally hire someone to create their internet sites for them, but if you feel you are up to the challenge, you can build the site yourself. When you decide on a domain name for your website be sure that it pertains to your E-book. A domain name like bettergasmileage.com, would really be a terrific domain name for someone selling an E-book that shows individuals how to get better gas mileage. If you want people to be able to find your site, be sure your domain as well as the content of your internet site is associated with each other.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're willing to set up a site to sell an E-book, and put time into proper SEO, you will find that this can be extremely profitable. You need to remember that information is power and when you sell information that men and women want and need, you'll be able to make more cash.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you take a look at what is here, you will see that these are rock solid pieces of advice on the subject matter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are so many who have been helped with information just like this, and we also know that on our own end. You can easily find tremendous amounts of information on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldmVyeWJvZHlsb3Zlc3Jld2FyZHMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;discounts on everything&lt;/a&gt;;, and there are relevant sites that are very helpful. But do not rush into anything especially when it comes to moving forward on the data you find.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another thing, though, is that as you probably know very well; you can locate excellent related content that will be helpful. Try to avoid getting to scattered with what you choose to do based on this information, and it is always a good idea to limit your activities to something that you favor for whatever reason.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Resources:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FuZHloZXNhcmdlbnQubGl2ZWpvdXJuYWwuY29tLzY0MDYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Earning Money With E-Books Is Actually Achievable If You Understand How To Do It&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aG91Z2h0cy5jb20vYmxvZy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Earning Cash With E-Books Is Actually Possible If You Know How To Do It&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]You Will See That You Can Make Money Along With E-Books[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>