<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c889fb08bbc137604f34b9b084573c2c">			Green Smoke Coupons Review:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We have tried over 98% of these products out there and Green Smoke e cigs consistently enjoy the highest volume of smoke (ie: vapor)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While green smoke coupons are my number 1 choice overall for look, taste and feel I also this way I know I am addressing a very solid company. (I have yet to identify a better product with better customer support construction business. They are no small players. You may have seen them for a NASCAR sponsor for TJ Bell.) Therefore you are at no risk in trying green smoke coupons and validating this for yourself. Like all the brands that made our list they provide for a 30 day cash back guarantee (plus they back up almost all their products with a one season warranty.)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Green Smoke Coupons deserve lots of credit as they were the first company to offer a cleaner easier to use 2 part design for e cigarettes. They also use high quality lithium ion batteries and designed the tip so it will start blinking you have always wanted to recharge. They make disposable electronic smokes too but with a return policy which you could basically try their products without the need of risk I think your money can buy the starter kit or even the social smoker kit is a better deal. (The main difference between the starter kit vs the social kit is your starter kit comes with two batters to help you always have a fully charged battery handy.)&lt;br /&gt;;Green Smoke Coupons have also started offering a color choice in the LED light at the tip that lights up when you inhale. For a long time My partner and i preferred red because I liked the realistic look but now you get a choice of two in the starer kit plus it was a smart idea. If youre looking to enjoy your electronic cigarette in a great deal of places where smoking is generally banned like restaurants then the green tip allows you to avoid any comments from individuals who thing youre smoking regular cigarettes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Our tip regarding the battery may be to sure you charge your battery long enough to get the full vapor effect. I also love to charge up the battery just before its fully drained. (Increases battery life.) Their long battery lasts about long enough to do to enjoy ten to 11 cigarettes!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Bottom line, there are good quality brands on the market that are less expensive (and I most certainly will review them here) but if you want what Ive found as probably the most reliable quality (to me any variety of hassle is no bargain) and also the most realistic smoking experience then Id have to say go with Green Smoke cigarettes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Update: Back in July they also released a new Flavor Max cartridge that lets you get 360 puffs per cartridge and about 25% more vapor. They were already the leader in vapor production so must say I am impressed!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Entertaining Facts:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Starter kits include a membership card to your wallet. Just show any waitress, pickup's cab driver etc. the card plus it clearly explains that an egic is completely safe and allowed in sites where smoking is banned.|&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Again here is my &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lY2lnY291cG9uei5jb20vZ3JlZW4tc21va2UtY291cG9uLWNvZGUtZGlzY291bnQtcHJvbW8_" target="_blank"&gt;;green smoke coupons&lt;/a&gt;; that you should use to save Five Percent for orders under 1 hundred dollars. Or you can use my GreenSmoke Coupons to save 10 percent on orders over $100 dollars.&lt;br /&gt;;green smoke coupon 5%  = DISC5-25830&lt;br /&gt;;greensmoke coupons ten precent = DISC10-25380		</conversation>	</conversations></author>