<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="5aa20a21707fb70e2f3f8ba5707a2b47">			Ambit Energy distinguishes themselves from the MLM network marketing industry that is dominated by health and wellness companies promoting everything from lotions, juices and pills, candles,&amp;amp;nbsp; to magnetic patches and purifiers. It can be hard to truly compare the opportunity we have with Ambit Energy to everything else out there because the products are so different, but check out these 7 compelling reasons to ditch the lotions and potions and get electrocuted with Ambit Energy
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Ambit Energy Brings Irrefutable Customer Value
&lt;br /&gt;;Ambit Energy must offer value since nobody would switch to us if it were going to raise their electricity or natural gas bill. This is a far cry from most mlm network marketing products which are not exactly a bargain...in fact most products in the mlm network marketing industry are marked up so there is more to pay out in the compensation plan. Of course most mlm network marketing products are far superior to what you find in stores, but wouldn't be nice if you could represent a product/service with irrefutable customer value.
&lt;br /&gt;;2.Ambit Energy brings just that kind of customer value to the plate. In most states we operate with a written guarantee of savings which means that we guarantee customers are going to save money. NOBODY else in the marketplace thus far has been willing to put that kind of faith forward to their customers. Not only does Ambit Energy put in writing but we've been backing it up for 3 years now. In Texas it is not possible to provide a written guarantee of savings, but in most cases the savings is far greater than what we can guarantee elsewhere.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With Ambit you can develop a rock solid residual income by bringing real customer value and savings to a service in electricity and natural gas that is a significant part of every family budget in America. What better value proposition and business plan is there?
&lt;br /&gt;;3. Ambit Energy Does Not Require Changing Buying Habits
&lt;br /&gt;;It sounds like a great concept; buy online and save, or buy through this catalog and get better products, or get this supplement every month because it has more of xyz ingredient...the problem is that people don't like change. We never have and never will. Most MLM network marketing businesses require you to get people to change their buying habits to use your products. People want what they want when they want it.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ambit Energy does not require you to change customer buying habits.People are already writing out a check every month to pay their gas and electric bill. With Ambit Energy the only thing that changes is the amount of the bill..its less! Switching to Ambit Energy is a painless 5 minute process, doesn't cost a dime and is completely seamless. The lights won't even flicker in the switchover process...Ambit Energy guarantees in writing.
&lt;br /&gt;;4. Goodbye Begging &amp;amp; Convincing...Hello Ambit Energy
&lt;br /&gt;;I hate to break it to you but most people are not accustomed to buying health products on an auto-ship basis every month. I realize not every MLM network marketing company sells health related products, but in most cases you are dealing with a situation where you have to convince people to spend more money on products or services they we're not already accustomed to spending money on. They may give it a try for you but rarely are they going to stick with it long term.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ambit Energy deals with a utility that enjoys 100% acceptance in the marketplace. Somewhere around 99.99% of Americans pay an electric and/or gas bill and the opportunity to switch providers has just been introduced with the recent deregulation of energy. There is a massive shift in the marketplace right now and Ambit Energy is smack dab in the middle of it. Energy will only deregulate once and it is happening right now with or without you....Ambit Energy is your ticket to grabbing a piece of this last and largest industry ever to deregulate.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>