<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2cb91b851894f3fdf824b1307378b21c">			Residential fire safety is without a doubt a big deal. In the United States there is a good record of home fire safety and numerous governmental and private testing organizations make sure the products we purchase are safe. Many products are labeled with logo's and declarations of safety by testing agencies like Underwriters Laboratories and TUV Rheinland. When we encounter a product that is not safe, sometimes the results are catastrophic. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When dangerous products are identified we've the U.S. Consumer Product Safety Commission to report unsafe products to. The U.S. CPSC will investigate and initiate a recall if necessary. The consumer electronics industry did much to insure that people are safe inside their homes from fire caused by electronic devices. The television industry decided that TV's in America would be safe by making sure no flammable parts are exposed to electronic devices that could throw off a spark way back in the 1970's.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Consumer electronics have many parts that could throw off a spark such as resistors, diodes, transistors and capacitors. Simple overloads or component malfunction could cause a condition generating tiny fires inside your television or stereo. Voltage surges because of lightning as well as electric company problems are one of the primary factors that cause electronic part failure. A voltage spike may cause a sudden failure or a delayed (or latent) failure of these components.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When an electronic part fails, it may merely cease conducting electricity or open the circuit it is in or it might short the circuit. Short circuits could cause excessive heating of the component in question or surrounding circuits. This excessive heating might cause a little fire inside your electronic device and is often seen outside the cabinet as a puff of smoke as well as bad smell coming from the device.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It truly is essential that this tiny bit of fire can not be utilized to ignite any surrounding flammable material and create a more substantial and more serious fire. In American televisions, the plastic cabinets are made from fire resistant material and even though you can burn a hole in the cabinet with a torch, the fire goes out when the torch is taken away.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There exists a internet site where a customer that had a ‘whole house’ audio unit catch fire within his home and he details his experience with the manufacturer, Russound and also the testing agency TUV Rheinland. The Russound CAV caught fire in his home and burned outside the cabinet. He was able to extinguish the fire with a fire extinguisher, but if he was not home, his home and family might have been lost.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Instead of admit there was a problem with the product,  a Russound executive threatened to sue the customer if he told anybody about the fire. There was a CPSC recall of the product, but the prescribed fix for the CAV audio unit left  the combustible material exposed to all the components capable of burning up. Russound and TUV Rheinland instead made the decision  to put a fuse in line with only one component that can emit a spark. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Neither Russound nor the testing agency, TUV Rheinland examined the Russound CAV6.6 system that caught fire prior to proclaiming the defect and prescribing a fix. The question is: Would you sleep better with consumer electronics that can’t catch fire, or products like those built by Russound and tested by TUV Rheinland that probably won’t catch fire? You decide. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itsonfire.org%2Frussound.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.itsonfire.org/russound.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.itsonfire.org%2Ftuvrheinland.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.itsonfire.org/tuvrheinland.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DizHY0VfQ7rE"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=izHY0VfQ7rE&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>