<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="fecfa09460824e1ad9f99e78891f01bd">			24 / 08 / 2012the 19th of August 2012, we burried our sister,Mariette Nel, who died of a stroke, age 46. Last year, also in Agust, we burried our mom, this year our steph-sister. August is NOT a god month for our family, because disaster strucked 2ce in a row, concerning death.My steph-mom's cancer is growing vigourlously, and her daughter's death on top of it, is realy geting her under. She is a good woman, mom and friend! Why does she have to suffer this much on earth??? Burrying your kids is the worst experience ever. You tend to loose interest in life, mourning never ends, longing for the departured is a torture, and feeling so alone can kill you, slowly but surely!My steph-family does NOT want anybody to mention my steph-sister's death in front of my steph-mom, and I feel this IS SO WRONG! How are you supposed to mourn when the subject of death isn't allowed?? Mourning is a MUST in times like this, talking about your feelings, is the only way to deal with the loss of a loved-one. Avoiding the subject, you are supressing the reality of the situation, which WILL have bad consequinces! Been there, done that. When my child died, I did not give myself time to mourn her death, until I realised it is affecting my way of thinking, and had nightmares about my daughter's death for years, Just because I preferred to ignore the hurt, pain and longing for her. I finally went for professional help about this problem, and I did get the needed help. Today, I can talk about my late child, although I still long for her, all the time. Death of a loved-one is a whole process you have to go through, in order to deal with it, not a one-night-stand-thing!! So please people, ALLOW YOURSELF TO MOURN, it is only for the best. It is also a matter of taking life day-by-day, thinking of your loss, what that person meant to you in life, your feelings need to be lifted by talking about it, NOT AVOIDING IT! If you feel alone at times like this, IT IS NATURAL, you are not alone, when you have lots of family members and friends to rely on, considder yourself lucky, because there are many people who do not have this advantage in life!This message is specially for my family and steph-family, who need to hear it from someone who has been through this ordeal, several times in life. I DO know what I'm taliking about, Experience taught me all of this. Sad, BUT TRUE.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f79e7c1d63f7db2d974605a71d9915aa">			I've learned a good lesson about family-relationships, and how to maintain it. I was as child, in a difficult love-and-hate relationship with my mom. We grew further apart as time went by, lost communication, and grew into strangers towards each other. She was finally living in Bonnievale, Western-Cape, while I'm living in Gauteng, most of my adult-life, when she passed away in August, 2011. At the time when we attended the funeral, mixed emotions got the hold on me, as well as regrets about the way things could have been better, if only I wasn't so consumed with hate for her actions towards us, over the years... Crying over spilled milk is a waste of time and energy, but somehow I couldn't help myself thinking about it. I did considder myself tough, but with my mom's death, I realised that how much I missed her input, love and presence, in my llife, although there were none of these things at all, and how vulnerable I realy were. Somehow I lost the abillity to maintain the 'tough' face, but the wall cracked as soon as I got the bad news about her death...I just couln't handle her discriminations, lies and deceipt towards my late dad, and grew into a cold-hearted person over the years, which complicated my life majorly! On top of it, it was a terrible experience, which can only lead to self-destuction. Unadabted teenagers become unadapted adults, and moving forward, is mission impossible. Finally, with my mom's death, I decided I need closure about that part of my life, and for that reason I attended the funeral. Now I've got the closure, and I'm ready for life, again!My message; People, please, if you have been in a similar position as I me, make an efford to respect your parents/ family-members, friends, no matter how deep the are in the dirt, IT STAYS YOU LOVED-ONES, forever. When they die, it IS TOO LATE for doing the right thing! The right thing is due while still alive, but after death, you're also out of time!! Accept each other for who they are, NOT OTHERWISE. Sharon.		</conversation>		<conversation id="2dda73e787648e9e396117f27f4bf662">			Yahoo! Mail: The best web-based email!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>