<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ae118f690417f9e49f4dc5123366a7c6">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raW50dWV4cGVkaXRpb25zLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;INCA TRAIL CUSCO PERU&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;KINTU EXPEDITIONS specialists operate Inca Trail (Expert Tour Operators), we are one of the leading operating this route since 2002. We are an authorized Agency to enter the Inca Trail, 2010 - AG 1431 and also with INRENA (National Institute of Natural Resources).
&lt;br /&gt;;Kintu Expeditions(inca trail cusco peru) specialists to operate the route of the Inca Trail, with a professional staff, professional guides, porters and our chefs.
&lt;br /&gt;;We are a legally established in Cusco, the capital of the ancient Inca Empire. No other agency offers the best prices for travel to Machu Picchu. See our advantages we offer: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Kintu Expeditions doing programs Travel to Machu Picchu to your needs since 2002.
&lt;br /&gt;;We do not define the starting date nor return, the traveler decides when to go and when to return. We customize the program according to the interests of our travelers as they have availability.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We offer the passenger a safe journey comfortable. With advance reservations, with a guarantee of a travel contract to a low value on our tours that charged by other agencies. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In our menu of programs we can make suggestions about programs on traveling to Machu Picchu. We can make any modifications you want in the programs, we are also specialists in meeting the special demands which you want to Tours in Peru, as a honeymoon, tours and more. Applicable at any time of year. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raW50dWV4cGVkaXRpb25zLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Inca trail cusco peru&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Dates
&lt;br /&gt;;We have groups for the Inca Trail every day of the year. Least February when the Inca Trail is closed throughout the month. The months of February you can visit Machu Picchu by train or walking cleaves one of the old walking alternatives we have. But it will not be possible to walk the Inca Trail.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Availability
&lt;br /&gt;;They allowed only 500 people per day Inca Trail. This number includes tourists, guides, porters and cooks. The quotas are for everyone, people who want to do the Inca Trail. So to walk the Inca Trail is essential to book months in advance.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The availability of quotas for the Inca Trail is the same for all agencies. Thus, if there were available no agency can get space for the Inca Trail cusco peru.
&lt;br /&gt;;PROGRAM
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Day 1: Cusco - Km 104 - Wiñayhuayna - Aguas Calientes: 
&lt;br /&gt;;Being 6.00 in the morning we will pick the Hotel to make the move to the train station to catch our train to Km 104 where the Inca Trail starts short. After we visited off at km 104 Chachabamba (2250 m). The trek continues with a visit to Wiñayhuayna (forever young) for some was the former home of former priests of Machu Picchu. On the way visit fantastic scenery of the Urubamba River. We will make a brief stay in Machu Picchu at the end of the afternoon we descend to the village of Aguas Calientes. Overnight at selected hotel. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5raW50dWV4cGVkaXRpb25zLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Inca trail cusco peru&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Day 2: Aguas Calientes - Machu Picchu - Aguas Calientes - Cusco: 
&lt;br /&gt;;After breakfast well served at the Hotel Machu Picchu climb on foot. Guided tour of the main temples of Machu Picchu for about 2 hrs. And free time to climb Huayna Picchu visit. In the afternoon we descend to Aguas Calientes where we will have to return to Ollanta train and then bus to Cusco. Inca trail cusco peru
&lt;br /&gt;;Huaynapicchu is located behind the mountain where Machu Picchu in order to take up aerial view of the Inca citadel. There is a checkpoint at Machu Picchu to climb Huayna Picchu. You must enter your name and receive a ticket to climb Huayna Picchu. The guide directs how to get the ticket, but need not pay anything more. Only 400 people can visit a day divided into two shifts. Machu Picchu receives over 1000 visitors a day and generally lacking quotas to climb Huayna Picchu. No book has before. Generally, travelers arriving by other paths get quotas because they reach Machu Picchu more earlier. In order to get better up early and watch the sunrise.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.kintuexpeditions.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.kintuexpeditions.com/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>