<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b0814e57a8f2c96d26aab13d9a6f9d0c">			1, '22.  Because the 1918 Pittman’s  Act requirements were met during 1928, no Peace silver  Dollars had been made from '29 thru 1933.  Once the line ended in 1935 ; over one hundred ninety million Silver Peace Dollars overall minted.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Peace dollar was created via a youthful, thirty four year old, Italian immigrant engraver Anthony de Francisci during 1921. The schedule had been limited for the pattern  competition and not taking a chance to obtain a professional to posse Anthony de Francisci  asked his wife, Teressa, to be his muse representing Liberty’s head. &lt;br /&gt;;These were all 38.1mm in diameter, with a mass of 26.73g, made from 90% silver and 10 % copper, consequently possessing .7734oz of silver, the  edge will be reeded.&lt;br /&gt;;Its obverse has Liberty with a crown of rays, just like the Statue of Liberty’s.  Her  long locks are up, apart from the windblown locks around her face.  The date  arcs under Liberty together with “LIBERTY” encompasses over.  “IN.GOD.WE” appears on the lower portion having her throat splitting “TRVST”.  The  replacement using the “V” as the “U” within trust was its throwback to its first pattern that utilized Roman numerals for its year.  Francisci's  initials will be under her throat wherever her shoulder could have been.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Its tails has a bald eagle perched on a rock  holding an olive branch.  This stone has “PEACE” on it.  There's solar rays coming in the lower portion, depicting the sun rise.  “ONE” runs over its bottom 3rd of this coinage separated by the bald eagle followed by “DOLLAR”.  Surrounding its very top rim is “UNITED.STATES.OF.AMERICA” and directly below is “E.PLURIBUS.UNIM”.  The mark of the mint (“D” for Denver, “S” as in San Francisco, there won't be one for Philadelphia), will be under its “ONE” and higher than the eagle folded wings.&lt;br /&gt;;When the United States’ Congress passed its Pittman Act on 4/23/1918, they decided that they would offer England up to 350 million silver us dollars  out of the Treasury’s stockpile of Morgan silver dollars.  The Treasury would be  expected to substituted the 270,232,722 Morgan dollars that were  melted down and sold.  This had been 47% of all the silver Morgan  dollars that had been minted.  Members within the American Numismatic Association   began pushing for a silver dollar to honor the victory  regarding Europe's Great War.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Peace Dollar idea required a while to materialize  for upon 5/9/1921 the US Mint started minting the Morgan  dollar again.  Eventually on the 19th of Nov.  '21 a competition to get a Peace silver Dollar commenced with the  submissions due upon 12/11/1921 and on the 12th Francisci’s design was picked.  During their haste to get the dies ready at its  Philly facilities alterations were made by Morgan on the primary  die drums.  These reliefs had been somewhat high ,they were corrected during  '22 after Philly already minted over thirty-five thousand Peace silver  Dollars most amongst these high relief coins were retained then  melted down.  This Peace Dollar is the only USA's coin possessing “peace” on it.  These happened to be the end regarding  silver dollar business production in the US.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvZWN3cGN4dW9lYXdzcXJzdHlyYmcvY29udGVudC9hLXBlYWNlLWRvbGxhci1zaWx2ZXItY29pbi01MDQ3NTQy" target="_blank"&gt;;A Peace silver dollar Coin &lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="57df1cfed08ce93d01792935ccb45249">			The timetable was limited for their pattern  contest and not taking time to find a model Anthony de Francisci  asked his spouse, Teressa, as the model representing Liberty’s face. &lt;br /&gt;;The Peace dollars were all 38.1 mm in diameter, weigh 26.73g, composed of ninety percent silver and ten percent copper, consequently possessing .7734 ounces of silver, its  edge will be reeded.&lt;br /&gt;;Its front shows Liberty wearing the crown with rays, just like the Statue of Liberty’s.  Liberty's  lengthy locks are up, apart from the windblown hair close to her face.  Its year  encompasses underneath Liberty together with “LIBERTY” arches around  on top of.  “IN.GOD.WE” appears in its lower portion with the throat splitting “TRVST”.  The  substitution using a “V” as the “U” in trust was a homage towards the first design that used Roman numerals representing its mintage.  Francisci's  initials will be under Liberty’s neck where Liberty's upper arm could have been.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The back has a eagle standing on a stone  clutching an olive branch.  This stone has “PEACE” upon it.  There's solar rays emerging from its bottom portion, representing the sun rise.  “ONE” runs across the bottom third of this coinage  divided with the bald eagle followed by “DOLLAR”.  Around its very apogee side will be “UNITED.STATES.OF.AMERICA” and underneath there's “E.PLURIBUS.UNIM”.  A mark of the mint (“D” for Denver, “S” for San Francisco, and nothing for Philly), will be under the “ONE” yet above the bald eagles folded wings.&lt;br /&gt;;After the US' lawmakers passed its Pittman Act upon April 23, 1918, they committed that they would sell Great Britain as much as 350.000.000 silver dollars  via the Treasury’s stockpile of Morgan silver dollars.  Its Treasury would be dedicated to substituted the 270 million plus Morgan dollars that were  melted down then traded.  It had been forty-seven percent from every Morgan silver dollars which was minted.  People within the ANA   began to push for a dollar silver coin to memorialize America's victory  of the World War I.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Their Silver Peace Dollar concept took a while to come into being  for upon the 9th of May '21 the Mint began making the silver Morgan dollar once more.  At last on November 19th, 1921 a competition to get a Silver Peace Dollar commenced having all  submissions expected upon the 11th of Dec. the following day Francisci’s design was picked.  In the haste to get the master dies ready at its  Philly facilities alterations had to be done via Morgan upon the primary  die drums.  These reliefs were somewhat tall and were corrected during  1922 however Philadelphia already made 35,401 Silver Peace Dollars almost all amongst these higher portrait coins had been kept and  smelted.  The Peace silver Dollar is the only USA's coinage possessing “peace” issued. &lt;br /&gt;;The Pittman Act dollar silver coin replacements were completed during 1928 therefore  zero Peace Dollars were made during '29 until '34.  Congress approved a law responding to record low silver rates.  The US Mint was compelled to procuring silver by United States mines and make coinage with it, thus turning a profit.  The Silver Peace Dollar ended  up being struck in 1934 in addition to '35.  These marked the conclusion regarding  silver dollar business strikes for these United States Of America.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2dyb3Vwcy5kaWlnby5jb20vZ3JvdXAvZWN3cGN4dW9lYXdzcXJzdHlyYmcvY29udGVudC9hLXBlYWNlLWRvbGxhci1zaWx2ZXItY29pbi01MDQ3NTQy" target="_blank"&gt;;A silver Peace dollar Coin &lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>