<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="21701867d534b31d108093a662b9efb3">			Solawise are a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;renewable energy&lt;/a&gt; company specialising in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;Solar Photovoltaic&lt;/a&gt;  and environment friendly power solutions.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/183054885_8376449_48794513.jpg" /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="74117b8a4d77e25cfb65f0550be08012">			&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/183054885_12749406_49096041.jpg" /&gt;
&lt;br /&gt;Solar Power – It is a renewable source of energy which converts solar energy into electrical energy by using the mechanism of solar panels. There is lots of research being carried out for making the maximum use of solar panels. For example in India there is a state called Gujarat which is having 1900 kms of canals. A pilot project has been recently launched where in the solar panels are installed above the canals. There are two advantages of this. The first one is that power is generated. The second reason is that water evaporation has reduced. There are various &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;solar power companies&lt;/a&gt; in the market. Hence it is highly advisable to go with the known and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;branded solar company&lt;/a&gt;. Making the right choice while &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;selecting the solar power company&lt;/a&gt; is highly essential, else it may result in to a costly affair.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Solawise is one such company which specializes in Solar Photovoltaic and provides environment friendly power solutions. The solar panels produce Direct current (DC) which is converted to Alternating Current (AC) with the help of inverter. Solawise is having a team of experts, who guide from beginning till handing over. Solar panels are available in different shapes, size, colors etc. It is &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zb2xhd2lzZS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;Solawise&lt;/a&gt;, who will identify the best solar panel after conducting the survey at your premises.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>