<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b5e78076d142fb9cca23d9e0bd2fb9e7">			You will usually create pages for Me, Contact Information, together with Legal Disclosure. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10. Change your theme. You can change your theme at any time by going to the &quot;Appearance&quot; tab, &quot;add innovative themes&quot;. There you will have a selection of features that you may choose from for your blog design. Once you find a design which you like, you simply click &quot;install&quot;, and then &quot;activate&quot;. Your new chosen theme will appear with all your web site entries. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After you have done these steps, you are done creating your blog. Now you are willing to start blogging. Bloggers usually update their blogs on a regular basis. The more time and dedication you give that, the better you can make it. It is a number of fun and a great way to market yourself. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Blogging is big business these days and if you are looking for a quick way to start earning a few bucks online then having your own blog is absolutely essential. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are two main types that To get the cheapest having a look with - Wordpress (for any more advanced among people) and Blogger. com (for beginners) &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A wordpress blog is definitely the better of the two because you can actually control the design, entries and all the plugins that come with it but if you might have very little background in using the internet or HTML code you may want to hire someone to push the button for you. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you need to do it yourself I suggest starting by getting a Blogger. com account for nothing. Blogger. com is owned by Google and some great features that are easy to build. Plus anything owned by way of the largest search engine company in the world is worth checking out. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here are the steps to setting up a Blogger. com blog of your own. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. First of all log online and go to blogger. com. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;two. Find the orange arrow that says &quot;Create your blog now&quot; and click on it. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Enter a user name and password, along with the name of your blog and your email address. Write down your customer name and password. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try and use the same customer name and password you make use of for other things. Your password should contain at least 2 letters and the rest can be numbers. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;several. Click &quot;Continue&quot; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Next enter a title for a blog such as &quot;All About Golf&quot; and a blog address. The address will be part of the web address for a blog. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For example, if you type &quot;allaboutgolf&quot; your blog address would be allaboutgolf. blogspot. com. That's the address you'll give to anyone who wants to visit your blog. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choosing a name that relates to the theme of your blog is advisable. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. Now you may choose a template which is how your blog can look. Whatever template you select it is possible to change it later without the need of losing any content so don't worry if you're not 100% sure you like it at this stage. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. Mouse click &quot;Continue, &quot; and Blogger. com will create your blog. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And there you have it, 7 simple steps on developing a blog!! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After getting finished these steps simply go through the &quot;Start Posting&quot; button and just write something. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZ21lbnRvci5jb20vc2VvLXNlcnZpY2VzLWNhbmFkYS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;SEO Services Canada&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>