<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="84ee7fd8cae638fab9ee4fdffe8da95a">			When accessing a VPN, all information uploaded, downloaded, or otherwise transmitted is encrypted, ensuring that anyone who views the transmissions is denied the ability to read or use it. Even other users from other segmented intranets on the same VPN provider are not given access to the information, so your browsing or sharing session is completely privatized.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Proxy Servers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often confused with VPNs, proxy servers also provide a tunnelled connection to the Internet. However, they provide a completely different avenue of service. Proxy providers give you a way to circumvent specific restrictions and access the Internet through another, international, location. This is important when government restrictions prevent you from viewing specific websites. What they do not do, however, is encrypt your browsing session, which can still leave you vulnerable to cyber-attacks or spyware.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When you are using a VoIP platform, for example, your VPN provider will encrypt everything, guaranteeing that your conversation remains private. If you have the same VoIP conversation via a proxy server, you may avoid specific roadblocks along the way, but ultimately the information is still floating &quot;;out in space&quot;;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Speed is another discrepancy involves the speed of Internet access. Virtual private networks will always tend to run a bit faster than proxy servers largely in part because of the technology employed. When you access via a proxy server, the proxy sends a request to the site, which then sends the information back, and directly connects you to the website. VPNs tend to work faster, partly due to the better hardware/network that is typically being used with such a service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use a virtual private network to prevent prying eyes from stealing your personal information, maintain a high browsing speed, and ultimately protect yourself from any other cyber-threats that exist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In this guide we will look over how to use an internet connection on an airplane and what is VPN access. More and more of us are travelling for business and pleasure so the use of our iPhones is a hugely important part of both. Having an internet connection on an airplane for short or long distance travel is now a must for any business person.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your iPhone can be a source to your email, web and other business documents stored online, so by having a constant internet connection while travelling will greatly benefit your business needs. Protect your iPhone with iPhone 4 skins or iPhone 3gs cases when you travel as the damage during this period is more likely.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Airplane mode on your iPhone turns off mobile, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth and GPS signals to avoid interfering with aircraft operations. Airplane mode will disable many of the iPhone features. Many countries now allow the use of Wi-Fi while in Airplane mode so that you are able to:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Send and receive email&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Browse the web&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sync you contacts, notes and calendars&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stream videos&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access map locations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access weather updates&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;Buy music and apps&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In some countries the use of Bluetooth is also allowed to use with your Bluetooth devices on the iPhone. If you are using a VPN at a hotel or other public location then the connection can be slow and unreliable, this is due to the unmanaged connection and the amount of people that access the network at the same time will slow the network connection down.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXJlc2VsbGVy" target="_blank"&gt;buy vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;secure vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWF1cw__" target="_blank"&gt;fast vpn service&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVz" target="_blank"&gt;uk vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWNh" target="_blank"&gt;europe vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dnBu" target="_blank"&gt;buy vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVr" target="_blank"&gt;strong vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank"&gt;online vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWR5bmFtaWM_" target="_blank"&gt;buy online vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXNldmVyYWw_" target="_blank"&gt;best vpn&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="6874bea247f65c8a84fecf66867096c4">			Reviewing some more networking equipment. Both run Cisco's well renown adaptive security appliance, The AIP SSC-5 and the AIP SSM-10. These are 2 slightly differently built items, but have the same sake. Rapidly deployable, and easily manageable they enable small businesses, branch offices and enterprise teleworker environments to minimize operation costs. All come with functions like firewall protection, intrusion prevention, antivirus, worm scanning, malware protection.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The SSM-10 is rack-mountable, while the cheaper SSC-5 is an external hardware. The SSC-5 has a total of 1 expansion slots, and an Intel Celeron 1.60 GHz processor, 256 mega of installed RAM, 64 MB of flash memory, the firewall's throughput is 150 Mbps, while VPN throughput is 100 Mbps, can handle 10 IPSec VPN peers and 2 SSL VPN peers. Confronted with the SSM-10's features, the SSC-5 seems puny. While having the same amount of flash memory, and RAM, the SSM-10 can handle 50 IPSec VPN peers, and 50 Web VPN peers, runs 6k concurrent sessions (32k in virtualization).&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These excellent items might non function through time, in that case, I don't recommend buying new ones, instead send them to get repaired, or at least buy used ones. Dominating prices lead to a certainly under-estimated second hand market, which still has to show us it's true potential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After all, if it's checked, you got to consider this is not something you wear, and should be seen, instead, a repaired unit will function the same way as a new one does. Save the planet!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These excellent items might non function through time, in that case, I don't recommend buying new ones, instead send them to get repaired, or at least buy used ones. Dominating prices lead to a certainly under-estimated second hand market, which still has to show us it's true potential.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;VPN Services and Proxy Services - An Important Distinction&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;As we work our way through Virtual Private Networks and how they can be utilized to ensure that Internet security is never compromised, it's important to distinguish the difference between VPNs and Proxy Servers. Once they are defined, our hope is that you have a better understanding of the differences and the various elements that can leave you unsecured with one of them. While both can grant you access to websites even if you are in a nation that censors the internet, only one of them can protect and encrypt the information sent and prevent others from storing or viewing your session.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Virtual Private Networks&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;VPNs, as they are called in the digital realm, provide a private intranet that individuals that have log-in information can access. When accessing a VPN, all information uploaded, downloaded, or otherwise transmitted is encrypted, ensuring that anyone who views the transmissions is denied the ability to read or use it. Even other users from other segmented intranets on the same VPN provider are not given access to the information, so your browsing or sharing session is completely privatized.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;Proxy Servers&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Often confused with VPNs, proxy servers also provide a tunnelled connection to the Internet. VPNs tend to work faster, partly due to the better hardware/network that is typically being used with such a service.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Use a virtual private network to prevent prying eyes from stealing your personal information, maintain a high browsing speed, and ultimately protect yourself from any other cyber-threats that exist.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXNldmVyYWw_" target="_blank"&gt;cheapest vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXJlc2VsbGVy" target="_blank"&gt;cheapest vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0" target="_blank"&gt;secure vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVr" target="_blank"&gt;vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWR5bmFtaWM_" target="_blank"&gt;reseller vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWZpdmU_" target="_blank"&gt;online vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWNh" target="_blank"&gt;online vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZwbnNlZWsuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;online vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPXVz" target="_blank"&gt;reseller vpn&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3BlcmZlY3R2cG4ubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wYWdlPWVpZ2h0dXNh" target="_blank"&gt;cheap vpn&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>