<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="6">		<conversation id="1fa8f7cdf986a2fcb84d140ffe02654e">			Beauty is defined as pleasin’ to the eyes,
&lt;br /&gt;;But what is true beauty without stimulatin’ the mind,
&lt;br /&gt;;I could try to, wine, dine, then spread any cute faced dime,
&lt;br /&gt;;But now-a-days its rare to spend three hours only connected by ya phones but ya’ll talkin’ the whole time,
&lt;br /&gt;;So instead of ya beauty bein’ skin deep,
&lt;br /&gt;;Have it glisten from ya heart,
&lt;br /&gt;;The cute face and slim waste mean nothin’,
&lt;br /&gt;;If you aint got a beautiful mind from the start.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f51acdb4bf6ab590e49e9f97e353c5b0">			This is to you, my inspiration…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I adored you, admired you, I could have loved you yet now, 
&lt;br /&gt;;I can’t stand you; I look down at you, and hate you with all my will,
&lt;br /&gt;;I trusted you; I was there for you 24/7 from dusk til dawn,
&lt;br /&gt;;But you used me, abused me, and played me like I was ya pawn,
&lt;br /&gt;;I would of took a bullet for you, wrote you a symphony, and even took ya breathe away,
&lt;br /&gt;;Now I’m the sniper, and a hate poem is what I write ‘er, and I’d leave you layin’ face down in the dirt,
&lt;br /&gt;;I would have cried for you, I always tried for you, at one point in time I might of even died for you girl,
&lt;br /&gt;;But now I’d spit on ya tears, I wouldn’t give you a second if I had a million years, I am now the ideal man woman all fear and I hate what you done to me…I hope its clear…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Much love and thanks to My Inspiration.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d19f586b357da31c77d04406454c3584">			Lights it… Puff…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He thinking, what life when you livin, the shit we do is pose to be high livin? Itsa givin this shit deemed stupid, but here he sits eyes low, loosin wit, laughin and havin fun though?...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Puff…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Damn, his mind aint clear no mo, cant really hear no mo, troubles with verbs, his thought process is all kinds of fucked up, his partner says “you coo boi”…he think he can handle, he all coo now, smiles lika g…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Puff…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“Oh shit, only three” he thinkin, this man higher than a 1000, head bobbin, eyes hung low, he gotta sway kinda swagga in a lawn chair, and his lungs swoll, so this is what we work fo, a lil high to get outta some lows…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pass…
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Blurred vision gave a new ambition, think a thought, he cant, and his concentration slippin, one last thought before he don’t remember shit til the next day…....\\\&quot;at the end of the day, insurance will still have to be paid, phone bill 100 this month, and tuition every 30 days, but as for right now, my nigga FUCK IT!\\\&quot;		</conversation>		<conversation id="8972b3323890ca195abc7a99911db917">			Now I lay me down to sleep,
&lt;br /&gt;;I pray to god my soul to sleep,
&lt;br /&gt;;Keep me safely through the night,
&lt;br /&gt;;And wake me with ya mournin’ light,
&lt;br /&gt;;If I die before I wake,
&lt;br /&gt;;Tell my momma not to cry,
&lt;br /&gt;;Give my dad the hug I never did, 
&lt;br /&gt;;And watch over my sister, keep her in ya sight,
&lt;br /&gt;;Tell my grandma keep the faith,
&lt;br /&gt;;Hug my lil cuz, and give my niece a lil peck on the face,
&lt;br /&gt;;Cleanse my soul and forgive my sins,
&lt;br /&gt;;But I’ll sell it back to you if my momma never has to work again,
&lt;br /&gt;;If I die without my wrongs bein’ right,
&lt;br /&gt;;Know that through all the bad I always known ya word was right,
&lt;br /&gt;;So now I lay me down to sleep,
&lt;br /&gt;;I pray to god my soul to keep,
&lt;br /&gt;;As I lay my head to rest, 
&lt;br /&gt;;I pray to god for anotha day I wake up blessed.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a33ca03533f992fae6a5eb264226383a">			She said write me a love poem and tell me how you feel,
&lt;br /&gt;;I said I could write til' my pen dries, I could write til’ my hand tired,
&lt;br /&gt;;I could write til’ I'm outta paper, and I’m gonna write til’ it pains and aches,
&lt;br /&gt;;I can write you a love poem as long as the skies,
&lt;br /&gt;;As deep as the ocean, and as beautiful as ya eyes,
&lt;br /&gt;;I can write you a love poem to make ya eyes leak like when it rains,
&lt;br /&gt;;Make ya heart beat like when hands catch rhythm on a drum, and make ya love blossom like when a daisy come up in the spring,
&lt;br /&gt;;So this is her love poem, and to all girls matter of fact,
&lt;br /&gt;;For any chick who holdin' it down, love they niggas, and always got they back,
&lt;br /&gt;;Yea, this is ya’ll love poem
&lt;br /&gt;;Much love and keep doin’ ya’ll thing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;-- King Skinny Sr. &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/biggrin.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="6035168aedad160691ecf67c82d03711">			Heads ache and hearts break, feelings fall and tempers rage, 
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s just a chapter, I wanna turn the page,
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s just a dream, but the real won’t go away,
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s so bad the deep wont shake, 
&lt;br /&gt;;And the deep so dark it’s like from this nightmare I’ll never wake,
&lt;br /&gt;;And this wake can’t creep, so my bad dreams build anyway,
&lt;br /&gt;;But heads ache and hearts break, feelings fall and tempers rage,
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s just a chapter but I can’t turn the page,
&lt;br /&gt;;And I’m looking for a actress the play the happily ever,
&lt;br /&gt;;But after all these days of going after I must be on the wrong stage, 
&lt;br /&gt;;She pose to be my high, but now it’s like blowin without the daze,
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s like ballin, but you can’t nail that step back fade,
&lt;br /&gt;;But just wait, as the love fades away, 
&lt;br /&gt;;The happy turns to gray, 
&lt;br /&gt;;And the belief goes astray…
&lt;br /&gt;;But heads ache and hearts break, feelings fall and tempers rage, 
&lt;br /&gt;;It’s just a chapter, but I just can’t turn the page. . .		</conversation>	</conversations></author>