<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="fad4f1d3eea4bdf72d36b15a13259b51">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rdGhlYm9vay5jb20vc3VwZXJtYW4tY3VzdG9tLW5pa2UtZHVuaw__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_11593317_50226858.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Superman, also known as the Man of Steel, is one of the most powerful superheroes in the DC Universe. His abilities include incredible super-strength, super-speed, invulnerability, freezing breath, flight, and heat-vision. Born as Kal-El on the dying planet Krypton, his parents Jor-El and Lara sent him in a rocket to the planet Earth where he would be the last surviving member of his race. His rocket was discovered by the kindly Jonathan and Martha Kent, who raised him as their son Clark Kent in the town of Smallville, Kansas. His upbringing provided him with strong moral values, and life-long friends Lana Lang and Pete Ross. In his secret identity he works as a reporter at the Daily Planet in the city of Metropolis. This is where he interacts with his love interest Lois Lane, and his co-workers Perry White and Jimmy Olsen. His greatest nemesis is the brilliant super-villain Lex Luthor.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An influence on early Superman stories is the context of the Great Depression. The left-leaning perspective of creators Shuster and Siegel is reflected in early storylines. Superman took on the role of social activist, fighting crooked businessmen and politicians and demolishing run-down tenements. This is seen by comics scholar Roger Sabin as a reflection of &amp;amp;quot;the liberal idealism of Franklin Roosevelt's New Deal&amp;amp;quot;, with Shuster and Siegel initially portraying Superman as champion to a variety of social causes. In later Superman radio programs the character continued to take on such issues, tackling a version of the KKK in a 1946 broadcast. Siegel and Shuster's status as children of Jewish immigrants is also thought to have influenced their work. Timothy Aaron Pevey has argued that they crafted &amp;amp;quot;an immigrant figure whose desire was to fit into American culture as an American&amp;amp;quot;, something which Pevey feels taps into an important aspect of American identity.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nike Dunk High shoes is a lifestyle sneaker shoes in the market. They are comfortable to wear. This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kdW5rdGhlYm9vay5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Custom Nike Dunk&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; Superman  Shoes by Brass Monki, which is my favorite and it is the most popular shoes. The design of Brass Monki Shoes was derived from super hero Superman. The Nikes superman Premium ID Blue Red Yellow sneaker is completed off with yellow added to the midsole, shoelaces along with other areas. Additionally, the Custom Dunks ID Superman Shoes is customizable by customers and allows excellent cushioning to your technique full-length EVA midsole.		</conversation>		<conversation id="301d17fc6e6c20fcc0c8fdd36efdeac9">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_12530195_30742434.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vbmlrZS1haXItam9yZGFuLXNob2VzLWFpci1qb3JkYW4tMS1jLTFfMi5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Jordan 1&lt;/a&gt;;    was designed by Peter Moore and marked a new era in basketball shoewear design. There has been multiple color of this shoe and also other shoe brands made models where you could see lots of similarities with &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vbmlrZS1haXItam9yZGFuLXNob2VzLWMtMS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Jordan&lt;/a&gt;;  .
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most of us already know the the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Jordan 1 Retro High Premier&lt;/a&gt;;   will make a comeback in the Spring 2009 season from Jordan Brand, what we didn’t expect was this new Blue Sapphire pair to be included into the mix that already includes a Black and Infared pair  as well as a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Pewter Black  Max Orange Jordans&lt;/a&gt;;   that comes at a Premier level. It’s safe to say that with these three &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaWtlam9yZGFuc2FsZS5jb20vYWlyLWpvcmRhbi0xLXJldHJvLWhpZ2gtcHJlbWllci1scy1wZXd0ZXItYmxhY2stbWF4LW9yYW5nZS1wLTE1MjYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Retro Air Jordan 1 High Premier&lt;/a&gt;;   pairs being released in Spring 2009, Jordan fans will definitely be pleased with the assortment from JB. This shoe features a dark pewter colorway along with a foil-like finish on the upper and max orange accents, including the inner lining. The ankle area features the Jordan Wings logo in black which goes well with the black sole.		</conversation>		<conversation id="95a4b213090a391346644463f4d0dac4">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_9822548_30769942.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;High profile, high style, high horsepower—the immortal &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk High&lt;/a&gt;;   is got it all. Score serious points with your slick moves in the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Dunk High Shoes&lt;/a&gt;;  , featuring comfort and support in a vintage-inspired profile. Considered Design for high performance and low environmental impact Leather, suede and nubuck upper High profile for ankle support Full-length EVA midsole for cushioning Flexible rubber outsole with a full cupsole stitch for durability.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Nike 6.0 division has been running at full speed in 2010 with a ton of great colorways of the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike 6.0 Dunk High&lt;/a&gt;;  , but its the materials used that have us impressed. We’ve already seen denim and a fleece/sweatpant material used already, and this &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank"&gt;;High Plaid Trace Dunk Shoes&lt;/a&gt;;  , appears to have a nylon/twill in use. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtZHVua3MtaGlnaC9uaWtlLTYuMC1kdW5rLWhpZ2gtcGxhaWQtdHJhY2UtYmx1ZS1vcmFuZ2Utd2hpcA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike 6.0 Dunk High Plaid Trace&lt;/a&gt;;   textile in contrasting colors also make these pop but are united with a neutral beige swoosh, and a white mesh lining should make for easy and cool walking.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a060e55a28c6e32fbf32c3cc6a19f371">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_15714200_30770041.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Air Max&lt;/a&gt;;    uppers was made of nylon mesh and synthetic suede, but the first leather edition Air Max 1 was released in 1988. For a while now, we have been giving you some looks at the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Women’s Air Max 1&lt;/a&gt;;   Safari pack  and now they are finally starting to pop up for sale. For a while now, we have been giving you some looks at the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Women’s Air Max 1&lt;/a&gt;;   pack and now they are finally starting to pop up for sale.Now that they have begun to make their way onto ebay, we have some great detailed images for you to check out. This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Air Max 1 Red Plum&lt;/a&gt;;    sports a red plum upper and midsole with several sections covered by Nike’s beloved Safari print. Aside from the Red Plum overload, some minimal accents are provided by a touch of white and some tangerine orange on the lining and the upper eyelet holes.Very nice this &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC0xLTg3L25pa2Utd21ucy1haXItbWF4LTEtc2FmYXJpLXBhY2stcmVkLXBsdW0_" target="_blank"&gt;;Red Plum Air Max 1 Safari&lt;/a&gt;;  with the red plum theme all around the shoe. Don't sleep ladies because these will not be around for long!		</conversation>		<conversation id="8bc1b26065bd2e7e62ea59a67d501877">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/143492135_4346651_30780973.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Air Max 90&lt;/a&gt;;  was first named the Nike Air Max III until it was reissued and renamed in 2000. Its current name comes from the year this iconic sneaker was launched, 1990. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Max 90&lt;/a&gt;;    was originally constructed with a Duromesh upper, synthetic suede, and synthetic leather. Striking color combos, comfort and clean lines made this model an instant hit, and the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Air Max 90 White&lt;/a&gt;;   is still extremely popular today.The next shoe &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Air Max 90 Kids&lt;/a&gt;;   sneaker rocks virgin white. All parts – outsole, midsole, upper and inner lining come in white, reminding of the famous Air Force 1 from 1982. The visible Air unit comes clear translucent. The shoe will drop at the beginning of 2011 in January.The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaG9lLXBhZ2UuY29tL25pa2UtYWlyLW1heC05MC9uaWtlLWtpZHMtYWlyLW1heC05MC13aGl0ZS13aGl0ZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Nike Kids Air Max 90&lt;/a&gt;;    is a good running shoe.Polyurethane midsole with visible Max Air cushioning in the heel;leather/mesh upper for light-weight and breath.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>