<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2d25021dd18c8800c8e5cf07711fb680">			Paying 15% interest on the $40, 000 loan amounts to a monthly payment of just $500.&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; Assume that you waited 90 days with regard to seasoning of title and sold the property to an FHA first time homebuyer for $79, 900. Assume that you payed off a commission of 6% to the realtor and another 6% to fund the buyers closing costs. You would still world-wide-web $70, 000 from the following transaction. After paying heli-copter flight hard money lender the $40, 000 that people borrowed, you would still be left with a profit of $30, 000. You will still held the house for six month before locating a buyer you would just have spent $500 every month in interest for a few months. Your total interest cost would only are $3, 000. This would leave you which includes a net profit of $27, 000. &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And also expressed another way, using no money down (borrowing the different money) you could potentially make a profit of $27, 000. How easy would it be to sell a house like this to a first time home buyer? The answer is it could be extremely easy. The clients are putting down just $3, 000 (3 &amp;frac12; %) to purchase a house with a monthly mortgage payment which is on the same as their monthly rent. You are paying all of their closing costs. And the federal government will give them a great $8, 000 tax credit if they purchase before the stop of 2009. It can be a win/win for everyone. The bank gets to sell their house quickly to a profit buyer. The cash buyer extends to flip the property and generate a quick profit and the final FHA buyer gets your can purchase a home for the same monthly payment as rent. &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The secret to the above transaction is to find an $80, 000 property which you could buy for $40, 000. This is the part that requires exercise, knowledge and experience. Finding deals like this is an art form and the people which find these deals are termed &quot;bird dogs&quot; or &quot;property scouts&quot;. &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many chicken dogs sell their deals to cash investors to get a small profit. This is known as wholesaling. For example a wholesaler might contract to obtain the above house for $40, 000 and then sell it for $45, 000 to another cash investor. This process, the wholesaler does not want to borrow money from a hard money lender. The wholesaler simply finds a deal, signs a contract to own it and then flips the contract to your cash investor for some sort of profit. This is known as &quot;assigning a contract&quot; and the profit that is payed off to the wholesaler is known as an &quot;assignment fee&quot;. &amp;nbsp; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Banks do not want wholesalers flipping legal agreements on bank owned buildings. For this reason, banks do not let assignable contracts. This ensures that a wholesaler cannot determine a bank owned property to a new cash investor. The reality is there are still ways that a house can be assigned. The best way is to purchase the home in a Land Trust and then assign the beneficial involvement in the land trust. Another way is always to purchase the property in an LLC and then assign the membership involvement in the LLC. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uZW91LmZyL3ByZXNlbnRhdGlvbi1kdS10cmFkaW5nLWVuLWxpZ25lLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;trader option binaire&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZXp5dG91LmNvbS9wcmVzZW50YXRpb24tZGVzLW9wdGlvbnMtYmluYWlyZXM_" target="_blank"&gt;;options binaires&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWZlcmVuc2VvLmZyL3ByZXNzZS8yMDEyLzAxLzI1L2FjaGV0ZXItZGVzLWFjdGlvbnMtc3VyLWludGVybmV0" target="_blank"&gt;;option binaire&lt;/a&gt;;Everything in our lives, to your greater or lesser extent, is connected to money and art is no exception.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>