<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b294e2d5abd4216711fc7770e439fcb0">			What’s So Special about Shearling Coats? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thinking of buying a shearling coat or shearling coats for women? Here is an in-depth look at everything you need to know about shearling coats. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A beautiful coat or jacket is definitely a must have for any fashionista who knows her stuff. While it’s tempting to choose a jacket that’s simply fashionable, aesthetics should never be more important than durability. Seeing as how jackets are worn over and over again—a common occurrence if you live in a cold area—it makes complete sense to purchase something that will last. One of the most highly sought-after coats in the world today is shearling coats for women. These coats feature a sheared wool and leather lining that’s remarkably effective at keeping you both comfortable and toasty. The shearling is undoubtedly one of the most sought-after coats in the world, despite its often high price tag. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Shearling coats have changed styles over the years, but the demand has still remained the same—even increased in many countries—compared to previous years. Aside from styles, shearling coats come in a wide variety of quality, with basic coats fetching prices of around $500, to coats featuring the supplest leather being regularly sold at over $5,000. Those prices may be obscene to many, but the quality of a high quality shearling is very much worth its weight in gold. The higher the quality of a shearling coat, the better it looks and the longer it will last. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The quality of a shearling is often dependent on where it’s from and how it’s made.  Shearlings from Spain are prized for their suppleness and quality, which also explains why they are the most expensive. Argentinean shearling coats are just as good and are priced similarly. Shearlings that are produced in both of these countries are renowned for being very soft and supple—a feat which other countries can’t seem to emulate with their own materials. Whatever their secret is, it’s a known fact that both Spain and Argentina produce the world’s best and most expensive shearling coats. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Flexibility and durability are two other factors that separate high quality shearling from the rest. Flexibility and lightness is always a mark of quality, something which the shearers and tanners of Spain and Argentina have managed to perfect over the years. Heavier coats, which can still fetch prices in hundred dollar figures, are often made in England and Australia. Aside from the weight, the coats from these countries are of good quality too. For example, Uruguayan coats are known for being heavy due to the heavy sheepskin they are made from. However, the weight also translates to better protection and insulation in extremely cold weather. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What many people don’t know about shearling is that it is actually sheepskin, as in it is the hide of a fully grown sheep. Fakes often look the same, but one can really tell the difference between genuine shearling and a fake. It doesn’t even require a trained eye; just a familiarity with what real leather and wool feels. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.leatherdeal.com%2Fshearling-jackets-and-coats-c4.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;https://www.leatherdeal.com/shearling-jackets-and-coats-c4.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.leatherdeal.com%2Findex.asp"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;https://www.leatherdeal.com/index.asp&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.leatherdeal.com%2Findex.asp"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;https://www.leatherdeal.com/index.asp&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>