<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f9703656b9d1ae61cec631496fe05f5a">			eighteen horses to help keep an eye out for during April's Uk Horse Racing|}&lt;br /&gt;;April could be the month once the turf Flat time begins to strike complete stride and for a lot of punters the fixture that lighting the blue touch paper may be the Craven meeting at Newmarket inside the middle from the thirty day period.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prior to sampling the breezy delights of Newmarket's Rowley Mile program, nevertheless, there is the compact make any difference in the ever-expanding Grand Nationwide meeting at Aintree that starts using a cracking card on April 6.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In recent many years Aintree's prestigious three-day meeting has begun to rival Cheltenham's somewhat bloated four-day fixture for thrills and spills, and there's small &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYW51Y2tzamVyc2V5c3Nob3AuY29tL2FsZXhhbmRyZS1idXJyb3dzLWplcnNleQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Alexandre Burrows Jersey&lt;/a&gt;; doubt the highlight in the Merseyside racing calendar offers three days of top-class racing culminating inside the running of the world's most well-known race over the final day.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As racecourses go, Cheltenham and Aintree are chalk and cheese: where the previous is twisty and undulating having a punishing uphill complete, the latter is extended and flat and basically sharp in character, and offered the 2 contrasting program configurations it will take a great horse to win a race in the Cheltenham Festival after which do the exact same at Aintree.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Specifically a calendar year back at Aintree that's just what Fota Island managed to do when adding the John Smith's Red Rum Handicap Chase to the Grand Yearly Chase that he had won in such superb style at Cheltenham just over two along with a 50 % week's beforehand.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not amazingly there will likely be a lot of horses from this year's Grand Yearly that could be looking for compensation on Merseyside such as Andreas, an early casualty within the Grand Yearly when a nicely backed favorite and Green Tango, who created strong late headway in the identical race regardless of seeming unsuited to Cheltenham. Aintree's flatter track must fit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Inside the Betfair Bowl Chase about the opening day, Cheltenham also-rans boast a healthy file and Gold Cup failures Monkerhostin and Beef Or Salmon could well be amongst people bidding to banish the blues of the bad Festival operate, when the flexible Impek, a runner-up inside the Ryanair Chase in the Cheltenham Festival, could compete and is already a winner over slightly shorter on this sharp course earlier inside the season. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Within the significant juvenile occasion, the John Smith's Anniversary 4-Y-O Hurdle, several key players from Cheltenham's Triumph Hurdle seem most likely to figure such as Reasonable Along, the Triumph Hurdle runner-up, who has already won a race more than course and distance, together with Afsoun, who was below the weather in the Triumph, and rates a robust fancy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Around the 2nd day - April 7 - the major race will be the John Smith's Melling Chase, and due to the fact its inception in 1989 this race's roll-call of winners has featured the top rated chasers in training, who've successfully stepped up in trip after excelling at their specialist distance of two miles.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remittance Guy, Viking Flagship, Katabatic, Martha's Son and Moscow Flyer are just a small number of previous two-mile champions who've extra this valuable prize right after getting crowned two-mile champions having a triumph in the Queen Mother Champion Chase in the Cheltenham Festival. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Newmill, this year's shock Queen Mom hero, won't be operating at Aintree but Kauto Star and Dempsey may well line-up for this prize. The previous, who was a heat favourite for your Queen Mom, fell early in that race bringing down the nicely supported Dempsey. If they've recovered from their tumbles, they should go close, whilst Irish raider and program winner Fota Island will be a likely contender too.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The exclusive Grand Nationwide fences arrive into perform for the John Smith's and Spar Topham Chase on the 2nd day, and sound-jumping and well-seasoned campaigners do well in this hurly-burly contest, when within the John Smith's Mildmay Chase it pays to look for any refreshing horse that hasn't endured the rigours of operating in Cheltenham's Royal &amp; SunAlliance Chase, a race that tends to spoil their chances at Aintree.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Grand National day features the big race itself that stands alone as the key betting race with the year. The 2006 contest is dominated by Clan Royal, a runner-up in 2004 and previous year's easy winner, Hedgehunter. Due to the fact the program was modernised in the early nineties and the fences produced easier and the landing sides raised, the classy and better horses have occur to fore and dominated the event. Indeed, the Nationwide now has the look of just another long-distance steeplechase but a single with lots of history attached.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All eyes are going to be upon the fillies within the Shadwell Stud Nell Gwyn Stakes about the 2nd day of Newmarket's Craven meeting on April 19, but sadly in current years this race has supplied couple of serious pointers in the direction of the 1,000 Guineas, when further Classic clues may perhaps be on offer in the Craven Stakes for colts on April 20, the meeting's last day. In 2004 the Barry Hills-trained Haafhd became the first colt given that Tirol in 1990 to finish the Craven-2,000 Guineas double.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The search for Classic pointers switches to Newbury on April 22 once the Lane End Greenham Stakes requires place over 7f. In recent seasons Turtle Island, Celtic Swing and Victory Note have all landed Classics soon after scoring here and backers must pay this race lots of respect within the colts' Classic reckoning.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Spring Cup Handicap at Newbury on April 22 is another race worth a 2nd glance. Horses that have run nicely within the William Hill Lincoln through the earlier month have a fantastic document here, and any that arrive from Redcar subsequent a prominent showing inside the first massive Flat handicap will surely warrant close consideration.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;At Ayr on the same day there is the Scottish Grand National to whet the appetite. A single thing's for sure and that is any horse which has operate inside the Aintree Grand Nationwide ought to be avoided as this kind of runners have an appalling file within the Scottish equivalent.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In 2004 Northern-trained Ryalux recorded a well known success and if the ground turns soft at the West of Scotland track a lot of folks will probably be rooting for another northern runner in Ossmoses, a strapping grey and stout stayer who all but landed the Midlands Nationwide over a related marathon excursion at Uttoxeter previous thirty day period.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Twelve months in the past trainer Paul Nicholls failed by a whisker to win this race with Cornish Rebel and the exact same trainer's lightly-raced Ladalko has been kept fresh new for this valuable prize. The Nicholls yard may perhaps also run Desert Quest, the County Hurdle winner, in the Scottish Champion Hurdle whilst Monet's Garden, a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYW51Y2tzamVyc2V5c3Nob3AuY29tL2hlbnJpay1zZWRpbi1qZXJzZXk_" target="_blank"&gt;;Henrik Sedin Jersey&lt;/a&gt;; runner-up within the Arkle Trophy Chase, bids to land a three-mile novices' occasion at Ayr. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The curtain comes down on April's busy and varied thirty day period with the mixed jumps and Flat card at Sandown on April 29. The Betfred Gold Cup is the jump season's final major handicap and fancied runners in the Paul Nicholls and Nicky Henderson stables should be noted. The latter almost landed this prize as well as a important bonus a year in the past with Juveigneur and he could nicely become a serious candidate again.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Paul Nicholls really should also be the trainer to watch inside the Betfred Celebration Chase, with either Kauto Star or Andreas, two with the stable's crack team of two-mile chasers, most likely to land the honours. Over the Flat the Betfred Mile Stakes would be the highlight, and horses that ran nicely in Newmarket's Earl of Sefton Stakes previously inside the month hold a very good document within this Group Two contest.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>