<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="dc8afa771a3ca2bfd8d99ab885e247">			The United States the Washington post recently published a scientific research shows that even positive emotions, have too much still bad, not only produce behavior recklessly, drinking too much, and other aspects of the tendency, also increases the risk of fraud and judgement.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Too happy mood often easy to trapped in a fixed mode,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b2RzNnNhbGUuY29tL3RvZHMtZ29tbWluaS1kcml2aW5nLXNob2VzLW1lbi1jLTEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Tods Gommini Driving Shoes Men&lt;/a&gt;; thus resulting in judgment errors when not only produce behavior recklessly, drinking too much, and other aspects of the tendency, also increases the risk of fraud and judgement.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Happiness is everyone's yearning, then, isn't the better the more happy? Is not necessarily the case. The United States the Washington post recently published a scientific research shows that even positive emotions, have too much still bad, not only produce behavior recklessly, drinking too much, and other aspects of the tendency, also increases the risk of fraud and judgement.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;American journal of personality and social psychology, published in a research report, a northwestern university psychologist organized a survey, let 94 college students a mock students court to college students' case with judgment. But before the hearings, half the students were positive influence, and mood cheerful; The other half student is the mentality is moderate. Results two group of students to hear the case of conclusion quite different: happy students are mostly think called Juan Garcia students beating of a roommate, and mentality of the moderate students think Juan and another student John Ghana has about the same suspect.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In fact, half of the students make judgment more accord with the facts&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b2RzNnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;tods 6 sale&lt;/a&gt;;. Too happy mood often easy to trapped in a fixed mode, which occurs when the deviation in judgment.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And emotional sad, people often with more systematic way of thinking, and more attention to detail, vulnerable to external factors influence; And happy people more anxious to make a judgment, including mingled with the personal racial and sexual factors.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8b0ca368b9ed897a4cc062654cbc05f9">			According to Taiwan &quot;central club&quot; report, prosecutor investigation department slab new north city one girl in school infant case, find out the grandfather of the young girl in between June last year, once a week in frequency, 3 degrees of sexual abuse girl,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b2RzNnNhbGUuY29tL3RvZHMtZ29tbWluaS1kcml2aW5nLXNob2VzLXdvbWVuLWMtMi5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Tods Gommini Driving Shoes Women&lt;/a&gt;; yesterday will he pay increase in mandatory sin too charges, for punishment 30 years.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New north city of instruction and a woman on April 25, the students in the school toilets accident to give birth to baby girl, after the event would not reveal his identity children, says only by the kiss was invaded the human nature, Taiwan inspection p initiate investigating force.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But the girl's uncle in three days after the crime, was found dead Chen the big fellow, prosecutors p phase check him out; Female students' &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b2RzNnNhbGUuY29tL3RvZHMtZ29tbWluaS1kcml2aW5nLXNob2VzLW1lbi1jLTEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Tods Gommini Driving Shoes Men&lt;/a&gt;; grandfather, is in a few days later to drink cleaner suicide were rescued.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Taiwan inspection p acquisition girl male family members related inspection body, and baby girls do DNA matching, found the DNA of baby girls and the maiden grandfather type don't conform to, prosecutors 5, JuPiao opened, the command to the police hospital will limit grandfather mentioned case, after news sound and after approved.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sets out the prosecution, about the 66-year-old grandfather, early June last year saw the residential area school girl shopping, dining invitation girl got home. Not material, the young girl entered, grandfather have put girl down to the bed, ignoring the girl resistance, sexual assault to succeed, then with the same technique, he invaded the women to succeed.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Due to the young, the young girl the innocence, January found between stomach more, but can't further confirmation, and the girl was a strong body, family also is not check sleep.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sets the prosecution during the investigation, the young girl said to testify, worry that enjoys will get caught to close, just keep hair; Grandfather is denying it, even in the face of the prison DNA will report, you still didn't do, to suicide reason, just say in a bad mood.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A young girl, DNA testimony in the prosecution of the prison for report evidence, that my grandfather fines to clear, in accordance with the grandfather of women under the age of 14, the increase in crime into charges against mandatory. Prosecutors found sexual assault grandfather criminal record, the pain of not good and take care of his grandfather granddaughter, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50b2RzNnNhbGUuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;tods 6 sale&lt;/a&gt;;but for their desires, ignoring the sex abuse human girl, and then let the girl pregnant girls, serious physical and mental development of the people, and after making ShiCi excuses, so a sin in accordance with a penalty, will do all three make for punishment in November 14, combined punishment for 30 years.		</conversation>		<conversation id="4d3e3caa18091509658850df895a3ad9">			Generally speaking, to human body suitable humidity was 40%-60%, humidity is moderate, the person's spirits. According to the scientific determination, the air humidity, some bacteria and viruses to breeding and dissemination, when the air humidity 65% higher,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWJyYW0ta3NvLmNvbS9tZW4tdmlicmFtLWZpdmUtZmluZ2Vycy1jbGFzc2ljLWMtNy5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Men Vibram Five Fingers Classic&lt;/a&gt;; the bacteria breeding fastest.
&lt;br /&gt;;If wearing wet clothing, easy to a cold or cause joint pain, eat the mildew bad food, it would cause gastroenteritis, even to lead poisoning, so the resistance of poor women must attach importance to prevent ShiXie invasion. To avoid any &quot;ShiXie&quot; of depressions. The 7 recruit dispel body moisture teach you:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1, pay attention to a dull boy
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fatigue is easy to cause ShiXie swoop in, therefore, must arrange work and rest time. Even at the same time strengthening exercise, the exercise can enhance physical, helping digestion, promote the blood circulation.
&lt;br /&gt;;The heavy rain can ward off the high temperature, bring us filar silk cool meaning, a lot of people so appetite. But with more rain wet summer, and is often ChangWeiBing multiple season, so food hygiene careless. More rain wet season is very suitable for intestinal bacteria and mould to grow, so easily induced summer acute intestinal infectious diseases and food poisoning.
&lt;br /&gt;;According to the weather change increase and decrease clothing. Whether blow air conditioning or out, not too greedy cool, prevent is wet and cold.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWJyYW0ta3NvLmNvbS9tZW4tdmlicmFtLWZpdmUtZmluZ2Vycy1rc28tYy02Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Men Vibram Five Fingers Kso&lt;/a&gt;; Don't get wet in the rain, cold and to prevent such as arthritis, rheumatism disease recurrence. Traditional Chinese medicine thinks, &quot;the wind and easy to ShiXie sticky be bored with, and the most difficult to&quot;, wet the rainy weather will make &quot;old rheumatism&quot; recurrence, is likely to happen some healthy people rheumatism. If wear sandals walking in the rain, back home in time to wipe your feet dry, and changing into dry shoes.
&lt;br /&gt;;The body moisture heavy most of the people are eating greasy, lack of exercise, especially often sat in the office OL, these people often feel the body is heavy, aching to activities, but the more love sports, the body of the more moisture deposition, as time passes, inevitable will lead to moisture scored his spleen, cause a series of disease.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sports can relieve stress and promote body organ, accelerate the moisture out of body. Running, walking, swimming, yoga, tai chi, sports,&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWJyYW0ta3NvLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;vibram-kso&lt;/a&gt;; help to activate blood circulation, increase water metabolism.
&lt;br /&gt;;Green onion, ginger, garlic is not only home commonly used seasoning, also has an irreplaceable medicinal value. For instance, we can try at home cooking a bowl of hot the very hot ginger soup, with ginger soup body the excellent utility moisture force spread out, to send to the whole body after khan, symptoms will to ease, this method also apply to prevent a cold after the rain.
&lt;br /&gt;;Intestines and stomach system related to nutrition and water metabolism, the best way is right amount, a balanced diet. Wine, milk, fat GanHou taste rich food is not easy to digest, easy to cause the intestines and stomach MenZhang, inflammation. Sweets Fried product will make the body produces peroxide, aggravating inflammation.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>