<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f8dfb53866f4da5ba728010056d39f00">			Dan Kennedy &amp; Dustin Mathews “The Ultimate Secret of Success” Book Released!&lt;br /&gt;;Dan Kennedy has been publishing books for years, but I think this is the greatest Dan Kennedy book ever. In his most recent book Dan Kennedy lays out all the greatest secrets of success he has gleaned from his 30 years in the marketing business. If you read only one Dan Kennedy book, make it this book! In this book Dan Kennedy generously provides his most powerful tools, strategies and techniques for getting ahead, with no success secret held back! This book “The Ultimate Success Secret” demonstrates why Dan Kennedy is considered one of the best marketers of our time.&lt;br /&gt;;In this book, Dan Kennedy has also tapped into the wisdom of Master Marketer Dustin Mathews. Dustin Mathews is one of the most sought after marketers in the country today and is the Chief Marketing Officer for 7-Figure Speaking Empire. Speaking Empire  trains National and International Speakers how to at least double or triple their profits to earn 7-figures or more per year. Dustin Mathews has read every Dan Kennedy book ever published and has spoken on stages with Dan Kennedy. When Dan invited Dustin to partner with him in creating the latest Dan Kennedy book , Dustin was pleased to except the offer.&lt;br /&gt;;In Dustin Mathews and Dan Kennedy’s book, each marketing guru takes a turn at sharing their most powerful (and inspirational) ways to accelerate your personal success and take decades off your learning curve. The secret to your success is carefully outlined in the book and highlighted with successful examples, designed to show you how you can succeed once you know the most powerful secrets to success.&lt;br /&gt;;The “The Ultimate Secret of Success” book is well named, because that is exactly what it is, a blueprint to your success! Get this Dustin Mathews and Dan Kennedy book today and get to reading … true success awaits you!&lt;br /&gt;;Paul Cline – Author  &lt;br /&gt;;To find out more about Dustin Mathews go to:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fsecretsuccessbook.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://secretsuccessbook.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>