<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="5596f885680663474d775a6f87c83b37">			There are many &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXdhcnJhbnR5LnVz" target="_blank"&gt;;home warranty plan&lt;/a&gt;;  companies out there that offer home warranty insurance. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you will be buying your first home, you no doubt get fears of big repairs bills, right? So many real estate agents may try to put your body and mind at ease and tell you &lt;i&gt;; &quot;this house carries a home warranty&quot; &lt;/i&gt;;. So my advice is, if they offer it at no charge to you, then okay, feel free to take. However there are some important things for you to know, especially if they're just offering it for some sort of fee. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a start, you want to realize that with most home warranty insurance companies out there, many of them get major complaints and they do not really pay off. Why is this? Unfortunately, many are citing some fine print in the contract. In my research, I only found the one that was any good. But you will have to do your homework too. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thus, you intend to be prepared and really figure out what is covered and precisely what is not. Also, you must know that &quot;pre-existing conditions, defects or deficiencies&quot; may not be covered at all. It's very normal for the policy to experience a 30 day waiting period after you close before it takes effect. This allows time for these &quot;pre-existing&quot; things to surface as soon as you move in. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having said that, what is this type of insurance supposed to covers? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here's that short list:&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; &lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; Home appliances &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; Interior Electrical System &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; Plumbing System (excluding fixture) &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; Central Hvac Systems &lt;/li&gt;; &lt;/ul&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Each and every home warranty insurance company carries a whole variety of ways they detail what the following coverage offers. For example they may have different levels with programs. So you have to ask, &quot;What is Covered&quot; and make them be specific. You can do this by asking a series of &quot;What if&quot; questions. For example, some of them cover Ac units while other do not etc. Just be certain to ask. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The good part of having this type of coverage is you would possibly not have to worry about major repair bills inside first year after closing. The bad thing is actually, you may have to help fight rather hard to obtain it covered. Why is this? Well, many times the contractor mailed by the insurance carrier is paid a small flat fee for that repair. So they may well resist replacing anything. If you believe about it, there is no real money in it for your kids. So be prepared and find out ahead of time precisely what is involved to file a claim and what ones recourse may be in the event you are dissatisfied. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another thing you may expect to hear is that the item is not covered by your home warranty insurance. Now that you are over a barrel, because you need that, you will be available a new one as a replacement. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All is not lost though, there is only one company (using dozens) I found which has a great record of taking care of their customers. Make sure that any company you are considering has good reviews. This can be a good thing to do before you make the purchase. That way you know that this insurance company and the coverage they offer is worth the money you may spend.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f9361d9df23effa47caf98aada1197e2">			Once you choose the best home, you may quickly realize the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXdhcnJhbnR5LnVzL2hvbWVwcm90ZWN0aW9udG90YWxwcm90ZWN0aG9tZXdhcnJhbnR5LWJ1eWVycy5odG0_" target="_blank"&gt;;total protect home warranty&lt;/a&gt;;  economical implications involved. After getting signed on the dotted line, you have got to provide the seller with a deposit. The deposit plays a significant role in every residential the property market transaction. The following column attempts to answer some common questions regarding this important, even though often misunderstood concept. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When an offer to obtain a home is produced, the purchaser can provide the seller with a deposit on the purchase price of the home. This deposit assures the seller that the purchaser intends to finish the transaction if their own offer is accepted. The amount of the deposit will vary and it is usually determined by negotiation between the real estate agents. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The deposit is not really paid directly to the seller, nevertheless is paid to the seller's real estate agent, with trust. This agent retains this profit a special bank account before closing date. With closing, several things will take place. Your deposit is deducted in the total purchase price, thus lowering the final amount owing to the seller. As well, the agent for the seller in most cases take its commission for any sale from the deposit. The seller's agent will pay the purchaser interest over the deposit monies which were in a special bank account. Because the money is not held for a long time and the interest rate to the money is quite low, that will not amount to a great deal of money. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When selecting a new home, your deposit is paid on the builder. To fund building costs, the builder often uses a larger deposit than one designed for a resale home. To safeguard purchasers from builders intending bankrupt or failing to complete the purchased property, this Ontario New Home Assurance Program (now termed Tarion Warranty Corporation) safeguards deposits on both brand-new freehold properties and innovative condominium properties. Since deposit protection is limited, purchasers ought to be careful when providing builders with more than the insured amount. Clients should ask their lawyer about which has a large deposit held in trust by the builder's lawyers or organizing for excess deposit insurance coverage. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Being a purchaser, it is best to provide the seller while using the lowest possible deposit. The biology behind this is simple: When an unforeseen problem arises along with the transaction does not close on time, the purchaser stands to lose less if they have provided owner with a relatively low deposit. On the other hand, if they provided the seller which includes a higher deposit, they stand to give up more. Remember that if a dispute involving purchaser and seller develops, owner may not release the deposit until the matter has been managed. In such a case, the purchaser is in a very compromised bargaining position because the seller has their profit. Moreover, owner may use the down payment the purchaser gave these phones force a settlement of the dispute. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That deposit represents a financial commitment in order to complete a real estate dealing. Owner should always attempt to extract from the purchaser the largest deposit possible, while the purchaser should adopt the opposite view. Typically, negotiating these terms with the offer are best left for an experienced real estate professional.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>