<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="5cb361d372c240d8cdf59daeeded96d4">			Here is the secret language of birthdays, during the &lt;strong&gt;;Week of Freedom (May 25-June 2)&lt;/strong&gt;;, we find people born during the Month of the &lt;strong&gt;;Diversifier &lt;/strong&gt;;(also known as Gemini in the zodiac system of astrology) at their most highly individualistic.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The secret Language Of Birthdays Explaining Your Behavior&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All of us will share these influences during this time period, finding ourselves acting feisty, hard to control and concerned with being ourselves and not tied down or forced into a mold.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;America’s greatest poet, &lt;strong&gt;;Walt Whitman&lt;/strong&gt;;, typifies those born during this week. In his epic poem &lt;strong&gt;;&quot;Leaves of Grass,&quot; &lt;/strong&gt;;Whitman not only reveals himself to the world, immortalizing his inner thoughts and highly individualistic attitudes, but also clearly presents himself as a citizen of the world as well.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Marilyn Monroe &lt;/strong&gt;;and &lt;strong&gt;;John F. Kennedy&lt;/strong&gt;; were also born during this Week of Freedom, and were even rumored to have had a love affair with each other. Both were known for their highly individualistic and freedom loving attitudes. Those born this week are not always easy for others to deal with in intimate relationships, nor do they specialize in long-lasting ones. The &lt;strong&gt;;secret language of birthdays&lt;/strong&gt;; makes it easier to predict and understand our as well as others behavioral pattern.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Secret Language Of Birthdays Explaining The Challenge Of This Week&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One challenge of this week for us all is to have the courage to be ourselves, despite the resistance by more conservative and authoritarian teachers, parents, siblings and colleagues. We will often turn to those friends who truly understand us for comfort and understanding. In addition, because we will be so interested in our own world we will have to remind ourselves of the existence of others, who have their own wants and needs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Secret Language of Birthdays Explaining Ways To Win the Challenges&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Learning to listen and not just plunge ahead with our own best interests at heart will be a difficult task during the Week of Freedom. In addition, we will have to tone down some of our outspokenness if we are to be welcomed socially into the groups around us. Our feistiness should not serve to isolate us from others.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Learning more about the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXBlcnNvbm9sb2d5LmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;secret language of birthdays&lt;/a&gt;;   eliminates the trouble of understanding yourself as well as others who are an integral part of your life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/132147251_14680349_29599426.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Secret Language Of Birthdays - Celebrities Born during The Week of Freedom&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of the Bold One - May 25&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lauryn Hill, Molly Sims, Jamie Kennedy, Anne Heche, Mike Myers, Connie Sellecca, Frank Oz, Ian McKellen.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of the Stalwart Protector - May 26&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Matt Stone, Helena Bonham Carter, Lenny Kravitz, Genie Francis, Sally Ride, Hank Williams Jr., Pam Grier, Stevie Nicks.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of Driven Dedication - May 27&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;André Lauren Benjamin, Paul Bettany, Joseph Fiennes, Todd Bridges, Adam Carolla, Peri Gilpin, Louis Gossett Jr., Henry Kissinger.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of the Innovative Trailblazer - May 28&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Colbie Caillat, Jesse Bradford, Elisabeth Hasselbeck, Kylie Minogue, John Fogerty, Gladys Knight, Rudolph Giuliani, Maeve Binchy.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of Quicksilver - May 29&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Melanie Janine Brown, Noel Gallagher, Melissa Etheridge, Rupert Everett, Annette Bening, La Toya Jackson, Danny Elfman, Anthony Geary.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of Nimble Time - May 30&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Jennifer Ellison, Jenny Mollen, Cee-Lo Green, Idina Menzel, Wynonna Judd, Ted McGinley, Candy Lightner, Gayle Sayers.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of the Cutting Edge - May 31&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Colin Farrell, Brooke Shields, Lea Thompson, Chris Elliott, Tom Berenger, Joe Namath, Sharon Gless, Clint Eastwood.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of the Popular Eye - June 1&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brandi Carlile, Alanis Morissette, Heidi Klum, Lisa Hartman Black, Powers Boothe, Ronnie Wood, Morgan Freeman, Pat Boone.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;The Day of the Problem Solvers - June 2&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Jon Favreau, Dominic Cooper, Justin Long, Zachary Quinto, Wayne Brady, Wentworth Miller, Dana Carvey,Lasse Hallström		</conversation>		<conversation id="edbb24de772e16846f60d575b2692510">			Communication is the central theme during the &lt;strong&gt;;Week of New Language (June 3rd through June 10th). &lt;/strong&gt;;Probably it will have a great impact on the secret language of relationship.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Secret Language Of Birthdays For People Born Between June 3 - 10&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those celebrating their birthdays at this time are people who must not only be heard but also understood. For all of us, as well, this is a time in which we should strive to get our points across during discussions, debates and arguments in as clear and direct a verbal manner as possible, while keeping our emotions under control.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many outstanding writers such as the Spanish poet and playwrigh&lt;strong&gt;;t Federico Garcia-Lorca&lt;/strong&gt;;, American poet &lt;strong&gt;;Allen Ginsburg&lt;/strong&gt;;, and German novelist &lt;strong&gt;;Thomas Mann&lt;/strong&gt;; are born during this week. Moreover, many artists who created a new language in their performance and other creations include&lt;strong&gt;; Lori Anderson, Prince, Judy Garland, Cole Porter, composer Robert Schumann, and the architect Frank Lloyd Wright.&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Not everyone can be expected to immediately understand the highly individualistic manner of those born during the &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXBlcnNvbm9sb2d5LmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Week of New Language&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;/strong&gt;;, and patience is required in getting to know them better. The secret language of birthdays reveals the nature and behavioral pattern of your near and dear ones. Understanding the secret language of birthdays will solve many puzzles, thus making your bonding with them stronger.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The principal challenge to all of us during this time is, of course, engaging in meaningful verbal and written dialogues with others, whether in person or over the internet or cell phone.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/132147251_5118699_29643544.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Highly critical tendencies often surface now and there is a risk they can harden into condemning attitudes. Such tendencies should be dropped whenever possible in favor of more accepting and caring ones. It is easy to pick someone apart if you have not stood and walked in their shoes. Witty stories, jokes and comments, however, can add life and spice to any party and will be particularly appreciated by most people during this time period.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The secret language of birthdays has everything to explain you why a person is the way he/she is. Consequently it also gives an understanding how to make that person feel comfortable in your company.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>