<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e86136687dff8cd68334ce2b94be6da3">			Are you just beginning when it comes to copywriting? Have you attempted to produce your first copy in the best way possible? If yes, then this article will be very helpful to you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Focus on Your Prospect: Don't make the mistake of talking mainly about yourself in your copy. Your prospect has to be the center of attention most of the time. There is no way that you'll be able to convince your prospect to buy your product if you're simply going to keep bragging about how amazing your offer is. The first question that your prospect will have in her/her mind when they see your copy is &quot;What's in it for me?&quot; Your focus, then, has to be on the actual benefits to the reader and not how great the product is in general. You have to appeal directly to the needs and interests of your target audience. Always keep in mind that people don't buy products, they buy dreams. They're not interested in helping your business, but in overcoming their own challenges. To them, you and your product are only a means to an end. This may be the single most important principle of copywriting, so pay attention to it when you create your copy. In general, it's a healthy sign if your copy uses words like &quot;you&quot; and &quot;your&quot; more often than words like &quot;I' or &quot;my.&quot;By way of example, if your copy is about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.interdominios.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.interdominios.com/&lt;/a&gt;;  then you should see to it that you give your prospect the highest priority through it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do not Make the Ordering Process Difficult: Making the ordering process too hard is one of the main things that copywriters tend to do when they are first starting out. You cannot make things hard if you want your prospects to begin and finish the ordering process. Do not make your customers sweat and wonder how and where they can get a hold of your product. This is because that way, you'll simply lose customers instead of gaining them. Your ordering process should be expected and simple to comprehend. This is because making it complex will obviously make it difficult for a regular person to spend their time searching through your copy simply to place an order. No one will want to spend time browsing online. Everyone is always rushing. No one likes to deal with a difficult process. So think about what a customer would think when it comes to the ordering process. See what you can do to simplify the process.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Emphasize Your Guarantee: One of the things that will make your copywriting more effective is the guarantee. This is where you decrease the risk for your prospect. Make them feel safe about going through the ordering process. You should focus on emphasizing to your prospects that they do not have anything to risk by buying your product. Even if your guarantee is very basic, you will see your sales go up if you use this strategy right now. Your sales copy should point out how your product is the best option for them and that there is no risk for purchasing it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can get started writing some copy now! By implementing these copywriting guidelines, you'll find that you can convert more of your prospects into customers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Resources:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blurty.com%2Ftalkpost.bml%3Fjournal%3Drickyncarr%26amp%3Bitemid%3D267http%3A%2F%2Frickyncarr.livejournal.com%2F616.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.blurty.com/talkpost.bml?journal=rickyncarr&amp;itemid=267http://rickyncarr.livejournal.com/616.html&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="97b1263bf8e1fafb4f0d28a95240cb7b">			Email copywriting can be an important aspect of your business, and in this article we'll be covering some proven strategies you can start using right away.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Give People a Time Limit: It's best to convince your readers that they only have a certain amount of time to respond to your offer. People these days have a lot of options when it comes to buying a product and if you want them to take notice of yours, and actually take action, then make it urgent. Let your readers know that your offer isn't going to be there forever and unless they take advantage of it right away, they'll be losing on it. Once your prospect has opened your email and has gone through your copy, the next step is to give him/her a strong reason to buy from you without much delay. The more urgent you can make your offer, the more likely it is that people will respond. At the same time, it's important to be truthful in your advertising, as people are tired of things like fake scarcity and deadlines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Landing Page Needs to Match: When you're doing email marketing, there is almost no time lapse between reading the email message and the rest of the promotion on your website. Because of that, there needs to be a &quot;seamless flow&quot; between your email message and the landing page where you have sent your subscribers. It is important that the email message and the landing page message match, including the sales copy, graphics and even sales pitch. Prospects could leave before creating a conversion if they think they have clicked through to the wrong site because nothing seems to match. You need to repeat the same elements that you have in your email copy in your landing page. To avoid mismatches between landing page and the email copy, be sure that you use the same tone of voice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avoid Words that Would Trigger Spam Filters: You have to avoid certain overused words in your email that are generally used by spammers. Words and phrases such as &quot;free&quot; or &quot;make money&quot; in the subject line are likely to get blocked. If you use words or phrases like this, your emails will be relegated to junk mail folders and never read. That's why you should be aware of how you word your emails and subject lines. If you're doing email marketing, you probably use an autoresponder (or you should), and most of these services alert you to words that are likely to be blocked by spam filters.Go ahead and apply these &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.interdominios.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.interdominios.com&lt;/a&gt;; suggestions to your email copywriting to obtain the most out of it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take what you have learned and put it into action and you will see that every tip that we discussed in the above article will work. So to improve and enhance your email marketing campaigning, work to improve your copy first.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Links:		</conversation>	</conversations></author>