<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="601b28c3ec37f309d9efffc6f71c5800">			They can prescribe treatments to mask your neck pain and they can do x-rays and also other tests to see in which the pain is coming with. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When people do find something wrong with the neck they will probably want to schedule surgery, which can prove to be a painful procedure which has a long recovery. Surgery, although sometimes necessary, really is highly recommended a treatment of previous resort. You can always do the surgery, but if you do the surgery first, you eliminate all kinds of other effective and conservative options. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you have neck pain it usually is wise to consult which includes a chiropractor before going to the extent of something even more serious such as surgical treatment. Some of the first points that a chiropractor will do on your first visit is to ask you questions concerning your neck pain. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some questions they may ask are: &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Any time did your neck pain start &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;: What have you done to try to ease your neck soreness &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Are there any other parts of your body that your neck pain stems to or with? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;These are a few questions that your Chiropractor probably will ask. After the initial consultation they will then perform a actual physical examination. The examination will involve chiropractic tests, orthopedic checks, and a neurological assessment. This entire process will allow the chiropractor to get to the root of your problem and allow him or her to come up with a solution to your pain. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A typical practice of chiropractors is always to perform a neck change. A neck adjustment is a form of spinal manipulation, and is very specific in nature. This is a very precise technique and it is usually very effective within alleviating neck pain. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Here's some heartfelt recommendations for my medical counterparts. Get to know some family or wellness oriented chiropractors locally. Try to understand what it's we do, how we undertake it and why. Know that there is absolutely no conflict if your affected individual sees a chiropractor. And know we can help. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A recent study published in a major medical journal revealed that these Americans that use &quot;;alternative and complementary&quot;; healthcare services (mostly chiropractors) not even half tell their medical doctors that they are doing so. Think that. Most people I see as a chiropractor have already sampled almost everything medicine boasts and decide to try chiropractic being a last resort. Most of those end up getting better. That's where things between medical practitioners and chiropractors seem to go wrong. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chiropractic together with medicine are mutually exclusive, separate and distinct. One of the things I often knowledge is someone telling me that their medical doctor told them that chiropractic is usually either unproven, unscientific, a cult or even worse, dangerous. Don't glimpse down while running; instead scan the way in advance of you for any obstacles you may need to avoid, there is no reason to remain running with your encounter down. Failure to look straight ahead so brings about straining the neck's curvature and increases back pain, neck pain, and a swarm of other conditions you don't want. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Chiropractors have much good advice about running; the wise runner who follows these suggestions will stay away from the pitfalls and reap the most benefit from their physical efforts. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5naWxkZW5mYW1pbHljaGlyb3ByYWN0aWMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;Chiropractor San Diego&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>