<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="2df241bbbc5f63aa15e964ef697f4809">			iPad HD vs iPad 2&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The iPad HD Announced today&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why there are so many people waiting for the iPad HD is really beyond me. Will apple really make a product that will replace their old ones. Well i know they won't. The iPad 2 is a huge hit and continues to be so. I think the iPad HD is just a good facelift. Adding new technologies into the device to make it last longer with current technical trends. The fact is Apple was losing ground to the Samsung Galaxy Tab, and a few court cases at that. Maybe they are inventing the iPad HD to ratake their market share and this time patent a whole lot of things so Samsung can't &quot;Copy&quot; it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is said that the iPad HD will be equipped with a brand new iOS titled iOs 5.1 rather than iOS 5 and also be equipped with a brand new processor titled Apple A6.  This processor is said to have a quad-core ARM-base due to the fact that there are a variety of other ARM partners that are now releasing their own quad-core technologies such as the Tegra 3 (Nvidia) and the Snapdragon S4 (Qualcomm).  As for the display of the iPad HD, many individuals are saying that the screen will be a retina display since the popularity of this viewing quality proved to be beneficial for both the iPhone 4 and the iPhone 4S with 2048 x 1536 resolution and 9.7 inches in width.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So iPad HD vs iPad 2.&lt;br /&gt;;The screen is better&lt;br /&gt;;The Processor is Faster&lt;br /&gt;;Battery will be better&lt;br /&gt;;All models to have an SD Card slot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are pretty much confirmed upgrades, we are expecting the pricing to be moderate. but with the top end model if the iPad HD witch I think will retail at $999. But the entry level models priced between the iPad 2 &quot;middle level&quot; models for the entry level iPad three.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Saying that so your choice to buy an iPad HD will be to spend the same amount of money on a iPad 2 with 32GB ram or an ipad HD with 16BG of ram. Rumour being that they will have a 8GB iPad HD. So they are leaving you with more choices than rather getting rid of their old models.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many individuals all over the world have taken a large interest in the use of personal electronics.  Apple, the world’s leading designer and manufacturer of personal electronics is providing their new and existing customers with the ability to purchase the iPad HD.  Although the device itself has yet to be announced by Apple, there are a variety of sources that are leaking reputable information revolving around the release date and the specs of the iPad HD.  With these resources you can be assured that you will be able to place your iPad HD pre order within a limited amount of time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;iPad HD Released Today 7th March 2012&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As previously mentioned, valuable resources have said that the iPad HD is due to be released on Wednesday, March 7th of 2012.  There will be a variety of new features that will be implemented in order to ensure that all users will have a fun and valuable time playing and working with the tablet.  Sources within the United States and within Asia have said that Apple’s supply chain is now preparing for the shipment of the tablets on the prospective launch date.  With the new iPad HD specifications, users will be undoubtedly impressed.&lt;br /&gt;;iPad HD Pre Order&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having the ability to acquire an iPad HD pre order can prove to be exponentially beneficial due to the fact that they will inevitably begin to sell out incredibly fast.  With the implementation of an iPad HD pre order individuals will be assured that they will be receiving their iPad HD’s on the release date rather than having to wait for the retail stores to receive full stock.  Considering that the devices are said to be shipped out either later this month or in April, be prepared to acquire your own iPad HD pre order.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]ipad hd vs ipad 2[/url]		</conversation>		<conversation id="eb5af0f714ba1242793f13f869ee9543">			ipad 3rd Generation vs ipad 2&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So ipad 3rd Generation vs ipad 2&lt;br /&gt;;The screen is better&lt;br /&gt;;The Processor is Faster&lt;br /&gt;;Battery will be better&lt;br /&gt;;All models to have an SD Card slot.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are pretty much confirmed upgrades, we are expecting the pricing to be moderate. but with the top end model if the ipad 3rd Generation witch I think will retail at $999. But the entry level models priced between the iPad 2 &quot;middle level&quot; models for the entry level iPad three.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Saying that so your choice to buy an iPad HD will be to spend the same amount of money on a iPad 2 with 32GB ram or an ipad HD with 16BG of ram. Rumour being that they will have a 8GB iPad HD. So they are leaving you with more choices than rather getting rid of their old models.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many individuals all over the world have taken a large interest in the use of personal electronics.  Apple, the world’s leading designer and manufacturer of personal electronics is providing their new and existing customers with the ability to purchase the iPad HD.  Although the device itself has yet to be announced by Apple, there are a variety of sources that are leaking reputable information revolving around the release date and the specs of the iPad HD.  With these resources you can be assured that you will be able to place your iPad HD pre order within a limited amount of time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ipad 3rd Generation &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why there are so many people waiting for theipad 3rd Generation is really beyond me. Will apple really make a product that will replace their old ones. Well i know they won't. The iPad 2 is a huge hit and continues to be so. I think the iPad HD is just a good facelift. Adding new technologies into the device to make it last longer with current technical trends. The fact is Apple was losing ground to the Samsung Galaxy Tab, and a few court cases at that. Maybe they are inventing the iPad HD to ratake their market share and this time patent a whole lot of things so Samsung can't &quot;Copy&quot; it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is said that the iPad HD will be equipped with a brand new iOS titled iOs 5.1 rather than iOS 5 and also be equipped with a brand new processor titled Apple A6.  This processor is said to have a quad-core ARM-base due to the fact that there are a variety of other ARM partners that are now releasing their own quad-core technologies such as the Tegra 3 (Nvidia) and the Snapdragon S4 (Qualcomm).  As for the display of the iPad HD, many individuals are saying that the screen will be a retina display since the popularity of this viewing quality proved to be beneficial for both the iPhone 4 and the iPhone 4S with 2048 x 1536 resolution and 9.7 inches in width.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having the ability to acquire an ipad 3rd Generation  pre order can prove to be exponentially beneficial due to the fact that they will inevitably begin to sell out incredibly fast.  With the implementation of an iPad HD pre order individuals will be assured that they will be receiving their iPad HD’s on the release date rather than having to wait for the retail stores to receive full stock.  Considering that the devices are said to be shipped out either later this month or in April, be prepared to acquire your own iPad HD pre order.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ipad 3rd Generation vs ipad 2 Pe-Order Date 16th March&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As previously mentioned, valuable resources have said that the ipad 3rd Generation is due to be released on Wednesday, March 7th of 2012.  There will be a variety of new features that will be implemented in order to ensure that all users will have a fun and valuable time playing and working with the tablet.  Sources within the United States and within Asia have said that Apple’s supply chain is now preparing for the shipment of the tablets on the prospective launch date.  With the new iPad HD specifications, users will be undoubtedly impressed.&lt;br /&gt;;iPad HD Pre Order&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]ipad hd vs ipad 2[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>