<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="8">		<conversation id="d9821c93ee7f6a429c2ebb8509160b8a">			While Toshiba and Globalfoundries were believed to have participated in the bidding process, it seems as if Micron is ready to pay somewhere between $1.3 billion and $1.5 billion for its rival.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The value of Elpida is mainly in its Hiroshima manufacturing facility, which is estimated to be worth about $1 billion, according to a Bloomberg article. Building a new fab is substantially more expensive for every chip maker. As of March 2012, Micron's balance sheet lists about $2.1 billion available in cash and short term investments. However, the company's quarter results have worsened since the end of 2010 and dipped into the red into the most recent quarter when the company reported a net loss of $224 million on revenues of $2.1 billion.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Recently appointed chief executive officer Mark Durcan said that the company expects DRAM prices to recover, but explained that even if the company has been able to sell more NAND Flash and DRAM in the last quarter, the greater volume was offset by lower average selling prices. Increased manufacturing capacity and cost improvements could be one way for Micron to protect itself in the future from downturns in the market. Micron recently made a similar move when it acquired Intel's shares in the flash memory joint-venture IM Flash.		</conversation>		<conversation id="9fac62558ab942138cb8bf80edee552c">			This site gives you the most significant changes and how these myriad shifts translate into a new movement of 2012 global trends. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We have travelled the globe and scanned world experts, reviewed design fairs and forecast reports, noting the most significant changes and how these myriad shifts translate into a new movement of 2012 global trends .Explore these new palettes to refresh and create your own stylish schemes in terms of business, lifestyles and the like using one or more of these amazing design finishes.		</conversation>		<conversation id="dbfa4df001fe1267bfe7547159a30f09">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdigg.com%2Fnews%2Fbusiness%2Fchapman_associates_micron_miniature_comman.."target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://digg.com/news/business/chapman_associates_micron_miniature_comman..&lt;/a&gt;;.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Designed by Chapman Associates and manufactured in the U.K. by K-Tech Limited. Overview 'MICRON' is a very small radio-controlled switching system, fully CAA approved for security use on aircraft, in which the miniature Radio-Switch has the capability to acknowledge automatically any valid commands received from an operator using a hand-held Command Unit. It operates at very low power in the licence-exempt UHF band, is battery powered, and all functions are managed by intelligent low-power microprocessors. Main features The 'MICRON' Radio-Switch produces virtually no RF radiation		</conversation>		<conversation id="c743197b8a727d11f061b4f9ad848a42">			At Bark &amp; Co our expert legal team has built an enviable reputation for the quality of representation, responsiveness to client needs, and high levels of client satisfaction. An original member of the Specialist Fraud Panel, Bark &amp; Co are amongst the top firms in UK specialising in defending criminal and civil fraud, regulatory litigation, money laundering, insider dealing and cyber crime. Our civil department specialises in all aspects of HM Customs and Excise investigations including VAT and Duties Tribunals and have established a leading practice in the fields of cash and asset recovery.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d918b0c2b603475f8b733d090dde3853">			These are our some of our cases of note. For information about our recent cases the please click here.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;R v Nadir
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Description: Bark &amp;amp; Co have been instructed by the former CEO of Polly Peck International (PPI) in an alleged multi-million pound fraud. The client faced 66 counts of Fraud &amp;amp; Theft, but failed to appear in the 1993 trial. Mr Nadir has returned to the UK to fight to clear his name.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The trial date is now set for January 2012.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Significance: One of the first high profile SFO prosecutions.		</conversation>		<conversation id="343a4192e05438902a5e9c05a369ac32">			A former UBS employee accused of unauthorized deals that cost the Swiss bank 1.7 billion euros ($2.3 billion) has pleaded not guilty to fraud and false accounting charges.
&lt;br /&gt;;In one of the world's biggest-ever cases of alleged &quot;rogue trading,&quot; Kweku Adoboli has entered a plea of 'not guilty' in a London court where he faces charges on four counts of fraud and false accounting.
&lt;br /&gt;;Adoboli, who could receive a maximum 10 years in prison if found culpable, spoke only to confirm his name and reply &quot;not guilty&quot; to all the charges when they were read out to him at a packed Southwark Crown Court.
&lt;br /&gt;;Judge Alistair McCreath remanded Adoboli in custody and set a trial date of September 3.
&lt;br /&gt;;The losses incurred by UBS were a severe blow, leading to the resignation of the bank's chief executive Oswald Grübel and triggering a shake-up of its investment banking services.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Adoboli's rogue trading cost UBS a lot of jobs and money
&lt;br /&gt;;Adoboli worked for UBS's global synthetic equities division in London's financial district, buying and selling funds which track different types of stocks or commodities, such as precious metals.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b0f47d6ab4e65be2c19a845970d5f0d4">			LONDON - A former UBS trader arrested in London on charges of fraud linked with unauthorized trades that cost the Swiss bank more than $2bn pleaded not guilty Monday to the charges against him.
&lt;br /&gt;;Kweku Adoboli, 31, pleaded not guilty to two counts of fraud and two of false accounting between 2008 and September 2011 at London's Southwark Crown Court.
&lt;br /&gt;;The trader was arrested on Sept. 14 after on charges of committing fraud that cost the bank over $2 billion.
&lt;br /&gt;;The incident pushed then-CEO Oswald Gruebel to resign and damaged the bank's efforts to clean up its image after being involved in a United States tax evasion investigation and sustaining huge losses on subprime mortgages during the financial crisis.
&lt;br /&gt;;City watchdog the Financial Services Authority and its Swiss counterpart have launched an investigation into why UBS failed to spot allegedly fraudulent trading.
&lt;br /&gt;;Adoboli's case was delayed last year after he replaced his former lawyers at Kingsley Napley law firm with a new team from Bark &amp; Co., which specializes in fraud cases. McCreath set a provisional trial date for September 3 and remanded Adoboli in custody. He said he was willing to hear an application for bail.		</conversation>		<conversation id="ca7c4581b05613504a12cb389e427b5b">			Welcome! to the most exciting list of tourist attractions and travel destinations around the world. Our directory helps you find information and reviews about activities from sites all around the world that offers different places of interest and types of recreation. Drill down into the locations below to find out more about each place and see how the local customs create a unique atmosphere.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Just Relax and Enjoy!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>