<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="c506fc072604bff9776323c072bff238">			Research has shown that memory loss due to aging begins before you are thirty years old but there is good news. You can reverse much of the effects of aging on memory and reduce your risks of developing such cognitive disorders as Alzheimer's disease and other forms of dementia.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Memory Loss Reasons: - 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Drugs: some drugs, benzodiazepines for example, can cause temporary memory disturbance as can anesthetics.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Alcohol: there are two ways in which alcohol can affect memory. In acute form – getting very drunk – the loss is temporary and often relates to what happened during the period of intoxication. In alcoholism vitamin B12 can become deficient. 
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Dementia: all the dementias can lead to memory loss. It often comes packaged with other changes such as altered personality and intellectual decline. Quite a bit of long term memory is usually preserved.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Epilepsy: seizures of all types can give rise to bouts of temporary memory loss often associated with some disorientation.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Head injury: the loss is often temporary and retrograde; however more serious injury can produce permanent memory impairment.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Stroke: again the degree of impairment varies according to the amount of damage caused. Nearly always occurs in conjunction with other types of neurological deficit such as paralysis or speech problems.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Natural ways to Better Brainpower: - 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Feed Your Brain - This means feeding your body of course. Your brain needs a lot of energy, and will generally function better if you eat some good proteins and complex carbohydrates. Trail mix, with nuts and dried fruit works well for some.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Mindfulness exercises - Concentration and clear thinking are more or less automatic once you remove distractions. Learn to stop and watch your busy mind. As you notice things that are subtly bothering you, deal with them. 
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Exercise - Physical exercise has been shown to improve brain function both immediately (after ten minutes on a treadmill, for example), and long term. The short-term effect is because of the immediate increase in blood flow and therefore oxygen to the brain. 
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Gingko Biloba - The leaves of this tree have been proven to increase blood flow to the brain. The trees are often planted in parks. My friends and I used to eat a few leaves when we wanted a brain boost. It is also inexpensive, if you buy the capsules or tea at any health food store.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Avoid sugar - Any simple carbohydrates can give you &quot;brain fog.&quot; Sometimes called the &quot;sugar blues&quot; as well, this sluggish feeling makes it hard to think clearly. It results from the insulin rushing into the bloodstream to counteract the sugar rush. Avoid pasta, sugars, white bread and potato chips before any important mental tasks.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You may be interested in reading &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ayurvedicherbalcure.com%2Fhealth-products%2Fmentat-syrup.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ayurvedicherbalcure.com/health-products/mentat-syrup.html&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ayurvedicherbalcure.com%2FHerbs%2Fashvagandha.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ayurvedicherbalcure.com/Herbs/ashvagandha.html&lt;/a&gt;;.  Also Read more on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ayurvedicherbalcure.com%2FHerbs%2Fbrahmi.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ayurvedicherbalcure.com/Herbs/brahmi.html&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="5d092fa671bf94e8065be398ebcae04c">			People frequently end up using hair loss treatment that is not suitable for their particular problem. This attitude regarding hair loss treatment leads not only to disenchantment but to aggravation of the damage also on many occasions.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These three factors are the most common ones. Among other hair loss causes there are also the following:&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ayurvedicherbalcure.com%2Fhair-care.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.ayurvedicherbalcure.com/hair-care.html&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Emotional strains, stresses and nervous disorders,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Aging,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Infections,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Hormonal imbalance,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Polluted environment,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Toxic substances,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Injury and impairment,
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Radiation.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The most comprehensive and effective methods for treating hair loss work both inside your body, as well as out. If you want your hair back, you need to keep this in mind when looking for a product that works.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Male - Prevent Hair Fall: - 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Regular use of mild shampoo keeps the dirt and grime off. Clean scalp is the first step towards healthy, unbreakable hair.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Ten to twelve glasses of water keep the internal system flushes and eliminate toxins. Great for your entire system and hair.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Protein intake is necessary through consumption of leafy green vegetables, fruits and dairy products.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Brahmi oil is great for a lustrous hair.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Condition your hair twice in a week. Never apply conditioner to the hair roots which aggravates hair fall.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Vitamins, iron, protein and other nutrients must be present in your food. Spinach keeps you and your hair hearty and healthy.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Increase the intake of zinc. This prevents hair loss and premature greying. Food items like wholegrain flour contain zinc.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Surprisingly, copper, stops hair fall. Contained in the blood serum, it prevents hair fall. Peanuts, cashew nuts, beans, whole milk and seeds contain copper. Have them to check hair loss.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Female - Prevent Hair Fall: - 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As women age, their hair tends to thin out, although the results are not as dramatic as they are for many men - think of your grandmother's hair compared to your grandfather's. Women's pattern of hair loss is analogous to men's, but has several important differences. The ages we begin having hair loss are the same. A few of both sexes will begin having hair loss very early in their twenties, but most do not note changes until the mid-thirties to forties. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Women's hair loss tends to be an even overall thinning; as opposed to men's hair loss in which the hairline recedes and/or there is balding at the crown of the head. Women tend to lose hair on the crown and at the hairline, which is referred to as female-pattern hair loss.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You may be interested in reading &lt;strong&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.herbalcureindia.com%2Fhair-product%2Fhair-loss-remedy.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.herbalcureindia.com/hair-product/hair-loss-remedy.html&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="66f3e4802cdba2aab1b5046ff3ce7e37">			Comes in different types and the common one is the acne vulgarism that is common during puberty wherein there can be pimples, blackheads, and whiteheads. Another common type of acne is the Resaca, which can be experience by people in their later years. Symptoms on this type of ace include reddening or blushing of cheeks, nose, or forehead. Bumps and papules or pustules may also form.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;People suffering from cystic acne can really benefit from an herbal acne pill, since they are designed to treat acne at its source, from the inside of the body, rather than topically. Cystic acne sufferers really tend to have hormonal issues, which acne pills address by &quot;calming&quot;, soothing and balancing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Symptoms of Acne:-
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	Pimples
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Pustules
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Whiteheads
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Blackheads
&lt;br /&gt;;•	Cysts
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For the purpose of acne relief, usually a paste of neem is applied to the affected area. Treatment with turmeric (antibacterial her&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/cool.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; is an age-old therapy of Indian origin for skin disorders. One can also opt for a combination therapy comprising of neem leaves and turmeric powder for application as a paste on the area affected with acne.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Fairly new herbal acne remedies that actually clear acne through precise combinations of herbal compounds and pure, natural ingredients. These herbal acne pills have been used as very successful, and often times permanent, remedies to clear acne on both adults and adolescents.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Natural Treatment for Acne: - 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;•	GARLIC: - Garlic is one of nature’s strongest antibiotics and used externally by cutting open a clove of garlic and rubbing it on the problem area. People told me that it doesn't burn but it did. What did work better for me was to crush the garlic clove and mix it with half a cup of hot water in a pan. Soak a clean wash cloth in the solution and then apply to the affected areas only. 
&lt;br /&gt;;•	LEMON: - There are several things that you can do with fresh lemon. Slice a lemon in half and rub it on the effected area and leave it over night and rinse your face in the morning or squeeze the juice and mix it with rose water and apply to the effected areas.
&lt;br /&gt;;•	CUCUMBER: - This is one of the most gentle and refreshing treatments that I have ever used and not only does it helps treat acne but also refreshes the skin and leaves your skin looking and feeling younger. What you should do is blend the cucumber into a paste and apply. 
&lt;br /&gt;;•	ICE: - One of the most simple and least expensive remedies of all is good old fashioned ice that you make daily. You can use this at any time and it will reduce any swelling that you have caused by acne but should be used at the onset of a breakout.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read more on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.swamiramdevmedicines.com%2Fherbal-remedies%2Fdivya-kayakalp-vati.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.swamiramdevmedicines.com/herbal-remedies/divya-kayakalp-vati.html&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>