<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b693615d626f19477051249abce435ca">			You can have to most expensive and highest quality tools for doing anything, but if you are not competent with using them then your results will be substandard.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is not hard to give you many examples of this; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVicmlkZ2V2aWxsYWdlLmNvbS5hdQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;retirement village murray bridge&lt;/a&gt;; is such an example because it is popular. You can take a thousand people all using the same group of methods, and you know what will happen in terms of how well they do.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It all begins with awareness about your self and what you do in your business, and that awareness can actually cause you to implement positive changes for the better. All strategies and marketing or advertising methods are put together with different parts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your campaigns should never remain static, and so the point we are making here is the need to be dynamic and test those sub-components of landing pages and all else.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The 12 Month Millionaire: Audio Coaching Sessions With Vincent James, a six-part audio interview, is a program of Russell Brunson, an Internet marketer who has generated millions online. It's a take off on THE 12 Month Millionaire, the out-of-print book authored by Vince James. Even though he is a past criminal, today Vince James utilizes direct mail marketing to generate revenue that exceeds that of many CEOs. The book advises online marketers in moneymaking strategies and Brunson mainly interviewed James to learn how he could experience more success in his own online marketing business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brunson has personally earned millions through the techniques he studied with James and today people flock to hear him speak on the subject of Internet marketing. In the interview, you could expect to find out how you can become successful when moving your online business offline and, if you're looking to do this, the information will be very useful to you. The typical web marketer is likely to not benefit from the majority of information covered in the interview. However, it does go over some information that will be helpful to the ingenious marketer who will take this information and better his business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The initial session of the interview is precisely how Vincent James launched a million dollar business as a 21 year old boy. He discusses the niche he picked and tells how he was able to achieve success. He put together a membership web site which had 65,000 paying customers in a period of 12 months, and he talks about how he did it. The next part of the interview discusses information publishing and developing info products. Vincent made available info products via direct marketing and direct mailing, and he shares his tricks on how he did it. People are always talking about building a list and the third session discusses Vincent's methods of creating a list of prospects as well as potential customers and being positive that the information remains up to date. You're going to know the value of your customers and how to turn them into a steady stream of income.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vincent uses the fourth part of the interview to share precisely how he realized business success with his advertising strategies. If you need to learn how to convert site traffic into sales, this session is very important. In the fifth part of the interview, you'll discover more ways to advertise on radio and TV. In the sixth session, Vincent explains different ways to deal with issues that will inevitably crop up in your business. Find out how to handle it when somebody copies your product without your permission.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are several products online for teaching you how to generate profits. They differ in quality and simplicity of use. In this program, you'll learn a number of valuable tips, especially in reference to using offline marketing to make money. Whether you just started website marketing yesterday or have been at it for years, these interviews will give you some good information.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Additional Links:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbGl4eWEuY29tL2Jsb2cvNDIwNTE5Ny8xMi1Nb250aC1NaWxsaW9uYWlyZS1BdWRpby1Db2FjaGluZy1TZXNzaW9ucy1XaXRoLVZpbmNlbnQtSmFtZXMtU3VjY2Vzcy1UaHJvdWdoLU9mZmxpbmUtTWFya2V0aW5n" target="_blank"&gt;;How You Can Generate Profits Offline-12 Month Millionaire: Audio Coaching Sessions With Vincent James&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uZXhvcGlhLmNvbS91c2Vycy9sZXdpc2hlYmF0dGxlL2Jsb2cvMi1ob3ctdG8tZWFybi1tb25leS1vZmZsaW5lMTItbW9udGgtbWlsbGlvbmFpcmUtYXVkaW8tY29hY2hpbmctc2Vzc2lvbnMtd2l0aC12aW5jZW50LWphbWVz" target="_blank"&gt;;12 Month Millionaire: Audio Coaching Sessions With Vincent James - Success Through Offline Marketing&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXluLmNvbS93YXluYmxvZy5odG1sP3djaT12aWV3ZW50cnkmYW1wO2VudHJ5X2tleT0xOTQ4Njc_" target="_blank"&gt;;Tips On How To Generate Profits Offline-12 Month Millionaire: Audio Coaching Sessions With Vincent James&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>