<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="30bef09feacde023269c903af4aef0b6">			Panasonic was set up in 1918 by Konosuke Matsushita.  Their first commercially produced devices were a two way bulb socket adapter along with an add-on plug adapter. The first Matsushita merchandise were very popular because they were better quality having a cheaper cost. These founding ideals are working within Panasonic in the present day with high quality electronic products with premium characteristics but no  premium price tag. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After The Second World War, Panasonic expanded dramatically. Panasonic merchandise, especially the transistor radios rapidly had become world renowned. Exports in to the United States increased at a rapid pace as Panasonic built manufacturing factories around the world. Matsushita first opened U.S. locations in New York in 1959 as Matsushita Electric Corporation of America (MECA). Panasonic’s rapid advancement attracted world-wide awareness and in 1961, Panasonic’s CEO, Konosuke Matsushita in fact was on the front cover of Time Magazine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ever since then, Panasonic continues to be a innovator in technological innovation. Panasonic has had plasma TVs that were some of the biggest available for sale.  Panasonic &quot;;1sts&quot;; in the television market place include the first seventy inch plasma, the earliest 103 inch plasma televisions and today offers a 152 inch  plasma TV. While at the same time distributing a line of Liquid crystal display televisions, Panasonic has polished and enhanced the plasma TV engineering to present among the best plasma televisions available in the market while some other leading brands like Pioneer, Mitsubishi and Fujitsu abandoned plasma development and fled the plasma marketplace. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A primary reason a number of the plasma TV producers ditched plasma was concern with regulation prohibiting the plasma devices that traditionally utilized more electricity compared to the competing Liquid crystal display technology. Panasonic persevered and designed plasma televisions that require substantially less electrical power and are also considerably slimmer to match LCD sets. These plasma televisions happen to be unparalleled in black level, brightness, off center viewing and high speed pixel reaction times by their LCD competition. Image “burn in” and plasma display lifespan that seriously affected very early plasma sets have both long been reduced by the much better designs. These features produce a significantly better viewing experience than competing makes and technologies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Panasonic Viera line of high definition (HD) televisions is among the very best available today and includes Liquid crystal display, 3-D optimized Liquid crystal display, plasma and 3D optimized plasma TV's. In addition to TV's, Panasonic manufactures all types of consumer electronics. Whenever you invest in a quality device, you should maintain and repair that unit to obtain maximum satisfaction and product life. When searching for an authorized Panasonic television repair center in the Chicago land area you will find only one choice, Rex Service Company.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Rex Service Company is a proud member in good standing with NSA (National Service Alliance), Electric Service Dealers Association (ESDA) and NESDA (National Electronic Service Dealers Association). Rex Service has a business license from the Village of Worth Illinois, has got workman’s compensation insurance and legal responsibility insurance. Rex Service is also ranked positively by the BBB. Phone Rex Service Company today at: 800-HI-REX-TV (800-447-398) or visit us at 7030 W. 111th Street, Worth Illinois 60482&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.chicagotvrepair.biz"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.chicagotvrepair.biz&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>