<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="236f6a072d8313a73be5627e6b366fbd">			It is one of my favourites to get some bargains in the small market with commodity being on sale, where I can often buy wonderful goods with extremely low prices beyond the expectations, which is definitely a pleasant experience. Lady Gaga Tell You to Settle Most Amazing &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany jewellery&lt;/a&gt;;  My boyfriend Michael took me out in car every weekends, voluntarily to be my bodyguard shopping around every corner of the markets.Top ten Troubles of the Popular retro glasses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I have never forgotten the day, 19th June, which was a pleasant Saturday with a few pieces of white clouds flowing in the azure blue sky and cool gentle breeze fondling our faces.Like usual, we set off in the early morning. He drove, and I appreciated the beautiful scenery outside and simultaneously taking care that whether there were ad boards of small markets which provided things for sale.We stopped and moved on in a repeated way and drove around freely for the whole morning.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When we drove back, on the roadside near home, a huge billboard came to my sight where there was a brilliant ring and some words written with bold red paint &quot;Jenny, will you be my wife?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since our car was moving so fast that I gave a glance of the board just for several seconds. Yet I admired the brave man who had written this advertisement. It was amazing and the beloved Jenny was really a lucky dog.All of a sudden, I seemingly came to my mind, sit up swiftly and asked &quot;Michael, am I that Jenny?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Sure,&quot; said Michael calmly, &quot;do you?&quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;Yes!&quot; The word just came out with no hesitation in my mind, which is so humiliating! Hearing this Michael took out a lightblue box immediatey, and put the Tiffany diamond ring in the box on my slim finger.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;The ring on that brand is given to whom?&quot;I asked with rear realization.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&quot;It's just a duplicate of this ring.&quot; He said with a cunning smile.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We back the car, took the billboard down. That year we married, and our love goes on witnessed by the billboard and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany sale uk&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;You may like these site:
&lt;br /&gt;;Tiffany Jewelry --&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany jewelry&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;Buy Tiffany &amp; Co Jewelry, Silver Tiffany Jewellery at Tiffany &amp; Co On Sale --&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany uk&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;Tiffany &amp; Co Silver Jewelry! Best Tiffany Jewelry On Sale - MyTiffanyWorld --&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany store&lt;/a&gt;; .		</conversation>		<conversation id="919980b2c0fe65e364c1597dae78eb09">			A real strong woman at the workplace, &quot;universal&quot; jewelry is indispensable, these jewelry are neat, simple, stylish and no shortage of fine. 3 New You Should KnowThey not only accord with characteristics of dragon ladies, but also exert a subtle influence on intensifing their qualities in workplace. Learn Plain Tips to Resume  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany uk&lt;/a&gt;;  from Anne HathawayOf course, the effects of almighty collocation with clothing and situation in staffer can also make the worth of the jewelry multiply.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First tip: jewelry of modern lines and modern dynamic type.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No matter Tiffany bracelets or Gucci bracelets is a wonderful selection.Because on the one hand, the concise lining sense revealed by the jewelry can well echo the high-level texture of your professional suit.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On the other hand, such lines full of the style of modernism can make you very fashionable, very modern.What's more, these lines can also declare your attitude of keeping up with the time and fashion, stressing directly your stance of pursuing innovation and change.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The second kind: small, exquisite and delicate jewelries wining big ones.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Small and exquisite jewelry looks neither luxurious nor showing off, so it is the typical non-antagonism type among all the jewelry worn in the workplace.While the delicate links of London charm is the classic collection among the links of London. It has been highly appreciated by the high-level executives for their compact and stylish designs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With all-purpose style, unique and lovely design which full of ingenuity and never feels artificial, you may feel easy to choose any business suits and workplace to match with it.By dressing them, you will not be considered as a &quot;dragon lady&quot; at the office. And meanwhile, their careffully designed and made style will indicate your high standards for conducting yourself and your business.Such a lady who knows how to be internalized and forceful is sure to win the success in staffer.It is easy to imagine that how many envious looks will be attracted when you wear this kind of jewelry.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Thirdly, the jewelry owning simple outline and winning in texture.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Less is more is true for either &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany jewellery&lt;/a&gt;; or staffers just as leaving space when drawing.Such compact design however, gives the jewelry more sense of texture, leaving much room for imagination. And such jewelry would also make you look more capable, ready and trim.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This year, Cartier’s new work - &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany store&lt;/a&gt;; , best exemplifies such design.This neat and fashionable style is made by the gold of 3 colors and 3 circles.Outlines full of sense of architecture and stereoscopic sensation suggest your resolution on work, and simple lines and decoration indicate your worldly wisdom. Both of the aspects greatly increase your personal charisma.More importantly, this series is not only suitable for different ages, styles of women, but also very suitable for men to wear.		</conversation>		<conversation id="34a9df8823d214acd5c36b5d2444ad5d">			To get married is a very important thing to many girls. In fact, nearly every girl wants to be a princess and dreams to have a romantic proposal. Therefore, how can men realize their girlfriends' dreams and propose successfully? Do you belong to one of those men and are worrying about your proposal? If you do, please listen to the following suggestion which may bring you some benefits. Tiffany, which is the queen of jewelry industry, is your best choice when you propose because it can help you win your girlfriend’s heart.
&lt;br /&gt;;So, are you thinking why you should choose the diamond ring of Tiffany? I will tell you know something about it. As far as I know, Tiffany is famous for its silverwares and jewelries. It was founded by Charles Lewis Tiffany in1837 in New York. In 1886, the first platinum six – claw diamond ring made the whole world find the charm of its simple style and original creation. Tiffany is the symbol of American and the quintessence of its design is to show American characteristics. The designers of it acquire inspiration from natural world and every masterpiece reflects the frankness, optimistic and wisdom of American people. Besides, its designs require perfection. Every simple and clear line of its masterpieces tells the calm and elegant of themselves and harmony is naturally presented in every design of Tiffany. So are the designs of Tiffany’s diamond rings.
&lt;br /&gt;;Love and beauty, romanticism and dream are the main theme of Tiffany’s diamond rings. Their subtle and beautiful designs can satisfy all females’ desire. In many films, we can hear the acclaim “I got Tiffany!” of many leading actresses. In western countries, Tiffany has nearly been equal to proposal and the happiness it represents even surpasses the ring itself.
&lt;br /&gt;;Do you want to give a surprise to her? I Do you want to get married with her? If you do, please come on to buy the diamond ring of Tiffany because Tiffany is the beautiful dream of nearly every girl. Maybe you think it is out of time to hold a bunch of flowers in one hand and hold diamond ring of Tiffany in another hand to propose to your girlfriend or maybe you think the proposal way is not important. However, it is always a publically admitted way to propose and it can show the sincerity of you. So, what are you waiting? Please take action as quickly as possible. I hope, all of you can lead a sweet life in the company of Tiffany.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?
&lt;br /&gt;;Relate Useful Website:
&lt;br /&gt;;CCNA, SCJP, CompTIA, A+, CIW, OCP, IT Certification Practice Test -Provue.org --&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany jewellery&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;Pass4sure Offer Kinds Of IT Certification Training Materials --&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany uk&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;cheapglassessale.com Cheap Eyeglasses,Shop Cheap Eyeglasses Online --&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany sale uk&lt;/a&gt;; .
&lt;br /&gt;;CCVP Certification 642-436 QCVOICE -- &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ldXJvdGlmZmFueS5jby51ay8_" target="_blank"&gt;;tiffany store&lt;/a&gt;; .		</conversation>	</conversations></author>