<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="dc9242185fd6c5e22df866490349ecc5">			In 1997, when &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waW5ram9yZGFuczIwMTIuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Women Jordan&lt;/a&gt;; Brand officially became an entity independent of Nike, the first ever womens-exclusive Team Jordan model debuted. It was the perfect method of brand expansion as it tapped into the burgeoning WNBA, which had its inaugural season in 1997, and the growing awareness and popularity of women’s basketball as a whole thanks to superstars like Cynthia Cooper and Cheryl Swoopes. While there was no true model name for this shoe (simply dubbed ‘Womens Air Jordan), it was a highly popular model around the WNBA at the time (seen below in the in-game shot), with the male counterpart finding no shame in going 1.5 sizes to cop his own pair; it carried a sleek design with the Air Jordan XIII signature ‘dimples’ on the upper, and to this day remains one of the most unique and collectible Jordan models to date. It’s not often we get to see these fifteen-year-old Jordans, but here’s a look at a Girls size of this model below; take a look and don’t forget to place your bid on the listing from inkjordans2012.com
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;From &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waW5ram9yZGFuczIwMTIuY29tL3dvbWVuLWFpci1qb3JkYW4tNC1yZXRyby12b2x0YWdlLWNoZXJyeXdoaXRlYmxhY2stcC0xLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Jordan 4 Cherry&lt;/a&gt;; basketball shoes like the Air Jordan 2012 to the iconic styles of Jordan Retros, there's a Jordan shoe for any season and any occasion. Since their release in 1985, Jordan shoes have become a juggernaut in the sneaker world. A unique amalgam of innovative technologies, sweet design detailing and fresh color combinations add up to a line of sneakers that rule the courts and the street. Whether you're looking to dominate the basketball court or own the pavement with the freshest kicks around, Air Jordan shoes give you the look and feel you deserve. And every Jordan Retro shoe has a story to tell - from &quot;The Shot&quot; in the Jordan Retro IV sneaker to Michael Jordan's first title in the Jordan Retro VI shoes. Featuring top-of-the-line Nike technologies, the most recent Flight performance shoes are built to provide you with an edge on the court, while the lifestyle shoes feature the freshest colors and designs. Match your Jordan sneakers with Jordan clothing for a unique look you'll be proud to call your own. Don't forget to check out &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5waW5ram9yZGFuczIwMTIuY29tL3dvbWVuLWpvcmRhbnMtNC1jLTEuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Women Jordan 4&lt;/a&gt;; and sin hundreds of styles, sizes and colors for men and kids.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>