<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f4c22b7302a42faf2b77a88f4363eb64">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FRobert_Raven_Kraft"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Raven_Kraft&lt;/a&gt;; Kraft following a daily running progam for 36 years since 1975 spent his early years on the country-western music scene in Las Vegas and Nashville USA. Robert Raven Kraft keeps a daily online diary of each of his running programs and the nicknames of those who have completed one of his daily programs with him from the 1300 people who have joined him on South Beach. Robert Raven Kraft's 8 mile daily running program in summer starts at 17:00 and changes in winter beginning at 16:00 starting from the lifeguard stand on Miami Beach, situated at 5th Street and back again.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Robert Raven Kraft often is joined by fellow runners who like to keep him company on his 8 mile run on Miami Beach USA. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FRobert_Raven_Kraft"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Raven_Kraft&lt;/a&gt;; Kraft is a world hero indeed as he is currently the only known runner who has 36 years unbroken running record on the sand within the same location. Robert Raven Kraft is an extraordinary man that has seen every sunset in South Florida for 36 years and run beneath it inspiring others to do the same. Those who run alongside Robert Raven Kraft on his daily eight mile run and complete it earn themselves a nickname and a place in his online diary. For over 35 years Robert Raven Kraft has drawn media attention from magazines such as Runner's World and the USA National Public Radio Show including a feature cover on SportsCenter Magazine. Runner and published writer Lee Williams based the lead character in his fictional book &quot;The Lifeguard Murders' on Robert Raven Kraft due to the amount he was inspired by this streak runner. Robert Raven Kraft was 33 years old in 2008 and by the turn of the new year had 'clocked' an amazing 96,000 miles of daily streak running. By 9th March 2009 Robert Raven Kraft hit the magic 100,000 miles which is 20,084.5 hours of unbroken daily running and is roughly estimated to be the same distance four times around world. Feature stories were run in the Miami Herald and ESPN when at 34 years of age Robert Raven Kraft reached his record one hundred thousand running miles. Miami City honoured Robert a month later in 2009 during a city commission meeting where they showed his 100,000th video run. In May of the same year, ESPN ran Robert's story &quot;Outside the Lines&quot; across the globe to an audience of millions and newly inspired international runners began to follow Robert's online diaries.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Robert was honoured to be a celebrity guest for the city's homeless people in the same year and helped raise funds for those in poverty on the streets of Miami.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The personal and now famous website for &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FRobert_Raven_Kraft"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Raven_Kraft&lt;/a&gt;; Kraft can be found at which features milestone achievements, videos and profile of thisdetermined and amazing man.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>