<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="3183da4e6333a9da6106b95d92baa393">			Lots of automobile owners do not understand what a carburetor is but on the other hand it doesn't hurt to learn a little bit about what a carburetor is as well as what it does.  Learning a thing or two about carburetors can certainly go a great distance when or if yours will stop working. You might not be able to fix broken carburetor yourself but at a minimum you will comprehend what the technicians are speaking about when they diagnose your carburetor. Listed below are some key facts about carburetors.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What Is The Carburetor?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The carburetor is a device on the engine of a car or other vehicle that mixes fuel with air. These are featured on internal combustion type engines. In most cases, the carburetor is no longer used though. Most cars now use fuel injection as opposed to the use of a carburetor. Nevertheless, the carburetor is still used on many small type engines and in older or specialized vehicles. Cars built after the decade of the 1980’s, no longer use a carburetor, but use an electronic, computerized fuel injector instead. In many cases, the motorcycle still used a carburetor.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many high performance cars or vehicles with more than four cylinders could use more than one carburetors but in general, many use just one carburetor. So what is the purpose of a carburetor?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Those who are unfamiliar with the Bernoulli principle, it states that air that is moving has pressure that is lower than air that is still.  What this means is that the quicker this air moves the lower its pressure will be.  The engines throttle controls the quantity of air that flows into the carburetor compared to the quanity of fuel that is consumed.  When the carburetor creates a vacuum it draws in more fuel which in turn allows for faster air flow.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to repair work that is done on the carburetor, it is necessary to learn not only what is wrong with it but also what is needed to repair it and why that is. When you understand how the carburetor works, you can get a better idea of what is needed to repair it. And, you will need to consult a professional if the task is beyond you because not repairing the carburetor correctly can and does lead to more serious problems with the engine down the road.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Carburetor Manufacturers&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many different carburetor manufacturers in the market and many specialize in specific areas or the type of engine they make and sell.  If you're in the market for a new carburetor, below is a list. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Autolite - Manufacturer for Ford carburetors&lt;br /&gt;;Hitachi, Keihin or Mikui - Manufacturer for Japanese vehicles carburetors&lt;br /&gt;;Rochester Carburetor - Manufacturer for GM carburetors&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Alternatively, purchasing a rebuilt carburetor would be a more economical way to rebuilding your vehicle.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read more:   &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.carb-x.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.carb-x.com&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fen.wikipedia.org%2Fwiki%2FCarburetor"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Carburetor&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="bcd42a1eca75c4bfe8e75f19269fb7a6">			Having difficulties with your carburetor in your automotive and have to fix what ever is broken?  You might not be have the ability to repair your own carburetor if you really don't have any car restoration expertise but some of information regarding carburetors could only help.  Read on to learn about what a carburetor is and the role it plays in your engine.  The following are a number of details about carburetors.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Carburetor Helps Your Vehicle Run&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The carburetor is a device that was popularly used in vehicles prior to the 80's. It helps your car run by mixing fuel and air in internal combustion engines.  However, carburetors are no longer used in newer car models. Many use computerized fuel injector now.  For car enthusiasts looking to restore their classic they will need to buy their rebuilt carburetors from a rebuilt carburetor specialist.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many high performance cars or vehicles with more than four cylinders could use more than one carburetors but in general, many use just one carburetor. So what is the purpose of a carburetor?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Have you ever heard of Bernoulli’s principle? It says that moving air has a lower pressure than air that is still. That means that the faster the air moves, the lower the pressure will be. The throttle controls the amount of air that is allowed into the carburetor as opposed to the amount of fuel that is used. The vacuum that is created by the carburetor is what draws in more fuel into the carburetor and allows for faster flows of air.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to repair work that is done on the carburetor, it is necessary to learn not only what is wrong with it but also what is needed to repair it and why that is. When you understand how the carburetor works, you can get a better idea of what is needed to repair it. And, you will need to consult a professional if the task is beyond you because not repairing the carburetor correctly can and does lead to more serious problems with the engine down the road.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Carburetor Manufacturers&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are many different carburetor manufacturers in the market and many specialize in specific areas or the type of engine they make and sell.  If you're in the market for a new carburetor, below is a list. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Autolite - Manufacturer for Ford carburetors&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Hitachi, Keihin or Mikui - Manufacturer for Japanese vehicles carburetors&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Rochester Carburetor - Manufacturer for GM carburetors&lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Alternatively, purchasing a rebuilt carburetor would be a more economical way to rebuilding your vehicle.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Visit these resources for more info:  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXJiLXguY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Remanufactured Carburetor&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2VuLndpa2lwZWRpYS5vcmcvd2lraS9DYXJidXJldG9y" target="_blank"&gt;;Carburetors&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>