<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="3a0244a65abf964d85db1d4ddd84d3a">			1.It's Inexpensive. Solutions range from $199 - $999, this price range allows for multiple videos and annual video refreshes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2.It attracts visual learners. Different people learn in different ways. Some people learn best by seeing things demonstrated rather than reading or listening to someone talk about it. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Adding video allows you to better reach visually-oriented customers.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3.It builds your search results and helps customers find you. Search engines prefer video which significantly improves search engine optimization (SEO) results. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Google has added content such as blogs, video and images to what their engine indexes and returns in search. Recently, the company said such content is returned in one of every four searches.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4.Drives more leads. In addition to increasing SEO results, distributing your video to popular Internet video sites raises your visibility and expands your audience. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5.Increases conversions. High-quality, professionally produced video, offers a stronger sense of credibility to advertisers and more effectively communicates what makes your business better than the competition. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6.It promotes your products or services. For retailers, what's more likely to make a sale - a static picture on your Web site of your chain saw, or a video that shows how quickly it can cut down trees? If you're a service business, video allows you to interest prospects by offering free samples of your trainings or seminars.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7.Preferred ad format. Internet users click a video’s “Play” button more than they click on image ads. Online videos are more interactive, engaging and informative than other advertising methods.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8.More efficient (and enjoyable) communication. Watching a video is much easier and faster than reading text-based web content. Internet users want to know as much as possible as quickly as possible. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9.It gives good customer service. Instead of handing them a lengthy installation manual, customers can play a video on your site and learn how to set up your product.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10.It's personal. If you have a magnetic company executive who could simply talk to the camera about what you do and why you're better than the competition, it can be very welcoming. It feels friendly and makes customers feel more comfortable contacting you.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;11.It taps into the power of YouTube. Besides posting your videos on your own site, you can also post them on YouTube. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Roughly one-quarter of all Internet users visit YouTube each day, viewing up to 20 hours a week. It's an increasingly popular place to find how-to information, and using YouTube gives your business a chance to find entirely new customers from outside your existing network of contacts.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;12.Easy to share. Good videos go viral as your customers share with their friends, creating the best kind of leads … referrals.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Shane Melanson is a highly sought after online marketer and social media expert for real estate professionals known for his unique and cutting edge marketing techniques. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Shane is also the author of numerous books, including, YouTube Marketing Secrets for Real Estate Agents, 31 Days to Dominating Your Local Market as well as the widely read Free Report: How To Land a Client In 2 Hours or Less, Free, Using a Short 2 Minute Video.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To know more call 1.800.931.7497 Ext 1 or go to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fvideoinfluenceproductions.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://videoinfluenceproductions.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="d95d6445bcf589b17defb5914c634797">			Driving to my office, I routinely listen to sales and marketing talks. Guys like Jim Rohn, Jeffery Gitomer, online marketing guys like Rich Schefren and others.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I’m always interested in new spins or old ways of marketing a business. As I recently closed a large real estate/business transaction I am even more focused today on how we can attract and keep customers.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Consulting for small business is fun for me- mainly because I love it, and love talking with other like minded business owners. Now, there is another reason it is fun to be a consultant, there is less stress than being the actual business owners.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Being an owner in 5 different business (brick and mortar) I know how stressful it is to start up and then find the right people to help grow it. One of my business, Video Influence Productions, I am marketing consultant for small business with their online social media and web video needs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If I screw up a marketing campaign (which is really a subjective test of the market place), I loose a client and some money. Now, I am not saying that I take this lightly, but it got me to thinking as the new business my partners and I started. We are in the process of hiring numerous consultants, some of which may include an offline marketing consultant.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What shocked me was the attitude many of the consultants take. It is as if they figure money grows on trees and that there would be no consequences if things didn’t turn out.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I will say this, the guys we hired, have been tremendous assets to our team so far. But, to find these diamonds in the rough (cliche, but true) took time and preparation on our part.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here are some lessons we learned, some costly, that I feel will help you in hiring a any consultant. I’ll gear it to hiring a marketing consultant, but think that most of the advice would be good principles to follow regardless of service provider or consultant.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Always get at least 2 RFP’s (request for proposal).
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Can’t say how many times we met with the 1st provider and thought, well, lets go with these guys, they seem great. Only to find out that they were inferior to the competition.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The other benefit to multiple interviews- you learn what questions to ask.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here is a great line my mentor taught me, at the end of any meeting
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“Thanks you for meeting with us. Was there any question we should have asked, that we did not?”
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Always get detailed quotes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Find out if they plan to charge you for putting together a quote. Some guys will expect you to pay them for putting together a quote- its not good or bad, just know ahead of time.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Understand the terms of service.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Too often the communicated request from the business owner to provider is lost in translation. Here is why it is even more critical to work with a seasoned professional.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many times there are questions that you may not ask (for various reasons) and can come back to haunt you.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I always do this towards the end of the meeting.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To recap- Here is the outcome and results I am after. Can you deliver these at the quoted price?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How long will it take to deliver these results?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What, if any circumstances do you foresee that may slow down or alter the results I am after?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How do you handle ongoing support? Who takes calls after hours?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So those are the 3 tips I thought would benefit your business. Hiring anyone is difficult these days. Finding the best takes time, but it is worth it.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As an aside- not one of our consultant did we hire based on price or hourly rate. In fact, many of these guys are typically the best and thus charge 2-3x their competitors. But, here is the key: they deliver results and that is all that counts.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more information visit: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZpZGVvaW5mbHVlbmNlcHJvZHVjdGlvbnMuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Video Influence Productions&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>