<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2fdd6ec1576b06ab515b9c36da54d8ea">			A great smile does not make a real truth teller. A talker of transform does not define a reformer. Make no blunder, for the very good of the nation I want President Obama to succeed in obtaining us out of the scandalous financial meltdown we are immersed in. But I do not like quite a few of his steps, policies and methods for accomplishing this, nor does the stock sector.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I usually had my doubts that he was a accurate agent of modify and reformer when it arrived to the construction of the political and authorities technique. He took an awful whole lot of dollars from the quite rich and powerful in his campaign. Guaranteed, with his excellent speaking skills he has the capability to win public approval, but most People in america are not deep, important thinkers, nor do most have the greatest detailed facts. What if he is just yet another untrustworthy politician? What if he does not maintain his claims? With these issues in head, I have examined 4 areas where I come across President Obama's conduct disappointing.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Most distressing is that he set men and women in strength who failed to protect against the economic disaster, notably the Treasury Secretary. As an individual with significant encounter in federal government, I was appalled that President Obama has picked so a lot of expert men and women for his cabinet and high degree White Home positions who earlier had strong positions in authorities or the financial sector but failed to avert the financial meltdown that is however worsening. Or even sound loud alarms about what was profoundly mistaken with financial process. Why not appear tough for people today that had been criticizing various elements of the house loan and financial regions? Individuals from the educational world, observe puppy groups and public curiosity organizations that might have labored previously in govt could bring more creativity to the issues. For a person who built a big campaign deal of staying towards politics as normal, Obama has shown treasured very little evidence that he would like accurate outsiders to steer his administration. His chief of workers Rahm Emanuel is the epitome of a protector of the position quo political process. Somewhat than picking out a lot of massive identify Democrats and a couple of Republicans, why not find out independents, whistle blowers and reformers to resolve the economic meltdown?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Accepting a big shelling out invoice loaded with pork earmarks it starkly contradictory to what Obama promised during the marketing campaign. Throughout the campaign this is what candidate Obama claimed: &quot;;We need to have earmark reform. And when I'm president, I will go line by line to make sure we're not shelling out income unwisely.&quot;; He has talked repeatedly about fiscal responsibility and actual modify in politics. Converse is low cost. This paying bill is not. Not with more than nine,000 earmarks totaling some $12 billion. It is sheer nonsense for him and his supporters to say shamelessly that the investing bill is one thing left around from the Bush administration. Well, so is the Iraq war, but Obama absolutely was all set to make alterations with it. Why not have the integrity and courage to veto this spending bill and deliver it back to Congress with the mandate to reduce out the pork? Why need to we feel guarantees to wait until eventually he cuts earmarks from foreseeable future investing charges when plainly Congress, both Democrats and Republicans, are not ready to give up earmarks. And why won't they? Straightforward, they create earmarks as component of the legal corruption that makes it possible for marketing campaign contributors to get the earmarks they want.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Take into account this example. Representative Anthony Weiner, Democrat, New York, received more than $160,000 in campaign contributions from for the Sephardic Addiction and Loved ones Training (Safe and sound) Groundwork in Brooklyn, New York, which has an earmark from him for $238,000. He was also sole sponsor on a $300,000 earmark for Brooklyn's Ohel Children's Residence and Family Providers, whose board members and employees have also given him money its director has personally given $six,240. And the bill incorporates 14 earmarks requested by lawmakers for tasks sought by PMA Group, a lobbying business used by all kinds of entities to get earmarks, which is at the center of a federal corruption investigation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And consider this: Not supporting congressional efforts to type a fact commission to appear into Bush administration misdeeds, this kind of as letting torture of intended terrorists, key detention, and domestic spying, is also challenging to fathom. Obama retains up the malarkey about wanting to glimpse forward, not backward. But the pursuit of justice and finding how our Constitution has been flagrantly violated by President George W. Bush and some others are essential tasks for a real democracy. &quot;;Nothing has completed much more hurt to America's location in the entire world than the revelation that this nation stretched the legislation and the bounds of executive strength to authorize torture and cruel cure. Such a commission of inquiry would shed light on what errors have been manufactured so that we can master from those errors and not repeat them,&quot;; mentioned Patrick Leahy, chairman of the Senate Judiciary Committee, the chief advocate for a commission.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Appreciably, a USA These days/Gallup poll in February located that 62 % of People in america favor a criminal investigation or an independent panel to seem into the use of torture, illegal wiretapping, and other alleged abuses of energy by the Bush administration. So how can we realize why Obama does not passionately assistance undertaking this? I like what Georgetown University professor David Cole mentioned: &quot;;in the encounter of credible evidence that substantial-stage Bush administration officials authorized torture, a crime against humanity, the least we ought to do is undertake a significant, independent investigation.&quot;; What is frightening is that maybe Obama fears a person day facing anything equivalent for his misdeeds as president. It all comes down to this easy but profoundly critical concept that Us residents are meant to embrace: certainly no 1 need to be above the law.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post Resource: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2FEzineArticles.com%2F2077012%26lt%3Bbr"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://EzineArticles.com/2077012&lt;br&lt;/a&gt; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;REFERENCES:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fiinformyou.com%2FArt%2F396586%2F24%2FOnline-Integrity-Test-A-Great-Tool-For-Employers.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fiinformyou.com%2FArt%2F396586%2F24%2FOnline-Integrity-Test-A-Great-Tool-For-Employers.html%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://iinformyou.com/Art/396586/24/Online-Integrity-Test-A-Great-Tool-For-Employers.html&quot;;&gt;http://iinformyou.com/Art/396586/24/Online-Integrity-Test-A-Great-Tool-For-Employers.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&lt;/a&gt; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwhydir.com%2Farticledetail.php%3Fartid%3D130561%26amp%3Bcatid%3D10%26amp%3Btitle%3DBreakthrough%2BIn%2BHuman%2BResource%2BManagement%2BUsing%2BOnline%2BIntegrity%2BTest%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fwhydir.com%2Farticledetail.php%3Fartid%3D130561%26amp%3Bcatid%3D10%26amp%3Btitle%3DBreakthrough%2BIn%2BHuman%2BResource%2BManagement%2BUsing%2BOnline%2BIntegrity%2BTest%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bbr"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://whydir.com/articledetail.php?artid=130561&amp;catid=10&amp;title=Breakthrough+In+Human+Resource+Management+Using+Online+Integrity+Test&quot;;&gt;http://whydir.com/articledetail.php?artid=130561&amp;catid=10&amp;title=Breakthrough+In+Human+Resource+Management+Using+Online+Integrity+Test&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&lt;/a&gt; /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.1articleworld.com%2FArt%2F694554%2F106%2FBreakthrough-In-Human-Resource-Management-Using-Online-Integrity-Test.html%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bhttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.1articleworld.com%2FArt%2F694554%2F106%2FBreakthrough-In-Human-Resource-Management-Using-Online-Integrity-Test.html%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.1articleworld.com/Art/694554/106/Breakthrough-In-Human-Resource-Management-Using-Online-Integrity-Test.html&quot;;&gt;http://www.1articleworld.com/Art/694554/106/Breakthrough-In-Human-Resource-Management-Using-Online-Integrity-Test.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>