<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="c874783ed2f0054da86a146b50406db5">			When people are conjecturing the trend of Autumn-Winter Fashion in 09, top designers have designed serials of Autumn-Winter Fashion. Summarize the New Prime &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55Y29qZXdlbGxlcnkuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;tiffany jewelry&lt;/a&gt; of Kylie Minogue They design the clothes with their keen powers of observation and deep design foundations, in which the fall season elements are all collected ,now let us feel their design one by one.You May Pass over These When Decorate with &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aG9tYXNhYm8udWsuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;thomas sabo&lt;/a&gt; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. 4 Basic Things that You May not Know about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aWZmYW55Y29qZXdlbGxlcnkuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;tiffany jewelry&lt;/a&gt; Color texture natural autumn With the love of nature is far exceeds the distinction of seasons, and this point is reflected on the fashion is the most obvious undoubtedly. The peculiarity of the the shoulder gown skiert pattern is the enjoyful rendering of flower In the decoration, exaggerated style necklace is more and more popular in resent years, and style is changeable Can consider collocation of color sweater, coat, also can wear European fashionable in his loins, shaping the mix effect of Japan and South Korea style
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. Modern interpretation of geometry. The fact that people like geometry is the best embodiment of the space sense. Scrutinize the ever-changing fashionable arena, whether glaring space, still full of building charm of pop style, all need the help of geometry. The grid-line figure which is typical geometry element is already represented the European style and many girls who like cute things can’t stop loving it any more. Take a close look you will find that autumn and winter coats are short-sleeved,if you wear tight clothes or sweater inside, you will not feel cold.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. Boot One issue can not be neglected is that you should take care of the feet when the weather becoming cool. Hence, the change of boot is more sensitive than the dress for you to have a health statement. Let's find some tips to protect our foot when you put delicate shoes and comfort slippers away for sometime. With cream-colored, aureate, as a representative of the color of brown boots is always the most can catch a person eye at this time, both warming your feet and unlacking of fashion sense.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>