<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="abef8d3a7c09b6a35079bf3b5af26708">			&lt;P&gt;;We all know that we should smear sunscreen products on face to resist ultraviolet light, then at the same time do we ignored the body sunburns?The correct thought of sunscreenig should be smear sunscreen products to all the bare skin under the sunshine to avoid &quot;white face, black neck&quot; and such embarrassing situation!Keep in mind that you have to clean your make-up after smearing the sunscreen.Want to Know Manners that Have Injure to ? Here It Is!&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;The same with the facial skin, there are also some old horniness to be wiped up, generally speaking, making some friction with towel when have a bath can be reached the effects of exfoliator, but at the joint should be use the specially exfoliator products.Girls, who care body skin caring, must know the daily skin care techniques such as smearing latex after a bath, in fact, many points still need of special care?How to Eradicate It? &lt;A title=abercrombie href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myafclothing.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Babercrombie%26lt%3B%2FA%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myafclothing.com/&quot;&gt;;abercrombie&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;; can Help You Make It!&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;In the previous passage, we have mentioned the joints such as elbow and knees and neck chest. Excellent Lindsay Lohan for &lt;A title=&quot;cheap bridesmaid dresses&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.boncyboutique.com%2Fbridesmaid-dresses%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Bcheap"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.boncyboutique.com/bridesmaid-dresses/&quot;&gt;;cheap&lt;/a&gt;; bridesmaid dresses&lt;/A&gt;; Inspiration These parts require special maintenance procedures compared with others.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;UL&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;LI&gt;;Joints: the complexion of joints always gives people the melanocratic feeling, because the joints accumulate the horniness easily, besides removing the horniness mentioned above in the article, preserving moisture and moisturizing are also indispensable.&lt;/LI&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;LI&gt;;Neck: the neck will produce cervical stripe easily, so don't keep down your head long-term in daily life in case the skin of the neck drapes,Use gentle exfoliating product to remove neck keratin weekly or bi-weekly, the extra facial mask sheet can also be used as the neck membrane after the facial mask.The most basic means of the neck maintenance is after washing and smearing lotion, nourishing the neck with the excess lotion, a little massage will be better.&lt;/LI&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;only starting from the details, will you have the chance to own perfect skin.&lt;/P&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="19cdfef25f532d3d44dff315c45e0f66">			&lt;P&gt;;On the Japanese street, you would not find any woman without facial decoration. What's Most Gorgeous now?: &lt;A title=&quot;tiffany jewelry&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiffanyshop.org%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Btiffany"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tiffanyshop.org/&quot;&gt;;tiffany&lt;/a&gt;; jewelry&lt;/A&gt;; Even a clean looking face will also be dealt with exquisite foundation, together with appropriate brushed eyelash and a little eye shadow. Superior and Fashionable &lt;A title=&quot;tiffany jewelry&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiffanyshop.org%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Btiffany"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tiffanyshop.org/&quot;&gt;;tiffany&lt;/a&gt;; jewelry&lt;/A&gt;; for Under $300 Now! They consider that it is lack of respect to others if not beautiful. Seize the Moment!! &lt;A title=abercrombie href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myafclothing.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Babercrombie%26lt%3B%2FA%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myafclothing.com/&quot;&gt;;abercrombie&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;; is Most Lovely for Love in 2009 This is Japanese women.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;At present, Tokyo is still one of Asian makeup fashion coordinates. It is no doubt Tokyo women who combine the modesty of Asian women and western fashion. Tokyo women attach more importance to foundation, which we can draw a conclusion from the SHISEIDO Marquillage, which best represents the Japanese style, or from the performance in the Tokyo 2009 autumn and winter fashion week.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;we may find that Japanese style doesn't focus on heavy colours. They pay special attention to the foundation which matches the skin perfectly. But the blush is excluded. The prominent blush can gain more praise for the good skin. Exiquisite base make-up is a scenery in Tokyo's streets. Japanese women to foundation cream is what French women to kiss when meeting. Japanese women emphasizing foundation cream is not only a habbit, but also about courtesy.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;Autumn coming, Shiseido, Kanebo cosmetics these two Japanese brands have simultaneously brought out new foundation cream. By carefully investigation, you can find the cream is thick but the makeup is extremely natural and leading you to the shinny healthy skin. The Japanese brand IPSA mainly hits earth tone in this autumn,so at the same time, Aupres also launches two new brown tones.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;Just for the reason that the ground colors fit the Eatern people best, and it is never out of date. Upright Japanese makeup always gives people a light feeling, without heavy eye shadow.&lt;/P&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="cef9c7c331cedf742aad38bc2329fd4c">			&lt;P&gt;;Two spain scientists passed through neurological and optical analysis, then made a new interpretation of Mona Lisa's enigmatic smile. Autumn’s Most Terrific &lt;A title=&quot;abercrombie and fitch&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myafclothing.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Babercrombie"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myafclothing.com/&quot;&gt;;abercrombie&lt;/a&gt;; and fitch&lt;/A&gt;; Tendency Their latest study suggests that Mona Lisa Smile results from the visual errors. The reason for the appearance and disappearance of her smile is when we are watching her, our eyes convey different information to our brain.Come to Buy Sterling &lt;A title=&quot;abercrombie and fitch&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.myafclothing.com%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Babercrombie"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.myafclothing.com/&quot;&gt;;abercrombie&lt;/a&gt;; and fitch&lt;/A&gt;; ! They Are Now at the Most Competitive Price!&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;&quot;Mona Lisa&quot;, created by the famous Italian painter Leonardo da Vinci, is the most prestigious portrait in the world. Hey! Stop Damage Your Impeccable &lt;A title=&quot;tiffany jewellery&quot; href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tiffanystore.org%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3Btiffany"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tiffanystore.org/&quot;&gt;;tiffany&lt;/a&gt;; jewellery&lt;/A&gt;; And the charming smile of the Mona Lisa is a dream-like miracle through ages, which is called the mysterious smile by art historians. Why she was radiant just now and suddenly turns to look so serious? Her enigmatic smile makes many admirers and researchers puzzled and confused.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;The scientists Louis Martinez Outlaw and Diego Alonso Pablos from Alicante Academy of Neurology of Spain made a deep research into that. In their view, different cells of the retina convey different categories of information or &quot;channels&quot; to the brain. These channels will encoded the objects, size, clarity, brightness and location of visual range. Outlaw said, &quot;Sometimes a channel will be covered by another channel and then the smile can be seen, sometimes the channels will be dominated by other channels, and then no smile can be seen.&quot;&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;To analyse visional smile of Mona Lisa at large, Martinez Outlaw and Alonso Pabulusi made volunteers stand different position and angle to appreciate Mona Lisa and recorded their smile change to study different visual channels.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;At first, they asked the volunteers to see the picture in the different distance, but it was difficult for the volunteers to distinguish her facial expression from the far distance as a result of tiny picture. And with the approaching to the portrait, the picture became larger and the subjects saw the smile-the bigger the portrait was, the easier the smile was seen. This suggests that the central vision cells are able to carry out the information of smile as well as the peripheral vision cells are.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;Then they made a contrast study about light to make sure whether light will affect Mona Lisa's smile or not. Two kinds of cells determine the brightness of objects in the environment. One is called &quot;concentrating cells&quot;. This kind of cells can be stimulated only when the center of the object is bright, and it`s this kind of cells that let us see the stars in the night sky. The other one is &quot;scattered cells&quot;, which is only activated when the center of the object is dark. It is them that make us identify the letters in the textbook.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;Martinez Outlaw asked the volunteers to stare at the white screen and the black screen for 30 seconds respectively, and then let them watch the Mona Lisa portrait. Volunteers after watching a white screen are easier to see the Mona Lisa smile. It is because the white screen reduced the &quot;scattered cells&quot;. Therefore, Outlaw came to a conclusion that &quot;concentrating cells&quot; could perceive the Mona Lisa smile. This is of course not all the conclusions of the study because the volunteers' eyes can not help but move to her left cheek right after they distinguished her smile. This indicates that peripheral vision was also involved.&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;Could it be that that da Vinci tried to increase the trouble to the admirers instead of providing the muse for scientists? Outlaw said, &quot;It was absolutely sure. He had written in his note, he would print the expression with extensive changes which were just all mortal beings in his eye.&quot;&lt;/P&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;P&gt;;That was not the first time for scientists to unscramble the masterpieces of Leonardo da Vinci. In 1993, the Canadian art historian Susan Giroux revealed shocking research findings that Mona Lisa's lips which have enchanted numerous lookers should be the back of a naked guy. American Maryland Dr. Joseph - Bao Stokowski said, &quot;Mona Lisa does not fundamentally smile, and her facial expression clearly shows that she wants to cover the fact that she does not grow front teeth.&quot; Dr. Jean-Jacques Kongdaite, a brain surgery expert, believed that Mona Lisa had suffered a stroke before long, which made the muscles of her half face loosed with wry mouth which seemed that she was smiling. In 2005, a U.S. research team said that the interference factors between the path of the retina and the visual cortex will determine what we see either a smile or other expressions.&lt;/P&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>