<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="540110053a9c2f4136d0cc19f999ee67">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thewindowstorecolorado.com%2Fwindows-colorado-springs-why-should-you-take-care-of-windows%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.thewindowstorecolorado.com/windows-colorado-springs-why-should-you-take-care-of-windows/&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Free Advice for Windows Colorado Springs&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most of the homes irrespective of their geographical location comprise of windows and these elements form an innate part of any household. Maintaining and up keeping the windows of the house is a task which is daunting for most of the people. Keeping this in mind, there are many companies which provide services in maintaining the windows. Even in the region of Colorado Springs, there are numerous services for windows Colorado Springs and they specialize in assisting locals in keeping the windows of their houses crystal clear. Every household is well-defined in terms of the windows which are not only a source of beautifying the house but also allowing a considerable amount of air and light to circulate in the house.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Replacement windows colorado The windows within a house serve as the prime source of circulation of fresh air across the house, in the absence of which, the air within the house is expected to be thick and thereby unhygienic.		</conversation>		<conversation id="80d5a7a8c68925627afaf1f19aea2683">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D_3ORlcNvV98"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_3ORlcNvV98&lt;/a&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pioneer Wood Flooring &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.pioneerwoodflooring.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.pioneerwoodflooring.com&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;Discover the differences between prefinished wood flooring and site finished wood flooring.  Pioneer Flooring can help you decide what works best for your home in Colorado Springs.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>