<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="59168c3509cd024814fec710ea05dced">			Experts say Truk Lagoon is the remains of a massive volcano. Despite the fact that diving in Chuuk may sound harmful, many knowledgeable divers around the globe would travel many miles only to dive in Chuuk. They want to see what Chuuk has to offer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it comes to diving, Chuuk is a great place to be. Simply because Chuuk is abundant in marine life. Divers will see not simply different fishes but additionally various coral formations as well. Chuuk’s diving attraction is not the marine life divers would see. The main attraction of Truk Lagoon diving is really a part of World War 2’s history. Simply because Chuuk is actually a part of the US’ Operation Hailstorm during those times. This was a enormous naval operation where US navy had launched a huge aerial attack on a Japanese naval base on South Pacific.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Operation Hailstorm was a large one, and lots of ships and planes have referred to the South Pacific seas as their graves. That battle had sung six destroyers, 3 warships and even 3 cruisers. Aside from warships, there are also over 30 merchant ships lying on the bottom of the sea. As a matter of fact, tons of scrap metal are now lying on the bottom of the ocean due to the battle. Now, the seas around Chuuk is a testament of that battle. Today, these wreckages that have become well-known diving spots. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53YXluLmNvbS93YXluYmxvZy5odG1sP3djaT12aWV3ZW50cnkmYW1wO2VudHJ5X2tleT0zMTg5ODk_" target="_blank"&gt;;Dahab diving&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy51bHRpbWF0ZWRpdmluZy5jby51ay9kaXZlLWhvbGlkYXlzL21pY3JvbmVzaWEvY2h1dWstdHJ1ay1sYWdvb24tZGl2aW5nLmFzcHg_" target="_blank"&gt;;Dahab diving&lt;/a&gt;;, [url=]Dahab diving[/url]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nowadays, Truk Lagoon’s famous wrecks have become home to millions of fishes along with numerous coral formation. This wreckage has become a large yet unique ecosystem. There are many diving spots in Truk Lagoon that lets you see these famous wreckages. These diving spots are Shinkoku Maru, Nippo Maru and Hoki Maru. The most well-known dive site of all is the Fujikawa Maru shipwreck. The real reason for this is that of all the wreckages around Chuuk, it is by far the biggest. This 450 ft. long whip wreck is visited by many, not because it is big but because it is also situated in clear and shallow water. This way, divers can easily explore the entire wreckage. Every part of the ship, from top to bottom of the wreck is visible if not almost visible.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Chuuk is a good diving spot, not only because of the good aquatic sceneries one will find, but also because of the climate it has. It is because, the climate in Chuuk is almost uniform all year long. Usually, skilled, skilled and professional divers visit Chuuk all year long, even if during the windy months of June to November. During January - March, winds are more stable and calmer, making it ideal for novice divers as well as amateur one to easily dive and relish the sceneries.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Undeniably, Chuuk can be considered as the top diving destinations. It is because of the great aquatic sceneries it has that no other diving spots have. The diving operators of Chuuk are also skilled and knowledgeable when it comes to diving and they are scattered around Chuuk. There are also many resorts that provide good food in addition to accommodation. There are also good diving destinations aside from Chuuk. Divers may try the Red Sea diving experience or the Dahab diving for a numerous diving flavour.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>