<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="19d99719d18db556106dd2fb09545338">			Geir Lolleng was born in Oslo in the year 1957. He received his law degree from the University of Oslo in 1981. To further advance his expertise, Geir Lolleng pursued business courses at the prestigious Standford Business School in the United States.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Being a practicing lawyer in Norway since 1986, &lt;A HREF=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdelicious.com%2Fgeirlolleng"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://delicious.com/geirlolleng&lt;/a&gt;;]Geir Lolleng&lt;/A&gt;;  , held numerous legal positions. He served as an Associate Judge from 1984-1985 in Sandes City Court, Norway where he handled several criminal and civil cases. Geir Lolleng earned the esteem of the Chief Justice. He also extended his career in the field of corporate law, as First Manager then later as Associate Director in the Norwegian Association for Oil Companies based in Stavanger, Norway from 1981-1986. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;A HREF=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3D7TheuSl_WaI"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7TheuSl_WaI&lt;/a&gt;;]Geir Lolleng&lt;/A&gt;; also became part of Norway's formidable law firms, first as an associate lawyer in Ottesen and Mellbye Scholdager Seijersted Tenden from 1986-1989. He moved as a key partner in Kvale &amp; Co and Stabell end Steenstrup Stordrange from 1990-2003. Having rendered dedicated service as one of the three top employment lawyers in Norway, Geir Lolleng has a exhaustive comprehension of legal matters concerning international employment concerns. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;His work experience in the various facets of law allowed him to provide consultancy duties in Nordic Mgmt Consultants as CEO (management for hire) of the Delling Group PLC from 2006-2008. &lt;A HREF=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgeirlolleng.no%2F%3Fpage_id%3D26"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://geirlolleng.no/?page_id=26&lt;/a&gt;;]Geir Lolleng&lt;/A&gt;;  had established strong and lasting relationships with the following leading companies: British Petroleum, Marubeni, Time Warner, European Union (the Commission), ConocoPhillips, Telenor, Berge S. Bergesen, Radio 1, Visa Int., Adecco, Mitsui Corp., Bank of America and a number of other primarily Norwegian, Swedish and American companies. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gier Lolleng's reputation and expertise is on building up and restructuring companies that includes financing. He has been known to resolve complex negotiations and communication covering multi-levels. &lt;A HREF=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cappelendammakademisk.no%2Fakademisk%2Fauthor.action%3Fid%3D10050"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cappelendammakademisk.no/akademisk/author.action?id=10050&lt;/a&gt;;]Geir Lolleng&lt;/A&gt;;  is a seasoned lawyer with years of corporate and high-level management experience.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>