<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3ae7e21eb12c63c9f65baca8ab5cfeb4">			&lt;p&gt;;It is critical that one understands the audit Written Audit Program-(required) developed to guide the auditor through the [url=]audit part of the cpa study material[/url].&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Here are the most important points to remember:&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;The practitioner must document the understanding of the work papers. A practitioner may not accept an engagement if the understanding with the client has not been established.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Re-audit-engagement to audit and report on financial statements that have previously been audited and reported on by another auditor.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;The engagement letter (not required, but are recommended) helps ensure that the auditor and the client clearly understand the services the auditor is engaged to perform. Makes reference to 1) periods covered, 2) assurance the audit will be performed in accordance with GAAS, 3) any assistance to be rendered by the client personnel, 4) managements responsibility for preparing the financials, 5) fee basis, and 6) other matters&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;The successor auditor uses the predecessor's work papers as a start for obtaining confidence in the beginning balances. The successor CANNOT make any reference to the predecessor's work as a basis for the successor's own opinion.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;The audit firm may employ personnel who perform technical aspects of the engagement but who do not have final responsibility for the audit.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;Auditor-professional is responsible for the engagement. If this professional is in charge of field work, and supervising assistants, he should inform assistants of their responsibilities, and review assistant's work.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;If the auditor assesses inherent and/or control risk at less than the maximum, there should be an appropriate basis for the assessment. The basis must be documented by the CPA.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;The detection risk that an auditor can accept is based on the maximum acceptable level of audit risk and the assessed levels of inherent and control risks. The auditor cannot rely completely on assessments of inherent and control risks to the exclusion of performing substantive tests.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;The auditor should aggregate uncorrected misstatements in a way that enables the auditor to consider whether they materially misstate the financial statements taken as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;;  &lt;p&gt;;You must memorize the auditor's engagement procedure as there are several [url=]cpa exam questions centered on this topic.[/url]&lt;/p&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>