<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="3f97ffdd55b5f44ee6275b5ef41720e4">			Arm of Revenge: Calling all the fighters on the earth... Would you like Street Fighter, KOF, Devil May Cry, or Shank? You got essentially the most fun fighting/action game on the Flash platform -Arm of Revenge! Touching story, smooth moves, more than 30 skills to combo, 3 kinds of arm to improve, survival mode...plus more! Challenge your friend and hit the highest combos! Remember, this really is essentially the most fun fighting game you won't ever seen around the Flash platform! Have fun with this! Try Pressing JKJKJKJK...Try switching to Gun Arm or Blaze Arm...Unlimited combo combinations are waiting that you can discover...)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL25pbmphaGF0dG9yaWdhbWVzLm9yZy9ydW5uaW5nLWJsaW5kLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Running Blind&lt;/a&gt;;: Intro regarding the game: Ever tried running using your eyes closed? Ever tried jumping on platforms along with your eyes closed? Intent behind the action: Here your eyes are blindfolded and you're just walking both the sides from left to right and to certainly left. Your goals is always to keep jumping on the ladder like base levels and attain the top spot How you can play: It's not necessary to move in a direction in this game. The Action itself keeps moving automatically. All you have to do is perfectly time the boy's jump to reach the superior spot. Game keys: Don't use anything but the room bar key of the keyboard to jump. Few other keys or mouse is of any use within this game&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5uaW5qYWhhdHRvcmlnYW1lcy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;;Ninja hattori games&lt;/a&gt;; is a classic animated comedy the place where a young lad called Ken befriends an equally little Ninja called Hattori. Hattori could possibly be small in space but his powers are a minimum of any supreme Ninja. He can move at high speed, sleep suspended around the ceiling and knows the martial arts like the back of his very fast hand. Hattori is hardworking, conscientious and quite strict with regards to disciplining Ken, but he's got a heart of gold and cannot help but pull Ken beyond tight spot. A heart-warming, high energy and super funny show in the makers of Doraemon.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Yan Loong Legend : Yan Loong should use his sword and dragon fire spell to get over all enimies who blocking his way and find out exactly why wars happened in the world. Your mission on this third part of Yan Loong series is by using your sword and dragon fire spell to get over all enimies who blocking on your path to see the reason why wars happening in the world. Find the true answer. Use WASD KEYS to move around. Press &quot;K&quot; KEY to jump. Press &quot;J&quot; Critical for attack. Use &quot;I&quot; Critical for pause the actionAndshow skill panel. Push &quot;W&quot; KEY and press 'Attack' to carry out spells. Move character over the item and press 'down' to pick up it. For more instructions please read in game help. Good luck!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29kcmVhZHMuY29tL2V2ZW50L3Nob3cvNDIyODgzLXlhbi1sb29uZy1sZWdlbmQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;Hungry Sumo&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pYW1zcG9ydC5vcmcvcGcvYmxvZy9HaWxsaWFuRG9sczI1L3JlYWQvNjIwOTcyMS9ib3dqYS10aGUtbmluamEtMg__" target="_blank"&gt;;Ninja hattori games&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2NyaXN0b2JhbHByeW9yNTIud2lraXNwYWNlcy5jb20vWWFuK0xvb25nK0xlZ2VuZA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Yan Loong Legend&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>