<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="9">		<conversation id="e1731b53cf6da4c4af9a5f6f693cc48">			is really starting to suck...i meet someone, and we go on a great date...from what i hear atleast....then it takes them forever to call...or be able to hang out...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;guys please tell me....is it some secret code that y'all have not to call or show lots of attention to the girl you guys are into??? wtf. I don't get it.&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;sometimes i just don't get y'all... at all! so confusing. ok...well...replying time!		</conversation>		<conversation id="c8bd1bc4b4363318de9ed36eb8eecd58">			I only have one friend on here...it's ok...I don't really know how to work this site...I guess i'll have to learn.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;does anyone really read these things?? &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="8c4b4495a430a1402f0f5f4e541e27dc">			do anyone here play sims?? 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I am currently addicted....again.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;i have an alien family that i created.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;i am lame.		</conversation>		<conversation id="69f5703b737e38b3d9f65a39c8bc61bf">			so...moving into a new place with someone is more complicated than i thought...the getting ready part is very stressful...VERY STRESSFUL...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;and my patience is running out..maybe i'm just an impatient girl...i just think things could be moving a little faster than they are...most of the things we've been working on should've already been done...but they aren't...that's frustrating.. can anyone relate?? &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="97b21ac8824e8dd918ab5812e211ddfe">			So we Broke up and i'm the crazy one...wtf. I'm sorry if i don't like dating a drunk. We dated for 9 months and i was in love....it's so hard to get over it. He was so hateful. calling me names, making me cry....i don't deserve that right???
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;maybe there are better fish in the sea, just nowhere near here...lol too bad. &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;life will go on....it will just take time to break away from all my feelings for him....i guess i need a random fling. hahaha that would get rid of my feelings. lol. if only i was a whore..lol! &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/tongue.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;maybe things will look upward...hopefully.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d99276b58e5d26d151677626dc33535">			guess i am content enough to head off to bed...goodnight and thanks to all of those uplifters!!! you should add me...i don't know how to add anyone...lol...i haven't figured this site out yet!! goodnight!!! peace, love, and blueberry cereal!		</conversation>		<conversation id="b4bebeac8471ea65b524ff264c17ed41">			FUCK THIS BULL SHIT! i hate living here. Nothing is shared...it's all theirs. FUCK ME.....even though i'm her daughter. GAHHHH! I'm so pissed.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;anyone want to give away a used old computer that can get online? hahahahah!		</conversation>		<conversation id="ce6d35925314445317188a143f632905">			I officially hate all American men. all of them. &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;they suck balls.		</conversation>		<conversation id="cc34d861ca1acb7b1b45594d4aef3042">			From all the comments i have received on my previous blog....I have decided to explain why i say what i say.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1.) MOST of all the guys i have met here...in America...are losers. 
&lt;br /&gt;;2.) I have NOT met all of them...that would be impossible.
&lt;br /&gt;;3.) MOST of the good guys have either a g/f or a b/f.
&lt;br /&gt;;4.) Sorry if i offended anyone. I have been through a lot with guys, and it's hard to like them.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most of you are right, not ALL guys are bad.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;MOST OF THEM ARE THOUGH!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;so there. &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/angry.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>