<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="28eb182cc2fe81a7f55f4cacbaba406b">			&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I met Rodney at the pool (AQUA - just a few meters away from your house). the first time i saw him.. i thought he was a GAY (oopss! sorry!) yeah! really, i really thought he was a gay.. that was my first impression! the reason why i thought he was a gay because of his god damn beautiful sexy voice! it's really like a girl! *giggle!* it really sounds like a GIRLL!! but i find him very handsome the first time i met him.. but so sad to know that because of his voice i was extremely DISCOURAGED!!! but oh well... just a few minutes later... i talked to the guy he was talking with and just give them a few minute chat along with others.. while we were chatting.. there i instantly realized that he wasn't GAY at all.. and there i knew he attend the same school as i.. and so... that was during enrollment time - m still new... i told him to go with me during enrollment and teach me how.. and so... that was = next day after... we met at school and he go with me.. and lend me 100 pesos for the payment of my fines.. as we were enrolling (but i already paid him back so no worry!) and then later and days after.. right exactly when the school start.. he asked me about something.. which i didn't expect him to ask me.. &quot;Could you be my girlfriend?&quot; of course, out of my love for him.. i immediately did not refuse his offer... and so... here we are right now.. very loving for each other.. you can see us walking down by the street very romantic.. but of course you cannot reject the divergence between the relationship because it is said that whatever disagreement you have in your relationship it is what makes your relationship NORMAL.. and easy.. anyway.. hope you also realized that.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;thanks for reading my blog.. this is my first blog entry.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Go, Coleen A.		</conversation>		<conversation id="aae477e294cca9785fbf64b2908bf15b">			&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wacko.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; it was actually my first time having an academic summer class at our school.. and i was so new and unaware og what's gonna happen to me during summer classes.. i rarely thought that there will be only a few of the students who will be at school during classes (so for me i thought everythig will be all right then if i attend summer classes) but my first time was absolutely BAD!! as i go inside my room for my subject.. i saw a lot of people and students staring at me as i started to enter the class (because i am late! so no wonder right?!) it was an awful experience.. i was pretty shy then.. but anyway.. i thought summer class will be  a great fun for me.. but no.. it's really WORST... imagine... summer classes will not help me accredit all the junior subjects required for my seniors business subjects which are as well my majors subjects - too bad isnt it?! and the worst of all is that.. i don't have extra time to be with my boyfriend... (see?! it's worst... really worst..) but there's nothing i can do... but to sacrifice it all... anyway... i think i only have 1 year and a half left to graduate... il be joining the OCTOBERIANS maybe... but its okay.. i haven't tried any retakes but so far.. m doing well with my studies.. it is just that... m not sure if i can graduate soon.. if i can graduate at the date which m expecting to graduate... but it's okay.. it's all right.. finally, il be graduating ... just 1 and a half year from the present... but please my dear friends.. pray for me.. that God may do some sensation which will change everything.. heheheh &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/mellow.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;this is just a piece of share my dear friends.. im just sharing to you my experience right from the very start of my summer class... duh! it's WORST.. that's all i can say!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/sad.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/love.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="65ee781847704ce684088c3080708659">			&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/flowers.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hey guys... know what?! writing a blog is like writing a diary or a journal.. it is a piece of chronicle that tells about your memoirs and experiences.. It comprises detailed matters of your daily incidents.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Writing a blog message is really a great HELP to everyone.. so i encourage you to write a blog message atleast once in every day of your life.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It extracts distressed and sadness deep within you.. because as you write out from it... the things you carry deep within you will no longer be  burden as it is used to be before... it is only in writing and in letting others show what you have wherein you can really take out all the painful things inside you.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;as i was saying... if you are to write a blog message... just always think that you are writing on your own diary.. share to everyone the worst and the best experience you ever had.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;let's not be selfish to ourselves.. and let's not keep on pretending how good we are nor how bad we are.. but rather.. let's show to others what we have... the greatness and the poorness we have inside... because everyone is created uniquely by our great majesty - our very own , God.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;so i encourage you all to write a blog message.. with your experiences on your blog message.. it may be worst or best.. but i assure you that it will be a great honor to others to read the most beautiful masterpiece of a unique man whom one could ever imagine doing such a thing that he is not ashamed of.. by writing his experiences -  worst or good.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Enjoy writing a blog message... Think that it's all about Writing your own DIARY!!! 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your message then will positively be PERFECT to read.. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/flowers.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/flowers.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/inlove.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;; &lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/flowers.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>