<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="13053a91c6e525dde46c0ffe8102e025">			Sometimes, keeping your skin healthy is hard to do, but an effective skin care regimen does not have to be too difficult. You must become knowledgeable about caring for skin care before you try to repair your own skin. By reading the following article, you will begin the process of learning how to properly take of your skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If your skin is oily, using products made for oily skin can help your skin stay oil free and fresh looking. Use an astringent or gentle toner to remove excess oil, and prevent it from creeping back on your skin's surface during the day. Use a moisturizer specifically formulated for your skin type if you have oily skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whether the sun is shining or overcast, you need to protect your skin every day. Sunscreen should be applied a half an hour before you go out, and you should do so with a sunscreen offering protection against a broad UVB ray spectrum. To get the most protection, use the sunscreen with the highest SPF possible. The sunscreen will prevent sunburns and premature aging.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always read the sunscreen label to know the limits of the protection, and reapply frequently according to the directions on the label. Reapplying sunscreen can be quite an easy process when using a powder. This powder comes in a small container, convenient to carry.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Improve the health and appearance of your skin by cleansing your face of all makeup prior to your bedtime. This prevents bacteria growth and also reduces oil. As you sleep, your skin can renew and rejuvenate itself.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use a moisturizer with humectants on your face each night before going to bed. When you sleep, your body temperature raises, and it can create sweat and moisture. Standing sweat can simultaneously clog your pores and dry out your skin, so an overnight moisturizer is a must.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will want to exfoliate the skin a couple days before you shave using gentle, hypo-allergenic products. The abrasive action of the scrub will help to remove dry, dead skin cells, allowing you to get a closer shave. Also, the dead cells can make the shaven hairs stick to the skin. This can be irritating to the skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If your skin is showing signs of aging, ask your dermatologist for a prescription anti-aging cream. There are anti-aging creams approved by the FDA that have been proven to reduce wrinkles and fine lines on the skin. Watch out, though; many of these creams can be harmful to a fetus or nursing baby, and can interact with other medicines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You should reapply sunscreen at least once an hour for maximum results. You may find sunscreen easier to put on as a powder. For this you use a dry brush, avoiding the heavy oiliness of creams. Such types of sun protection typically come in handy containers ideally suited for your purse or pocket.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You need to control your stress levels to maintain healthy skin. When you are overly stressed, your skin can become more sensitive and have adverse reactions. Try relaxation methods or find an activity that helps you forget about your problems.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don't let poor skin care take over your skin, use the information you have obtained from this article and do whatever is necessary to make sure that you have properly cared for you skin at the end of every day. Happy skin leads to a happy mind and a happy body.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/sergiolancaster/blog/blogid=9899564" target="_blank"&gt;;Freshen Up Your Skin Care Regimen With These Tips&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="fbb29935b9d5ae36e3a3b2c153db9ae9">			There are a lot of old wives' tales, voodoo ideas and myths about taking good care of your skin. Ignoring myths and using a down to earth approach towards skin care can yield optimal results. This article will give you tips on caring for your skin, the right way.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Watercress is a good food to eat if you want to reduce pore sizes, facial puffiness and overall inflammation. Watercress is a good thing to eat with a meal or have as a snack because it makes your skin glow in the sun and is good for your health. Not only does it have many benefits for your skin, it can also help to remove free radicals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Making the right choice when it comes to facial cleansers is important. It is best to buy soaps that are free of chemicals and perfumes. Choose a soap that contains a mild moisturizer and toner instead.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using gentler skin care products is helpful for those with extra sensitive skin. Try to find products have no dyes and are hypoallergenic. Any type of perfumes or chemicals can cause irritation to your skin, and you may breakout or develop a rash.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You need to be so careful when shaving. Razor blades are sharp and can easily irritate or cut your skin if used improperly. You will want to use some kind of lubrication on your skin like shaving cream, lotion, or gel. In order to achieve the best possible shave, use clean razors. Don't shave against the grain.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always avoid putting wet clothing on your hands and feet, like wet gloves. Your skin may be irritated and you may even suffer eczema if you put on wet socks or gloves.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use a humidifier during the winter months to prevent your skin from becoming dry. A furnace in your home can actually lead to dry skin, because it eats up the moisture. Use a humidifier in the room you're mostly in to add moisture to your air.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read the directions on your sunscreen bottle and reapply as often as is suggested. Some powders contain sunscreen. Powder-based sunscreen comes in compact containers so you can easily keep it in a purse or a pocket.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Determine your skin type to ensure that the products you use are good for your skin. For example, if you have dry skin, there is no point in buying skin care products that are designed to treat oily skin. You can speak with a dermatologist or other medical professional if you do not know what skin type you have and what products you should be using.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A couple of days before shaving, exfoliate your skin. Use natural products that are mild and hypo-allergenic. This helps slough away dead skin cells, and allows the razor to flow smoother on your skin. Unexfoliated skin is rough and can cause friction during a shave.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Every time you step outside, you should make sure that you are protected from the suns rays. Use sunscreen that has a a good UVB ray protection rating and apply this about 30 minutes before exposure to the sun. Choose the greatest SPF available for your area. The sunscreen will prevent sunburns and premature aging.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Though there are a bewildering variety of products and treatments available to take care of your skin, remember that you need not spend lots of money or plan extensively to make your skin healthier. Improving your skin only takes a few simple steps.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]Simple Things You Can Do Everyday To Have Healthy Skin[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>