<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f61276e0e7987e30e5f04ad71f6b9b1b">			&lt;span style="text-decoration:underline"&gt;;i love this while read on motivateurself.com &lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/smile.gif" alt=":)" /&gt;;Principles Of Life&lt;/strong&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?Winning isn’t everything but wanting to win is.
&lt;br /&gt;;?You would achieve more, if you don’t mind who gets the credit.
&lt;br /&gt;;?When everything else is lost, the future still remains.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Don’t fight too much or the enemy will know your art of war.
&lt;br /&gt;;?The only job you start at the top is when you dig a grave.?If you don’t stand for something, you’ll fall for everything.
&lt;br /&gt;;?If you do little things well, you’ll do big ones better.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Only thing that comes to you without effort is old age.
&lt;br /&gt;;?You won’t get a second chance to make a first impression.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Only those who do nothing do not make mistakes.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Never take a problem to your boss unless you have a solution.
&lt;br /&gt;;?If you are not failing, you’re not taking enough risks.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Don’t try to get rid of your bad temper by losing it.
&lt;br /&gt;;?If at first you don’t succeed, skydiving is not for you.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Those who don’t make mistakes usually don’t make anything.
&lt;br /&gt;;?There are two kinds of failures: Those who think and never do, and those who do and never think.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Pick battles big enough to matter, small enough to win.
&lt;br /&gt;;?All progress has resulted from unpopular decisions.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Change your thoughts and you change your world.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Understanding proves intelligence, not the speed of the learning.
&lt;br /&gt;;?There are two kinds of fools in this world.: Those who give advice and those who don’t take it.
&lt;br /&gt;;?The best way to kill an idea is to take it to a meeting.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Management is doing things right. Leadership is doing the right things.
&lt;br /&gt;;?Friendship founded on business is always better than business founded on friendship.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;=====================
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;taken from &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tb3RpdmF0ZXVyc2VsZi5jb20vbW90aXZhdGlvbmFsX2FydGljbGVzLzI0LXRob3VnaHRzLXRvLXJlbWVtYmVyLWFzLXlvdS1nby10aHJvdWdoLWxpZmUv" target="_blank"&gt;;motivateurself.com&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>