<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="58efafbbc435ecdff82d03db14142ecc">			Dental implant is a cosmetic treatment that involves fixation of artificial teeth. Placing a dental implant is deemed as the most expensive and the most complex surgical procedure in dentistry. The procedure takes months and even years to bring the desired result. With the advancement in cosmetic dentistry procedures, demands for dental implants are rising. Nevertheless, the entire procedure is painstaking and time consuming.&lt;br /&gt;;Primarily, it is the cost factor, which makes the procedure financially uncertain. As you know, cosmetic dental treatments are not normally covered under dental insurance plans. In addition, dental implant being a highly expensive cosmetic surgery, rarely any insurance companies offers to cover such a treatment plan. However, there are companies that offer dental implant coverage, but they charge a very high rate premium for the procedure.&lt;br /&gt;;This is because dental implants are generally considered as a luxurious solution and normally people do not opt for such treatment methodologies if they can help it. The cost of dental implants is not same everywhere. Depending upon the complexity of the problem and the quality of the implant material, the prices vary. In this context, single teeth implant can cost you anywhere between $1000 to $4500.&lt;br /&gt;;There is also a risk of a further rise in cost if the patient shows rejection of the implant. Correction procedures and surgeries might be required if the patient is not comfortable with the implant. There is also a good chance that the entire procedure might fail. Under such cases, the patient suffers from heavy losses. In addition, he cannot claim for compensation because the risk of failure is a part of such procedures. Moreover, while signing the agreement for these surgeries the patient is made to accept all the responsibilities for a possible failure.&lt;br /&gt;;Apart from the cost involved, there are several hazards that make the procedure of dental implant generally risky. Dental implants are placed by creating a hole in the gum and the bone supporting the teeth. The success of the entire procedure depends on how well the wound heals and how well the tissues grow back surrounding the implant. This highly invasive procedure might take months to heal and the patient might experience a lot of discomfort and pain throughout the entire duration.&lt;br /&gt;;Even though dental implant clinics advertise that they impart painless implant treatments, it is highly unlikely that a patient undergoing such an invasive surgery might never experience any form of discomfort. Besides pain, there is a high risk of infection that can be caused from several sources. In several cases, the patient catches the infection from the implant itself.&lt;br /&gt;;Conversely, presence of microorganisms inside the gums or bones adjoining the implant can initiate an infection. An infected implant can cause severe pain, bleeding and other symptoms. Lack of proper oral hygiene or faulty eating habits can also pose the risk of instant infection. Under such cases, the dentist might reverse the entire procedure or extent the treatment by removing the implant for a certain period.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56YWhuaW1wbGFudGF0ZW9ubGluZS5kZS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Zahnimplantate&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="1a3bebf25c4fd53c247b288664fd7b1a">			Dental implant is a cosmetic treatment that involves fixation of artificial teeth. Placing a dental implant is deemed as the most expensive and the most complex surgical procedure in dentistry. The procedure takes months and even years to bring the desired result. With the advancement in cosmetic dentistry procedures, demands for dental implants are rising. Nevertheless, the entire procedure is painstaking and time consuming.&lt;br /&gt;;Primarily, it is the cost factor, which makes the procedure financially uncertain. As you know, cosmetic dental treatments are not normally covered under dental insurance plans. In addition, dental implant being a highly expensive cosmetic surgery, rarely any insurance companies offers to cover such a treatment plan. However, there are companies that offer dental implant coverage, but they charge a very high rate premium for the procedure.&lt;br /&gt;;This is because dental implants are generally considered as a luxurious solution and normally people do not opt for such treatment methodologies if they can help it. The cost of dental implants is not same everywhere. Depending upon the complexity of the problem and the quality of the implant material, the prices vary. In this context, single teeth implant can cost you anywhere between $1000 to $4500.&lt;br /&gt;;There is also a risk of a further rise in cost if the patient shows rejection of the implant. Correction procedures and surgeries might be required if the patient is not comfortable with the implant. There is also a good chance that the entire procedure might fail. Under such cases, the patient suffers from heavy losses. In addition, he cannot claim for compensation because the risk of failure is a part of such procedures. Moreover, while signing the agreement for these surgeries the patient is made to accept all the responsibilities for a possible failure.&lt;br /&gt;;Apart from the cost involved, there are several hazards that make the procedure of dental implant generally risky. Dental implants are placed by creating a hole in the gum and the bone supporting the teeth. The success of the entire procedure depends on how well the wound heals and how well the tissues grow back surrounding the implant. This highly invasive procedure might take months to heal and the patient might experience a lot of discomfort and pain throughout the entire duration.&lt;br /&gt;;Even though dental implant clinics advertise that they impart painless implant treatments, it is highly unlikely that a patient undergoing such an invasive surgery might never experience any form of discomfort. Besides pain, there is a high risk of infection that can be caused from several sources. In several cases, the patient catches the infection from the implant itself.&lt;br /&gt;;Conversely, presence of microorganisms inside the gums or bones adjoining the implant can initiate an infection. An infected implant can cause severe pain, bleeding and other symptoms. Lack of proper oral hygiene or faulty eating habits can also pose the risk of instant infection. Under such cases, the dentist might reverse the entire procedure or extent the treatment by removing the implant for a certain period.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3phaG5pbXBsYW50YXRlcmlzaWtlbjEyLndvcmRwcmVzcy5jb20vMjAxMi8wMy8yMy9kZW50YWwtaW1wbGFudHMtYW5kLWl0cy1zaWRlLWVmZmVjdHMv" target="_blank"&gt;;The Risks of Dental Implants&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9sYW1hcm1hY2s2MTYvcG9zdHMvOTIwNjk1L0RlbnRhbCtJbXBsYW50cythbmQraXRzK1NpZGUrRWZmZWN0cw__" target="_blank"&gt;;The Risks of Dental Implants&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3phaG5pbXBsYW50YXRlLXJpc2lrZW4wOC5vbnN1Z2FyLmNvbS9SaXNrcy1EZW50YWwtSW1wbGFudHMtMjIzMzY4Njc_" target="_blank"&gt;; Dental Implants and its Side Effects&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>