<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="efccfb936e20f593193badc1ff6e43a3">			Isn't it funny how when your a teen you want to be 18 to get into places. Then when you finally hit 18, you find yourself not getting into places because everywhere is 21s. Then, when you finally hit 21, you realise that you would rather stay in the places that you always end up in because they are cheap and not so expensive lol and end up staying where you always go every weekend, and not even try out anywhere new lol. You are so comfortable going to your local or the 'same old place' you might as well be 18, because the places you go are filled with them anyway lol haha
&lt;br /&gt;;When your not allowed in a nightclub or place you are EAGER to get in there. When you finally are allowed, you'd rather stay in!! lol 
&lt;br /&gt;;Life, isn't it funny		</conversation>		<conversation id="3d25e2cdc5d140ed8b901ee96a97540e">			I wrote a blog earlier about is it possible to like this music and not do drugs. I got a lot of blog messages saying how there is plenty people out there who go raving and listen to this music and don't touch drugs. 
&lt;br /&gt;;I can understand this, how many people choose to not touch them which is a fabulous decision in my opinion! But i was more thinking along the lines of someone who HAS taken them before, know what its like, and to actually go back to a rave or be in an atmosphere with lots of pill heads and resist taking them!
&lt;br /&gt;;I think it is easier for someone who has never experienced class A drugs to say no, but is it possible to go into that atmosphere again and say no, when you've already taken them?
&lt;br /&gt;;Im sure its possible..but is it really believable? When you've already been high plenty of times in your life and know how good it can be..and you want to stop..can you really go back to those places and resist or should you avoid being around those people altogether?		</conversation>		<conversation id="c6dc49cbcb073a78a2de498bb9eaf360">			So..alot of women are quite obsessed with their weight. They spend hours of the waking day worrying about what they eat and how much exercise they do.
&lt;br /&gt;;I think it's easier for men if they are a little overweight because men look good if they have a little meat on them. Of course im not talking obese here and just saying if you saw a skinny guy next to a skinny girl, the skinny guy would not look so good, yet a skinny girl looks hot!!
&lt;br /&gt;;I just wanted some opinions from men or women as well to ask is it really that guys want a girl who is so toned and thin that she looks hot, or can she have a little weight on her and still be just as tempting?
&lt;br /&gt;;And then again im not talking stick anorexic thin, im talking Charlie thin, say from big bro...her bodies hot..(or is that too thin? i dont think so).or would you rather a girl say size 12?
&lt;br /&gt;;Cas for me i don't like muscly guys, a lot of them love themselves and therefore i feel uncomfortable infront of them...i like a guy who has the weight of A MAN, lol and nice and toned. A bit of a beer belly doesn't bother me, i think thats sweet.
&lt;br /&gt;;But what do men REALLY think? Please, do tell!		</conversation>		<conversation id="7be3e51ed0afa8077d5242d60b41df3e">			Before you read this i am a very happy person usually, i was just feeling a bit low last night..
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Im so upset but i dont know why
&lt;br /&gt;;Trying to figure it out, im going to try
&lt;br /&gt;;Every happy moment, i do embrace
&lt;br /&gt;;Yet i find myself on my bed, tears falling down my face
&lt;br /&gt;;Just feels like im going to fall
&lt;br /&gt;;Just trying to begin figuring out it all
&lt;br /&gt;;I pray for answers needing to find out about myself
&lt;br /&gt;;I look for clues, i cry out with my mouth
&lt;br /&gt;;Low self esteem can rip you apart
&lt;br /&gt;;But this is only the start
&lt;br /&gt;;There is so many thoughts i think that shouldn't even be there!
&lt;br /&gt;;These sort of things i shouldn't even care
&lt;br /&gt;;Lie's are being fed to me.They will not go away!
&lt;br /&gt;;All of these thoughts will determine the mood of my day
&lt;br /&gt;;Shameless nights of drunken mistakes
&lt;br /&gt;;Looking back my heart only breaks
&lt;br /&gt;;Paronoid thoughts soon appear real
&lt;br /&gt;;Dreading the thought of my very next meal
&lt;br /&gt;;The mirror is my enemie, the mirror is my friend
&lt;br /&gt;;When is my body, mind and soul going to mend?
&lt;br /&gt;;Secrets i have i cannot tell a soul
&lt;br /&gt;;I am my own actress in my story, im the leading role
&lt;br /&gt;;To tell ones i love will only makes things worse
&lt;br /&gt;;With this is i am control of my whole universe...
&lt;br /&gt;;What i do to get through is between me, not you
&lt;br /&gt;;I hope someday i can love me too		</conversation>		<conversation id="7d3c567af0269ebe81391dfd3127f9c2">			If you want more people to look at your blogs I have gone through mine and realised what people like to hear about, those with the most amount of comments. I will share some of them with you...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here are all the 'blog titles' that interested people the most...
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Men's opinion needed
&lt;br /&gt;;Need a man's point of view
&lt;br /&gt;;Men and the hard to get game...
&lt;br /&gt;;Bad boys
&lt;br /&gt;;Men posing as lesbians
&lt;br /&gt;;What turns blokes on?
&lt;br /&gt;;Decent sexi men...
&lt;br /&gt;;What a lot of men say
&lt;br /&gt;;Are men really perverts or are we just asking for it?
&lt;br /&gt;;Has it got to do with age?
&lt;br /&gt;;A poem i wrote last night
&lt;br /&gt;;A poem
&lt;br /&gt;;Trance,dance,club,techo,d+b,hardcore
&lt;br /&gt;;New version of 'i will survive' lyrics#
&lt;br /&gt;;Sex
&lt;br /&gt;;Does internet take away your life?
&lt;br /&gt;;Haters
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In my conclusion i have found out that men like to hear a lot about themselves which obviously interests them. (lol) Well who doesn't like to hear about what poeple think about their species, just like women like to wonder what men think about them. Its interesting!
&lt;br /&gt;;Of course you hear everyone in the 'shouts' on pan.netsaying how bored they are which makes them all horny and want some loving, so of course, sex will appeal to everyone, and alot of men of course!
&lt;br /&gt;;What else have we got, yes i realised a bit of talent in the poetry department everyone likes to hear a bit of poetry and also some song lyrics. Got a good song to write or a poem? Post it!
&lt;br /&gt;;And of course humour goes a long way, so if your funny that is a bonus!! hehe
&lt;br /&gt;;Things about the internet....well everyone reading is on the internet and most people get addicted to the internet so write something about that, people will want to read...
&lt;br /&gt;;If you've got something to say about growing up and age..well we all are not getting any younger so people are interested in that too.
&lt;br /&gt;;Music! Is another one...but the highest amount of comments i got is on the subject ECSTACY lol...well i can understand why. So if you've got anything to say about drugs..lots of druggies or x-druggies will be interested in that. Drugs are mad, drugs are unexplainable, you forget half the time your high neways so its always good to hear about what people have to to say about the mystery of the 'other level' lol. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If anyone has got anymore ideas for me..let me know!! Chow..x		</conversation>	</conversations></author>