<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2e07b485d3f28b653262e4d10d573937">			See previous articles on sexting on this website, including &quot;Teen Texting, Sexting, and Suicide. &quot; ParentDish. com, in the article titled, &quot;Sexting plus your Kids, &quot; updated the sexting picture with new information on the consequences of sexting according to surveys from CosmoGirl, which often teens read, and the National Campaign to prevent Teen Pregnancy, which these people don't. According to that will update, which includes sexting estimates somewhat below what the above figures, &quot;22% involving teens admit that technological know-how makes them personally much more forward and aggressive, 38% say exchanging sexy content makes dating or hooking up with others more likely, and 29% of teens believe those exchanging sexy content are 'expected' to date or hook up. &quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the case, sexting has blossomed from your foolish but relatively innocuous activity-innocuous apart from Jessica Logan-into a channel facilitating and encouraging teenage sexual intercourse. Many teens did not need any such facilitation or encouragement but the parents who thought their own kids were merely getting stupid by sexting and who have been just joining the crowd have another thing coming. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ParentDish's advice for moms and dads isn't awfully original but holds worth repeating: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Don't watch for an incident to occur to your child or your child's friend before you decide to talk about the outcomes of sexting. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Remind your kids that once an image is sent, it can't ever be retrieved-and they will mislay control of it. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Talk about pressures to send disclosing photos. Let teens know that you understand how they can be pushed or dared inside sending something. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;;Teach your children that the buck stops with each other. If someone sends them a photo, they should delete the idea immediately. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;/ul&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Depending on the child and her or his relationship with the parent(ohydrates), those words of wisdom may very well be met with casual not caring or by active aggression, or they will serve being a wake-up call to kids they could pay for the rest of their lives for being overly friendly. On the other hand, hearing that an attractive photo or two might get them a hook-up, some teens will race to their bedrooms with cell phone in hand, leaving the parent(s) to wonder what they've already wrought. Life and rearing teens undoubtedly are a crapshoot. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Most people are unaware that pornography can actually be addicting. &lt;/strong&gt;; That's not a joke or a ethical judgment. People get dependent on porn and it disrupts their lives and those around them. The Internet has contributed greatly to your porn addiction phenomena because access to pornography has become easy beginning with a very young age group. Further, people who would normally don?t you have porn, suddenly have absolutely free, easy, 24/7 availability at their fingertips And it's also even discreet and straightforward to hide. So how does that effect teenagers and how could you prevent it? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;How does pornography reach teens internet? &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many parents assume that will their children are naive but will not go looking for adult content online so they is not required to worry. However, a child doesn't need to be actively searching online to find sexual information. It comes to him/her via email (spam), via cybersquatting (sites whose names indicate some thing innocent but whose content is not really), via friends sending links, etc. Even each time a child is exposed to help adult material and realizes it's inappropriate, he may have trouble getting &quot;out&quot; of the site due to tricks as used by some websites. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;It's available but is it truly so terrible if my own teenage son sees a few naked women? &lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We each have our own world views and facial lines we?? draw when it comes to sexual content. What is important to realize is that the type of content available on the online market place today is not reduced. Anyone can post content on the web and there is virtually no authority that monitors, not to say controls, the content which gets posted. There is, unfortunately, an abundance associated with content - pictures, videos and?? text?? that goes far beyond tasteless to downright disturbing. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]Teen Porn[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>