<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a147560da21310227b9b7bac50bd4a5">			Right now, more and more people go for contacts. This creates a question on how much these people actually are informed about the contact lens development background, classification, etc. The most recent studies have shown an increasing understanding of lenses among people, because of the fact that consumers are actually more educated of this area compared to 4 years ago, nonetheless, still not enough. The obligation due to the right selection of lenses, their particular usage as well as other specifics that establish safe and comfortable usage of contacts is placed partly on the practitioner (ophthalmologist, optometrist or optician) and also partly on the consumers themselves.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;More info on this page: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmoje-lece.si%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://moje-lece.si/&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Contact lenses are actually corrective lenses that are in direct connection with the cornea of the eye. The first idea of the lens method come forth in 1508 when Leonardo Da Vinci sketched the principle of the eye and the lens in a liquid shape. Further 300 years had to pass before the lens was actually used. The lens, produced by glassblower Muller, was initially physically used in 1887. A year later, contact lenses have been enhanced by Muller, aided by Fick and Kalt. The very first contacts have been created for correcting irregular astigmatism as well as for individuals with high myiopia and hypermetropia within the presence of aphakia. These types of lenses have been scleral, crafted from glass, which was later on replaced by celluloid. When examining the first lens crafted from plastics, it was established that the contact lens is much more resistant to blows and has for that reason a longer life-span (invented by Fick from Zurich). The following big step in the development was in 1963 when Otto Wichterle manufactured HEMA (2hydroxyethyl methacrylate/methyl methacrylate/ethylene glycol methacrylate) contact lenses in Prague. Those contact lenses were the 1st soft contacts. In 1973, the CAB material (cellulose acetate butyrate) came into use and the first contacts manufactured from this material have been named Persecon (still used today by some). The main advantage of the CAB material is a more versatile lens.  11 years later, the Boston material was created which is still used in the field of the contact lens manufacturing. Merely a year later (1985), a new, extremely oxygen-permeable material called EQUVALENS was invented. Today, soft contact lenses are mostly made from plastic materials (hydrogels) containing H2O. The newest generation of soft lenses (silicone hydrogels) represents the most important improvement in the material development since they enable a five time larger permeability of oxygen that reaches the eye through the lens.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will find 3 groups of contact lenses: hard lenses, rigid gas permeable lenses (RGP or GP lenses) and soft contacts. Absolutely no oxygen will be transmitted through hard lenses. They're manufactured from PMMA material (polymethyl methachrylate). As opposed to hard contacts, RGP contacts permit the oxygen through the lens. Lots of materials are available for their production and all of them are gas and water-permeable. Soft contact lenses are incredibly hydrophilic (they are highly water-permeable). They excel in a somewhat secure and extremely thin lens; they are permeable, but vulnerable to mechanic injuries and stains.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Some great benefits of soft lenses:&lt;br /&gt;;* superior permeability,&lt;br /&gt;;* highly comfortable use,&lt;br /&gt;;* reduced chance of damage to the eyes in case of accidents.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When handling lenses, hygiene is definitely of vital importance. It is obligatory to wash hands before getting in contact with lenses. The cleaning solution must be replaced each and every day. The lens cover must be washed and left out to dry.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Contacts must be washed right after every use. You'll be able to make use of them only for the period of time according to producer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don't use the solution more than once. In no way clean contacts with water. In no way loan your used contact lenses to anyone else. Even though you might be a regular lens user, it is recommended to have prescription glasses as well. It is also advisable to visit an ophthalmologist annually.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>