<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="9">		<conversation id="969c242e43440d9ee2ce39a405beb29">			We may differ in shape Or even be alike. We may do things together Or even have the same thought. BEING ARROGANT IS A VERY EFFECTIVE WAY TO RUIN YOUR REPUTATION.		</conversation>		<conversation id="4a7df0a606b47fc2fae51ad169212174">			Better is a little with the fear of the LORD, Than great treasure with trouble. (2) Better is a dinner of herbs where love is, Than a fatted calf with hatred.		</conversation>		<conversation id="67174207b2f255d405c40feaf3f1e9f5">			The poor man's hated even by his own neighbor, but the rich has many friends. He who despises his neighbor sins; But he who has mercy on the poor, happy is he. Do they not go astray who devise evil? But mercy and truth belong to those who devise good.		</conversation>		<conversation id="332862361b68d090cf985d054b61cc42">			The name of the Lord is a strong tower; The righteous run to it and are safe. The rich man's wealth is his strong city, And like a high wall in his own esteem. Oh I love this word With God all things are Possible.		</conversation>		<conversation id="6ec126470d5b7b0da06a14bd98952e36">			Pls will you be my Love because i desire to choose you?		</conversation>		<conversation id="221bd90959cde0cdc09b6d4fa16980c0">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215Lm9wZXJhLmNvbS9ldGVvYm9uZy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Eteobong ononokpono&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="c0fe02b1711a1f91289037663e37dc3c">			If you want to help someone through give, try to give the person the give that will make him/her to feeled good. And remember that is only God you've to give the Great Gift. I want you to know that through the give Noah give God. God stand up on His throne and say to Noah' because of your give I will not curse the earth again. So, I want you to think about the kind of give you can give someone in your life which can make him or her to Bless everyone . Your gift that you give to only one person, it can  help someone else. God bless you for taking the new step hence.		</conversation>		<conversation id="14a88b379b6c23d5cae82ea58e042b45">			God Love us! &quot;Yes the reason why I bold to say God love us&quot; is  that, One of our brother sang that man born to suffered. And I think about it until I realized that the word of man born to suffer is invaled or intoto wrong. God love us! Yes, because no man whom God create to suffer. If you suffer, know that is the work of wicked people. Your parents can also cause it for you. Thank You Readers.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f5081286f0609fd0dccb647f9b24dbb6">			I'm looking for God fearing lady from age of 22 to 25 to be my wife. If you care for this pls call me on this number +2347030155781 or email me through &lt;a href="/go/messages/send/receiver=Eteobong2010@yahoo.com"&gt;;Eteobong2010@yahoo.com&lt;/a&gt;;. Thank you and God bless you.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>