<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="8c0d4b252112ee1b27eaa355c8e2b185">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2V2ZW50cy5odWJvZWNkYWtndWdsYXlkcy5wb2RvbWF0aWMuY29tL2VudHJ5LzIwMTItMDQtMjRUMTZfNDNfMDgtMDdfMDA_" target="_blank"&gt;;Plumber - 6 Facts That One Knows and You May Not&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/princecody/blog/blogid=8664291" target="_blank"&gt;;Plumber - 6 Facts That One Knows and You May Not&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29kZWxsY2FybHNvbjUxMi53aWtpc3BhY2VzLmNvbS9QbHVtYmVyKy0rMTYrVGlwcytPbitIaXJpbmcrT25lJTIx" target="_blank"&gt;;Plumber - 16 Tips On Hiring One!&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plumbing can be looked as one among the challenging and hard job required to work with pipes and tubes for making and maintaining drinking water systems in the consistent way to make its flow correctly. A marked difference can there be between plumbing and water and sewage systems. The plumbing systems serve one building whereas the water and sewage systems serve a group of buildings or a town. The plumbing systems in the simplest forms consist of an supply pipe leading for a fixture and a drainpipe choosing the used water away from this fixture. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If we start to see the history of plumbing, plumbing in the ancient times was extremely rare until the modern cities became popular in 19th century. In the olden circumstances the waste disposal system merely constituted collecting waste and dumping it on the ground or into the riv. It was in 2700 B. C when the downtown settlements of Indus Valley Civilization found the fore. That was the time when the concept of standardized earthen plumbing piping originated with broad flanges using asphalt for preventing leaking. Improvement in plumbing systems was slow until the 19th century. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plumbing started out during ancient civilizations such as the Greek, Roman, Persian, Indian, and Chinese Civilization. Finally, in 19th century that development of separate, underground water and sewage systems put an end to the open sewage rivers. The authorities put a stress on proper disposal systems to become installed. In addition to help pipes and tubing, lots of other fittings are also required in plumbing systems such as valves, Elbows, tees, and unions. The plumbing system that's installed in the homes ought to be checked thoroughly from time to time for the maintenance. It is necessary to get the clean and hygienic drinking water. Similarly, the plumbing for air work is also done to make sure that people are safe from any gas leakages and also the dangers of fire. The plumbing industry can be a basic and substantial part of every developed economy to be able to supply clean water and to transport waste. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plumbing originated through the ancient civilizations such as the Greek, Roman, Persian, Indian native, and Chinese civilisations. This is due to the need for water system was soon realised as public baths were developed to deliver portable water and drainage; however the development and improvement associated with plumbing systems was very slow with virtually no progress made until that 19th century. Eventually however the development of separate, underground water and sewage solutions eliminated open sewage ditches and cesspools. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since the development of the plumbing system in the 19th century the materials applied to present day plumbing solutions involve a network involving high-pressure pumps and pipes, which as now made of copper, brass, plastic, material and cast-iron, lead is no longer used in the installation of modern plumbing systems due to the toxicity. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're having problems with your plumbing system it can be vital that you know where your Stop Cock is actually. Your stop cock can be a valve used to switch off the water supply to your dwelling. It is important you know where it is to help you turn the water off of and prevent damage in the event of a leak within your home.		</conversation>		<conversation id="59a2d541ef49c534cd5605990c757c8e">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL29kZWxsY2FybHNvbjUxMi53aWtpc3BhY2VzLmNvbS9QbHVtYmVyKy0rMTYrVGlwcytPbitIaXJpbmcrT25lJTIx" target="_blank"&gt;;The Importance of Technical Skills for a Plumber&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/princecody/blog/blogid=8664291" target="_blank"&gt;;Plumber - 16 Tips On Hiring One!&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2V2ZW50cy5odWJvZWNkYWtndWdsYXlkcy5wb2RvbWF0aWMuY29tL2VudHJ5LzIwMTItMDQtMjRUMTZfNDNfMDgtMDdfMDA_" target="_blank"&gt;;Plumber - Easy Fixes For Leaky Pipes&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The press has recently focused attention just as before on New Orleans along with the process of rebuilding. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Perhaps the very best long-term achievement of Louisiana's film endeavors is a many production people, actors and actresses, and others mixed up in creative process who continue to move to New Orleans after falling gets interested its Southern charm on their visits. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;New Orleans is among the list of largest and the the majority of fascinating cities of Louisiana. The town of New Orleans can be found at the southeast end of the state of Louisiana. The city is fortunate with great natural scenic beauty as it is situated right during Mississippi River and Sea Ponchartrain. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New Orleans is among the most few cities in the world that had been under the control associated with three nations. This town belonged to Spain, France and United states of america. It was founded by French in the year 1718 and named following your Duke of Orleans. Afterwards in the year 1762, metropolis was surrendered to Spain. But in the 12 months 1800, it was again returned back to France. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;New Orleans is a commercially significant place and a major international seaport connecting almost half of the country. It is also desired by several oil companies and have their corporate workplaces here. It is also a major service and distribution middle of offshore equipment companies and distributors. The back bone in the economy of the city is the manufacturing industry along using petrochemical, aerospace and shipbuilding industries. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The town of New Orleans exhibits some of the major and exceptionally beautiful attractions. These world class attractions are drawing thousands of tourists from globally. Some of the most prominent attractions in the city include The Aquarium with the Americas, Audubon Zoo, the Entergy IMAX Theater and the French Market etc. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Aquarium of the Americas is among the most must visit and the majority of exciting places of Innovative Orleans. This marvelous organization is a part of the Audubon Nature Institute. This is the place in which the locals can enjoy numerous animals from all over the world. If you are for a family getaway, then this is a must visit place of the city. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Fish tank is home to some of the most fascinating and rare species of animals such as piranhas, anaconda and clown fish along with amazing bonnet head sharks. One can also watch warm weather penguins including African and Rockhopper penguins. &lt;br&gt;; New Orleans also offers an array of museums such as Confederate Art gallery, Louisiana State Museum that comprises five historic buildings, the Musee Conti Feel Museum that houses a lot of wax idols of famous local residents with the city. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Confederate Museum is the oldest museum of the state of Louisiana. This magnificent museum was constructed inside year 1891 for storing war records, artifacts and remains with the Civil War. Most in the exhibits and contents of the museum were donated through the people of the town. One can find that uniforms and attires worn through the officers and soldiers during Civil War in addition to Confederate weapons that include guns, bullets and swords. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This museum is situated just a minute faraway from the Ogden Museum of Southern Art and in the National D-Day Museum together with Arts Center. It remains open from Monday to help Saturday from 10 some sort of. m. to 4 p.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>