<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="44c03b303d8324ae114cd42144b067b9">			Bothered By Hemorrhoids? Read This Helpful Piece&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Swelling of the rectal veins can cause hemorrhoids. The swelling can be attributed to chronic constipation, straining during bowel movements, and sitting for a long time. Effective treatments can include additional fiber and increased water intake along with a stool softening medicine when needed. This article can help you understand the additional causes as well as potential treatments.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A great way to get rid of the pain associated with hemorrhoids is to soak in a warm bath with about 2 cups of Epsom salt. You may think salt would burn the hemorrhoid, but it actually draws the moisture slowly out of it, reduces the swelling, and ultimately helps to eliminate the pain.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For more info go to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvd3RvZ2V0cmlkb2ZoZW1vcnJob2lkczIuY29tL3doYXQtZG8taGVtb3JyaG9pZHMtbG9vay1saWtlLWFuZC10aGUtd2F5LXRvLWN1cmUtaXQv" target="_blank"&gt;;What Do Hemorrhoids Look Like And The Way To Cure It&lt;/a&gt;;. If your are among one of the many people suffering from hemorrhoids, try increasing the amount of fiber and liquids you take daily. Increasing your fiber intake and drinking six to eight glasses of water daily can make your stool softer and less bulky. Producing a softer stool reduces straining and helps prevent hemorrhoids.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you believe that you have hemorrhoids that aren't going away with over the counter remedies, seek the advice of a doctor. Many treatments are now able to be performed in the office with minimal discomfort or needed follow up care. You can try an over the counter remedy first, but always follow up with your doctor.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Never hold your breath when you're trying to pass a bowel movement. Doing this puts additional strain on the veins in the lower part of your rectum. This is a sure fire way to end up with hemorrhoids. Relax when you go to the bathroom and you're more likely to prevent the discomfort of hemorrhoids.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A great tip for your painful hemorrhoids is to cut back on how much sodium you consume. This is essential because salt dries out your body, and this is the worst thing you can do to yourself if you are already suffering from difficult and painful bowel movements. On a side note, salt is not good for your heart health either.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To relieve the pain, itching and inflammation of hemorrhoids, try medicated witch hazel pads. These special pads are soaked in witch hazel and can be tucked against the hemorrhoid to soothe the irritated area while shrinking the swelling. Witch hazel towelettes are also available, if you prefer a swipe-and-go solution.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use moist toilet tissue or non-alcohol wipes when cleaning yourself on the toilet. Dry paper equates to rough paper no matter the softness of the tissue. The paper can cause bleeding from the hemorrhoids and should be avoided if possible. If you have access to a bidet you can use this as an alternative for paper.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you are out at a restaurant, make sure that you do not eat salsa or order any foods that contain a lot of spices. Spicy foods can irritate the symptoms of hemorrhoids, which can make you feel uncomfortable. Eliminate all spicy foods from your diet to control your hemorrhoids.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Although it maybe tempting to enjoy a hot bath when you're suffering the pain and irritation of hemorrhoids, avoid doing this. Stick to warm water instead, and do not add any products to the water that contain dyes, fragrances, or essential oils. These ingredients are notorious irritants for hemorrhoids.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A great tip for dealing with hemorrhoids is to use ice to soothe the discomfort they cause. Simply apply an ice pack to the affected area, and allow it to stay there for several minutes, or as long as is necessary in order to achieve a numbing effect. In this way, swelling can be reduced and pain eliminated.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To relieve some of the discomfort caused by hemorrhoids, try applying witch hazel to the region. Witch hazel is a natural astringent that can help ease the pain caused by hemorrhoids as well as lower the swelling. Just apply some to the inflamed area and you will quickly feel great relief.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avoid constipation to avoid hemorrhoids. Constipation is the result of not enough fiber and not enough water in your diet. This will give you hard stools that are difficult to pass. This then results in hemorrhoid flair ups. For best results in preventing hemorrhoids, keep your diet healthy and your stools soft.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you have hemorrhoids, you will want to stay away from all spicy foods (chili, hot sauce). These types of foods are very irritating to any current hemorrhoids. It is also recommended to avoid coffee, beer, and all types of carbonated beverages. Until you are feeling better, the blander foods you can eat, the better off you will be.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avoid spicy foods if you are dealing with a hemorrhoid flare-up. The way spicy food causes painful bowel movements is not just a comedy routine staple; spicy foods do indeed irritate the rectum on their way out. Hemorrhoids are especially vulnerable to this irritation, and eating too much hot stuff can make them harder to get rid of.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Squat, don't sit during a bowel movement to prevent hemorrhoids. In countries where people squat instead of using a sitting toilet during a bowel movement, hemorrhoids are very rare. Purchase a foot stool to keep your feet elevated, or try to squat with your feet on the seat to prevent hemorrhoids.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you need relief? Try Aloe gel! It can soothe the itch and burn that you may get from hemorrhoids. Aloe gel can greatly reduce the amount of burning or itching in that area. You should apply the Aloe gel directly to the hemorrhoids. This can make your hemorrhoid inconvenience more tolerable!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cut back on your salt intake. Salt can make your body swell including your hemorrhoids. Reducing your salt intake may be difficult at first but will be well worth it in the end.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are experiencing pain and inflammation from your hemorrhoids, try to soak in a warm tub. Fill your tub with enough warm water to cover the area and lay back with your knees raised. The warm water will increase the blood flow to the anus and reduce the swelling. Do this a few times a day to help reduce the swelling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The importance of a healthy lifestyle was presented in the beginning of the article and it cannot be emphasized enough for those who wish to avoid hemorrhoids. By using the advice in this article along with a healthy lifestyle, you can greatly decrease the incidence of painful hemorrhoids in your life.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>