<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="8bb3784cb578efc3c79adaad011eb30">			The moment i saw the song “ emosonal attachyachar” for the first time, i understood, some thing really interesting is coming up. And spotting Abhay Deol in it, made my faith more profound. Everything seems nice and classy, but to be frank i did`nt understood the name “ Dev D” ?? Why only D..i mean what it could mean. Later on some kind and enlightened souls, told me that “ abe its devdas, thats why only D”….what the fuck…are u kidding. Itna bindas devdas ??
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Though the wintage wine glass is replaced by Smirinoff, the gracious Chandramukhi is replaced by candid Chanda, saree and shawl clad Paro is replaced by desparate and bold Paro ( kindly refer to her mattress carring act ), even chunni is in a new avtar yaar !!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;And what to say about Dev Babu or the egoist Devdas Mukhrjee, which is replaced my sadda Devender Singh aka Dev. But the charm and pace of the movie is not lost. The same age old story in a completely different form.The whole team worked very hard on the transformation of the story.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Music is a significant part of any love story, and if it is a FOSLA`s love story then it is more important.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My apologies for calling Dev Babu a fosla, but guys this is what he is indeed !! Though Paro`s pehla pyar is Devdas but after her marriage she becomes completely loyal towards her husband. Now this is a point of discussion.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Coming back to music….what to say….complete transformation….again a mile stone album after Rock On. Emosonal attachyachar is simply mind blowing, and some lesser known songs like Pardesi, Saali khushi and Aankh Michowli are also of the same genre. In the videos of Pardesi and Saali Khushi dont miss a trio depicting the shades of Dev, through their dances and facial expressions. Seriously guys..this is class apart to other Bollywood movies in ways more than one.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How can i miss to mention Abhay Deol here. If you go by regular definition of Bollywood heros, then he is not a Hero !! Playing a character which is immensely popular among generations, ie Devdas, and that also changing the image of it. It calls for lots of guts. Kudos !		</conversation>	</conversations></author>