<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b6251e39d7d9f41b2fc19fe93f28fae9">			Forced blind date he went so far as to send me frankly just to complete the task tomsshoes I am a very ordinary girl looks, she is not the kind of bright spots, education is the common institutions of &lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsshoes2012.net%2F%26quot%3Btitle%3D%26quot%3Btoms"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tomsshoes2012.net/&quot;title=&quot;toms&lt;/a&gt;; shoes&quot;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;toms shoes&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; undergraduate work is the company clerk, his family was very general, parents are ordinary workers, now retired, but also a sister, a school teacher, has long been married. May be life no luck with the opposite sex, a long time, I have not talked to eight children to love. In college, I'd secretly like a boy, is my classmate.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But for the modesty of the girl, watch that boy love, break up, and love, I was always afraid to his confession, until graduating from college, our relationship is only classmates, even friends are not really.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Flash I'm 27 years old, still single, mother, sister worried that I would so go on, it really will be the rest, so they are four Trustee for my blind date. I know he was just an ordinary girl, but not outstanding, so my condition is not high, but I do not know why the total never quite make themselves satisfied or heart of man, several blind are nothing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Until last April, my sister took photos let me see, handsome, gentle man in the photo. The sister said he called the Order of the industry, and his colleagues, is also a teacher, two years older than me, good character. Said the man a lot of good things, my sister did not forget to told me: &quot;This is a lantern is immune to find a good man, you Do not give up easily. &quot; I did not care for my sister, based on previous experience,&lt;a href=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsshoes2012.net%2F%26quot%3B%26gt%3B%26lt%3Bb%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tomsshoes2012.net/&quot;&gt;;&lt;b&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsshoes2012.net%2F%26lt%3B%2Fb%26gt%3B%26lt%3B%2Fa%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tomsshoes2012.net/&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;; I proposed the first phone chat, chat a feeling, then too late to meet. Not my eventful previous blind date I have a fear, the two strangers sitting face to face is not nothing to say, is simply to say do not mix, then it is kind of suffering.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;About 3 days later, I received a phone Chengye talk each other feel are very good. I really like his voice, very magnetic. After us almost every day the phone, most of them call me, the phone talking to him decent, thoughtful people also know how to care for, such as &quot;cold, remember to wear clothes&quot;, &quot;work to cross the road vehicles pay attention to safety, &quot;the dry weather, drink plenty of water, &quot; these private savings, then listen to make people feel warm.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Phone chat more than a month after we met. In reality he fell and the photo is no different, very handsome, but I do not know what we already know each other on the phone, after that meeting but feel a little strange. Sit for a while, I suddenly felt my stomach, they put forward to want to go home. He just said &quot;the road carefully, and did not take the initiative to send me the meaning of home, did not even ask if I would see a doctor, I am very disappointed, feeling and telephone careful and considerate of his different person.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After the bearing industry still give me a call, he is still in the phone I am very concerned, the strange thing is, once met, I do not feel his concern. A few simple examples, with his shopping, large bags carrying the tired out of breath, he never took the initiative to help; first went to his house, I said I was leaving, he should only be a cry, did not stand up to send what I mean; second to his home, he did come out to send, to the downstairs, I politely said to him, do not send, and go back. He said no, I have to complete the task of my mother accountable.		</conversation>		<conversation id="c94643c15b7aeb5868168233c3803045">			Why quasi-newlyweds before marriage broke up say knot not knot | toms shoes Prospective couples in fear? Fear of marriage itself caught in a fear of the future and the mother-in-law or wife's &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsshoes2012.net%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3Btitle%3D%26amp%3Bquot%3Btoms"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tomsshoes2012.net/&amp;quot;title=&amp;quot;toms&lt;/a&gt;; shoes&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt;toms shoes&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt; mother to get along, fear a child raising children. While some outsiders is somewhat &amp;quot;alarmist&amp;quot;, but these prospective couple into the siege of this landmark and historic moment.
&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;quot;Marriage break up, because the prospective newlyweds, talks to break up even when planning a wedding and future life.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Faced with this problem, some people really break up, some people fooling around, then, points will not be under what circumstances? What happens when two people the run-in period of temper? Not have to break up is not available?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Side of parents in planning a wedding and even wedding invitations are sent out, the side of this alignment couples has trouble breaking up, a lot of noises I do not end up with this marriage! &amp;quot;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Why this happens?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;First of all, almost every alignment couples have premarital phobia, but the severity of the difference between.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prospective couples in fear? Fear of marriage itself caught in a fear of the future and the mother-in-law or wife's mother to get along, fear a child raising children. While some outsiders is somewhat &amp;quot;alarmist&amp;quot; However, in these prospective couples in this landmark and historic moment into the siege, the tense mood disturbed mood is normal. At this time, and temporarily want to bugger disgruntled, it is easy to trigger pre-marital break up.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Followed by the red tape of the wedding will make people moody pressure larger disagreement trouble breaking up.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We all know that marriage is a laborious time-consuming and costly job. Especially for the bride perfectionist complex, most likely to wear what the price of the wedding in which the hotel organized to do or even how many tables and trouble broke up. This situation is very common, even wayward bride threat: &amp;quot;If you do not wear a certain brand of wedding, this marriage I do not end up with. &amp;quot; Men stormed: &amp;quot;do not knot not knot! &amp;quot; They will not be happy and scattered.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Finally, pre-marital trouble breaking up the firm's performance is a love.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the parties are in love, will be anxious to get married quickly. Pre-marital break up downtown, the heart of this love and marriage is not enough firm, this situation than the bride or groom wedding &amp;quot;did a bunk only&amp;quot; a little to each other face some.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How to avoid pre-marital break up, two killer, the first is to understand. Understand each other's dedication and hard work. Sentence: &amp;quot;My dear, it is tough! &amp;quot; Which can resolve all grievances. The second is inclusive. Each other to make a little patience, it would be tolerated. Have a global situation consciousness, do not tell each &amp;lt;a href=&amp;quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsshoes2012.net%2F%26amp%3Bquot%3B%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3Bb%26amp%3Bgt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tomsshoes2012.net/&amp;quot;&amp;gt;&amp;lt;b&amp;gt&lt;/a&gt;;; &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.tomsshoes2012.net%2F%26amp%3Blt%3B%2Fb%26amp%3Bgt%3B%26amp%3Blt%3B%2Fa%26amp%3Bgt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.tomsshoes2012.net/&amp;lt;/b&amp;gt;&amp;lt;/a&amp;gt&lt;/a&gt;;; other general knowledge. At this time, before being happy to step into the wedding hall.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>