<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="1b4e4d664901a5973402e073ba48c913">			How is Cataclysm skill point gain different then previous expansions? Players only need in order to level 5 more times going from 80 - 85 instead epidermis way to 90. Seems nice but avoid being fooled as the experience essential for those 5 levels is really a lot more than usual.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The quest chain to acquire you started begins inside newly designed Orgrimmar. Probably a good thought to log out within the big city come spot day. It's important to try to get a jump on Cataclysm leveling as many of the entry level quests tend to be Kill &quot;;X&quot;; or accumulate &quot;;Y&quot;; type quests. With a whole server looking to quest, you can expect a serious delay.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A neat little tip to attempt to skip past this bottleneck of players is to fill your quest record with completed quests but not to turn them with until Cataclysm is introduced. A full quest sign can grant you over 500k experience that will give a nice 50% hop to level 81.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Doing the pre-quests may help loads in Cataclysm leveling since now you will be ahead of the server on release day. Even if you don't anticipate trying to be the 1st to 85, having a 50% enhance into level 81 is nice by itself and it is now time to pre-quest as we have a month until the release of the expansion.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Cataclysm leveling has not changed a tremendous amount compared to previous expansions. You can expect a whole lot more vehicle quests and tasks that will take a lot longer. If you plan on hoping to get to 85 as fast since you should definitely look in to a leveling guide addon. The paths they employ to quest cut out every one of the large filler quests Blizzard included in slow you down. Don't worry you would not miss a beat when it comes to content - it will just conserve time and stress.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As many of you know, questing is by far the fastest way to level up in WoW when you play solo more often than not. You will find that without meaning for your requirements will start taking all the quests you can and will start doing them in any order. First of all this is not the obvious way to level up your Wow character. In fact, you will find that you just would have been wasting a great deal time running back and forth. The quickest way to hit the new level cap in Cataclysm should be to know exactly where to go and which quests you have to take. Knowing exactly what to accomplish in order will massively increase your leveling swiftness.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is why some sort of Cataclysm leveling guide will likely be extremely useful. For all the players WoW and would like to hit the new, level cap as fast as possible. Maybe you are the particular competitive type and want to be one of the 1st levels 85's on your own server. Alternatively, maybe you have numerous level 80 characters and have to get them all to levels 85 as quick as is possible. Whatever your reason for wanting to level up faster in WoW I am able to assure you that having a Cataclysm leveling guide you can level much faster.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before you go buying a Cataclysm guide please make sure that you get the correct one available for you. Detailed information on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jYXRhY2x5c21sZXZlbGluZ2d1aWRlcmV2aWV3cy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;world of warcraft leveling guide&lt;/a&gt; can be found at main website.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>