<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="755e4c5b7d93b730eeb2501f6cab2434">			Getting married is very exciting, but it can be a very stressful event as well. There is a lot of planning that has to take place. You need to consider the cake, flowers and venue when planning your wedding. The advice in the next few paragraphs will help streamline the process of planning your wedding, so you can focus on the enjoyable parts rather than the stress.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wbGFubmluZ2NlbGVicmF0aW9ucy5jb20vYXVzdGlud2VkZGluZ3BsYW5uZXIuYXNw" target="_blank"&gt;;austin wedding planner&lt;/a&gt;;If you can't afford expensive floral arrangements, consider using potted plants throughout the reception and ceremony areas. Use some glazed, colorful ceramic pots or embellish earthy terracotta stoneware using decoupage, ribbons, or some fancy paint effects. The guest's wedding favor can be the plants in the pots, or you can put them in your garden.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A wedding dress is a big expense. Consider looking into dresses that are not designated as wedding dresses. You should check out the selection of bridesmaid dresses at the bridal store. One could fit your style at only a fraction of the cost. Even if you need the dress to be altered, it will probably be less expensive than buying a wedding dress.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;An overabundance of flowers on reception tables causes trouble. Usually, the flowers are only in your guests' way. Some people attending your wedding may have pollen allergies, as well. Instead, you could place candles (non-scented) on the table tops to add a romantic feel to the reception.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ask a close friend or family member if they'd be interested in becoming ordained online to be able to officiate your ceremony. This adds a personal touch to your ceremony, and also saves you on the costs of an officiant. However, be sure to check all the required legalities before you opt for this.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If dinner isn't a part of your reception plans, formal tables shouldn't be either. Lounge chairs, chaises and comfortable sectional pieces will help encourage interaction between your guests. Comfortable and inviting chairs allow your guests to feel welcome and relaxed, which creates a nice atmosphere at your wedding.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avoid dressing children in clothes that are too stuffy and uncomfortable. Use soft, loose fitting fabrics. It's important that any shoes they wear are comfortable, which means new shoes, will need to be broken in. Thinking ahead about small details like this can make all the difference on the wedding day and will cut down on fidgeting and fussing over uncomfortable clothing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are planning a wedding outside, always make sure that you have a 'plan b' in case mother nature does not cooperate. Have some tents on hand, or choose a venue that provides both indoor and outdoor space. In case of soggy ground, lay down an artificial surface on major walkways to avoid muddy shoes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you already know, there are only a few things that a wedding must have. A lot of the other aspects can change depending on religion, cultural or personal interests. Of course, many of these things can make you feel extravagant, but they can also add to the stress. By using this article, you will have a wonderful wedding that everyone can enjoy.		</conversation>		<conversation id="dbd1dfb69f24ea224ee2c17d05df828">			An engagement can be the most cherished memory between a couple. That said, the romance of the engagement is often quickly overshadowed by the stress of planning a wedding. If you want to make your wedding planning as much fun as the actual wedding will be, follow these ideas.&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wbGFubmluZ2NlbGVicmF0aW9ucy5jb20vYXVzdGlud2VkZGluZ3BsYW5uZXIuYXNw" target="_blank"&gt;;austin wedding planner&lt;/a&gt;;It is a good idea to plan for an even number of guests at each table, since people tend to pair off in conversations. Use age and relationship models to help group your tables, as this will help people locate good company.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try to plan your reception for the afternoon. Most people will make plans after the reception, which minimizes the amount your guests may drink. Lunch receptions tend to be cheaper than dinner ones because of a possible lower need for alcohol. That money can then be used for other wedding expenses.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you want seasonal flowers that grow near your home to decorate your wedding, you should keep in mind that they may be extremely difficult to acquire near your wedding location due to differences in climate. Speak with people who are in the area where your wedding is located to find out what blooms are available to you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Designing a wedding that lives up to the bride's expectations is the best way to ensure that she is thrilled on her wedding day. A wedding can be a stressful day for any bride, and if she's struck by disappointments, she may have a melt down. The bride's wishes must be followed or you will be facing an angry bridezilla!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Personalize your wedding by incorporating any elements or facets of your personal identity, your betrothed or especially the relationship you share. Select a theme that best represents what you mean to each other.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For aesthetic purposes, centerpieces are necessary, but they can really take a bite out of your budget. Instead of purchasing a large centerpiece that will take up the whole table, keep it very simple. Smaller centerpieces allow your guests to converse and interact without something blocking their view.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rather than going out shopping to buy an engagement ring, consider something a little different. Use jewelry that has been part of one of your families for generations. This kind of keepsake invites the bride into the family and offers a classic reminder of the marriage.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always guarantee full control of a lighting system at the venue, particularly the ability to dim or brighten the output. It may sound insignificant, but you are probably going to want to dim the lights for the first dance and turn them back up for the remainder of the reception. Be sure to find out about these details before you decide for sure.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It can be expensive to place centerpieces at your table at the wedding. Instead of going with a huge table centerpiece that uses up almost the entire table, keep it simple. Simple centerpieces help keep the table from feeling cluttered and make it easier for guests to talk to each other.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Remember the tips and tricks presented here when you start to become overwhelmed by the choices you have, whether it's for the ceremony itself, or the rehearsal beforehand, and the ceremony after. You will find that you have access to a number of wonderful resources and opportunities to make the big day go off without a single hitch.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>