<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d2f3c13bd31824795e79fbca6b4fe26">			The Playstation3 is a great gaming system. The graphics are fantastic. The sound is crips and clear. You can play BluRay DVD’s. There’s even the Playstation Network so you can play games online. You can download games, tv shows,  movies, add-ons and more. It’s just an all around great gaming system.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes, however, when you’re playing games a problem will develop. You’ll get the yellow and red light. You’ll get the red and black screens of death. Games will freeze. Bluray discs won’t play. Your wonderful gaming experience can turn into a nightmare.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fps3repairsx.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ps3repairsx.com&lt;/a&gt;;  aren’t cheap. If your Playstation3 is still under warranty you can return it to Sony and have it repaired free. You’ll have to wait at least six weeks to get it back though. If it isn’t still under warranty you’ll get hit with a hefty repair price (almost as much as the cost of a new unit) and you’ll still have to wait at least six weeks for it’s return. You’ll also lose all your hard drive data.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can take your Playstation3 to a local repair shop if you want to. Some might even have a loaner you can use until your machine is ready. Ps3 repairs may not be as expensive this way as going directly to Sony, but ps3 parts can be expensive. Either way you will have to wait and may end up with just an old refurbished box.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You could solve your problem by just going out and buying a new Play Station 3. This might fix the problem, but then again the new Playstation3  might eventually start experiencing the same problems. What do you do then? Buy another system? How long does this cycle go on? Of course you could just buy a completely different game system altogether, but it might not have the games you like to play. And it wouldn’t have the Playstation3 Network either.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes it’s something simple that you can easily fix yourself. The first thing to do is to make sure you’re plugged into a wall outlet. I know, I know, But you’d be surprised. Then unplug and replug all the machine’s cables. Make sure there aren’t any loose connections. You may need to remove and reinstall your hard drive. It’s not as difficult as you might think.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ps3 repairs are made easy with the proper  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fps3repairsx.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ps3repairsx.com&lt;/a&gt;; , the proper tools and the proper instruction. Once you know how you can keep your machine in tip top shape and enjoy gaming for years to come. But how do you find out what you need and how to do it as inexpensively as possible?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is a site where ps3 repairs are made easy. You’ll get all the information and support you’ll need.		</conversation>		<conversation id="330f2545c691657fe39297940312aeee">			The Playstation3 is a great gaming system. The graphics are fantastic. The sound is crips and clear. You can play BluRay DVD’s. There’s even the Playstation Network so you can play games online. You can download games, tv shows,  movies, add-ons and more. It’s just an all around great gaming system.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes, however, when you’re playing games a problem will develop. You’ll get the yellow and red light. You’ll get the red and black screens of death. Games will freeze. Bluray discs won’t play. Your wonderful gaming experience can turn into a nightmare.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ps3 repairs aren’t cheap. If your Playstation3 is still under warranty you can return it to Sony and have it repaired free. You’ll have to wait at least six weeks to get it back though. If it isn’t still under warranty you’ll get hit with a hefty repair price (almost as much as the cost of a new unit) and you’ll still have to wait at least six weeks for it’s return. You’ll also lose all your hard drive data.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can take your Playstation3 to a local repair shop if you want to. Some might even have a loaner you can use until your machine is ready. Ps3 repairs may not be as expensive this way as going directly to Sony, but  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fps3repairsx.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ps3repairsx.com&lt;/a&gt;; can be expensive. Either way you will have to wait and may end up with just an old refurbished box.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You could solve your problem by just going out and buying a new Playstation3. This might fix the problem, but then again the new Playstation3  might eventually start experiencing the same problems. What do you do then? Buy another system? How long does this cycle go on? Of course you could just buy a completely different game system altogether, but it might not have the games you like to play. And it wouldn’t have the Playstation3 Network either.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sometimes it’s something simple that you can easily fix yourself. The first thing to do is to make sure you’re plugged into a wall outlet. I know, I know, But you’d be surprised. Then unplug and replug all the machine’s cables. Make sure there aren’t any loose connections. You may need to remove and reinstall your hard drive. It’s not as difficult as you might think.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ps3 repairs are made easy with the proper ps3 parts, the proper tools and the proper instruction. Once you know how you can keep your machine in tip top shape and enjoy gaming for years to come. But how do you find out what you need and how to do it as inexpensively as possible?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is a site where  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fps3repairsx.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://ps3repairsx.com&lt;/a&gt;; are made easy. You’ll get all the information and support you’ll need.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>