<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="c7a0c69c7a59fcb5f6ab10c4b0c3f23">			so, with some spare time on my side, I decided its a time I do all these things I have always wanted to do and I didnt have time to do before. First of all I really need to go back to the gym or am gonna regret it for the rest of my 'fat' life.
&lt;br /&gt;;Leave alone the gym, I plan to do other lots of stuff. Infact my most important thing right now is am trying to discover my talent (I know am old enough to say that but I really mean it). I want to discover that is which I can do so well and from there am gonna make money out of it.
&lt;br /&gt;;That now brings me to my agenda of the day- am running some errands and after that am gonna go for my first piano lesson, who knows- I might actually be the next Stevie Wonder (seriously!!!!!!!!!!!!)
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Gotta run now, I want my fingers to be relaxed when they are on that piano.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Am outtta here!
&lt;br /&gt;;Good day peeps!		</conversation>		<conversation id="18ec95b08b7b2b8d2a445990a52a6669">			hey people, its been long since I last blogged and to tell you the truth I have a couple of reasons- and thats why am blogging now, to explain.
&lt;br /&gt;;so now, I still have that job that I love but dont like as much, contradicting yeah? lemmie explain. in my current job am not even sure who my boss is coz everyone is like a boss, that am not comp;aining about coz as a consequence I fail to report to the office (which I do often) but no one questions it coz every boss usually thinks I had an official reason which I probably communicated to the other boss. so in this job that I love and hate, the workload is not as much and when I dont feel like doing a thing I usually pay some guy to do my work, this brings me to my reason for hating my job, its a job that can be done by any uneducated person. it makes me feel like I am wasting my masters degree.
&lt;br /&gt;;so much about my work, I was meant to tell u about my reasons for being so scarce. now, as much as I have a job that I can easily miss without anyone noticing, I constanty find myself super busy. take today for example, I didnt go to work (no excuse was given to the boss), I went to the library to do abit of research. I was hoping I will do that till around 4pm but now its almost 6pm and am nowhere near completion. I was hoping to hit the bar at some point tonight but I dont see that happening, WAIT!! I have to go to the bar, have to do some shots of brandy, I think am getting a cold coz my throat feels like hell. I have to find a way to get a drink tonight.
&lt;br /&gt;;what was I blogging about again? oh, my reasons for being very scarce. I dont know whats up with my time coz am always running out of time to do everything, am I getting slower or is time really flying? as lilwayne says 'mine flies first class'
&lt;br /&gt;;am out of time and I have to go............................................
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;on my next blog I'll tell u guys whats been keeping me so busy.................have to go now. CHAO!		</conversation>		<conversation id="32a5a0b5be17c12acceeaf91db3ba7ac">			I know I still owe u an explanation as to why I've been too busy and scarce these days. am gonna do that when I get the answers myself......
&lt;br /&gt;;In the meantime I want to share my experience in the office today.
&lt;br /&gt;;here I go......
&lt;br /&gt;;so as I have always said in my earlier blogs I HATE my job, I started hating it July this year. before that I totally loved it and I can assure you I was the most handworking employee then.
&lt;br /&gt;;so this morning I walk into the office and as usual start reading my newspaper. wait..........did I ever told u that I also work with Swedish pple? if not now u know. Anyway as I go through my business daily my Swedish boss walks in. allow me to describe this guy first. he is ofcourse white with short hair but very well managed, he has this slender sexy body and a butt that u cant ignore- firm and spankable (I know!!!! its still my boss am describing).
&lt;br /&gt;;so my swedish boss walks to my desk and leans over (at this point I just want to grab him and do all thise things I see on TV). anyway am breathing so hard and I guess even if I got the guts I'd not get the energy to move an inch- I sat there stunned. He gave me a few instructions of which I had no clue what he was talking about- I was muted and deafed***(if there is anything like that)
&lt;br /&gt;;so after a couple of minutes he left. I recollected myself and life went back to normal, or almost. as I started working my  workmate came to my office to ask for printing papers. this guy is the complete definition of TALL, DARK &amp; HANDSOME I dont even know where to start, he is hot, hot hot. and to make it worse he flirts with me. so he walks into my office and hugs me (there is nothing abnormal about that- its an office policy). as he hugs me, he grabs my ass and smiles at me....................................................
&lt;br /&gt;;as am thinking about it my body is shivering!
&lt;br /&gt;;am gonna continue soon, lemmie take a glass of water!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>