<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="dfc743e7bc394a9c38e73468511e20b6">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0Nhc2hGb3JHb2xkTW9yZW5vVmFsbGV5LmJpZ2d1eXNqZXdlbHJ5YnV5cy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;Sell Gold Moreno Valley&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpZ2d1eXNqZXdlbHJ5YnV5cy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;Sell Gold Moreno Valley&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Perhaps you have chose to start investing in gold and silver. Club members can buy precious metals at the identical price, or even far better prices, than many desired dealers pay. Members pay true wholesale prices. It is possible to save up to 21% to 35% or more, and you don't even need a bullion dealer's license to do it. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 5) &lt;/b&gt;; Share Guy &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those who have a pool or jacuzzi, you recognize that it takes &lt;b&gt;; WORK &lt;/b&gt;; to keep it clean. You can setup weekly or monthly share cleanings with neighbors. Target a neighborhood with 3 or 4 pools so you can save time and gas by doing while doing so. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 6) &lt;/b&gt;; Clean Clearing &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My mother-in-law is actually on the be wary of strong, reliable teens who want to earn extra money clearing away brush and debri. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Matthew, my 12 year old, just made $20 bucks just the summer hours work! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 7) &lt;/b&gt;; Garden Tilling &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Every spring and fall, I hire my son Tony to till the organic garden. It's an easy way to earn extra money at home or even around the neighborhood. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 8) &lt;/b&gt;; Bookkeeping &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is not only a wonderful way to earn extra money, but a pivotal and useful skill to educate yourself. That is - if you're feeling brave while using the bills! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 9) &lt;/b&gt;; Panorama projects or Plant Doctor &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you have sort of a green thumb? Are you trusted? &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Both business owners and home owners need someone to water their indoor plants regularly or right after they go on vacation. This is certainly an easy, fun way to make some extra bucks. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Or if you have a strong back, you may break out the shovels and beautify yards which includes a tea rose garden, increased flower bed, or modest gold fish pond! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 10) &lt;/b&gt;; Artist &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do you have an artistic or talented teen? Encourage her to advertise her talents and draw, photograph, or sketch portraits to earn extra money at home. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I realize of an 18 year old girl who designs horse portraits for extra cash. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Or you may make you own pattern and sell t-shirts, mugs, etc. on CafePress. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are plenty of jobs for 14 year olds to produce money - you just need to be willing and excited. And do a small brainstorming! &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;If you're thinking about selling gold, knowing how much people stand to receive is the most crucial question. Let's say you purchased a gold bracelet with regard to $200, when selling your old watches, don't expect to obtain full amount you payed off. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Jewelry carries a high mark-up when it is sold to cover the charges of production, overhead and to generate a profit. Gold buyers must also pay to have their gold refined meaning less payout to the main selling gold. If you sold a bracelet you paid $200 for, you may expect to receive concerning $50 to $100 in return for. Depending on your situation that's still a nice amount of money. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Providing Gold: Find A Buyer &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now that you're ready to start selling gold your next step is to find a buyer. Some buyer offers you an appraisal before you submit your gold. &lt;br /&gt;;.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e7b16b0c5329e3f4d2b218226d798e24">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2JpZ2d1eXNqZXdlbHJ5YnV5cy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;Sell Gold Moreno Valley&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0Nhc2hGb3JHb2xkTW9yZW5vVmFsbGV5LmJpZ2d1eXNqZXdlbHJ5YnV5cy5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;Sell Gold Moreno Valley&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Perhaps you have chose to start investing in silver and gold. When you decide to help cash out and sell to your dealer, some coins and bullion solutions DO require the trader to file IRS Mode 1099B reporting the transaction with the sale. Here's some really good news. The dealer IRS reporting requirements DON'T apply to American Your old watches Eagle Coins nor do they affect American Silver Eagle Funds, regardless of the amount. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Please take note, when you sell, you are obligated to report your capital gains to your IRS. Remember to keep all of your receipts and records and always seek advice from your tax advisor. Additionally, please note that this author is not really a tax advisor nor an investment advisor. The reporting information above was thought as true at the time this informative article was written, but you know, tax law does change so it is suggested that you talk to a professional tax counsellor and investment advisor in advance of making any investment options. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As noted above, gold American Eagle coins and silver American Eagle coins make a superb precious metals investment selection. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Would you like to Find Out Where You should buy All the Gold and Silver You Want -- below wholesale? &lt;/strong&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I have discovered a small, distinctive, members only, buyers club for silver and gold coins. It's the only club of its enter America. Club members can purchase precious metals at the identical price, or even better prices, than many preferred dealers pay. Members pay for true wholesale prices. It is possible to save up to 21% to 35% or higher, and you don't even require a bullion dealer's license to do it. Grab a free copy of my innovative eBook, &quot;Insider's Guide To Buying Silver and gold At Wholesale&quot; and discover ways to start paying wholesale today:  http: //www. BuySilverAtCost. com  &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Here are 10 careers for 14 year olds to produce some extra money within their spare time: &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 1) &lt;/b&gt;; Wash Windows &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A bucket of tepid to warm water with a little vinegar inside and a squeegee is all it takes to make money cleaning windows. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the time any more to wash windows? I know As i don't! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;That's how come I happily pay my teens to do the &lt;i&gt;; dirty &lt;/i&gt;; work! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can charge by the window, for example $5 dollars per eye-port, or by the hour. The money adds up quickly. Try putting up a local flyer in the grocer's, library, etc. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 2) &lt;/b&gt;; Clean out the Attic or Basement &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Isn't it amazing the amount &lt;i&gt;; stuff &lt;/i&gt;; you can accumulate? Most homes are stuffed on the roof tops with &lt;i&gt;; waste &lt;/i&gt;;! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Teens can haul inside cash by cleaning out other people's junk. And some of it can also be recycled for even even more cash. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don't forget, a cluttered home can be a cluttered mind! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; 3) &lt;/b&gt;; Mow your Lawn or shovel that drive-way &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This will seem obvious - but I'm always &lt;b&gt;; AMAZED &lt;/b&gt;; at the amount of dads I see mowing their lawns... or shoveling the sidewalk - rather then Johnny Junior! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Besides being great exercise, mowing the lawn and shoveling the walk is good money and good exercise for an ambitious 14 year old. &lt;br /&gt;;.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>