<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="6b9a3cbfd3a589502d5d48f6a23a5711">			However, it does offer the facility to record conferences, making it a great business tool. If your business needs you to hold a lot of teleconferences, you should definitely choose this product over Cisco's.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Can Be Administered Centrally&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avaya's IP Office can be deployed at more than one location, yet be administered from a central office. This saves on an administrator's salary and, therefore, saves on costs. It is true, but only partly. The exams are a little difficult but with proper preparation it is easy to clear the exam. One has to first know about the syllabus for the exam and should also know the details of the various subjects to be studied. It is available for free on the Cisco's website.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One can get it from there. Then, the person has to decide whether he could study for the exam on his own. One could also use the help of various websites which provide tips on how to prepare for the exam. If the person feels that he/she is new to networking and cannot do self study, then he/she could always join some classes which help people in clearing the 642-145 exams. The recommended training from Cisco is Implementing Cisco IOS Unified Communications Part 2 (IIUC2) 1.0 and IPTX training would not be required.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In case you have not heard, Cisco has an affordable Small Business Unified Communications solution. It consists of two components, Cisco Unified Communications Manager Express (CME) and Cisco Unity Express (CUE). CME is the call processing engine. UC Manager Express runs on an Integrated Services Router (ISR) and does not require a dedicated server. The same ISR router can be used for access to the Internet, the corporate Wide Area Network (WAN) and Virtual Private Network (VPN). Depending on the router, UC Manager Express can support between 8 - 250 IP Phones. It supports the majority of IP phones and also supports softphone, IP Communicator.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CUE is Cisco's voicemail solution for the ISR router. It can support between 12 - 250 mailboxes. CUE comes as either a Network or Advance Integration Module (AIM). Both platforms support features like Integrated Messaging, which allows users to see their voicemail in email. With Unity Express you can create multiple Automated Attendants and play different greetings based on the time of day. Other nice features supported by Unity Express include Fax integration, Live Reply, Live Record, VoiceView and Remote message notification.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When combined together these two products provide a very powerful communications solution for any small to medium sized business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Communications Manager Express is one of the key topics covered&amp;nbsp; in Cisco's new Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA) specialization for Voice exam.&amp;nbsp;Candidates will need to know how to design and implement Communications Manager Express and Unity Express.&amp;nbsp; After Completing the CCNA Voice students can pursue the Cisco Certified Voice Professional (CCVP).&amp;nbsp; The CCVP is one of the highest paying Professional level certifications.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With extreme competition, and the global market continuously shrinking, any business that wants to remain successful today has to be aggressive and flexible. This includes being open-minded and accepting that the business processes currently in use, may be outdated tomorrow. Indeed, so why don't you give it a try?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fmaps.google.com%2Fmaps%2Fplace%3Fq%3Dcomputer%2Brepair%2Bnj%26amp%3Bcid%3D18115108814090217595"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://maps.google.com/maps/place?q=computer+repair+nj&amp;cid=18115108814090217595&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.jaydien.com%2Fproducts%2Fcisco-ip-phone-system.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.jaydien.com/products/cisco-ip-phone-system.html&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>