<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="96693f3e86edc86a194bd189012a97b7">			A large segment of the population already own property, or wish to become proprietors of property or are planning to become one in the long term. To own property, certain formalities are needed to ensure a smooth transaction and also to take possession of the property. &lt;br /&gt;;Purchasing a house is one of the biggest milestones in one's life, this act includes certain formalities that get you towards legal possession, some of them include:&lt;br /&gt;;The signature in the agreement of purchase must be completed. This step refers to the meeting between the parties solicitors. First both sides cares to determine the sales contract especially know the terms thereof. The client features a withdrawal amount of 7 days just just in case of change of mind. The seller and the notary shall initial each page. The customer signs the final page. &lt;br /&gt;;The payment of the security deposit. Usually, the notary demands the customer settling a first deposit of five to ten percent of the quantity of the transaction, this amount is usually decided by mutuial agreement. This amount varies regarding the amount of the transaction.&lt;br /&gt;;This amount will probably be cashed with the notary by having an account deposit and consignments. This amount will be secure. The seller can withdraw with 7 days of signing the agreement and this amount will be returned as a whole. If the retraction is after the 7 days the deposit will be paid to the seller and the buyer must first give its consent in writing to the other party. The notary acts as custodian between the two parties.&lt;br /&gt;;There's additionally a withdrawal period. The client has a time period of seven days if they wish to retract if they change their mind about buying this property. This decision ought to be in written communication letter with acknowledgment of receipt. Within this period the customer isn't obliged to warrant its withdrawal. The security deposit will be returned within a period of 21 days by the notary.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhcHB5aG9tZWVzdGF0ZXMuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhappyhomeestates.com%2Fproperty-in-navi-mumbai.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://happyhomeestates.com/property-in-navi-mumbai.html&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>