<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="a3676abab8335f6ebecb831744f52080">			“ &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fhowdoumakeout.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://howdoumakeout.com&lt;/a&gt;; , never wanted to. What am I to do, cannot help it.” Well, if you find yourself in a situation when you have fallen in love again and cannot help it, naturally, you want your sentiments to be reciprocated. So, how to make someone fall in love with you? That is the question. Unfortunately, there is no hard and fast rule which can be applied as there are no love potions or prayers that can instantly give you what you want. However, you may try out these tips and techniques to make someone fall in love with you. First impressions are lasting impressions, and an immediate chemical and physical attraction is going to help. So, if you know that the person of your dreams likes a particular physical type, such as tall, dark, and handsome, or blond-haired, blue-eyed, then it can help if you happen to fit that particular physical description. The main point is to get the person to notice you. An instant chemical and physical attraction is needed, so you need to make a conscious effort to attract the person you love. However, it is all going to be one-sided if there is no physical attraction on the other side, and the other person overlooks you whenever he or she is in your company. That means that there is no fire burning, and you are going to have a heck of a time trying to light one.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You may start bringing yourself to the other person’s attention by communicating with him or her. Be intelligent, be amusing. Do not badmouth others thinking that you are being witty. Learn how to listen. Desdemona fell for Othello while listening to his stories, and Othello fell for her because she was a good listener! Understanding the needs of the person you love can go a long way to making him or her feel sympathetic towards you, just do not be too aggressive or forthcoming in your actions.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There was an episode of the Oprah Winfrey show when the topic was, “How to make someone fall in love with you.” And on the show, there was this tiresome man who was very proud to say that he had targeted the girl he wanted to marry and was making her the object of his attention. He thought she would fall in love with him because he was bombarding her with presents. When the girl was asked her opinion about the man, she said quite frankly that she despised him because he was trying to overpower her.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;She also considered him to be a stalker and was sick and tired of him appearing on her doorstep with silly books meant to improve her mind! And he was foolish enough not to understand that her “no” meant “NO” and not “maybe.” Her frank opinion annoyed him so much that he yelled at her on the show and said that she did not deserve him. He was trying to make her out to be a cultured lady fit for him, but she did not appreciate his efforts one bit! So he then decided to find somebody else who would appreciate him more.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Watching that episode, it was hard not to get angry listening to that man’s aggressive pursuits. The girl had been lucky to escape! For women, bullies and egotistical clowns should be kept at a bargepole distance. If you are a man, then you should understand that these overpowering tactics are a definite put-off to women. You may think that you are being complimentary, but the woman is going to think you are being tiresome and overbearing. So, if you want to make someone fall in love with you, give them their space to breathe and enough room to be able to appreciate your good traits. Do not try to turn them into something that they aren’t. You should love a person because of who they are, and not for what you imagine they can be; this is the basis of true love.		</conversation>		<conversation id="c34ea36ed3406ee93d54bf3ac3b1e3a2">			Love is a many splendored thing, and there is nothing as painful as liking somebody and knowing that he does not like you in return. However, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvd2RvdW1ha2VvdXQuY29tL2hvdy1kby15b3Uta25vdy1pZi1hLWd1eS1saWtlcy15b3U_" target="_blank"&gt;;how do you know if a guy likes you&lt;/a&gt;;? Here are some points which can give you a hint about the state of his mind. A guy is normally going to be very shy, unless his disposition is brash and bold. And if you are his first crush, then he is going to do his best to try to convey that he is not affected by your presence even though he cannot resist being close to you and trying to talk to you whenever he can. If you like him, you can encourage him by communicating with him, but if you think he is a jerk, it is much better for you to be direct and tell him that you do not like him hanging around you.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Being quiet and coy in such matters, just because you do not want to hurt his feelings, may come back to bite you in the butt if he starts pestering you. Liking someone can either be mutual or one-sided. One-sided liking can turn into an obsession in extreme cases. However, if the liking is mutual, then it is all the better because you are going to be able to appreciate his actions even more. He is going to show his initial attachment by showing you that he is always there when you need him. You can talk to him and take his advice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is always going to be an element of physical attraction, and people who like each other cannot stop touching each other. The idea is to feel the physical presence and feel secure by it. The foundation of liking someone is an initial physical, mental, and emotional attachment which is going to deepen every day.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He will try his best to communicate with you when he is not around you. This means you can expect phone calls. You can even expect messages which might be funny because in the initial stages, boys do not send sentimental messages. Just try to understand the feelings behind the message and appreciate them. They are going to open themselves up to you and tell you things they may not have ever told anybody else. So appreciate that part of your relationship and respect it. Never break his confidence because that is a great way for you to break his heart.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He is always going to respect your wishes because you are the object of his love. Make sure that you do not take advantage of this because once he wakes up to you being selfish and mean minded and how you took advantage of his good nature, for example, by spending his money while fooling around with other guys, he is not going to want to have anything to do with you. So remember, if you think a nice guy likes you, respect his feelings, appreciate him, and try your best to make the relationship work.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>