<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="8c269e7b3f0ed54c5d55f5183c23d45e">			Suboptimal skin care can lead to all sorts of nasty outcomes like acne and dry skin. Proper skin care isn't something that you typically learn in school, so you need to learn proper technique from somewhere. The tips in this article give practical advice for maintaining healthy, vibrant skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No matter what skin care regiment you begin, you must make sure that you are gentle with your skin. If you pick at your pimples or buy into crazy skin remedies, you can permanently damage your skin, effectively causing more damage to your skin, in the end.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A good skin care tip for keeping your skin moist is by turning on a few humidifiers. Space heaters are known to put out dry air, while humidifiers disperse more moisture into the air. You can keep your skin moist and healthy simply by turning on a few humidifiers around your home.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When winter comes around and temperatures grow cold, it can be all too easy to forget about sunscreen. Sunscreen is a vital component to good year-round skin care. It is not the temperature of sunlight that puts skin at risk, but the sun is closer to the earth and its rays are even stronger in the winter.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you are moisturizing your face make sure that you do not forget to do the same thing to your neck and chest area. These spots are often forgotten, and they have the same damage done to them as the face if they are not taken care of like they should be.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To keep your skin healthy, consider eating a diet that is high in selenium and zinc. Selenium has antioxidant properties that help protect skin from free radical damage. Foods high in selenium include wheat germ, tuna, salmon, garlic, Brazil nuts and eggs. Zinc helps to prevent acne and calms skin irritated by breakouts. Zinc is found in turkey, almonds and wheat germ.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Diet is important in maintaining healthy skin. Care for your body and your face by taking a multi-vitamin every day. Vitamins and minerals promote healthy skin growth from within. That is the the only way to look your absolute best on the outside. A good vitamin pack will eliminate the need for additional tinctures and creams.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This will sound obvious, but if you are looking to have better skin, you need to watch your consumption of fatty foods, particularly foods such as pork, duck and fatty red meat. Though delicious, these foods contain so much fat that you can sometimes feel it coming right out of your skin the day after you eat it. So the best way to control your skin's oil output is to get a handle on your own fat input.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Skin care can be as complicated or as simple as anyone desires it to be. Basic skin care requires cleaning and moisturizing, and the secret is finding the plan that works best with a particular skin type. Some find their skin is dry and avoid harsh cleaning products, while others need complete oil removal to reduce blackheads and breakouts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These tips were provided to help anyone who desires to have a great complexion for many years, but none of them will work unless you try it. Hopefully, you have found some new information that will help you keep your skin looking youthful and healthy for many years to come.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other Resource&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Jlc3RhY25lc29sdXRpb24ubmV0L0RvZXMtY3JlYXRpbmUtY2F1c2UtYWNuZS5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;Does creatine cause acne? &lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="aaaa71b435aec42f94b19ee4bcc11071">			Do you want smooth, silky and soft skin? Do you want your skin to glow? Do you want to protect and nourish your skin? The tips below will help you achieve all of those things and lead you on a path to healthy, glowing skin! Just a few minutes each day can make all the difference!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Skin care regimes differ for each skin type. Find a cleanser that works for your type, and stick with it. If you have oily or combination skin types, try gel or foaming cleansers. Normal and dry skin types should stick with cream based cleansers. Toners are optional, but do wonders for your skin. Try them out, and go from there.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The sun can be a damaging force to skin. It produces ultraviolet rays that can cause damage to the skin. Wear a sunscreen lotion with an SPF of at least 15 and has the ability to block UVA and UVB rays. Apply to the skin before entering the sun (at least 20 minutes in advance).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do not use soap on your face as part of a skin care regime unless it is an especially developed facial soap. Ordinary bath or hand soap is too harsh on the facial skin and will strip it of the natural oils and moisture it needs to retain its healthy glow.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once or twice a week, mix a pinch of baking soda into a dab of your regular skin cleanser for an inexpensive exfoliating treatment that smooths your skin as you wash your face. Rub the cleanser on dampened skin in gentle, circular motions with your fingers or a washcloth, and rinse thoroughly with warm water.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Exfoliate your body with an oatmeal scrub. People with sensitive skin will benefit from an oatmeal scrub, as it exfoliates gently. Simply mix a little oatmeal with body oil and rub on the skin in circular motions. Leave for a few minutes and then rinse off with warm water. This also has a moisturizing effect, so it is useful for people who suffer from dry or flaky skin on their body.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sweating may be annoying, but it's also the way your skin removes toxins. If your job is mostly sedentary, be sure to schedule regular workout sessions. Working up a sweat on a regular basis helps your skin eliminate toxins, and your skin will glow with health. It's a winning equation all around.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's important to keep pores unclogged to prevent pimples and acne from forming. By using a facial cleanser with salicylic acid, you can loosen and rinse away dead skin cells that could clog your pores. Your skin will begin to look softer and smoother and less likely to have breakouts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Drink at least 2 litres, 6 to 8 glasses, of water everyday. The water will help to flush toxins out of your system and will also hydrate your skin. The body eliminates some toxins through the skin, so the less toxins in your body the better your skin will look.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With the above information, there is no longer an excuse not to keep your skin in the best condition possible. It doesn't require mass amounts of time or work on your behalf and the results are always worth what you put in. Do not wait until tomorrow to start taking care of your body when damage is being done today.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other Resource&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mbGl4eWEuY29tL2Jsb2cvNDMxNzMxOS9TdHJlc3MtTGVzcy1BYm91dC1Zb3VyLVNraW4tV2l0aC1UaGVzZS1FYXN5LVRpcHM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Tips For A Successful Skin Care Plan&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>