<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e0158d559228671ba027f039bf089bc">			The surface of Nintendo DS Lite uses two materials. 53.7% of People Complain that they Can not Afford Genuine NDSL  It uses the transparent plastic on the upper surface and the lower surface. The layer plastic packages the whole upper surface and the lower surface. The translucency of plastic is very good, surface is smooth. Even the perspiration and handprints are left, rubbing with a cloth will be able to restore cleanliness.Go R4 DSi which Rachel McAdams Fancy most
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nintendo DS Lite and the inner surface of L,R key use the frosted plastic surface. This layer of plastic feels a stronger friction, can keep good feelings when playing the game. But this also brings a very serious problem, and that is very easy to stain dust. In the actual use of process, we found that the phenomenon that the inner surface is smeared is not serious, more serious is the L, R key. If you use it for a long time, it will turn yellow or even black. In addition, it is very difficult to clean. It is recommended to wipe with an eraser.Superior and Fashionable DSTT card for dsi on Sale Now!
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The machines Nintendo DS Lite has recently put on sale were in three different colors, namely, milky white, icy blue and deep blue. During the sales, many people tended to choose the machines in milky white or icy blue, regardless of the problem of being stained. Nintendo has announced to put black Nintendo DS Lite into the market. According to the past marketing practices, they will also produce machines in other colors such as pink, bright green, and orange, etc. Similarly, Limited edition machine with pattern should be also planned. If you are not satisfied with the current color of the machine, you can wait patiently.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nintendo DS Lite's inner side is installed with lithium cell which needs charging for three hours. You just need to connect power with Nintendo DS Lite's lateral faucet, and it will began to charge. When it is charging, the light at the top right corner will turn orange. You can normally play games in the whole process of charging.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nintendo DS Lite is reducing the volume while it is reducing the power consumption. Even though Nintendo DS Lite has a bright screen, it can run a long time because it reduces the power consumption of circuit boards. The battery's life is related to brightness levels.Don't let out light can last longest, but you will not see anything on the screen, because the Nintendo DS Lite uses a full-transparent type liquid crystal. The using period of battery also depends on the operated games. Certain games require great deal of operation, which results in larger power consumption.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The battery of Nintendo DS Lite can not be taken out at will. The battery cover is on the back fixed with screws. If we want change battery, you need to take out the screws firstly.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Nintendo DS Lite is still available by game card. Users have to buy game cards in order to play the games. Nintendo DS Lite has two game card slots, which are NDS slot on the top and GBA slot below. That is, Nintendo DS Lite can not only dedicated to play NDS games, but also can play GBA games. Be careful, NDS can not play GB games and GBC games.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If NDS card is inserted into the machine, it will access to NDS game when you open the machine. During the game, if you close the cover, it will enter the standby mode. As long as Nintendo DS Lite has enough power, the game will always keep the standby mode. After you open the cover, the game will return to your last play areas. The set will be helpful to the game you play for a long time. You can play it at any time and stop it at any time.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you play GBA games, through the system you can set to upper-screen display or the lower-screen display. Nintendo DS Lite's upper-screen display effect is better than the lower-screen, on the perspective point of view, the upper-screen is easier to view, so we suggest everyone to adjust the upper-screen. Nintendo DS Lite to play GBA is very smooth and it has a good compatibility. The screen of Nintendo DS Lite is slightsly larger than the screen of GBA. When you play GBA, the picture is not full screen, otherwise, it will has the black side.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the king cards of Nintendo is on-line. The on-line function of Nintendo DS Life is better. It has get rid of the bide of wire. The insdie set WIFI wireless mode of Nintendo DS Life can realize the wireless on-line.		</conversation>		<conversation id="90f26ecae82e36a86ed10b030ccf08d9">			Apple is unmatched in changing the world. How to Protect the Color of iphone charger ? Its stunning productions include personal computer,iPod,iPhone and iPad which was just released expectingly.Summer’s New TV80 Mode
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After iPad was published, mixed half critical and half praiseful, while lack of camera function is the most common complaint heard of. In addition, it is reported by the media that the WiFi connection lines have some problems. But, these don`t matter, just like all other innovative productions of Apple, the point of iPad is hardware, but the revolution of operation system. Up to now iPad is most likely to change the reading mode and payment of network digital contents. Hence the declining publishing industry has a chance to recover.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;iPad has no memory card slot or photo taking funtion, but its open operating system allows users to choose the network, online games, or publishers' digital content, and users are not forced to buy these applications . Because of its feature of easy use and fun, it is probable that users are willing to spend time and money on it.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Besides, its design has wonderful reading effect which removes the trouble in reading, and is also suitable to enjoy movies and pictures. The trouble for the reading online in the past was that most of articles could only be garbled quote out of context or took part of essential contexts with other contents subjected to the design of the webpage or browsing habits apart from the delicate home page which was a great harm to reading. This is why iPad is able to help publishing take back the market which was took up by the free contents on the net.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;IPod changes the model of music sales, which sells digital music instead of CD, what is even more powerful is the iTunes music sales platform; While iPhone change its using purpose for intelligent phone which mainly focuses on application software sold by iTunes. In future, ipad will also change the modes of books, magzines and newspapers. So far few media has successfully charged cyber-friends. iPad multimedia capabilities are expected to bring consumers with high entertainment, and thus they are willing to pay the online newspaper subscription.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In early web environment, AOL or other portal sites are equal to gatekeepers of web news, netters have to through them and can see paradise of internet. Today, iPad will be expected to replace it, and it even makes users be willing to give up the original free content with unstable quality and pay for better content. It is the strength of Apple, which also highlights the importance that the hardware manufacturers control their own operating systems and obtain the original payment system. As for the Apple, it is iTunes to achieve it, while other companies may have to do it through the network operators. It is no wonder there are rumors on recent market that several companies are interested in buying Palm because Palm's mobile operating system is very easy to use and it has many patents.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>