<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="12e5d4308f69afb8bde11837fa2afba5">			Facebook is undoubtedly one of the most popular social networking sites. For its millions of users who are spread all across the continents, Facebook has now launched the ‘App Centre’. The users of Apple and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Ryb2lkLm9yZy9jYXRlZ29yeS9oYXJkd2FyZS9hbmRyb2lkLXRhYmxldC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Google Android Tablet&lt;/a&gt;;  and smart phones can now directly get all kinds of apps for their Android Phones and tablet. It is a smart initiative taken by Facebook as will transform the social networking into a key platform for online entertainment. This ‘App Centre’ is going to provide a huge market for lifestyle, productivity and gaming applications.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/182707883_13392458_49607886.jpg" /&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This will save the Android users from the unwanted hassle of getting the apps from the Android marketplace. This ‘App Centre’ is going to include approximately six hundred apps. One can also find most amazing and popular games here. This store is going to be made available for public access in the USA first, and then it will reach out to the rest of the countries of the world. This smart move by Facebook will help the website to make a huge comeback from the after effects of its IPO launch in the stock market. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Facebook ‘App Centre’ also offers personalised recommendations to the users of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Ryb2lkLm9yZy9jYXRlZ29yeS9oYXJkd2FyZS9waG9uZXMtYW5kcmlvZC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Android Phones&lt;/a&gt;;.  It also allows the users of Google Android Tablet and phones to easily browse  through the amazing apps that all their friends use. There is another great feature of this ‘app store’; it features only those applications that are top class and their apps ranking is based on the users’ feedback.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>