<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a32a7542e6586fb5a92ffbca6e6bfc27">			Earning bigger profits from your eBook and making sure you get the best out of your efforts is all about thinking out of the box. Listed in this article are some things you can do to increase your eBook's profitability.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use Targeted Newsletters and Ezines: Promoting your eBook often begins with your making good use of a variety of channels that are already available for you to use. This is another way of saying that you should be sure to get as much use as possible from the newsletters and ezines online that have already been established and built a reliable readership. So does that limit you to just one ad in a single ezine that relates to your niche? No, you actually go beyond that. Get in touch with ezine publishers within your niche market, and get them to re-publish quality excerpts from your eBook with a byline that links to your main eBook site. This will be the best situation you can have because you will get the best exposure possible while also allowing the publishers to give some good content to their subscribers. Make sure that the ezine you work with is actually targeted for your niche. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Do a Webinar: Webinars are really simple and easy to do these days--all they are online seminars. You can use any of the hundreds of different webinar tools that exist to help people without very specific technical know-how to host their own webinars. So how does a webinar help you sell more copies of your eBook? The webinars that you conduct will obviously be free, and people will get attracted to it because it offers such high value. They'll also refer all sorts of other people who could be interested in your offer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once you have the people lined up for your live seminar - the action starts. You simply give them juicy content at no cost while also pre-selling them on your eBook. By the end of the seminar, many of the participants will be convinced that you're the real deal, which is when you introduce them to your eBook and refer them to your site.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Join Other eBooks to Yours: The Internet is full of eBooks that come with exclusive rights for reprinting that will allow you to reprint that eBook and sell it for a profit or give it away for free. You can use the rights you've bought to combine these eBooks with eBooks you've written yourself to make something even better. People will be more likely to buy from you when they see that they are getting even better value for your asking price. Over delivering on your work is always a fantastic idea because it proves that your potential buyers will be getting all sorts of value for what they are paying. You do, of course, need to make sure that you are only spending your money on the best eBooks possible and that are relevant to your chosen market. Last but not least, eBooks are a permanent fixture now and are growing all the time. So take advantage of the opportunity now and make money like never before by marketing your eBook differently.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fdurhaminternational.co.uk"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://durhaminternational.co.uk&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>