<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="bbaaf959db874b72a81afadffa0fc7b9">			AL-AZHAR group of educational institutions is run by Noorul Islam Trust (Reg.No.198/92). The trust has been established with the noble as well as elevated vision of imparting sound wisdom and knowledge to the illiterate masses in Kerala especially with a view to educating the developing young men and women in and around Idukki district. The great visionaries, who have vast and profound experiences in the field of education, joined their hands together for the unique purpose and formed the trust (NIT) in1998. At present the trust has 21 acres of land in Kumaramangalam panchayat in Thodupuzha Taluk. The Al - Azhar education complex, which is blooming up 2kms away from KSRTC bus stand Thodupuzha town, is under NIT.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Janab Nalakathu Soopy, the education minister who is well aware of the need of the backward community took the initiative and laid the foundation stone for the Al-Azhar complex building on the 21st of Feb 2002.The trust has now started an Arts &amp; Science College,Training College,Public School and a Paramedical College. The govt. of Kerala has already given sanction to start new Dental College under the Trust. Moreover, the trust has been planning to start B.Pharm College and Engineering Colleges. The magnanimous people of Idukki Dist.,have extended their generous hands for the development of the trust.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Affiliated to Mahatma Gandhi University and approved by Government of kerala, the Al-Azhar College of Arts &amp; Science is intended to become a centre of academic excellence.Al-Azhar campus is situated at a distance of 2 kms from Thodupuzha town located at Perumbillichira (Thodupuzha-Kumaramangalam Road). The towns of Muvattupuzha,Palai and Adimali are within easy reach.Apart from being accessible the college is set in a panoramic and tranquil location.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Al-Azhar College of Arts &amp; Science
&lt;br /&gt;;Thodupuzha East
&lt;br /&gt;;Idukki,Kerala
&lt;br /&gt;;India. 686697
&lt;br /&gt;;Phone : 04862 - 221845
&lt;br /&gt;;Fax : 0485 2831035		</conversation>	</conversations></author>