<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="bd35cf2fd3b0d3e4d24dd4f8867dacd1">			.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL0xpc3N2dWV0dGV1cEdyYXppYWJ5bm8ubmV3c3ZpbmUuY29tL19uZXdzLzIwMTIvMDUvMTIvMTE2NzgzODktZGF0YS1kZW5pYWwtYW5kLWJ1c2luZXNzLWludGVsbGlnZW5jZS1ob3ctdG8tYWNoaWV2ZS1kYXRhLXF1YWxpdHk_" target="_blank"&gt;;KPI &amp; Business Intelligence&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wdXJldm9sdW1lLmNvbS9zYW1nYXJuZXI3MTgvcG9zdHMvMTM3MzAyMC9BZ2lsZStCdXNpbmVzcytJbnRlbGxpZ2VuY2UrQWRvcHRpb24_" target="_blank"&gt;;Executive Summary For Mobile Business Intelligence and Analytics&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb29kcmVhZHMuY29tL2V2ZW50L3Nob3cvMzgxNjkwLWRhdGEtZGVuaWFsLWFuZC1idXNpbmVzcy1pbnRlbGxpZ2VuY2UtaG93LXRvLWFjaGlldmUtZGF0YS1xdWFsaXR5" target="_blank"&gt;;KPI &amp; Business Intelligence&lt;/a&gt;;In today's information age group, many businesses are finding a real asset in their own historical data. Business intelligence provides you with solid, effective actions you may take to yield measurable results. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Most of the activity trading Intelligence Projects is underground - that is, down the tunnels from it. To much of the market, BI Is about the analytics tool or dashboard they see on the desktop - they get little understanding if just how much effort goes on behind the scenes to plug meaningful data to people tools and ensure that it is available to them regularly. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In truth of the matter, BI is a blend of: &lt;strong&gt;; Data + Company Requirements + Tools + Design + Transformation &lt;/strong&gt;;. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Data &lt;/strong&gt;; - Getting the business to fully appreciate the intricacies on the robust data management system can be a challenge - and quite frankly they don't essential info. However, they do need to take responsibility for the products data going forward. Piecing together historical data is not as easy as combining a few tables - the real issues will be in the years of badly controlled data entry, meaning erroneous data may be entered into the wrong fields and once combined - it creates an increased error rate for the information set. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once data has been cleansed of historical errors it ought to be maintained in a clean state going forward - this means locking down software fields with tighter validations and training users not to just plug random words in anywhere that's offered. It also means appointing data stewards to manage new data and changes to existing data definitions in each area of the business. These changes are then aggregated for a central repository, managed by way of the BI Competency Center [BICC]. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Company Requirements &lt;/strong&gt;; - The next challenge is in transforming data in order that it is usable for trending together with analytics. A lot of data in its current form cannot be disaggregated across months, weeks, days without semantic input in the business - for case, how to deal using erratic sales of commonly varying magnitude. Selecting the proper KPI and the attributes of people KPI is not additionally understood as one may well think. Too often, KPI used for reporting purposes are adopted by default for dashboards. Yet, many of these KPI are not fitted to performance management. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; BI Equipment &lt;/strong&gt;; - The layering with the BI tool on data only accounts for 10-20% of any BI job. It's all the users see, so it is often most of what they appreciate with regard to work effort in some sort of BI project. I realise this sounds simplistic, however this perspective is actually less from ignorance and more from deficiencies in time to stop and think about what a BI project involves. A little bit involving upfront education goes a considerable ways in setting more fair expectations from business people. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Pattern &lt;/strong&gt;; - often overlooked is a design element of dashboards. Dashboard design is a highly skilled art from - but the one that is relatively easy to learn once one is knowledgeable on key principles involving visual perception and pattern. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;; Transformation &lt;/strong&gt;; - lastly, there are actually the behavioral changes to make sure that BI becomes pervasive through the entire business. Weaning users of MS Excel spreadsheets onto overly complex BI tools is not the easiest.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e3b771e23fe22d9f3349346759dc727d">			Today's smartphones are fascinating, glitzy and fun to own and are selected by customers per their choice. With the help of mobile solutions they can download apps per their wish from this app stores or access them through web browsers. Customers desire to get mobile applications shaped per their use and in a personalized fashion. Business Intelligence is something different from this as they aim to provide users with repeatable analysis and high-quality, consistent info and reports. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While using the release of recent equipment and latest mobile apps that allow users to get some more self-service options and data visualization options but considering IT's effectiveness, security, other constraints and costs allow personalization to travel only so far but not as much as they use the items. IT managers are excited and not in a positive fashion. The most important concern is of data security since it is adhered to regulations that threaten punishment when personally identifiable information (PII) and other data if exposed. But in mobile BI it may be not as scary or risky since it is feared by businesses plus it managers but it can be considered to be a significant barrier while deploying BI and analytics on cellular devices. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the need for real-time data arises there could be another tough challenge that's to meet the expectations for performance and quantity. BI directors or THE IDEA managers are excited when it comes to any technology that is capable to raise opportunities for delivering right data to your right users at the right time: the credo with Business Intelligence. This happens because it is less relevant of users at precisely what time and what place will they interact with data or receive your alerts about changes and trends that make impact on their assignments. Mobile devices can fulfill all these objectives that are at the rear of BI deployments. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It can be wise to enable BI and analytics in the great mobile devices that has amazing features like content-interaction, collaboration features, touch screen etc. Being so attractive together with appealing for customers the product could bring a revolution in BI experience for customers and especially with non-technical persons. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This article is useful for those users who are on the run and for IT departments who are able to support mobile users with BI deployments. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Generally speaking the term &quot;business intelligence&quot; encompasses a host of business related software and tools. Businesses use these tools to organize and manipulate data from numerous sources. Organizing the data will take the form of info mining, analytical processing, and or, querying and reporting. Agile business intelligence is a new wave of methodology in the field of business intelligence. Agile BI uses new technologies which make this recent evolution with traditional BI more flexible plus more manageable. Data organized on spreadsheets has long been the system businesses use to organize, reconcile, and communicate information to help clients and between teams or associates. Agile BI methods are much more helpful to the user than the spreadsheets with which most individuals are already familiar. Agile BI concentrates on freeing businesses to identify areas of concern, take into consideration solutions, and quickly answer any questions raised during any component of this process. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2twaXN0YW5kYXJkLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;what is a kpi&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>