<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="adaee211ecfa21743a616453aa1b586f">			Trading with leverage is when you're able to gain wide exposure to the marketplace with low capital requirements. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the case of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.igmarkets.com.au"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.igmarkets.com.au&lt;/a&gt;;, you can trade on shares with a deposit, or margin, of only Five pc of the value of your position. This means that you can access a $20,000 share position for just $1,000 when trading traditional shares you'd need to outlay the entire $20,000. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Basically, you are borrowing the shares from your CFD broker in order to trade on them. If the market moves in your favour, you may still make the full profit that you would have made had you been trading standard shares, meaning that the return on your original investment can be particularly large in comparison. But should the market turn against you, you can lose more than your original deposit. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the equity in your account falls below the minimum amount required by your CFD broker, you may be subject to a margin call. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Let's say that you have $500 in your account and you choose to use that as a Five pc deposit to trade on shares, priced at $25 a share. You open a position on 400 shares, making the total price of your position $10,000. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the shares fall by $1, the value of your position will fall to $9,900. The margin requirement of your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.igmarkets.com.au%2Fcfd%2Faward-winning-service.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.igmarkets.com.au/cfd/award-winning-service.html&lt;/a&gt;; is Five percent, and Five percent of $9,900 is $495. But as the value of your trade and, consequently, your account, has fallen by $100, you only have $400 remaining in your account. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your CFD broker will alert you that a margin call is due (that you will need to deposit the extra $100 in your account to meet their minimum margin obligation), with an alert on your screen, or a phone call, or an email. Most CFD providers will give you 24 hours to close the position, add $100 to the account, or reduce your exposure to the stock. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the shares continue to fall and hit $23 (losing you another $100) and you didn't respond to the margin call, your CFD provider may close the position, wiping out the $200 and leaving the remaining $300 in your account. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you can see, it'll only take a tiny price movement in the cost of a CFD for you to be closed out of a position or to face a margin call. Instruments that don't use leverage usually have more space to move and more time to think, meaning that the bigger the leverage used the likelier it is that you'll face a margin call. &lt;br /&gt;; Ways to manage this risk include using stop losses and limit orders alongside prohibiting the amount you risk on any single trade. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One. Stop losses &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A stop loss allows you exit your trade immediately should the market turn against you to a degree. Having a stop loss means there is a limit to the amount you can lose, and you know it from the outset of the trade. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two. Limit orders &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A limit order works in a similar fashion to a stop loss but, instead of setting a closing level should the market turn against you, you set a closing level if the market turn in your favor. This means that if the market rises to a particular level, your trade will be closed automatically, defending your profits in case the market turns again. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Risk limits &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A common recommendation is that the satisfactory loss for a single trade is Two percent of your capital. This figure can often be used to help you figure out your trade and your stoploss, as you might place your stop-loss at a level between 0% and 2% of the equity in your account. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Also, if you only risk Two percent per trade, that means you'd still have Ninety percent of your capital left if you suffered 5 straight losses, and 80% of your capital left if you suffered ten straight losses! The more money you lose the harder it is to gain back, so restricting your risk in the first place will make it simpler for you return to a breakeven point, and make subsequent profits.      &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogabond.com%2FTripView.aspx%3FTripID%3D115323"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.blogabond.com/TripView.aspx?TripID=115323&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e1ad1f5cec436d85fbd57e42a66406a8">			Futures are contracts where, at the expiry date, the holder of the contract (the purchaser) has the obligation to take delivery of the asset under the terms of the contract, while the vendor is required to make the delivery.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;From an investor's viewpoint, profits and losses are incurred by selling and purchasing the futures contract prior to the expiry date, meaning that most futures trades occur among traders who never have the objective to make or take delivery of the underlying asset. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Markets available through CFDs and futures&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CFDs are available on a large range of markets, including forex, stock indices, shares, commodities, binaries, options, IRs and bonds. The online platform provided by the CFD provider will probably provide access to some, or all, of these markets. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Futures are also available on numerous assets, though they aren't as widely used as CFDs. Futures contracts are usually traded on commodities, indicesWhat is a CFD?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A Contract for Difference ( CFD ) is a derivative product where you trade the changes in the costs of financial instruments. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Unlike conventional trading where you must outlay the whole value of a position, CFDs are a geared asset. This means that you can open a big position on a stock, commodity or index with a deposit that is just a small slice  of the price of the underlying stock, commodity or index. Accordingly, the returns on your initial investment can be much larger than the potential returns on conventional shares. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Explaining futures&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A future is also a derivative product, with price derived from an underlying asset. Futures are contracts where, at the expiry date, the holder of the contract (the purchaser) has the obligation to take delivery of the asset under the terms and conditions of the contract, while the vendor is obligated to make the delivery.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;From an investor's point of view, profits and losses are suffered by purchasing and selling the futures contract prior to the expiry date, meaning that most futures trades occur among investors who never have the objective to make or take delivery of the underlying asset. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Markets available through CFDs and futures&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CFDs are available on a wide range of markets, including shares, stock indices, commodities, forex, binaries, options and bonds. The online platform supplied by the CFD provider will generally provide access to some, or even all, of these markets. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Futures are also available on a number of assets, though they aren't as widely used as CFDs. Futures contracts are typically traded on commodities, indices, interest-rate products and some currencies. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Margin trading&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Both CFDs and futures are traded on a margin, meaning that the investor can open positions with no need to pay for the full cost of the underlying assets. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Trading on a margin gives traders access to leverage, meaning that they can trade bigger positions, or trade more positions, with nominal capital requirements. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Margin trading with CFDs&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the case of CFDs, a investor will need an account with a CFD provider who will have a minimum margin requirement this can range all the way from 0.5% for instruments like forex and indices, to Five percent for liquid stocks, to 75% for large positions or illiquid stocks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This means a investor could open a CFD position on 400 shares, priced at $50 per share, for $1000. To trade traditional shares, a trader would need to purchase the shares outright, at a price of $20,000. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The margin amounts move in and out of the investor's account as positions are opened and closed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Leverage with futures&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Futures contracts are also traded on a margin, which allows investors to controlmanage a huge amount of a commodity with small capital needs. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If a investor wished to get a futures contract on 100 tonnes of corn, costed at $315 per tonne, the contract would be worth $31,500. But a trader  doesn't need to pay the full $31,500, but only wants to pay a margin just over 10% to open a position. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brokerage rates &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CFD commissions on shares start from just 0.1% of the value of your position, with minimum charges starting from $8 to $10. CFDs on other markets ,eg forex, indices and commodities, are traded commission-free, as the charge is generally included in the dealing spread. Against this, normal share trading commissions range from $15 per trade to over $80 per trade for full-service brokerage. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Futures brokerage rates can vary, as many brokers offer discounts to clients who trade giant volumes or frequently. Rates may vary from $15 to $40 per trade dependent on the trader's requirements, while traders who execute trades themselves from a web trading platform might possibly be able to negotiate rates as low as $8. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Over the counter vs exchange traded &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Futures contracts are traded on exchanges. This means that futures users and investors are guarded from contract default by a warranty / system implemented by futures exchanges. The exchange clearing house is an unrelated party that acts as an intermediary between buyers and sellers, so that the buyer and seller each create an obligation to their broker, who then has an obligation to the clearing house. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most CFDs are traded over the counter, through market maker or direct market access (DMA) &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.igmarkets.com.au%2Fcfd%2Faward-winning-service.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.igmarkets.com.au/cfd/award-winning-service.html&lt;/a&gt;;. Market makers provide their own costs for the underlying assets on which CFDs are traded, which might or might not differ from the going rate. Market makers might or might not hedge the CFDs they offer. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;From the other standpoint DMA providers hedge the trades their clientele make by 100%, and their prices are determined by prices in the underlying market. With a CFD broker offering DMA CFDs, a trader  can also trade within the market spread by dealing straight into the order book. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Contract sizes &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When trading future contracts, lot sizes can be fixed according to the terms of the contract, and the client's requirements. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the meantime, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.igmarkets.com.au%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.igmarkets.com.au/&lt;/a&gt;; can be gotten in a selection of contract sizes, with mini- and micro-lots available for traders who may not want to trade a full sized contract but still want to participate in the market. CFDs are also available on some of the bigger future contracts, but in smaller sizes.      &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.blogabond.com%2FTripView.aspx%3FTripID%3D115323"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.blogabond.com/TripView.aspx?TripID=115323&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>