<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e75248fab9612e974a9a868d097e2747">			Numerous issues can cause fatigue throughout the day, but lacking quality sleep is often the most common problem. Many people are unable to rest even when they choose to go to sleep early, because of a problem known as sleep apnea. For the majority of individuals, sleep apnea can be difficult to recognize since it is hard to notice breathing problems at night without a partner's vigilance. Some confusion may remain about how to treat sleep apnea even once it has been diagnosed, however. One of the most useful options lies in continuous positive airway pressure, or CPAP, masks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CPAP masks may look intimidating at first. They feature a flow generator which creates a pressurized air flow, a hose which connects to the flow generator, and a nasal or full face mask which provide a connection to the user's airway. Despite CPAP masks' unusual appearance, when utilized properly with continual use, they are the best non-surgical tool for treating obstructive sleep apnea (the most common form).  Another important fact to note about CPAP masks is that there are many different types and brands available. If one version seems too uncomfortable for use, then another mask sized in a different way, or with a different style, will most likely be more effective.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Individuals also may have heard horror stories about how CPAP masks can cause negative side effects such as eye irritation, nasal congestion, sore throat, and general discomfort. Thankfully, all of these issues can be dealt with by making certain that a CPAP user has selected the right mask for them. The type of CPAP mask chosen for the individual should be based on that person's most common sleeping position, breathing preference, and any sizing factors which they may want to consider. Additionally, certain CPAP masks have been created so that they provide a low air pressure when first worn, and slowly increase the pressure as the user nears sleep, thus lessening irritation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When compared with the adverse effects of untreated sleep apnea, which include impaired judgment, short term memory, and cognition, as well as moodiness, wearing a CPAP mask at night seems a small adjustment to make. Air from a CPAP mask is pushed into a user's airway, allowing the respiratory muscles less strain and preventing regions of the lung from collapsing. This means that in addition to helping relieve the aforementioned troubles, CPAP masks also can remedy snoring, thus providing the user's partner with a more restful sleep as well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;User convenience regarding CPAP masks has gone up over the years as they have become more portable, and remain one of the best options available for anyone living with sleep apnea. If users maintain regular care and maintenance for their mask, they should reap the utmost benefits of a more oxygenated and peaceful sleep. Searching for advice on what type of CPAP mask would best address an individual's needs should be the first step before investing in any mask, so that once can achieve rest with little difficulty and stress.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Author Bio:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I have labored in the subject of sleep medication for fifteen years and can provide you some very first hand info about CPAP masks. Be sure to catch my content articles with CPAP masks.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Visit my content articles from here:  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cpapmaskreview.com"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cpapmaskreview.com&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.cpapmaskreview.com%2Fcategory%2Fcpap-side-effects%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.cpapmaskreview.com/category/cpap-side-effects/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>