<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="9d74969c7a2b0519388bb91ca9797d83">			They don't cost an arm and a leg and she has many scheduled cities on her tour. Select the closest one and you're sure to be in for a wonderful evening full of entertainment and fantastic music. Maybe traveling a little is more what you had in mind. Make a trip out of it and select a great hotel along the way, enjoy a nice dinner somewhere and a jazzy night with beautiful live music. This combination can turn a concert into a family vacation for a minimal budget.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the best things about Taylor Swift tickets is she's an entertainer the whole family can enjoy. You won't have to worry about content that is 'too adult' or songs with cursing in it because it's simply not her style. Her shows are fit for an audience of all ages and her music can entertain both the younger generation and the older. These can make great gifts for someone's birthday, or graduation or even an anniversary. If no one has an event coming up that works well with a concert date, don't be afraid to give a gift early. If that's not your style, don't fret because everyone loves presents for absolutely no reason at all. Especially when they involve live performances by one of the hottest young singers out there!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once you've decided this would be a great idea, don't wait. Grab your Taylor Swift tickets as soon as you can. The earlier you act the better selection you're sure to have in regards to both seats and prices. You want to snag the best deal and spot so you won't miss a single second of the performance and so you'll have money left over for a Cd or shirt. Now that you have your tickets coming and you know who you're going with and when, take a few days to add to the anticipation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's definitely a good idea to spend some time with the person or people you'll be at the concert with while listening to her music. Make a game of guessing which songs you think she'll perform. Maybe even have a little family wager riding on the order they pop up in. This way you can make the excitement last longer than just one evening! There aren't many artists out there today that are wonderful entertainers, have great vocal qualities, are 'hip' to both the young and old. Taylor Swift manages to fill all these qualities while at the same time producing fabulous music!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And that's just the start of all we know about this artistic young girl! Taylor has as of now won innumerable awards that include three Grammys.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This vocalist from Pennsylvania set to penning songs from 10 years of age. The Fearless Tour 2009 got rolling on the 23rd of April, 2009 in Evansville, Indiana. It spanned 6 months including 50 cities around the globe with all shows getting sold-out very quickly, making it one of the most attended and talked about performances in 2009.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After seeing its success Taylor has now announced the second leg entitled the Fearless Tour 2010 which gets off to a start in Australia in February 2010 and ends on the 2nd of June in North America.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Taylor Swift was the best selling artist last year with both her self titled album and Fearless. You may want to order more than one, so that you'll be able to take a friend along too!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fplaytimetix.com%2Fconcert-tickets%2Ftaylor-swift-concert-tickets%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://playtimetix.com/concert-tickets/taylor-swift-concert-tickets/&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fplaytimetix.com%2Fconcert-tickets%2Fselena-gomez-tickets%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://playtimetix.com/concert-tickets/selena-gomez-tickets/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>