<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a6ba9e232d2409148d6bf1a1454592e5">			Dominican Republic is an island that has got the best features for your holiday. For instance, the accommodation facilities such as hotels are second to none when it comes to comfort. Apart from that, the population of the Dominican Republic is so friendly and always welcoming. More so, this island has got the best beaches and experiences regular festive seasons across the year. The presence of the Dominican Republic villas for rent makes it very convenient to take a holiday on this island. This is why most people prefer to take Caribbean holidays in this republic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;However, for you to enjoy the luxurious holiday, you have to consider a few things. First, you need to understand that people within this island use Spanish as their main language. However, we have some who speak English. This does not guarantee that you will be meeting the English speakers at your destination. It is therefore important to carry with you an English-Spanish dictionary. Definitely, with such a language guide your chances of exciting interaction with the lovely Dominicans are maximized.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prior to taking Caribbean holidays within the Dominican Republic, it is wise for you to equip yourself with the Dominican holiday calendar. Despite the fact that most holidays are celebrated, we have those that are well celebrated compared to others. For instance, the month of February is the most celebrated one as it is the time when the whole country celebrates the Carnival. Sunday afternoons are the moments when the highlights of the event are done throughout the country. More so, every town within this island has its own time of Carnival celebrations apart from the Sunday afternoon island Carnival. Therefore, knowing times of such events enables you select the best time to take your holidays in Dominican Republic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A few things must be noted about your health when planning to visit the Dominican Republic for a holiday. It is a fact that this republic has got no real summer or real winter. Basically, the sun is there throughout the year. By consequent, you have to carry with you sun repellent lotions. Apart from that, this island has got seasons when mosquitoes are common. To avert cases of malaria infection you need to arm yourself with insect repellents.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lastly, it is so important to know about the climatic conditions of this place. There are two main seasons that you must bear in mind. We have the hurricanes period which runs from June to November. The other one involves times when temperatures are quite high. Therefore, if you abhor such conditions then you have to do proper timing to avoid them while planning for a vacation in this island.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaW1wbHljYXJpYmUuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Caribbean Holidays&lt;/a&gt;; or &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zaW1wbHljYXJpYmUuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Dominican Republic villas for rent&lt;/a&gt;;, then make sure to visit us!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>