<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="51d813e0f926606e814d760c2dce0f01">			&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/179334484_2838770_46776537.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;Any dog owner will know that all pet dogs hate to be left on their own and let’s face it we all need to get out once in a while and do something other than dog walking Thanks to the new &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbmltYWxzb3VyY2UuY28udWsvZG9nLWJpa2UtYmFza2V0cy0tZG9nLWJpa2UtY2FycmllcnMtMzE4LWMuYXNw" target="_blank"&gt;;dog bike basket&lt;/a&gt;; you can now hop on your bike with your dog in the front or back. These new pet carriers are no longer the unsafe, wicker baskets they once were when the first came out. The first designs were terribly difficult to attach and detach from the bike, easy for the animal to escape from and far too uncomfortable for our companions.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These newly invented dog bike baskets are safe, durable, fashionable and most importantly they’re highly comfortable for our pampered pooches! Your dog will be the talk of the town as they happily jump on board and sit with you on those long summer bike rides. The handy bike carrier is also a useful tool making a trip to the vets seem a lot less daunting! The newer designs also include a safety strap, an important feature to stop dogs from jumping out.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hbmltYWxzb3VyY2UuY28udWsvaW5kZXguYXNw" target="_blank"&gt;;dog bike basket&lt;/a&gt;; is created with a hard wearing nylon material and can easily be safely attached to any bicycle. Unlike the older creations, the new dog bike basket is designed with a reinforced, sturdy frame and will last for years on end, making this unique carrier a brilliant investment for any pet owner. The dog bike basket is primarily designed for smaller breeds, however for the larger dog there is the dog bike trailer.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Again easily attachable to any bike and perfect for the injured and older dogs who still deserve to get out and about once in a while. Also just like the dog bike basket, the trailer is also available with reflective strips, enabling you to safety take your dog our during darker evenings. The dog bike trailer also transforms into a buggy, which may sound strange to some, but you wouldn’t believe how handy the dog buggy can be for taking your injured or older dog to the vets.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As with any new experience for your dog, bike rides may at first be a scary and confusing time for your fluffy companion, therefore it’s not advisable to go on a 5 mile bike ride on your dog’s first go. Ease your dog into this new experience by taking him on a short trip to the shops at first, then slowly increasing your journey length each time you go. Your dog will soon love their new adventure and let’s face it, as long as they’re with you they’ll always be happy!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>