<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e3ba661cfdaf7111ddcf7f03eb73e25c">			The medical Marijuana is also known as the medical pot. The Los Angeles medical marijuana is used in the treating some of the problems. Your marijuana is illegal throughout maximum countries. Although, in the United States federal government allows the citizens to get the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3NhbmdlbGVzbWFyaWp1YW5hZGlzcGVuc2FyeS5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;medical marijuana dispensary los angeles&lt;/a&gt;; from pot dispensaries in the Chicago. The citizens with the U.S. may take medical in more in comparison with 150 conditions until finally date.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fthepuffingtonhost.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2012%2F05%2FMedical-marijuana1.jpg"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://thepuffingtonhost.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/05/Medical-marijuana1.jpg&lt;/a&gt;;]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Clinical Uses of the Medical Marijuana&lt;br /&gt;;The supporters of the healthcare can argue for that benefits of the medical marijuana like vomiting, for the AIDS patients, queasiness and it can be used in numerous other complications. But about being an pain killer it is still a debated matter. There are different methods for the consumption of the particular medical marijuana, like it can be taken directly inside capsules. The other technique is taking it through process of vaporizing or cigarettes. The comparable study about which one on the methods of the consumption of the actual marijuana is effective was done by the National initiate of the health. According to the national institute from the health it is best to consider the medical marijuana in pills only. The medicinal marijuana which is given to this patients for the treatment methods are of very low amount. Also the usage of the actual marijuana for the fun purposes is strictly prohibited.&lt;br /&gt;;Recent Studies With regards to the medical Marijuana &lt;br /&gt;;According to the assertion of the US health Section in 1988 &quot;Nearly all of the medicines are having possibly lethal and harmful effects&quot;. But the marijuana will not be such a substance .In addition from the 1997 in order to 2005, zero deaths reported by the FDA (Food and Drugs association) due to the primary use of the marijuana. This marijuana is basically can be used in the treatment of the some complications nevertheless the marijuana can be very harmful for our health. This marijuana can lead to the different complications in the human body .The various complications which can be resolved due to the consumption of the of the medicinal marijuana are as follows&lt;br /&gt;;• Glaucoma&lt;br /&gt;;• Alzheimer's disease&lt;br /&gt;;• Spasticity in the multiple sclerosis&lt;br /&gt;;• Mental ailments&lt;br /&gt;;• Brain cancer&lt;br /&gt;;• Handling of ALS symptoms&lt;br /&gt;;• Lung cancer and chronic obstructive pulmonary disease&lt;br /&gt;;• Breast cancer&lt;br /&gt;;• Opioid dependency&lt;br /&gt;;• HIV / AIDS&lt;br /&gt;;These are some of the problems which can be treated by the Los Angeles Medical marijuana. It's been found that the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sb3NhbmdlbGVzbWFyaWp1YW5hZGlzcGVuc2FyeS5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;medical cannabis los angeles&lt;/a&gt;; has very positive effects on patients suffering from the depression in addition to mental disorders. &lt;br /&gt;;Even the marijuana is available on the marijuana dispensaries throughout Los Angeles. There is also the good criticism of pot by the people. To put it briefly we can say that the actual marijuana has their good and ill effects.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Related posts:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rpc3BlbnNhcnl0ODczLmJsb2d1ZXouY29tL2Rpc3BlbnNhcnl0ODczLzQ4ODQzMDYvTG9zLUFuZ2VsZXMtbWVkaWNhbC1tYXJpanVhbmE_" target="_blank"&gt;;Los Angeles medical marijuana&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4xMWFsaXZlLmNvbS9saWZlL2NvbW11bml0eS9wZXJzb25hLmFzcHg/VT03M2NlYTcwMDUzNzE0NTQ4YWU4ZWE5MTFhODdiOGFhMSZhbXA7cGxja1BlcnNvbmFQYWdlPUJsb2dWaWV3UG9zdCZhbXA7cGxja1VzZXJJZD03M2NlYTcwMDUzNzE0NTQ4YWU4ZWE5MTFhODdiOGFhMSZhbXA7cGxja1Bvc3RJZD1CbG9nJTNhNzNjZWE3MDA1MzcxNDU0OGFlOGVhOTExYTg3YjhhYTFQb3N0JTNhMTBkMTE1YmEtYWEwZC00NDMzLTk4NWItYjhmNjk4ZjBlMWRk" target="_blank"&gt;;Los Angeles medical marijuana&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>