<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="45a1abc78a9f869f155ab03a55c51cd9">			If you are searching for a way to get rid of the infection Smart HDD, which is blocking the work of your computer, there are a some things you have to know about this harmful rogue. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Smart HDD is found to be a false hard drive optimization app aimed at luring you into paying for its fraudulent services. Although Smart HDD uses a legitime layout, this evil creation of cyber criminals is not |made|coded|prepared} to repair your hard drive or detect hard drive errors. On the contrary, Smart HDD causes many problems and leans to slow Windows work and slow Internet connections.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you need to understand whether Smart HDD has managed to infect your operating system or not, just have a glance at the work of your computer. Do you see slow Internet speed? Are your Chrome settings modified? Are there minutes when you are not allowed to connect to the Internet? Do you start finding some documents on the Internet and then find yourself redirected at some shady and malicious web place? Well, if you see all of these signs on your PC, this is a visual sign that you have to check your system using a legit and legitimate application and check if Smart HDD is detected.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When the harmful program has managed to enter your computer, the malicious attacker start some scans of your system. This is done to scare you with the amount of reported hard drive errors and problems. Meanwhile, you must keep in mind that all the S.M.A.R.T.Check results are only evil tricks of Smart HDD. Threats found by this attacker have nothing to do with the actual health of your hard disk. In fact, Smart HDD is a deceitful and tricky malware aimed at fooling you into paying for its bogus full version.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Smart HDD deletes useful shortcuts from your Start Menu in order to make it impossible for you to start your work applications. Do not delete any files from your Temp folder because Smart HDD hides the icons of your software to this folder.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To do the situation even worse, Smart HDD will hide the documents of your folders. This will be done to scare you into thinking your documents have been broken and you have lost your documents. The truth is that Smart HDD has modified your Registry keys and this is only made to deceive you into believing Smart HDD will assist you to fix your Windows. Despite the fact that it looks like detecting issues with your everyday programs and notifies you that they cannot be initialized, do not be misled by these fake notifications. The warnings will tell you about these problems:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Windows cannot find Internet Explorer. &lt;br /&gt;;Make sure you spelled the name correctly, and then try again. &lt;br /&gt;;To search for a document, click the Start button, and then choose Search. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Know that Smart HDD is a malevolent software that will steal your savings. Do not be misled and take serious actions. Buy a genuine antivirus application to scan your PC and detect Smart HDD. Then, get rid of it, as well as many evil files it has created. To keep safe your system in future, use a real security application. Also, keep your programs up-to-date. This is important in order to stop harmful apps from getting advantage from security holes in older versions of your programs. Last, but not least, do not browse doubtful web sites and do not download or install unknown applications or updates.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Original article: &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aWtpLmNvbS9lbi9tZWxpc3NhLWFkYW1zLTErMTEwOTY1Ny9wb3N0L1N0YXktU2FmZS1Gcm9tLSsxNDMwNzkwNw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Watch Out For Phony HDD Scan Application&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>