<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2737af4a488f76c5b1a0263f40972e9f">			What You Need To Know When Planning To Buy Or Sell A Business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When buying a business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must know a lot of things when you are planning to buy a business.  People would basically favor buying a business than start to build a new one. This is also preferred by most new comers in the business arena. The setup a base that you can build on like customer base, recruiting employees, working on a lease is already being done for you by someone when you opt to buy a business. Do not think though that you can get everything that easily and no work is required from your side. You must make sure that you get what you need and this can only be possible when you do some research.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In choosing a business, it is dangerous to go for something you are not familiar with, so better look for a business that you have experience in the past or have enough technical know-how or the industry in which your education was based on or based on your hobby. When you have no idea or knowledge on those industries in which you are trying to buy a business of course greater chances of spending more money may be encountered.  In the end you get to realize it was unreasonable to buy that kind of business. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You may also want to go for a business that thrills you. This is because success is easier to achieve when you are doing what you love best, likewise in business matters. &lt;br /&gt;When you sell your business&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Do you have plans of selling a business? If yes, then read on to the following steps to help you be more successful in your selling career.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;1. Make sure the price range is reasonable and realistic: Take note that too highly expensive prices may not interest any buyer while too low prices may not benefit you at all.  The business must be just worth according to its real value.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;2. The tax implications must be well understood: These tax implications may be a threat to your sale income thus it must be considered all the time. You can ask the help of an auditor to assess the tax implications.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;3. How to make a business marketable: Your premises are not your only concern to make your business marketable but also your numbers in your balance sheet or profit &amp; loss accounts.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;4. Where to look for the probable buyers: Reaching to a wider audience is needed when you know that your business is not that well-known, otherwise, you just have to spread the news when the business is already popular. There is also a business broker to do this for you.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;5. The deal agreement: This is the most crucial step in selling since this will basically tell you how good or bad the deal you made was for you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;6. Authorize a Sale deed: What can you see in a sale deed? Among all things, it also has to have an exhaustive list of things you are selling and the price and the payment terms that the buyer has to adhere to.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;7. Finalizing and closing the agreement: The deal will be closed finally after it has been agreed upon by both parties and there will be a closing meeting in which you hand over the business to your buyer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbuyingbusiness.blogspot.com%2F2011%2F09%2Fyour-detailed-guide-in-buying-or.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://buyingbusiness.blogspot.com/2011/09/your-detailed-guide-in-buying-or.html&lt;/a&gt;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fbuyingbusiness.blogspot.com%2F2011%2F09%2Fconnection-between-selling-owner-and.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://buyingbusiness.blogspot.com/2011/09/connection-between-selling-owner-and.html&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>