<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d33ae24451ba26c35823a5ccf480f16f">			When it is about pulling in an income on the Internet, the Internet Marketing niche, more than any other, is immediately affected by the ongoing technological advancements. Until recently, virtually all sales letters were chiefly made up of formatted text. These days, what we see are state-of-the-art graphics packages combined with top-level copywriting. An even more recent type of sales letter is the video sales letter. As you can tell, it's not hard to be left in the dust by these types of advances. Growing public awareness of these evolving techniques makes our lives as internet marketers even more difficult , as the regular person clicks away as soon as he realizes he's reading a sales letter. Fortunately, there's another new sales technique that's working really well to boost conversions these days - the &quot;webinar&quot;, our subject here.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;We all know that getting people to trust you and feel comfortable with your advice is crucial to your success online. As all marketing niches become more and more packed with people offering products that fail to live up to their promises, that important element of trust is a lot harder to get. The issue is, how can those of us who take pride in selling sound products of real value be heard amidst all the dishonesty and junk? This is where webinars come in. For many of us, webinars have become our most dependable sales tool. A webinar is essentially an invitation-only online seminar or presentation put on by a product seller or one of their affiliates.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you've already been to a webinar, you are aware that it was scheduled for a certain day and time, and it was live. The format usually takes the form of disclosing valuable information that shows that the person presenting is knowledgeable and trustworthy. Some webinars have more than one individual sharing the presentation duties based on their individual expertise and knowledge. Once the presenter has demonstrated his expertise and earned your trust, you can expect some kind of special offer near the end of the webinar.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Scheduling a time for a webinar can be difficult because you may be dealing with attendees from all parts the world. Although it is okay to schedule more than one run through of a webinar, most presenters simply record the session and then make it available to anyone at any time. But then, since you'd really want that most people be present during the original webinar, it's common practice to offer something more, something special, to those who actually attend the live event. Encouraging individuals who are unable to make it to the live presentation to view it later is new to the webinar arena. One other fine aspect of recording your webinar is that it can be run and rerun any time you want, as much as you want, with no extra work on your part. This also lets you do away with or take care of any bugs or mistakes that may take place during the live presentation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is no doubt that webinars are an invaluable tool for any internet marketer, and if you take the time to understand the technology, you can look forward to more sales and conversions.		</conversation>		<conversation id="b001c79225b194cba6b2d2ecfbd25408">			In recent years, the number of road mishaps including heavy-duty trucks is significantly higher. We don't talk about heavy-duty trucks as those small-scale pick-up trucks but those scary 18-wheelers.  Though the reasons for the mishaps occurring vary, most of the time they are caused by the truck drivers.  However, in the face of causing these accidents,  the truck drivers seldom get hurt because of the tough construction of these 18-wheelers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A severe accident of this type might consist of several small cars, injuries, and even the death of some other drivers. If you want to avoid these types of accidents, you probably need to get good at defensive driving. The sad part is, in truck driving school, they are only trained how to drive fast, and completely pay no attention to the concept of safe driving. You must make an attempt to study defensive driving by yourself. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many people believe that driving a truck is just like driving a sedan. Although they both actually do the same things, they are two very different vehicles. A smaller truck involves less attention, the maneuverability is higher and even the crashes involving small cars are less dangerous. You are able to just imagine the difference by trying to park a truck as opposed to trying to park a car.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A significant number of mishaps involving trucks originate from tiredness. Even though the moving companies are obliged to give decent transport times, (the company must allow 3 days for a 1500 kilometers transport in some countries), the drivers rather stay at their homes for one or two days, and then they would try to catch up in the last day. Driving for twenty four hours is not trouble-free at all possibly even for the most experienced driver. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The more productive transport companies are actually installing GPS in the trucks in order to avoid these types of scenarios. When using the GPS, the outfits can keep track of how far a driver has driven over a period of time. Even though upfront cost is high, it will be of special benefit in the long term. One thing is that the cost of being in an accident is going to be avoided. In addition, people will view your company as respectable in making the effort to ensure safety and reliability. Third, the expense with insurances will be lowered, as an insurance company would have to take fewer risks if your trucks have GPS installed. In reality, a lot of insurance companies will suggest a unique package with special advanced services for all your trucks.     &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In some cases, the drivers would rather take their truck driver's license directly without doing the instruction for smaller cars. Though this does not occur regularly, it does happen. Even so, it is better to take the traditional method: take your license for driving small and medium cars, and get to the big cars later. That way you have got a strong concept of the basics which will help you become a safe truck driver.  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.squidoo.com%2Fbrothersewingmachinecom"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.squidoo.com/brothersewingmachinecom&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>