<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e2a0c03b6dd6a32f338149aa04745060">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhaWZsYXRpcm9uai5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;HAI flat iron&lt;/a&gt;; come in a variety of styles for customers who like quality, performance, and style. You can go online to choose the many HAI flat irons and professional hair maintenance systems made by HAI. Fashionable hair doesn't have to be created in the beauty salon. You can have magazine hair today which has a HAI Classic hair styling iron. Impress your friends which has a new, straight style and find your HAI flat iron today.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Simply plug it in before you decide to jump in the shower, and it will get nice and hot whenever you get out. The technology involved is pretty sophisticated precisely as it dries your hair the same time that it straightens that. This one aspect totally eliminates that hair dryer from your life. Additionally, it uses steam hydration therapy to keep hairs conditioned during practise. It's fast and nice hair will stay straight the entire day.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hai has been making cutting edge personal maintenance systems for over 70 years, so when they entered the Hai flat iron fray, we were looking at going to make waves because of all the time they put inside research and development. There are actually expensive flat irons, together with what everybody considers the cheaper counterparts. Can we really go the whole day which has no frizz?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Yes, it's with the Shine Therapy Hai flat iron. When frizz, heat and humidity are your primary enemies, after that get this tool to help you fight and win that battle. This iron is manufactured to straighten your hair while making it resistant to most moist conditions. A specialized feature is that the ceramic plates are infused which has a blend of conditioners together with avocado oil. The plates can heat up to 430 degrees, that's on par with more expensive models. In addition, it has a digital screen and beeps when it reaches the desired temperature.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hai Drenched 2 Straight&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are someone who is always pretty quickly to get in the shower and out of the shower, dressed and ready to head out the entry within 60 minutes, you don't really have time to waste on straightening nice hair. But, you're also sick and tired with always having to be happy with your naturally wavy or even curly look just because you have a time crunch. Luckily, being dressed in perfectly straight hair each day won't be out of ones reach. Your Wet 2 Straight Hai flat iron is made for people like you who need to get their hair straightened within a few minutes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If the words &quot;thick, stubborn and curly&quot; describe your hair type, then you're in dire need on the Hai flat iron to achieve top temperatures for perfectly straight hair super fast.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Titanium is a naturally strong element well known for its fast performance, durability, light weight and powerful heating. Other brands that are recognized for their &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhaWZsYXRpcm9uODkwLnR1bWJsci5jb20vcG9zdC8xNTU3NTQwODgyNy9oYWktZmxhdC1pcm9uLWZvci1lYXN5LXByb2Zlc3Npb25hbC1oYWlyLXN0cmlnaHRlbmluZw__" target="_blank"&gt;;best flat iron&lt;/a&gt;; are BaByliss PRO, Scorching Tools, and, FHI, HAI.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>