<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2f9696d0bcd02dc905acf6ac956b327e">			 I say:&quot;;Line, you call I old.Everyone call so I, I start to listen to more benignity.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;My Mei wear conscience &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;runescape power leveling&lt;/a&gt; to say.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;For let she not entertain foolish ideas, I hug her into a bosom, she without extra trouble take I the smoke in the mouth, absorbed an one mouthful, then flicked a window open outside, I be just prepare to say waste, her mouth give I come up, get bogged down in intense emotion fire of arouse to kiss, the common saying say have no before the bed of arouse to kiss where come to bed up of vacillating, in clear and ordered patternly did underneath of matter, she don't let me take a set and say that only meeting guest just take, oneself the person never mind and also say.Stop worrying, the inside be clean.Intense emotion later on, she according to Wei in my bosom.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She say:&quot;;I also very the surprise be how can you, hope you don't want suspicion I be dirty, this may be in the clout destine of, can't, you accept!You don't know us to do that line of of person.In fact the heart is also very lonesome, the nobody see we.&quot;;Say pair of Lan in my the hand on the waist tight tight, be like afraid lose me similar, if, I say if she isn't a chicken, I very gladly accept, then with she continue bottom to go to, I comfort she say&quot;; together is the person who look for a mind to consign.&quot;;Looking at her mouth side light smiling face, I is sympathize with or commiseration, still keep substituting her to feel sorry for, how 1 thoroughly the Ao Di be refit a Mr. hand over, her things of the past I also want to interfere with.I also don't want to know.Tell the truth, little orchid, don't should call Ting Ting, grow to have delicate looks can top 80 cent, just for the sake of work wear have to have much of Sao flavor.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Someone say that seeking a chicken do girl friend etc. own a small treasury at the same time, but I didn't consider as a money tree of Ting Tings, she knew me to work, usually buy clothes for me, after with she together, I had no oneself to spend money to once have a meal, don't know her is for the sake of from the money enslave I, let I ability real with she association.Or really think good to me, she said in silently paying for me, maying be my mouth that abandon her, let her feel life pretty meaningful.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;No matter how it is, this day still have to lead, slowly day already arrive La month, also quick New Year's Day, daddy's mama make a phone call to call I go home New Year's Day, I did it ever don't want to return, I hope I go home of when the time be glorious homecoming, give parents a physical life for satisfy, can I now food and clothing's being basic be all Ting Ting give mine.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Old Chen, fish P, Pan total also say that prepare go home New Year's Day, next year not know to return come not come to north Pei, everyone the second day all want to walk, evening drink an inebriate square rest, see the brotherses all want separate, look back this a few months to get along with of point intravenous drop drop, world all spread of dinner party, say everyone to raise wine cup, you wish me to congratulate on become rich, I wish your business Teng to fly, Pan total say us return would come back of, end again ask me to walk not to walk, I say me not to know, I not know me how plan of.The big hall ridden dragon chafing dish manager, lift 4 bottles of wine to say hello us to drink good, and wish us all the way walk good, this words listen to pout, but see lift 4 bottles of beer at him and we also didn't say what.Just so of the person also can make a manager, no wonder that we not seek a work.
&lt;br /&gt;Chapter 4:Saw a snow in 2006 again.
&lt;br /&gt;  The second day big early see them excitement of favour inside favour outside, move house, cent property.Pan is total to say old Chen's pants to return me, old explain you pair of socks return I, old Pan took off the socks on the feet to throw give old Chen.They walk the Ting Ting is behind to I continuous handed over the rent of a quarter degree, she also moved to come in and say convenience care I, want also stand the sign be logical.I now heel a have soft rice of about, I return ability say what?From the time I and the naturally of Ting Ting led top real of two human life boundary.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Haven't get to the Internet for a long time.The Ting Ting hasn't get up, I be alone more and more lonesome, walked into a net cafe to sit top to sit that set computer for three years, this time already have no in the past of excitement, the game be also in no mind, in the QQs of the class make once, everyone at complain, eat green grass to milk a cow, stem much take little, this all just top several class of month, how so complain, second half generation son still have to, what I rejoice be me now didn't°yet so of annoyance.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Work earn money, then spend money, such circulation, life definite have no new meaning, I have been look forward to of life is seek work at least enter inside produce stratum, otherwise oneself open what company, lead top to occupy secretary stem, have no matter stem secretary of the wave concuss life and see the classmates of annoyance, I dare not to find work, I don't want to need an industry, I also very look forward to have work of person, everyday on time go to work on time go off work, time all arrangement have to have much of regulation, need not be like me to usually miss me underneath should do what for a minute.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Let us start to concuss a double syrup, the boat son push away a wave.......&quot;;Cellular phone ring pulled me from the infinite disappointed thoughts and feelings back, Ting Ting dozen come of, asked me to go over there, she still smiled my 20 several people. still do a bell ring with the nursery rhyme, immature, I say you not to understand this call still preserve traces of childishness, think of past, though that time drive usually parents KO, that time vexed at least, flesh of pain would disappear, thought of the burden want to carry on the back lifetime.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Remind of parents, I want to return to see them very much, the text of Yan Wei of(mother) don't be to sing, &quot;;your body is in that other place and someone be concern about......&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Return to a house, I say me to want to go home and see, had a little homesick, the Ting Ting say that wanting return and then return, you again have no drive tie, I excitement once(because of she openings give me travel expenses), the Ting Ting say that want return with me together, may is afraid I later not come, I think all right, in case of my parents want to bind me in the home, I also have a shield.Then give home dozen telephone, I say me over come back for two days, just have no Zheng to money, in fact is basically didn't go to Zheng, telephone that say&quot;;money can later Zheng, want ?only Human body body good, so-so Anne Anne of ratio what all good.&quot;;Hear parents of generous, I can not help eye socket moist, wretchedness the world parents' heart!
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Winter of the temperature let person suffocate, but don't influence everyone to New Year's Day of enthusiasm, be full of everywhere festival of atmosphere, New Year's Day have what good, I now again have no New Year's Money, meeting face top long crease, and annoyance more and more, if probably pair of time congelation, I hope time stop at I big an of time, innocently all embrace to have to everything the most beautiful and good of imagination.After all this be the Arabian Nights, have to face the realities.The child in the city also play firecrackers, small of that kind of, play big of seem to be forbidden, hear sparse&quot;;Mao Mao Mao&quot;; me know right away will New Year's Day.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ting Ting bought a ticket, how many hours of jolt, the Ting Ting say you to all live of where?In addition to a mountain be still a mountain, I say heavy celebrate original be a mountain city, don't you know?See parents.The parents say me to become fat, I say parents again many grey hair, the Ting Ting pass to lift to take for my mother's a hand and say uncle aunt's happy new year.Need not I say, the parents should also know me with her relation, 2 before the month kill me can't believe with the Ting Ting walk so near, besides still brought back a house, evening the father ask me, she old house there of, do the parents know?I am a burst of to evasive answers past, the old daddy say you again to be one person's a building or?I say need not one person's 1, 1 enough, province we walk behind.Mama wash so many bed sheet, the old daddy also knew our development to arrive what extent and then from the drawer inside touch a set son to me, say that getting married can't harm a somebody else, my in the mind steal to smile, I took it to take advantage o father's inattention to still come out a window outside.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The second day, the place which took Ting Ting to go to my childhood frolic relate me past of childhood interesting news, a mountain be still that mountain, water be still that water, be just that the person changed.Becoming to have no will to fight, becoming myself all can't understanding oneself, I say to the Ting Ting, celebrated the New Year, I will go heavy celebrate earnest of seek work, I can't continue to play bottom go to, don't let the parents worry for me, I say Ting Ting, you also turn line, she say me what all can't.What can I make?Want the culture has no culture.I say you to do restaurant attendant, the Ting Ting say that how many moneys enough meet expenses fart, you naturally, I now also don't want to turn and wait me again do a period of time earn enough I accept a hand, depend, someone earn enough money of?
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is me a time quarrel with her, I origin think her meeting is I change, similarly was lure by the money of person, just establishment of some will to fight, is bury at deeply of earth.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At the home, I went out, I don't like to be asked this by the other people to ask that, home town relatives acquaintance many, and a lot of is all elder of concern, not answer ill-mannered, usually a problem want to answer within a day some times, this year of the Chinese New Year seemed to lack than the past what, still many what.I thought along while to also don't want to come up.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Foolish at home three day, the everyday soul occupy to give up of appearance.The parents are afraid I suppress a disease and call I breakfast return heavy celebrate to find work, the Ting Ting also start suffer from vomiting and diarrhea, I think to be to win a prize, and win a prize should can't have loose bowels, either.The parents say that is a not acclimatized, I just let go of heart and parents' knowing us be the house which rent by ourselves.The time faced to walk filled to us a pack soil special product, say outside what all want money, economy point.The time old daddy whom the past go to school say province point to spend money, I still put blame on him at that time stingy, now just know parents of concern and consideration is have no place not at.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The time faced to get on the car, the parents be a red envelope for Ting Ting, I don't know is how much , instruct her to eat point nutritive thing more, all thin heel bean sprout about, return call I good care she, the Ting Ting say what all don't , glower Jing to looking at me, I said with you is parents of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;runescape accounts&lt;/a&gt;intention.Ting Ting pair of money Chuai is in the Dou, this may is the income of Ting Ting most easy of once.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Looking at a quilt far far jilt after car of parents of figure, have kind unspeakable taste in the heart, I said all the person of 20 quite a fews, New Year's Money, press to all press not to live
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;New Year's Day new atmosphere, new results, the movie star clapped a new film, singer's new album, they is also for the sake of life dig hollow think of take out a fan like of the note is really a following upon success or failure and do what all have pressure, I don't know me to when become so touchy-feely.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Today big beginning of year three, the company openned the door.Don't say that seek a work.Give respectively fish P, Pan be total, old Chen2 Da3 telephone, wish once happy new year!Ask him the New Year's Day have what new plan, fish P say him to fix to go study C language, again advanced learn good be the black guest be black strength dance regiment that lousy game.I say my support you.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The net cafe also didn't open the door and make was like world to forget me, the Ting Ting also still put New Year holidays, unique of amusement way be with Ting Ting dozen poker with make love, dozen the poker lost to drink, original is to say that losing take off clothes, big New Year's Day of I don't want to do a sick personnel, be I drink to arrive 3 bottle of time feel have a little dizzy and giddy, past at least is also 4 bottle, would have so of symptom, take alcohol us pair of unique of amusement way conjunction at together, finished empress.My lie prone doesn't know at that drive how much person petting lead of double Feng up, say me how to should do, the life be boundless long have no road, I say me to really need to find work.She has no facial expression and be like her so of person, should also the nothing important action be just normal, I say me impossible so of make a living, I be invigorate.She say that that you encourage.My support you, be like similar male on the bed, live and then live a personal kind, later etc. you be rich to keep me, I not stem this line of.After all who also not hope oneself like of the person be that one is coward.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I know me to have no a result with Ting Ting, I not is care she isn't a virgin and marry a wife and be like to buy a washer.The key see province not province electricity.Be like her so, spend money to be like flowing water, I an ability with most month wages buy a bottle of perfume for her.Though I know is so of result, I still very selfishly coax her happy, because my economy the source be her, she also has been use money a captive my heart, with what can not pass.Can't can not pass with money, either.
&lt;br /&gt;Chapter 5:Want to work for the sake of life everyone(a)
&lt;br /&gt;  A week after, the Ting Ting went to work, the home leave my[one] person, a person in addition to get to the Internet, I true can not find still is other what matter do, only this time get to the Internet I be to do to seek job form, open all of the QQ is wish of message, old Chen also at, hair information give he, the along while also didn't see response, wanting him should is play legend, didn't again bother him, seek job there is one column on the form, special features, I don't know to fill what good, because in addition to that words son I really have no special features, impossible write a private parts, wanted to want to write an AU(be a strength dance regiment of brief name), I again wrote a resume oneself Han2 Chen2, XX university Chinese fasten undergraduate course graduate student, 1990 join little first brigade, 1998 join China total green regiment, 2002 join Communist Party of China, but grant, 2006 finish university.Finish write later again feel have a little walk same old things road, change, last year finish university, up to now need an industry, spark dynasty God door, fierce take out an one mouthful, this also calculate I seek job road top to exceed the square one of .
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Connect down the job advertisement meeting, talented person's market which then run everywhere for several days, the Ting Ting know me to seek work.Also do not worry me, incredibly in the place some times of dissimilarity meet a school together dissimilarity fasten of alumni, I remember that having 1 is Liu2 Zhi4 Qing of, he say now seek work is exactly an inning, just celebrated the New Year.A lot of company all lack hand, they gave me the exchanges to once seek job insight and say data top in addition to name and educational background outside.Otherly and all can exaggerative its phrase, return and say them to like to listen to of words.Sing them like to listen to of song, my depending this is to choose a talented person there, heel choose slave about.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I this just remind of.I didn't°yet graduation certificate, no wonder that had several my hurl the company of resume all Yao have no news, disappeared.Too honesty, honesty now how at society is also a kind of mistake.Don'ting know this is society of progress still retrogress.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I come back from walk.Want to see an electric wire post on road top to have to stick an advertisement, the urban landscape be pretty quite good and incredibly walked for 2 hours.I didn't see 1, suppressed the urine of the one urine bladder, sought Mr. Ci and if it weren't for true can not contain any more.I prefer to suppress to go home, what to see a toilet be an old man and I was direct to flee to go in.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Hey Hey Hey, give first money.&quot;;The old man say.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I say&quot;;I ain't true line.Wait me went first.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He firmly say&quot;;not line.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;He say again:&quot;;Top big still top small, top big a cake of send a pack paper.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I say:&quot;;I top small.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;That five Capes.&quot;;Then threw a steel Mao to him, if later have no one to turn to.I also open a Mr. Ci and at least still sit to transact of work.Write a placard up big 10 pieceses, top small 5 pieces.As long as you suppress live, you suppress.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Just at hiss hiss, good boy, inside in the toilet stick full cure a sexually transmitted disease (STD), gonorrhea, do a certificate of advertisement.The telephone which connect to seek a young lady all has.I seek you so bitterness, pleased top tip of brow.This advertisement stick a toilet not bad.The inside of the toilet do dirty of trade, very the sign be logical.Copied a few telephone number.I am just want and don't copy a telephone which cure a sexually transmitted disease to return for Ting Ting, in order to prevent in the days to come demand, can not seek.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The side walk side dozen lately- copy telephone, the other party be the women of a river south accent and ask me to want what, educational background, undergraduate course, graduate student, Doctor, ID card, passport, what can do.I say all what price.She say an undergraduate course cheapness point 200, graduate student 400, Doctor 800......., End say besides a sentence, absolute heel really similar.I say that whole cheapness point of, undergraduate course, she after saying &quot;;medium.&quot;; haggle 105 clinch a deal, tomorrow take my data for her and hand over 50 security deposits.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Ting Ting return in the sleeping because of be on night shift, I make a phone call to ask Pan total want to don't do 1, he say calculate.Don't want to seek a work.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I went to according to appointment of place, etc. the old along while also don't see person and put my pigeon son.Looking at everywhere cigarette butt, positive dispirited and discouraged, the inside of the lane son flee since the childhood one inside year women, beckon with the hand toward me, I turned quite a few lane son with her,
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She just stop bottom to say:&quot;;Recent do certificate high peak period, the business be better and have a little favour, so information also have a little tight, caution the point be good.&quot;;Pair of the whole explaination clear after.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She ask me:&quot;;Want don't English four class certificates, undergraduate course graduation certificate+English four class certificates add to collect 50 piece cost fee and do to want 100 piece per alone.&quot;;My meaning to say me very much is because of DOing not finish an industry to just do.I am still an university culture and thoughted bottom to say with her also useless.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I say:&quot;;Not demand, I have.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She say:&quot;;Six classes want don't .&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I say:&quot;;Don't , I this level be one openings, know is what cage the inside of the son fly out of bird.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She say:&quot;;That win, tomorrow this time the right here take thing.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;She turned round to walk and I said an etc..She think I still want to do what certificate, run very fast back again, I say you take me to go out.I don't know road, you are like maze here, she say that do be this line of original will so.Then took me to lane son, turn round to drill again into maze.This his mama all what morals of the world.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Return to a house all an afternoon 3:00, favour several day, I all feel very tired by myself, but tired get it.Worry to haven't been oppress to can not stand up for the physical strength in the meantime, later of slave life how lead.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The restaurant hasn't arrived to start to eat of time, the Ting Ting shoulded also get up, make a telephone call to ask her to get to the Internet not, she falter I along while, I listen to none understand and she probably hasn't wake up and after all she be a manual labor, is pretty tired.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sit meeting son a net cafe to see talented person's net to have what the post suit me fine.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Owner in the net cafe say:&quot;;Small hasn't found work Suo.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I say:&quot;;BE seek, now work not seek.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The owner say:&quot;;Encourage.I see you play games so severe, should nothing important problem.&quot;;Play games heel seek a work relevant fasten?That later everyone need not study direct get to the Internet play game calculate.My doing not know an owner is still in the Kua my cleverness to belittle my then can.Said again that seek a work and play games to be like chemisette chest &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ydW5lc2NhcGVhY2NvdW50cy5vcmcv" target="_blank"&gt;runescape gold&lt;/a&gt; and brain of relation, root be two code matters.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;certainly smiled, this several years I have never given you less investment.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;Mo worried do it slowly, play to admire together for a long time, I good think of several brothers&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I say:&quot;;Good, you come, at school of, I ask you to drink.&quot;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>