<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="23b883aa8c285b4603cead6474b03c2f">			Couple triumph more than By CO Poisoning 
&lt;br /&gt;Fire officials in Prince George's County are urging residents without any
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;vitality to carry out it safe.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Their warning follows a carbon monoxide publicity (CO) scenario within of the
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Fairmount Heights residence that lost vitality pursuing the storm.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Prince George's County Fire/EMS spokesman Mark Brady stated somebody within of
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the residence although from the 1300 avoid of Doewood Lane named 911 at about
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;10:00 am Thursday. Firefighters determined the couple, every single inside of
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;their mid 50's are actually struggling with CO poisoning. They experienced been
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;producing use of the gasoline generator inside of their residence to vitality
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;their electrical appliances. The female was found unconscious as well as the
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;male was disoriented. They are actually hospitalized and for that reason are
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;enhancing Thursday night.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The consumer product safety Commission warns in opposition to producing
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;utilization of cellular generators in enclosed spaces attributed towards the
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;actuality they are in a placement to start CO. 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;ShuangHao is professional manufacturer of generator, diesel generator,gasoline generator,diesel engine,gasoline engine,Diesel water pump,Gasoline water pump,Wearing parts and related products. we are famous manufacturer specializing in developing, producing and selling of engines and other machinery. It produces more than 50, 000 engines annually, and the foreign currency reaches 5 million US dollars, the saleroom reaches 40million RMB.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;CO is named the &quot;;invisible
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;killer&quot;; attributed towards the actuality it is surely an odorless, colorless and
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;poisonous gas.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Snow-related outages are also believed for getting linked to four house fires
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;although from the county overnight.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In two using the fires, an unattended candle and an unattended fireplace are
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;actually to blame. Fire officials are even now investigating the induce using
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the other two, but stated they are actually probable preventable. The division
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;provides these recommendations for residents all through vitality outages.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Use a battery-powered flashlight for emergency lighting.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Never use candles for illumination.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Turn aside electrical items you are actually producing utilization of as
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;shortly as the vitality went out.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Avoid opening the refrigerator and freezer.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Do not run a generator inside of a residence or garage.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;- Be good to turn the generator aside and permit it awesome minimizing preceding
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to refueling. Gasoline spilled on cozy powerplant elements could ignite.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Ensure you have refreshing batteries within your radio, and be prepared to stay
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;informed if a vitality outage occurs.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;-Before a vitality outage occurs, listen to online community stereo and
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;television established for updated information
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Residents are also stimulate to discover shelter within of the warming center.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The division of Parks and Recreation for Prince George's County has opened the
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Wayne K. Curry sports activities actions and studying Complex, situated at 8001
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Sheriff route in Landover, MD. Residents in call for and without any vitality
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;may go there and discover shelter. The county will probable be providing bottled
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;water.		</conversation>		<conversation id="84828aa0a2edb2cd95c6d028c0b8c6de">			Quantum Quirk: JILA researchers Pack Atoms jointly to refrain from Collisions in 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Atomic Clock
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;BOULDER, Colo.-In a paradox ordinary using the quantum world, JILA researchers 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;have eliminated collisions amongst atoms in an atomic clock by packing the atoms 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;closer together. The surprising discovery, described within your Feb. 3 scenario 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;of Science Express,* can boost the productivity of experimental atomic clocks 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;created of hundreds or tens of the big quantity of neutral atoms trapped by 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;intersecting laser beams.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JILA is jointly operated via the nation broad Institute of specifications and 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;modern advances (NIST) as nicely since the university of Colorado Boulder.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;JILA researchers demonstrated the brand name new tactic generating utilization 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;of their experimental clock created of about 4,000 strontium atoms. as opposed 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;to loading the atoms in to some stack of pancake-shaped optical traps as inside 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;of their earlier work, researchers packed the atoms right into a big quantity of 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;horizontal optical tubes. The end result was a added than tenfold improvement in 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;clock productivity given that the atoms interacted so strongly that, versus all 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;odds, they halted hitting just about every solitary other. The atoms, which 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;often favor to hang out separately and relaxed, get so perturbed from obtaining 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;forced close to jointly the truth that ensemble is effectively frozen in place.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;;The atoms utilized to possess the whole dance flooring to proceed near to on 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;and now they are confined in alleys, so the interaction vitality goes way up,&quot;; 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;says NIST/JILA Fellow Jun Ye, mind using the experimental team.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How particularly does big interaction energy-the degree to which an atom's carry 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;out is modified via the presence of others-prevent collisions? The last final 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;results make whole impression within your quantum world. Strontium atoms 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;definitely really are a program of particles recognized as fermions. If they are 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;in identical vitality states, they cannot occupy the identical place in the 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;identical time-that is, they cannot collide. often the laser beam utilized to 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;operate the clock interacts making use of the atoms unevenly, leaving the atoms 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;dissimilar adequate to collide.** nevertheless the interaction vitality of atoms 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;packed in optical tubes is now multiplied than any vitality shifts that may well 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;be brought on through the laser, stopping the atoms from differentiating 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;adequate to collide.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The idea was proposed by JILA theorist Ana Maria Rey and demonstrated within 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;your lab by Ye's group.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Given the brand name new knowledge, Ye believes his clock as properly as other 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;persons dependent on neutral atoms will occur to get aggressive in disorders of 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;reliability with world-leading experimental clocks dependent on main ions 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(electrically charged atoms). The JILA strontium clock is at existing among the 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;perfect executing experimental clock dependent on neutral atoms and, 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;collectively with many NIST ion and neutral atom clocks, a feasible prospect for 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;just about any lengthy phrase worldwide time standard. The products provide very 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;proper time by measuring oscillations (which serve as &quot;;ticks&quot;&lt;img class="smiley" src="http://www.pan.net/smilies/wink.gif" alt=":)" /&gt; amongst the 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;vitality quantities within your atoms.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In add-on to stopping collisions, the acquiring also signifies the truth that 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;added atoms within your clock, the better. &quot;;As atom quantities increase, equally 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;measurement reliability and reliability enhance accordingly,&quot;; Ye says.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To trap the atoms in optical tubes, researchers key use blue and red-colored 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;lasers to awesome strontium atoms to about several of microKelvin in your trap 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;that utilizes mild and magnetic fields. A vertical lattice of mild waves is 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;created generating utilization of an infrared laser beam that spans and traps 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;the atom cloud. Then a horizontal infrared laser beam is turned on, generating 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;optical tube traps in your intersection making use of the vertical laser.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The evaluation was supported via the Defense superior evaluation projects firm 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(grant administered via the Army evaluation Office), NIST, nation broad Science 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Foundation, and oxygen Force company business office for healthcare Research.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a non-regulatory agency, NIST promotes U.S. innovation and industrial 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;competitiveness by advancing measurement science, specifications and modern 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;advances in procedures that enhance fiscal security and boost our remarkable of 
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;life.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>