<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="bf790a5474ad382d08f34a44997be3f6">			Cooking is just one of life's daily chores, but it can be a fun hobby too. Anyone can cook well if they learn to do it the right way. The advice in the following article should help you learn everything that you need to know to make great meals.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Potatoes are divided in different categories, and each category should be used differently. Some potatoes are waxy and are great for making things like boiled potatoes or potato salad but are not so good for french fries, mashed potatoes, or baked potatoes. Russet potatoes are often recommended for making mashed, fried or baked potato recipes because they have high starch content.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Eat your oysters in new and exciting ways. Oysters are typically eaten raw with a some lemon juice, but they can be prepared in a number of other ways. Try placing open, shelled oysters into a broiler pan, then cover them with a small amount of cream. After, top them with some parmesan cheese, and finally broil them. Another option is to saute the oysters. Coat oysters with some seasoned flour and saute in warm butter for a couple of minutes, until they are golden. Bake the oysters while they are still in their shells. Place your oysters in a pan that is oven safe, dab some butter on the oysters and sprinkle some breadcrumbs on the top, then bake for about 4-5 minutes at 425 degrees. They are done when the juices on top of each oyster are bubbling. They go great with toasted baguettes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Buying quality knives is an important investment in your kitchen. This can save you time so that you don't wrangle with dull knives, and it's safer for you to use a sharper one! Most of the accidents that happen in the kitchen are due to someone using a dull cutting utensils.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get rid of any extra fat in your soups and stews. If you homemade stew or soup has too much fat, let your dish cool, and all of the fat will rise to the top. All you need to do to remove it is to place an ice cube directly on a spoon then gently rub it on the top of the soup. The ice draws the fat and it collects on the cube. You can skim fat off of the top of stews and soups by using a paper towel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you want a shell for double-baked potatoes or skins with additional firmness, try using a thick potato designed for baking. Don't use red potatoes, their skin is too thin to help a dense filling.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Add some chicken broth to your pan when cooking vegetables. Chicken broth is a great way to add flavor to your vegetables while keeping them from sticking to your pan. Chicken broth is cheap, and can be bought anywhere.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Garlic can add a tremendous amount of flavor to your food. However, when you are cutting and chopping fresh garlic, it can also leave its odor on your hands. After you are done working with garlic and any other odoriferous ingredients, try rubbing your hands firmly on the inside of your stainless steel sink. This will clean your hands and keep the smells from permeating whatever food you are handling next.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try not to under or over cook your cake. Many factors can affect the cooking times for cakes. There are guidelines that come on many cake mixes that can be helpful but do not take into account the things that could impact the cooking time. Insert a toothpick into the cake's middle. If your toothpick is clean, your cake is ready to be taken out of the oven. However, if there is batter left on the toothpick, keep baking for a longer period of time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cooking is a skill, hobby and vocation. There are many ways to cook food, and a great way to learn some of these ways is to learn from someone who is good at cooking. Make use of this advice next time you need to cook something!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVib3R0bGVhbmRqYXJjb21wYW55LmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;bottles&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVib3R0bGVhbmRqYXJjb21wYW55LmNvLnVrL29yZGVyL2JvdHRsZXMv" target="_blank"&gt;;mineral bottles&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVib3R0bGVhbmRqYXJjb21wYW55LmNvLnVrL29yZGVyL2phbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;jam jars&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="8a28593e65810d006cc0b99719643810">			Have you been looking for new ways to spice up your daily diet without relying on bland foods and beverages? You are about to find some excellent tips for juicing. Making your own juice is a great way to incorporate essential vitamins, minerals and nutrients into your diet on a daily basis. Read on to find many ideas to help you turn juicing into a healthy lifestyle change.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Consult your physician before you make anything other than a vegetable juice if you have diabetes or hypoglycemia. Drinking juice made of fruit can drastically increase your blood sugar. Be sure to regulate how much fruit and sugar you are mixing in your juices if you have medical conditions. Using vegetables in your juices will allow you to get all necessary vitamins and minerals, but won't put your health at risk.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before you create any concoctions, do some research on your fresh produce. Lots of differences exist in the nutrients you will receive from the large produce variety in the market. You should strive to keep your juices balanced by using ingredients that cover your daily nutritional needs. In addition to fueling your body with natural ingredients, you will also discover a world of unique and delicious flavors.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're like most people, you'll need to keep your juicer available and ready for almost instant action if you want to truly establish juicing momentum. As such, your juicer will serve as a daily reminder.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Making fresh juice to store in the refrigerator is a good idea, but you need to take steps to prevent the juice from changing colors. Darker juices are not very appealing, but you can prevent this from happening. You can prevent this from occurring simply by squeezing about two teaspoons of juice from a fresh lemon into your juice blend. The lemon won't change the flavor all that much, but will preserve the look of the juice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vegetables your children won't eat may be palatable to them in the form of a juice. A lot of children neglect to eat their vegetables. By juicing vegetables and fruits you can create a drink with a great taste without children even realizing what they are consuming.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plan your juices by color. Reds, oranges, yellows and greens: they all add different nutrients to the final product. Using a wide variety of colors will give you a full range of nutrients and many exciting tastes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If your kids don't like vegetables, you can just make them vegetable juice to provide them the nutrients they need. Many kids out there just do not like vegetables. You can give them their favorite fruit juices spiked with vegetable juice. They don't need to know what you are doing.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In regards to juicing, it is important to consider how different juices may affect the appearance of your teeth. Darker juices will stain your teeth and can discolor them long term if you drink them often enough. Juice made from beets or carrots may do this. If you have experienced easy staining of your teeth in the past, it is a good idea to very carefully brush your teeth following the drinking of any juices that can leave stains.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Let juicing put you on the track to healthier living. It can form the basis of the remainder of your daily intake.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Studies have shown that consuming fruits and vegetables can improve health and well-being. This information can help you find out how juicing can help you have a positive impact on your body and spirit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVib3R0bGVhbmRqYXJjb21wYW55LmNvLnVrL29yZGVyL2phbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;glass jars&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVib3R0bGVhbmRqYXJjb21wYW55LmNvLnVr" target="_blank"&gt;;glass jars&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVib3R0bGVhbmRqYXJjb21wYW55LmNvLnVrL29yZGVyL2JvdHRsZXMv" target="_blank"&gt;;mineral bottles&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>