<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2e16acc91744f0543b2b751e20ca73eb">			Does the temperature at which you store and serve wine matter? Yes, wine should be stored at cellar temperature, not room temperature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First, let’s take a look at room temperature. What is it, exactly? At my house, it would probably be about 75 degrees. Prior to central heating and air-conditioning, average room temperature was lower — some records indicate as low as 55 degrees. Wine became extremely popular in the United States after World War II, when U.S. soldiers who spent a lot of time in Europe were exposed to it. They returned home with a taste for wine, and the rest is history. This was a time before central heating and air, so it is probable that it actually was OK for my grandparents to store their wine at room temperature.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you can see, room temperature has changed throughout history. Something that is pretty constant, however, are the caves and underground cellars used to store wine in Europe. After limestone was carved out of the earth to build a winery, a large hole was left. Ingenious French wineries decided to take advantage of the space and store their wine there. They found that if they kept the wine between 50 and 60 degrees, it would age best. Storing wine too warm can increase aging, causing it to lose flavor; the same is true of wine stored too cold. If wine gets too hot, it can actually cook and end up with a burnt orange or brown tinge and port-like characteristics.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Storing wine at 60 degrees is one thing, but should it be served at that temperature? If it is a red wine, yes. Flaws in wine are easier to notice if the wine is consumed at temperatures in excess of 65 degrees. Apart from the inability to distinguish flavor profiles, the taste of alcohol becomes prominent and can really reduce wine enjoyment.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;White wine is also impacted by temperature, but it's just the opposite. White wine is frequently stored in a refrigerator, below 40 degrees. Many refrigerators are set just above freezing. The proper temperature for the majority of whites is 45-50 degrees. Flavors are restricted when whites are served too cold. It is best to let your wine warm up a while by holding the glass in the palms of your hands and swirling it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But how can you serve wine at these exact temps in your own home? Certainly you can find guidelines like when visitors come over, put your reds in the refrigerator half an hour before they arrive and take your whites out half an hour before they arrive. But when you want to be sure, you can purchase wine gadgets that measure wine temperature, or, if you are a frequent wine drinker, you might want to buy a wine fridge or cooler with digital controls. A wine fridge can store wine for approximately a year at proper serving temps. The storage capacity is often as tiny as 4 bottles, or as huge as 100  bottles. Here's a great website with wine refrigerator reviews  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.modern-wine-cellar.com%2Fwine-refrigerator.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.modern-wine-cellar.com/wine-refrigerator.html&lt;/a&gt; .		</conversation>	</conversations></author>