<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="74bed5a2f9b2793bd1f9407e9324a43c">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcGhlbnJ5LmNvbS93YWxrd2F5cy5hc3B4" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fephenry.com%2Fwalkways.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://ephenry.com/walkways.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.landscapeonline.com%2Fresearch%2Flcn%2F2007%2F03%2Fimg%2Fdriveways%2Fdriveways-15.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.landscapeonline.com/research/lcn/2007/03/img/driveways/driveways-15.jpg&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; alt=&quot;;driveways]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Nowadays, retaining walls are also used in landscaping. These objects offer limitless design possibilities and they can follow whatever angles and contours you have planned for your outdoor space.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcGhlbnJ5LmNvbS9kcml2ZXdheXMuYXNweA__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ephenry.com%2Fdriveways.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.ephenry.com/driveways.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;However this can be thought of as a Diy design, it is vital that you simply seek advice from an area developer due to the fact they'll present functional viewpoints with regards to the matter. Moreover there are many ways to build walls just as there are several components to select from; for a lot more particulars I like to recommend you check with your native landscapers.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Retaining walls were first used for the easy and vital endeavor of keeping back earth.  It is true that erosion is natural process but if start causing washing away your home then it’s better to make a retaining wall to avoid its damaging impact.  Though these walls are not the only remedy.  It could be implemented in backyard to protect its aesthetic perception.  These walls can offer you more area for your house landscaping and may turn out to be an incredible a part of it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Retaining Wall Materials&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Traditionally these walls were made from railroad ties and found stone. The land is dug back, the stones or wood placed as a wall, and land filled back in behind, creating two flat surfaces where there once was a hill. The process is no different today but the uses and materials have changed.  Immediately the railroad ties and landscape timber can also be being used but these types of immediate placement of the substance can even further deterioration the soil composition.  Stones are also being used to get a natural look but if installed by professionals give classic look. Brick can offer a more staid look, while concrete blocks are inexpensive and simple.  You can also use steel, poured concrete or masonry but it depends for everything you are generating this retaining wall.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.thehousedesigners.com%2Fimages%2Fplans%2FAMD%2Fphotos%2F2459patio2.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.thehousedesigners.com/images/plans/AMD/photos/2459patio2.jpg&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; alt=&quot;;outdoor living]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcGhlbnJ5LmNvbS9vdXRkb29yLWxpdmluZy5hc3B4" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ephenry.com%2Foutdoor-living.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.ephenry.com/outdoor-living.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Usage of the Land&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The most common utilization of retaining partitions should be to hold or shift earth back.  It will involve to depart the land as lower grass to have a property for your property on top of that.  In such situation the partitions are still left exposed so their own search needs to give a pleasing impression to retain residence grandeur.  In case of cheap masonry the end product can be teasing, a flat concrete wall could give flat impression while stone retaining walls can add something you would like to show others. The purposes of these walls vary. If it is to retain earth or create more yard space, you will want to match the design to your home's exterior design. And if it is to create a layered landscaped look, then it is less about the walls and more about the landscaping design put in after the installation.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Garden Walls&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A wall around a garden is also a retaining wall to keep it separate from surroundings.  It is also called a screen wall which is used to create tiered or terraced garden.  A garden wall structure is not build so that it could hold soil weight properly.  It can become a nice addition to your home creating a beautiful wall with flowering in the place of a hill with lot of difficulties to grow or mow the grass. Next to a pool or patio it might brighten your summer days.  If being used for back garden window you can find a singular pleasurable look with each day existence.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Really don't forget about your unique environmental elements whereas making a choice on a specific types of retaining walls.  The use of timber or railroad can make trouble as a result of currently being chemical in naturel although concrete wall can ofefr resistance in drainage.  That is why what is being preferred nowadays are retaining wall blocks or segmental retaining walls because of having low cost, good look and environment friendly features.  The concrete wall are pre-made to provide wide range in designs as giving no predicament in drainage. Whatever materials you choose, a retaining wall will offer you more use of your land with the added benefit of creating a unique and elegant look to your landscape design.		</conversation>		<conversation id="41239321fd47def714e85515b7cd271">			We all have our own preference when it comes to the exterior and interior of the house and we are often delighted when we finally get to materialize the design we have in mind. However, this aspect can also turn into a tasking job especially if we canÕt find the right materials for our desired theme. For instance if we like to be close with nature, it is often difficult to incorporate this idea with the available resources in your area. Sometimes, we are required to import items and this can be quite costly especially if we have a limited budget. However there are certain materials which are easy to find since they are naturally occurring and so the natural theme you have planned in the beginning will finally materialize.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcGhlbnJ5LmNvbS9vdXRkb29yLWxpdmluZy5hc3B4" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ephenry.com%2Foutdoor-living.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.ephenry.com/outdoor-living.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Some developers suggest to home owners to use stones and bricks since they are the common materials used for nature impressed layouts. But the problem with these materials is that they costs more in spite of the fact that these are natural occurring materials. This is the reason why developers often recommend to owners to use stone veneers because they are relatively cheap to produce while the cost of installing these is affordable as well. Another advantage in using a stone veneer rather than the natural stone is that the former weighs less compared to the latter. The problem with natural stone is that there is an added cost in transporting them due to their mass but with veneers you can transport them using your own vehicle. Furthermore, it is easy to install and you can do away with hiring additional help which saves you some money. Another advantage of using stone veneers is that there are several colors to choose from. Natural stones lack this quality and so home owners prefer stone veneers because they can choose whatever color they like to blend in their design. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;What's more, you will discover stone veneers that have wonderful versatility and this is perfect for curved walls inside your houses.Finally, stone veneers costs less to maintain. They are durable too and can endure harsh condition should you choose to install them outdoors.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You can enjoy the same level of durability with your stone walls as you get in case of brick walls.  Even you can find several stone walls standing undamaged after passing thousands of years.  The use of stone walls is as old as the history of construction but it still retains its charm.  It is enough to prove them reliable in both aspects, physical one and aesthetic one as well. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.katyelliott.com%2Fbeta%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2010%2F05%2Fbrick-herringbone-driveway.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.katyelliott.com/beta/wp-content/uploads/2010/05/brick-herringbone-driveway.jpg&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; alt=&quot;;driveways]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Varieties of Stones &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcGhlbnJ5LmNvbS93YWxrd2F5cy5hc3B4" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.ephenry.com%2Fwalkways.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;www.ephenry.com/walkways.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stones are either rough or finished. A rough stone is any stone that hasn't been altered.  But finishing stones are perfectly shaped to be used as brick.  &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Varieties of Stone Walls&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Stone walls come in a couple of types, dry and mortar wall.  The dry stone walls usually rely upon the force of friction between its stones to stand still.  These stones are laid in overlapping manners over one another to form a loose but stable wall. Mortared walls fill in the gaps between the stones with cement, basically turning the wall into one solid unit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Building a Dry Stone Wall &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Other than the heavy lifting, a dry stone wall is easy to build.  First off dig the trench to place the wall inside. It should be slightly wider than the wall.  Then gravel is filled in the trench to make the foundation.  While using rough stone place larger one to cover the gravel and then use smaller ones to fill the gap.  This process is repeated to help make various layers.  Make sure that gaps are filled properly in order to make stable walls indeed.  When you use finishing stones the process becomes more convenient.  Finishing stones are more expensive and don’t have the typical rustic look of rough stones.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;How to Make a Mortared Stone Wall?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you are working with mortar then it’s an art and a skill as well.  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lcGhlbnJ5LmNvbS9kcml2ZXdheXMuYXNweA__" target="_blank"&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fephenry.com%2Fdriveways.aspx"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://ephenry.com/driveways.aspx&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fweb-vassets.ea.com%2FAssets%2FRichmedia%2FImage%2FScreenshots%2FTS3_OLS_Easel_656x369.jpg%3Fcb%3D1328823777%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://web-vassets.ea.com/Assets/Richmedia/Image/Screenshots/TS3_OLS_Easel_656x369.jpg?cb=1328823777&quot;&lt;/a&gt;; alt=&quot;;outdoor living]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You must decide on the processes and kinds of stone as reported by the purpose of wall that you are about to crafted for like as barrier, like a effortless artwork of you dwelling or as separation among back garden and garden.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>