<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="98e7addb2dbaca495dfe10d9632e7a07">			Most of them offer you entire breakfast, lunch, and dinner menus, and some have breakfast and fruit buffets and soup  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.getjealous.com%2Fblog.php%3Faction%3Dshowdiaryentry%26amp%3Bdiary_id%3D2112683%26amp%3Bgo%3Dhomerlindsay821"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.getjealous.com/blog.php?action=showdiaryentry&amp;diary_id=2112683&amp;go=homerlindsay821&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frestaurant-dc77.travellerspoint.com%2F1%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://restaurant-dc77.travellerspoint.com/1/&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/diMercaeadoOk/blog/blogid=4880883" target="_blank"&gt;;http://en.pan.netcom/diMercaeadoOk/blog/blogid=...&lt;/a&gt;;  and salad bars. The streets are lined with fusion  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democratandchronicle.com%2Fapps%2Fpbcs.dll%2Fsection%3Fcategory%3DPluckPersona%26amp%3BU%3Dfecd6f33d17047ae9e4e5d84d4fdd043%26amp%3BplckPersonaPage%3DBlogViewPost%26amp%3BplckUserId%3Dfecd6f33d17047ae9e4e5d84d4fdd043%26amp%3BplckPostId%3DBlog%253afecd6f33d17047ae9e4e5d84d4fdd043Post%253a00012b47-1352-4fd9-b3c7-29421bb5a638%26amp%3BplckBlogItemsPerPage%3D5"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.democratandchronicle.com/apps/pbcs.dll/section?category=PluckPersona&amp;U=fecd6f33d17047ae9e4e5d84d4fdd043&amp;plckPersonaPage=BlogViewPost&amp;plckUserId=fecd6f33d17047ae9e4e5d84d4fdd043&amp;plckPostId=Blog%3afecd6f33d17047ae9e4e5d84d4fdd043Post%3a00012b47-1352-4fd9-b3c7-29421bb5a638&amp;plckBlogItemsPerPage=5&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fcommunity.atom.com%2FPost%2FRestaurants-in-Washington-DC%2F03EFBFFFF0248EEF20008015FD7EF"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://community.atom.com/Post/Restaurants-in-Washington-DC/03EFBFFFF0248EEF20008015FD7EF&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Frestaurant-dc77.travellerspoint.com%2F1%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://restaurant-dc77.travellerspoint.com/1/&lt;/a&gt;;   restaurants featuring alfresco eating. The Bridgeview at 1300 West 9th Road, the Hat Factory at 1235 West 6th Road, the Bingham at 1278 West 9th Road, and the Grand Arcade at 1300 West 9th street occur outfitted with authentic challenging wooden floors, exposed brick walls, uncovered wood beam ceilings, oversized windows, and a loft type of residing. Another thriving component of the warehouse district is the fascinating night lifestyle. The strip of bars on West 6th road, like the Blind pig, Velvet canine, and Tequila Ranch have lines out the doorways every weekend. Only a number of blocks away is Brown stadium, the rock and roll hall of fame, the wonderful lakes science center, the good time 3, and of program Lake Erie. This district is ideal for the youthful specialist who is looking for a luxury house without having the luxury price tag, a thriving nightlife, and upscale dinning. For much more details on Warehouse district living Google Cleveland apartments or Cleveland Apartment Finders.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Gateway district is residence to two of our Cleveland sports activities groups, the Indians and the Cavaliers. Both Progressive field and Quicken loans arena are located in the heart of the Gateway district. This district centers around the schedules of equally teams. The streets of the Gateway district are lined with pubs that supply meals and drinks to sports activities goers yr round. These pubs include the Boneyard, Harry Buffalo, Flannery's Pub, the Clevelander, and the Thirsty Parrot. A number of of the apartments available in the Gateway district are Carter Manor at 1012 Prospect, Huron Sq. Flats 1001 Huron Ave, and the Osborn Building at 1001 Huron Ave. This district is perfect for the Cleveland sports fan who is either at the sport or observing the game in a bar, they don't head a minor publish recreation noise and targeted traffic, and the town look at they want in there window is Friday evening fireworks at progressive subject. For more info on living in the Gateway district Google Cleveland Apartment Finders&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The up and coming district in Cleveland is the East Fourth Neighborhood. This district is home to four separate rental structures the Buckeye situated previously mentioned Flannery's Pub, the Industrial, the Windsor, and the Fredericks positioned previously mentioned Saigon restaurant. Also positioned on this road are upscale restaurants and entertainment. The road contains Lola bistro Michael Symons restaurant, the Ponder bar, Zocalo, and Pickwick &amp;amp Frolic. The entertainment on this road is countless. The corner alley is an upscale bowling alley with a entire bar and kitchen area. Residence of Blues gives an array of concerts through out the calendar year. Hilarities comedy club has displays via the week which includes dinner theater, and if that isn't sufficient progressive field and Quicken loans arena are right across the street. This district is for an individual who loves the city and every thing that comes with it the noise, the visitors, the individuals, the enjoyment. For much more data on residing in the East Fourth Neighborhood Google &quot;Cleveland Apartment Finders&quot; and East Fourth Neighborhood.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The ultimate district in Cleveland is the Theater district. This district is house to the planet course Playhouse square.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>