<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d8c9e7c4c5b91f561444c57202f552e7">			This happens so often which it gets really annoying before long. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Another niggle: The focus ring does not feel and too a lot of travel. Although you can override the focus any time, you can't easily tell where direction you are shifting the focus because the travel is far to much time. Since there is absolutely no distance scale or a single thing, I can't ever really tell what Now i'm doing. Well, I know I feel not the best photographer on this planet, yes, but I find a way to shoot with manual focus cameras and also works out fine. Cash caused me to practically never attempt to adjust typically the focus manually. Which kind of takes a portion of the fun away. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The end straw: While I was never dissatisfied with all the pictures from the 18-105VR, I was not really satisfied either. For long periods, I couldn't tell why also it took me a really reasonable length of time to understand the rationale. Some of my imagery with my kit webpage the 18-55mm, especially all those shot in good light, had an almost magical &quot;pop&quot; in their mind. They looked really, truly good. Not that I am a good photographer, I am just debating the technical quality. You may looked at them in addition to said &quot;wow&quot;. I realized that none of your images shot with the 18-105 were of this nature. So I started analyzing the kit lens photographs more closely. The thing these pictures had in typical was: Kit lens, shot having an aperture of f8 and f11. Hmm, OK DOCUMENT thought, this is types of obvious, any lens requires to be stopped down a bit so you can get optimum quality. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So I started examining the photos from typically the 18-105, picking out typically the f8 or f11s. Many people looked fine, OK, they had no obvious problems. Nonetheless they did not have in which &quot;bite&quot;, that &quot;pop&quot; that something extra that this kit lens pictures have. This is the point of which a better photography site would placed comparison test shots from the two lenses. Since I am lazy and can't bother to shoot pictures only for testing, I will just say this: The 18-55mm kit aperture spanks the 18-105mm VR with image quality, period. Can you notice the difference? That i thought &quot;Lens sharpness might be way overrated, it's meant for pixel peepers, normal people can't begin to see the difference&quot;. Well, even together with my lowly 6 megapixel D40, I could tell the difference. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On with other story: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Armed with this info, I snagged a used 18-55mm VR to test out. Within minutes, it constructed me smile. What I had produced forgotten was how much fun the D40 is a light lens on it. While the 18-105 will not be enormously large, it still is noticeably heavier. The 18-55 VR, on the flip side makes the D40 handle like a dream. The close focusing distance means you can aquire much closer to subjects and also the maximum magnification for macro shots is larger than the 18-105. The image quality is likewise much better, I think essentially same as the set up lens, in other words and phrases: very good. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;[url=]izmir escort[/url]		</conversation>	</conversations></author>