<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="430f4bd4627e34371409f99d215ec059">			Yea that's fairly a lot their answer for all the things, so I went to Google and I discovered some very advantageous info on how to deal with the red ring of death.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I figured out that other consumers have had this issue as nicely and sent it in to Microsoft, and that seems to be the finest remedy for how to deal with the red ring of demise but they didn't get their console again right until months in the future. But if you are like me, you don't have that type of time to waste materials accomplishing next to nothing. Meanwhile, throughout my research, I chosen up some practical options to retain your Xbox running so that you will not have to have an Xbox 360 fix in the initial area. For illustration, make confident its receiving sufficient new air since it will get really hot. And preserve it off the ground so that great air can go into the vents. These ideas were being going to help retain my technique from heading awful but I necessary a resolution for how to correct it once it had presently malfunctioned.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So I continued searching for other solutions until I observed that there have been really guides on how to offer with this type of difficulty. These Xbox 360 fix guides were being created by pros who know how Microsoft items do the job. So I resolved to appear into this selection because there was no way I was planning to fork out over $140 to mail it in to Microsoft and wait for months hoping that they have basically &quot;fixed&quot; it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;u&gt;;Tips For Repairing Your Xbox 360&lt;/u&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;1)&lt;/strong&gt;; As shortly as you get the red lighting, switch off your console for a whereas and let it awesome down.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;two)&lt;/strong&gt;; Just after earning convinced that all the cords are accurately connected try out it yet again. And If you still get the red lights, continue to action three.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;three)&lt;/strong&gt;; At this level, you can open up your console to see if the relationship to the energy supply is unfastened or off. But if you are not snug with opening up your console or don't have any instruments you can make use of a temporary deal with termed the towel trick.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;four)&lt;/strong&gt;; The purpose why the towel trick operates as a non permanent fix is since just after some time 1 of the solder joints which hook up the chips to the mother board gets cracked so you have to find a way to solder it back again on, but most people today never have solder equipment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;five)&lt;/strong&gt;; This is exactly where the towel trick happens in, gently wrap your Xbox in a big cotton towel whilst your Xbox 360 is still working. Permit it operate for about 10 mins then flip it off.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;six)&lt;/strong&gt;; This will cause the solder joints to melt and form a correct link once once more with no you possessing to open up up the box, or get a soldering apparatus. But try to remember that this is a non permanent deal with and you will even now have to have a remaining answer. With this system you can squeeze out a further 30 minutes to 10hrs of playtime previously the three red lights exhibit up once more.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;7)&lt;/strong&gt;; You could possibly be ready to extend that time if you continue to keep the Xbox very well cooled and out in the open up. In much less than two several hours of next the guide you would have learned how to fix the red ring of death.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54Ym94MzYwZml4LmluY2hpY2Fnb2NpdHkuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Xbox 360 fix&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e2f2c6645f7d4561d792f8f22b1c00d1">			I necessarily mean it really is just sitting down there, not serving to you or any person. You love your Xbox but it just stop on you. You bought it to assist you offer with boredom and to perform Phone of Duty IV Modern-day Warfare on the net with your friends, but now it won't deliver the results and you never even know what to do with all by yourself and your time any more, and you actually will need a instant Xbox 360 fix.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is how I felt when my Xbox 360 stopped performing. I bought the 3 red lights and I didn't know the to start with detail about how to go about finding it mounted. So the first factor I did was consult my good friends how I could correct it. They asked me if my fingers are even now performing, and I reported sure, then they asked how arrive I haven't typed it into Google nevertheless. Yea that's quite significantly their response for all the things, so I went to Google and I uncovered some rather useful data on how to repair the red ring of passing away.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I realized that other persons have had this challenge as very well and sent it in to Microsoft, and that appears to be to be the perfect resolution for how to deal with the red ring of demise but they didn't get their console back right until months in the future. But if you're like me, you never have that kind of time to waste materials performing practically nothing. Meanwhile, during my investigation, I selected up some handy solutions to retain your Xbox running so that you will not need an Xbox 360 fix in the first place. For instance, make guaranteed its having enough fresh air simply because it will get seriously scorching. And maintain it off the floor so that calme air can go into the vents. These ideas have been heading to guide continue to keep my procedure from planning lousy but I essential a alternative for how to deal with it following it experienced by now malfunctioned.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So I ongoing looking out for other possibilities until eventually I found that there ended up truly guides on how to deal with this form of challenge. These Xbox 360 fix guides were constructed by gurus who know how Microsoft products function. So I chose to start looking into this solution mainly because there was no way I was going to spend in excess of $140 to deliver it in to Microsoft and wait for months hoping that they have in fact &quot;fixed&quot; it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;&lt;u&gt;;Hints For Fixing Your Xbox 360&lt;/u&gt;;&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;one)&lt;/strong&gt;; As shortly as you get the red lighting, turn off your console for a while and allow it cool down.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;2)&lt;/strong&gt;; Right after building absolutely sure that all the cords are accurately connected consider it once again. And If you still get the red lighting, proceed to phase 3.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;3)&lt;/strong&gt;; At this level, you can open up up your console to see if the relationship to the energy supply is loose or off. In a lot less than 2 hrs of adhering to the guideline you would have figured out how to deal with the red ring of demise.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy54Ym94MzYwZml4LmluY2hpY2Fnb2NpdHkuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;;Chicago Xbox 360 repair&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>