<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="6">		<conversation id="e2012eebc2d56df7405e5d7c8788a7b3">			Unlike a CD, a DVD consists of two sides made of plastic which are stuck together. These sides are also called layers. Data can be pressed at a far higher density on both layers than on a CD, giving the DVD a considerably greater storage capacity.
&lt;br /&gt;;DVD duplication is just that-duplicating a program, motion picture or inventive performance onto another DVD so as to share it with someone or to market it commercially. Somebody with a PC and a DVD burner can simply copy a DVD to a blank disc and produce an acceptable copy. This isn't routinely done at home for large amounts because it is very time thorough.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Stamping involves mildew for the DVD discs. An injection molding machine uses heated polycarbonate that is injected then briefly cooled before the info from the glass master is etched onto it. Because each disc is made from the same glass master that remains uncorrupted, a replicated DVD is generally of higher quality than a duplicated DVD. Replication also includes adding protecting layers to each disc to preserve the information. Duplication lays down the data on the disc without additional physical protection, leaving it more prone to scratches and pits. CD and DVD duplication is a similar process where the digital data is transferred onto an existing pre-made disc like CDR (Compact Disc Recordable) or DVDR (Digital Versatile Disc Recordable). DVD duplication is ideal for low volume DVD make and for quick turn requirements. Without the need of Glass mastering and longer machine set-up, CD/DVD duplication is affordable than &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN5cmVwbGljYXRpb24uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;DVD replication&lt;/a&gt;; and is preferred for small scale distribution.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f75b94b4dbeffecb0e27d3654e9e56d5">			Unlike a CD, a DVD consists of two sides made of plastic which are stuck together. These sides are also called layers. Data can be pressed at a far higher density on both layers than on a CD, giving the DVD a considerably greater storage capacity.
&lt;br /&gt;;DVD duplication is just that-duplicating a program, motion picture or inventive performance onto another DVD so as to share it with someone or to market it commercially. Somebody with a PC and a DVD burner can simply copy a DVD to a blank disc and produce an acceptable copy. This isn't routinely done at home for large amounts because it is very time thorough.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Stamping involves mildew for the DVD discs. An injection molding machine uses heated polycarbonate that is injected then briefly cooled before the info from the glass master is etched onto it. Because each disc is made from the same glass master that remains uncorrupted, a replicated DVD is generally of higher quality than a duplicated DVD. Replication also includes adding protecting layers to each disc to preserve the information. Duplication lays down the data on the disc without additional physical protection, leaving it more prone to scratches and pits. CD and DVD duplication is a similar process where the digital data is transferred onto an existing pre-made disc like CDR (Compact Disc Recordable) or DVDR (Digital Versatile Disc Recordable). DVD duplication is ideal for low volume DVD make and for quick turn requirements. Without the need of Glass mastering and longer machine set-up, CD/DVD duplication is affordable than &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN5cmVwbGljYXRpb24uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;DVD replication&lt;/a&gt;; and is preferred for small scale distribution.		</conversation>		<conversation id="89bea5ee287d84cd916163eb74da375e">			Easy replication understands your needs more than anyone else and makes high quality DVD duplication to ensure compatibility of duplicated DVDs to wide range of electronic hardware. Through our custom packaging planning, we can help you select best DVD packaging that suits your need. Besides, the cost that you get in easy replication is unmatched in the industry and highly affordable too.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Through our years of experience and commitment to excellence, we give best quality DVD duplication services at fast turnaround time. Using graphics and company logo, thermal print directly to the surface of the DVD, and silk screening, we help make your &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN5cmVwbGljYXRpb24uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;DVD replication&lt;/a&gt;; look very professional to impart a positive impact of your business in peoples’ mind. Therefore, if you are looking for effective business or music promotion, or are in an urgency of short run requirement of your master DVD, then think easy replication for cost effective high quality CD or DVD duplication services.		</conversation>		<conversation id="33d02b3b27ede9d349706297fcae8d3">			Quality CD and DVD Replication solutions for your company - Only a click away! This is what Easy Replication said and is also proving it. With easy replication, it's so simple and trouble-free. If you’re looking for a CD and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN5cmVwbGljYXRpb24uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;DVD replication&lt;/a&gt;;company that offers reliable service, low costs, quality products and a fast turnaround you have found the best company to contact. We meet and exceed your desired CD Replication and DVD Replication services in addition to USB Flash Drives and USB Branded Sticks and will bypass your expectations. At easy replication, we have the goal to give the customer service that will be above par performance. We fully understand the requirements of our clients and offer them the preferred optical media solutions.		</conversation>		<conversation id="6e0ace69ba96c34a672c098d1ec4833e">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN5cmVwbGljYXRpb24uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;Bulk CD replication&lt;/a&gt;; process features high quality duplicated CDs with 4 colors. It is done on CD silk screening. The companies that are involved in CD duplication use the latest technology and equipment and adhere to strict quality regulations and controls. Since a large number of copies are created during replication, it is not an expensive procedure. The vendor will give you the first duplicated copy of the CD to make sure the quality and get your approval. The first copy is also important because the quality of all the other copies depend on that first copy, instead of the master disc. Not only this, CD Replication service providers usually provide beautiful packages for the CDs. CD replication is a good option especially for the businesses, in which projects have to be worked on with a large number of CDs like five hundred or more and when all the people working on the same project require the same master disc.		</conversation>		<conversation id="adf518e0e81a9acf9930a5d2a311a9ae">			Many people may not know this but there is a difference between bulk DVD replication and duplication. To start off, DVD duplication is simply the process of burning data from an original DVD onto another existing DVD recordable disc. Bulk duplication is possible with high quality industrial grade duplicators which can produce formats playable in different DVD players.
&lt;br /&gt;;On the other hand &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5lYXN5cmVwbGljYXRpb24uY28udWs_" target="_blank"&gt;;bulk DVD replication&lt;/a&gt;; involves the generation of a clone of an original master copy. A glass master is created from the original master and from it a stumper is then created. The stumper is defined as the mirror image of the contents in the DVD. The stumper is then mounted onto a High Tech injection mould machine and in the molding process a replica of the mould is produced on the normal DVD disc which is then coated using a thin layer of reflective aluminum.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>