<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f7735b4dfb7044b9ebb825a850f4ecad">			Due to the fact that consuming organic foods is gaining popularity, choosing to live a holistic lifestyle is also becoming more prevalent. It makes sense that people who make the choice to live this way can benefit from organic gardening. Read these tips to get started.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plant strawberries for your children. You will find that they enjoy participating in gardening if they are allowed to pluck the fresh berries and eat them straight from the earth.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Try growing some organic garlic. Cloves should be planted whole during the fall or early spring months. Garlic grows best in soil that retains moisture but drains well. Lay each bulb into the ground ends up at a distance of about 4 inches away from the next bulb and 1-2 inches down into the soil. Cut the green garlic shoots and use them as a substitute for chives or scallions. When the tops of the bulbs become brown, it is time to harvest them. The bulbs should be dried well by the sun for a few days before storing. You can go ahead and store them in a cooler area, and you can either keep them loose or tie them up.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can use rainwater if you save it. You can use rain barrels or buckets to collect rainwater for use in your garden during the summer months. This will save you a lot of money in water bills. Rainwater is always free, and there sometimes plenty of it. Rainwater works just as well as water from other sources, so you might as well use it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Plant your organic garden in the shade. Shaded gardens require very little upkeep, making them ideal for many amateur gardeners. They also require a lot less watering, which could save you lots of time and work. The plants also grow slower, which means you will not have to pick weeds as often either.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For claiming your crops are credible and truly organic, get organic garden certified. This can increase your sales and also prove to your customers that they are getting the best produce out there.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lightly ruffle your seeds by hand or with cardboard, twice daily in your organic garden. While it might sound strange, research has shown that this method can increase the size of your plants.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;At least 3&quot; of organic mulch should be added to the flower beds and garden. This affects your garden in a variety of ways, including enriching the soil, locking in moisture, and improving the overall appearance of the garden.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Space is important to remember when planting an organic garden. Plants take up quite a bit of space as they grow, and it's easy to underestimate just how much. Space is vital for your plants not only due to their literal physical size requirements but also because of how much room your garden needs for air circulation. It is, therefore, important for you to plan accordingly and allow for enough room between your seed rows.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you have plants inside, make sure the thermostat stays between 65 and 75 degrees. Plants require a warmer climate to grow. If you wish to keep your house cooler than that, you may want to use a heat lamp just for the plants.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your watering schedule should flow perfectly with the seasons, yet be adjustable according to climate. Knowing how much to water your plants can be a difficult task. You will want to look into various things, such as time of day, quality of water and type of soil. For example, if your climate is humid and warm, you should not water the leaves because it will encourage leaf fungus. Rather, see to it that you water the root system well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Coffee grounds are a good addition to your soil. Coffee grounds add many nitrogenous nutrients to the soil that will benefit your plants. Plants need nitrogen in order to thrive, so give it a natural source with coffee grounds, then watch everything come to life much more quickly.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having an organic garden means that you can enjoy fresh, healthy fruits and vegetables whenever you want. While it is labor and time intensive, your garden will be quite amazing as a result.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNuYXp6eWNoaWNrZW5jb29wLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;discover how to raise chickens for eggs&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNuYXp6eWNoaWNrZW5jb29wLmNvbS9jaGlja2VuLWhlYWx0aC84LXJlYXNvbnMtZWdnLWNvdW50LWRlY3JlYXNlZC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;discover how to raise chickens for eggs&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNuYXp6eWNoaWNrZW5jb29wLmNvbS9lZ2ctcHJvZHVjdGlvbi9lZ2ctY29sb3JzLXNpemVzLWNoaWNrZW4tYnJlZWQv" target="_blank"&gt;;learn how raise chickens for eggs&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="9f9df207a3624b03a748e16a58f9d89e">			One of the smartest things you can do for you and your diet is to start an organic garden. However, effort is required in order to effectively grow. You probably do not know how to go about growing an organic garden on your own.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Invite biodiversity into your garden. Including a healthy mix of native grasses and flowers will attract wildlife. Create a more natural environment by planting lots of varieties in you garden. If you can accomplish this, your garden will be a pleasant place where you can relax, and you will have the satisfaction that comes from doing your bit for the environment.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Garlic is an easy deterrent for bugs in an organic garden. The smell of garlic will deter insects from inhabiting your garden. Garlic should be planted around the perimeter of your garden, as well as near any plants that are known to attract insects. An added benefit to planting garlic for pest control is that the pesticide is edible.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A cost-efficient way to water your garden is by collecting rainwater. Use barrels, buckets or any other appropriate containers to provide water for your garden. This will save you from paying money to water your garden. There is always plenty of rain, and it is free. You will find that your plants thrive on rainwater.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Maintaining your own compost pile is an excellent way to ensure a constant supply of fertilizer. A fun method to make this is to start a small compost bin with worms. Place red wiggler worms in the compost bin along with with dirt, kitchen scraps and shreds of newspaper.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use peelings from fruit or other left over pieces like apple cores to create your own low cost compost. These can create an excellent organic, natural compost for the beds, which will provide you with healthy and naturally beautiful plants at almost no cost.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mulching can be accomplished with three or more inches spread over plants and trees. This strategy is highly effective because it benefits both your wallet and your planet. Water conservation is a major environmental concern that accompanies other, non-organic gardening practices. You will also find the mulch attractive.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Find out as much as possible about your different options if you need to use a product on your plants. Use organic or natural alternatives in the place of the typical chemical fertilizers. Compost is a great example of what to use. Organic methods keep the soil clean, which in turn keeps the drinking water non-toxic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can keep bugs out of your organic garden by planting garlic in different areas. The smell will repel pesky insects. Try to plant the garlic near other plants that attract the most garden pests. You can also eat the garlic, as an added bonus.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A rule of thumb for when you are planting seeds in containers is to make the hole depth around three times larger than the seed itself. However, it is important to understand that some seeds require sunlight and should never be covered. Ageratum and petunias fall into this category. If you are unsure as to whether or not your seeds should be covered or not, try to read the package or find the answer online.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You need to avoid chores in your organic garden stacking up. Every time you go outside, you should take care of a few things so that you do not have too much work to do when you have the time to go back to your garden. Grab a handful of weeds, throw down some mulch, or toss some water on it anytime you walk by.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now that you've reached the end of this article, you know exactly what it takes to create an organic garden. There is a lot of information to be had and you need to know how to apply it. If you recall this advice, you can develop and hone your own techniques to create a flourishing organic garden.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNuYXp6eWNoaWNrZW5jb29wLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;learn how raise chickens for eggs&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNuYXp6eWNoaWNrZW5jb29wLmNvbS9jaGlja2VuLWhlYWx0aC84LXJlYXNvbnMtZWdnLWNvdW50LWRlY3JlYXNlZC8_" target="_blank"&gt;;learn how raise chickens for eggs&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5teXNuYXp6eWNoaWNrZW5jb29wLmNvbS9lZ2ctcHJvZHVjdGlvbi9lZ2ctY29sb3JzLXNpemVzLWNoaWNrZW4tYnJlZWQv" target="_blank"&gt;;learn how raise chickens for eggs&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>