<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="a62307755fdc0b956f7fe2ec5866af3f">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYXRpa2FzYWxrYW50YXkuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;SALKANTAY&lt;/a&gt;;  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cusco covers a total area of 70,015.30 Km2. In this beautiful land, it is possible to find colorful Andean valleys, snowy peaks, rivers, waterfalls, the beautiful Andean jungle, Inca and pre-Inca sites, and several Andean communities. These Andean communities are connected by thousands of paths. Some of these paths have been used before the Spaniards arrived to Peru. One of these paths is the one connecting the Andean valley of Mollepata with the Santa Teresa town located in the Andean Jungle. This path is well-known as the Salkantay Trek. After the Inca Trail, the Salkantay Trek is the most beautiful and popular one. Indeed, the magazine National Geographic Adventure rated the Salkantay Trek as one of the best 25 treks all over the world.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SALKANTAY TREK:SHORT SALKANTAY TREK 4DAYS
&lt;br /&gt;;When there are no permits left for the Inca Trail, the Salkantay Trek becomes the best choice. Hiking past the Salkantay Nevado is an incredible experience. While walking through different ecological levels, you will observe a variety of species of flora and fauna. This &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYXRpa2FzYWxrYW50YXkuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Salkantay&lt;/a&gt;;  Trek includes a guided visit to Machu Picchu on day 4.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SALKANTAY TREK:SALKANTAY TREK 5 DAYS
&lt;br /&gt;;This version of the Salkantay Trek is the best bet for an alternative trek when the Inca Trail is not available. In addition to the Short Salkantay Trek, this package offers a visit to the hot springs of Santa Teresa and a visit to the ruins of Llactapata. From Llactapata it is possible to observe Machu Picchu from a side only a few people have had the pleasure to see. This Salkantay Trek includes a visit to Machu Picchu on day 5.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SALKANTAY TREK:CUSCO-SHORT SALKANTAY TREK 7 DAYS
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Preparing for the altitude of the highest pass of the Salkantay Trek is very important in order to get the most out of this beautiful trek. Usually two days in Cusco prior to the departure date is enough to get used to the altitude of the Salkantay highest pass. While acclimatizing, a visit to the Sacred Valley of the Incas can be very exciting.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SALKANTAY TREK:SALKANTAY TREK TO MACHU PICCHU,MOUNTAIN LODGE TO LOGDE 7 DAYS
&lt;br /&gt;;If you are a trekker who is not into camping, this Salkantay Trek package is your best choice. This Salkantay Trek package will let you enjoy of the Salkantay Trek while staying at the Mountain Lodges built along the way. National Geographic Adventure highly recommends staying at the Mountain Lodges while hiking the  Salkantay route to Machu Picchu. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SALKANTAY TRE:CUSCO-SALKANTAY TREK 8 DAYS
&lt;br /&gt;;When National Geographic Adventure rated the Salkantay Trek is one of the best 25 treks in the world, the Salkantay route to Machu Picchu started to be hiked with more frequency. Although the Salkantay Trek is still not as popular as the Inca Trail, the people who have hiked both of them agree that their favorite is the Salkantay Trek due to its amazing landscapes, beautiful hot springs, and impressive Incan sites.  This package also includes accommodation in Cusco and a tour through the Sacred Valley of the Incas.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SALKANTAY TREK:SALKANTAY TREK 10 DAYS
&lt;br /&gt;;This Salkantay Trek package includes airfare Lima/Cusco/Lima, tours in Lima and Cusco, accommodation in Lima, Cusco and Aguas Calientes, and the fabulous Salkantay Trek. This package will let you get used to the altitude of the Salkantay Trek while you learn about the history of Peru. The staff of Latika Salkantay Trek highly recommends this package.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are two different ways to hike the Sal&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYXRpa2FzYWxrYW50YXkuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Salkantay&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYXRpa2FzYWxrYW50YXkuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Salkantay&lt;/a&gt;;   Trek. The first one is by staying at beautiful lodges along the way and the second one is by staying at tents. The most popular one is the second one. Whatever you choose, the Salkantay Trek will challenge you and astonish you.
&lt;br /&gt;;Our company offers two Salkantay Treks: The Short Salkantay Trek (4 Days / 3 Nights) and the Long Salkantay Trek (5 Days / 4 Nights). In our opinion, the second one is the most beautiful one because of the hot springs of Cocalmayo, located in Santa Teresa, and the ruins of Llactapata. From Llactapata, Machu Picchu can be observed from far. Both Salkantay hikes include one night at a hotel in Machu Picchu town, also known as Aguas Calientes, as well as a guided visit to Machu Picchu.
&lt;br /&gt;;The&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5sYXRpa2FzYWxrYW50YXkuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Salkantay&lt;/a&gt;;   Trek can be considered as a moderate to difficult trek. The Long Salkantay Trek covers a distance of 64 kilometers or 40 miles in average. Also, the highest point reaches about 4,600.00 m.a.s.l. or 15,000.00 f.a.s.l. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.latikasalkantay.com%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.latikasalkantay.com/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>