<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="71963688d1ff0ec1281f1f930b8665b3">			Hotels are vastly becoming the most popular style of venue for &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jbGlmZmhvdXNlc2FsY29tYmUuY28udWsvV2VkZGluZ3Mv" target="_blank"&gt;;British weddings&lt;/a&gt;;. Most hotels are now licensed, allowing couples to have both the reception and ceremony all in one place. Hotels appeal to many couples as they save on transportation costs, often have in house wedding organisers helping couples plan their big day and also generally have special offers for large numbers of friends and relatives booking rooms.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;South Devon has a wide range of superb hotels with a variety of price ranges. The town of Salcombe in particular is a popular choice for its quaint, picturesque villages and breathtaking scenery overlooking the beautiful coastline and magnificent countryside. Salcombe is known for its cove beaches, ferry trips and popular estuary. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those travelling longer distances to reach areas such as Salcombe, its a good idea to make the most out of your stay and lengthen your special day to a long weekend or even a weeks stay. There a wide range of hotels and bed and breakfasts to choose from, allowing you to also use this romantic destination for your honeymoon. Salcombe has a wide range of restaurants, pubs and boutique shops, as well as activities such as, surfing, wind surfing, sailing and kayaking for endless summer fun.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The rich and famous have started a fixation, giving many people the impression that weddings have to be extravagant and cost thousands in order to be special. Planning a unique and special wedding doesnt have to take up all your life savings. If a hotel is a little out of your price range, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jbGlmZmhvdXNlc2FsY29tYmUuY28udWsvV2VkZGluZ3Mv" target="_blank"&gt;;South Devon&lt;/a&gt;; also has many Manor Houses available to rent out for your special day. Manor houses are good option for those who wish to tailor make their wedding. Several period houses have organisers who can advise on the best local caters, photographers, florists and entertainers, ideal if you are new to the area.    
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Opting for a manor house as your choice of venue for your wedding will give you much more flexibility in terms of decorations, food and entertainment. Arrive at your beautiful hilltop setting by boat and mingle with guests in the picturesque gardens. Organise the times of your ceremony, dining, speeches and entertainment to suit your schedule not the hotels and end your celebration with drinks on the terrace under stars before vacating to your honeymoon suite.     
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a more traditional wedding of course you could arrange to have your ceremony in one of South Devons many churches before travelling to your chosen hotel or manor house by horse and carriage, limo or vintage car. There are many unique touches you can add to your special day, for instances you could arrange for your guests to be picked up via a vintage double-decker bus, you could organise a theme wedding where everyone in your party has to dress up in a particular style, you could even have your pet dog as the ring bearer, or instead of a cake why not go for tiers of cupcakes or wheels of cheese.   
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whether your style is more champagne and strawberries or warm apple cider and sandwiches, tailor make your wedding on the beautiful south Devonshire coastline.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>