<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="5">		<conversation id="56106067ddfbf3a7c4de64c9d464dbe4">			Daily we wake up from our  bed with 80% of what ever we need from the Most High God..... But due to our ignorant we struggle through the days activities trying to find the other 20% which always result to the lost of the 80%.... brethren ignorance can kill you.... No matter; what, who, how, where you are; you must give thanks to the Almighty cos if you have life trust me there is 80% possibility of you making it.... Give thanks to the giver of live... Shalom		</conversation>		<conversation id="33e01223fb3d4b5cc516366a7d373245">			strive to always work hard at your goals and improve. Yet, once in a while, consider how far you have come and appreciate and enjoy your progress.... for your success goes beyond you. in this interconnected world, when you create value in your life you cannot help but create value in many other lives...... shalom		</conversation>		<conversation id="16abc05170316f4d7b2affc8b02e6cf5">			You have a wonderful, beautiful valuable gift with which you can literally transform your life. That gift is this day you are living. Live it well... Shalom		</conversation>		<conversation id="aa49f3faf5fa683df9334f01317ab0bc">			in today contemporary world, man pass through the thin and thick just to get the right source of everything; serious and powerful protocols among others.... yes it is good but if your source is even the president, then you have a 4 year term or maximum of 8 years and that source will be over..... but if ELOHIM is your source, he never sleep nor slumber, no one can overthrown him from his seat as the creator.... today l am asking you &quot;where is your source&quot;... woe onto anyone who put his faith in a man.... shalom		</conversation>		<conversation id="b65171f6355c69549ef41b24837a6356">			we are not called to be human beings who have occasional spiritual experiences, but we are called to be spiritual beings who have occasional human experiences....we are called to be new creation that is very different from that which is only born of the flesh...shalom		</conversation>	</conversations></author>