<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="27531a9e00fad06d1b5f9bd224482bde">			If you have been working at your IM business and all to no avail, then it can be disheartening. Every once in a while the best approach is simply to let it go and take a mini vacation from the business. When was the last time you looked very objectively at the way you think about things? You really do need to become aware of what you think; the thoughts you have every day. Once you have done this, we are pretty confident you will see how negative you are. We are suggesting that these habits of thinking are making an adverse impact on your present level of success. Let's take a look at how you can use self improvement to turn your situation around.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;By the time you are ready to enter a business environment, your character traits have been ingrained in your mind. One obstacle to being successful in business is the person who is very unbending in their way of thinking. It's imperative that they train themselves to be more flexible. There is a huge gulf between the business growth of someone who is open to new ideas and the rigid minded person. If you put a new product on the market, or you are starting a new venture, you must put a efficient testing process in place and assess the results with an open mind. There are many methods to discover how a certain product is being received by the market. You must pay attention so you can do a realistic analysis of the product. Feedback is one of the most important factors in improving your business. You must listen to feedback and critical criticism and be willing to look at it objectively. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Each person has their own unique way of doing things. We all have our own little systems for staying organized, etc. The answer to whether you are organized or not is a simple one and only you know what it is.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Are you one of those people who has everything scattered to and fro? Change your habits and start finding a place for everything. You will gain a lot by doing so. Someone who lives amidst total clutter seldom gets their work done timely. Everything takes longer and their mind just can't be calm when surrounded by chaos. This just stands to reason. How can you function efficiently when you don't even know where anything is? You will really notice an improvement if you just take the time to organize everything. So, just do it!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Avoid thinking that sabotaged efforts seen in your business do not extend beyond that arena. If you find that you are very hard on your self, then that is something to pay attention to. Sometimes it seems that writers can suffer from that in an insidious way. The two traits, or learned behaviors of excessively critical and perfectionist, often go hand in hand. It is quite possible that parents who are overly critical of their children will cause them to become the same toward themselves. One of the keys to effectively dealing with this is awareness that you do it. That critical person inside you has to learn more positive attitudes such as becoming more compassionate toward your own self. This will take dedication, commitment and patience to make progress with. It is no joke that self improvement can be very tough to go through. The thing about this is the success of your business, and you, are at stake. But you should feel positive about this because if you can build a business, then you can blow through this, too.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>