<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="cb963734337f1635a52f127e7393d04d">			PKR Online Casino Review and Overview&lt;br /&gt;;Like the own before, PKR slots, PKR online casino is a great 3D internet gaming facility, presenting the best sophisticated and god dam suprising online casino experiences on the computer. PKR Casino shows by far the best futuristic gaming, from the 3D lobby to the tables and bandit machines, its like the thrill of looking around and playing at a totally real man built casino without even exiting your laptop desk.&lt;br /&gt;;Owned and run by PKR limited., PKR Casino was recently opened in November of 07, and has already become a highly rated partner of the online casino business, partly because to the extreme liking and modern design of PKR online poker. According to its many gamblers, 3D online casino gaming is the latest and greatest invention in the online gambling community. As another advantage, gamers of PKR online poker require no sign up, and may simply log into PKR Casino using their own PKR online poker Login ID.&lt;br /&gt;;PKR Casino Bonus and Offers&lt;br /&gt;;As a new gamer of the online casino industry, casino gamers can expect the best offers from PKR Casino right now. New gamers are due for a 100% bonus up to $200 on their initial deposit (lowest $35). Reload offers are frequently given via email, while VIP members are always eligible for a reload bonus.&lt;br /&gt;;play at the monthly featured game at PKR online casino to get amazing bonuses and prizes. The top 10 gamers for the month get a money prize. For example, the preferred game for the month of feb 09 was Roulette. The best 5 poker gamers throughout the entire month of jan - those who gambled the most, regardless of losing/winning - were awarded $500 cash.&lt;br /&gt;;NOTE: Offer package available only to gamblers signing up through paypal&lt;br /&gt;;PKR online casino has a great VIP Loyalty base based on Comp Point accumulation. Comp points are earned for playing slots games at the venue. The more comp points a player makes in a calendar month, the higher the VIP level is, from from Bronze to Silver, Gold and Platinum. The higher VIP level a gambler is, the higher the comp point to cash conv rate becomes. eg.., Bronze level awards $5 cash for every 100 comp points, making up to Platinum, which awards $2 cash for every _4|5|6|7}0 comp points.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Software&lt;br /&gt;;PKR online casino is pumped by the leading casino program developer, Playtech. The 3D images and avatar mobility are totally amazing. As expected, the provision of these stunning 3D online casino game play is only presented through a free software download - theres no Instant Play image online casino version as of yet. The downside to this is compatibility - Windows PC users will enjoy the 3D PKR online casino, but the software doesnt work with other op systems, like Mac.&lt;br /&gt;;Customer Support&lt;br /&gt;;The PKR company is well known for its professional customer support services and PKR Casino is no different. Contact PKR online casino cust support by email and through the online help form, or use the 24/7 Live internet Chat Support available in the forum and on the internet Support channel. The online forum is absolutely great, giving a sample attachment option if necessary.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5mYW5maWN0aW9uLm5ldC91LzM3ODM3NTYv" target="_blank"&gt;;pkr review&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="e484915c398157e9b5353a4408248b2d">			PKR Online Casino Review and Overview&lt;br /&gt;;Like the own before, PKR slots, PKR Casino is a great 3D internet gaming facility, showing the best sophisticated and downright entertaining casino experiences on the computer. PKR Casino shows by far the best realistic gambling, from the 3D lobby to the tables and slot machines, its like the drug of dancing around and playing at a real man built online casino without ever leaving your laptop chair.&lt;br /&gt;;belongiong and run by PKR limited., PKR online casino was recently opened in nov of 07, and has already become a highly rated part of the casino industry, mainly because to the overnight liking and great map of PKR online poker. According to its many gamers, 3D online casino gaming is the latest and greatest innovation in the online gambling world. As another advantage, players of PKR online poker need no registration, and may simply log into PKR online casino using their main PKR online poker Login ID.&lt;br /&gt;;PKR Online Casino Bonus and Offers&lt;br /&gt;;As a new part of the casino industry, online casino players can expect the best offers from PKR online casino right now. New players are eligible for a 100% offer up to $300 on their initial deposit (lowest $25). Reload offers are usually given via email, while valued VIP members are always eligible for a reload bonus.&lt;br /&gt;;Play the monthly dedicated game at PKR online casino to get special bonuses and gifts. The top 5 gamblers for the month find a money gift. For example, the preferred game for the month of January 2008 was slots. The best 15 poker gamers throughout the whole month of jan - those who gambled the most, regardless of losing/winning - were given $400 cash.&lt;br /&gt;;sidenote: Offer gift available only to gamblers signing up with CoinflipPoker&lt;br /&gt;;PKR Casino has a great VIP trusted base based on Comp Point accumulation. Comp points are earned for playing slots games at the online casino. The more comp points a gambler makes in a complete month, the bigger the VIP level is, ranging from Bronze to Silver, Gold and Platinum. The higher VIP level a player obtains, the higher the comp point to money conversion rate is. eg.., Bronze level awards $2 cash for every 300 comp points, making up to Platinum, which awards $4 cash for every _4|5|6|7}0 comp points.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Software&lt;br /&gt;;PKR Casino is fueled by the leading online casino program maker, Playtech. The 3D graphics and avatar mobility are simply astounding. As thought, the provision of these stunning 3D casino game play is only presented with a free software download - theres no Instant Play Flash casino version as of yet. The downside to this is compatibility - Windows PC users will enjoy the 3D PKR online casino, but the software doesnt work with other operating systems, like Mac.&lt;br /&gt;;Customer Support&lt;br /&gt;;The PKR online company is best known for it's great customer support advice and PKR Casino is no different. Contact PKR online casino customer support via email and through the internet help form, or use the 24/7 Live internet Chat Support available in the lobby and on the website Support page. The online forum is really useful, giving a sample attachment option if needed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RvcGZpZ2h0cy5uZXQvZm9ydW0vaW5kZXgucGhwP2FjdGlvbj1wcm9maWxlO3U9MTY4NTk2" target="_blank"&gt;;pkr review&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>