<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e069c139624ad1b159c3669dbcee7d70">			Computers have become an indispensable part of our lives. You need to use it for work, studies and even shopping over the web. There are few things though that you will do well to know so as to ensure that your experience of working on a computer remains a pleasant one without the hassles that can throw your work off schedule and require you to spend on computer repairs. Some precautions can make it a smooth sail for you. Let’s look at a few points to remember for the purpose.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Install anti-virus&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In a Linux based operating system, you do not necessarily need anti-virus software. In all other circumstances, you must have it installed on your system without fail. Keep the application updated for the latest threats that can affect your computer. Making use of the internet invariably constitutes a large part of our overall computer usage. Therefore, it is important that you protect your computer from unauthorized access, spyware and malware. Install appropriate internet security software, an anti-virus software and a firewall. A fact that deserves a mention here is that many spyware and malware applications gain access to computer systems masquerading as free anti-virus applications. Make sure you do not fall into such a trap.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Free resources only from trusted sources&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Download a file to read or free trial software only from websites that are trusted. Once the download is complete, check the files using anti-virus software before opening. Quarantine the file if it is infected. Do not use executable files from unreliable resources.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Defragmentation and [url=]computer repair[/url]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Disk check keeps a tab on errors in the disk and attends to them. Use it regularly. Disk defragmentation is needed to ensure that the performance of your computer does not suffer as you store more data on it. Defrag to get quicker access to data. The GUI interfaces in operating systems allow you to do all this at the click of a button.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Uninstall unused applications [url=]virus removal[/url]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The memory of your computer system is limited in size. Software that you install occupies a part of it. When a large chunk of the memory has been utilized, your system becomes slow. Uninstall applications that are of little use to you in order to free up the memory.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Avoid unknown applications&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Using a computer and even repairing minor glitches associated with your [url=]computer repair [/url][url=]laptop repair [/url]is fairly easy once you get a hang of things. This takes time. Till then, it is important to treat your computer with the respect it deserves. There is a process for everything and if you do not know how to go about it, do not undertake it. Else, you will end up paying more for repairs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even when you try to handle some troubleshooting issues yourself by referring to information available over the web, make sure that you use information only from reliable resources. Following just about any piece of information may do you more harm than good.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Despite the fact that computers are being used in every domain and these simplify and streamline our work to a great extent, the fact remains that these are machines that need to be handled well for a longer life span that is not saddled with frequent visits by a computer repairs specialist.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;About the author: Brianne is a blogger by profession. She loves writing on technology. Beside this she is fond of gadgets. Recently an article on 3d laptop attracted her attention. These days she is busy in writing an article on cool flash drives.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>