<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="746f8b0d28b2db323449f965983d5322">			It also has a blue LED fan which gives you one more color to work with. With all these cool features how can you refuse to pay just $109.99?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The other highly rated case is the NZXT Rogue Gaming Case. This custom built case is made with a 3mm black aluminum frame which is light enough to take to all those gaming parties. Never will this light weight case be an issue. The NZXT The Rouge Gaming Case has one of the leading cooling systems. We all know how heated those games can get - well no more. Not with this massive cooling device.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The Rogue comes with a great carrying strap, plenty of space for all four hard drives and those extra long video expansion cards. How Can you go wrong if your are just paying $124.99 for this amazing case?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another great choice is the Centurion 5 from Cooler Master. This case encompasses it all. The Centurion 5 has style and functionality. It comes to you with a sleek new design that features a clear window that is begging for the extras.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Since the designers at Cooler Master know you want to have more gaming time instead of spending your time setting up your computer into this new, sleek case; they have made this case tool free assembly friendly. That's right, no tools needed to set your computer up! Not only is it easy to set up, it has been designed to allow maximum airflow. This way, your computer will never seize up because it is so hot! This case sells for a measly $63.99.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In the gaming world, there are several options to choose from when it comes to the platform the game is being played on. There are PC games, and there are console games. The difference lies within the way the game is played.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Gaming is literally a lifestyle choice so each person prefers a slightly different approach when it comes to the way they play a game. Some like computer games, because computers allow them to customize the way they play the game along with certain tweaks in visual details and controls.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Consoles don't demand that you make such tweaks, since they're built with only games in mind. So when a game comes out and it's destined for PlayStation, then, if you own such a console, you're certain you can play that game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;But when a game comes out and it's made for PCs, then you have to check on what the system requirements that game has in order to be played properly. Since games rely heavily on the specs, or hardware of the &quot;;console&quot;; they're run, for PC users this would mean there's a constant struggle to stay ahead of the gaming developer world and build or purchase the ultimate gaming computer.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In certain cases, it's a lot easier to escape this struggle by purchasing a console and not having to worry if your system meets the necessary minimum hardware in order to run a game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The downside to consoles is, in my opinion, the lack of precision in movements and control. Additionally, you could also try installed a liquid-cooling system for maximum cooling effect.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb29sLWFuZC1xdWlldC5jby51ay9jb21wdXRlcl9jYXNlc19DMTE2Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;Computer Cases&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>