<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f3d8021890ba421b00a07c47880c6e24">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5qdWtlYm94YWxpdmUuY29tL2Jsb2cucGhwP2Jsb2dfaWQ9NTI3MTI5Mw__" target="_blank"&gt;;HAI flat irons&lt;/a&gt;; come in a variety of styles for customers who like quality, performance, and style. To the current end, you can find currently two very popular types of Hai flat iron that gives you great looking hair at under $50.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56aWtpLmNvbS9lbi9pZ25hY2lvLWZyb3N0KzczNTI4OC9wb3N0L0hhaS1mbGF0LWlyb24tcysxMzc1MDExOA__" target="_blank"&gt;;flat iron&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy52aWxhZ28yMS5jb20vZXZlbnQvVGhlK2Jlc3QraGFpcitzcmlnaHRlbmVyK2lzK2hhaStmbGF0K2lyb24vODg5MjIvcHJvZmlsZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;hair straightener&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hai Sparkle Therapy&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There's nothing worse than spending good time every day straightening your naturally curly hair and primping it to show the world, and then only an hour when you've stepped out in the hot, summer time heat or rain, it's only a frizzy mess. If it's not straight when, that's ok, just talk about it again or try turning the heat up a bit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rule: Keep on straightening until you've finished the bottom sections, then start on the top half and carry on until your whole head of hair is straight.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tip: Lightly apply some holding spray to remain your new, sleek form for longer, and if you are now living a humid climate you might like to use a serum special in repelling humidity. Now, feel free to keep benefits of the Hai flat iron to add flicks or maybe even a curling iron for extra style.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So there you might have it! Six steps to look from curly to straight with no hassle of visiting a hair salon (or the high fees). Just take into account that the best way to obtain smooth and shiny hair is to apply a good quality Hai flat iron in the beginning and taking good care of your hair. Even though good quality Hai flat irons involve far infrared heating with regard to moisturized locks and poor ion technology for frizz 100 % free results, you should always take any additional precautions to keep people hair soft and healthy at all times. This means not straightening on a regular basis, no matter how tempting it may be once you learn how to still do it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You can have that will model straight hair today with the help of a Hai flat iron. Not only does the Hai flat iron straighten your hair, it helps protect your hair from heat damage by allowing moisture being locked into your hair. This gives hair some sort of straight look with several shine. It also decreases frizz and fights next to humidity.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many Hai straightening irons are now being marketed today and you can find these hair strengtheners at places that carry hair maintenance systems. Being affordable in charge, a Hai hair iron is a superb choice for someone which wants their hair trend like they just stepped using a salon, but discover the results at home. It is important to find the very best product for a hair type and preferred look. There are many shapes, sizes, and types of Hai straightening irons, making the choices almost limitless.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Straightening irons are a good choice for people because otherwise, straightening would be accomplished by chemically treating this hair. Putting chemicals in nice hair can cause a whole lot of damage, and flat irons either straighten and protect nice hair against heat. Hai technology allows you to have your desired glimpse, without having to visit a salon or put harsh chemicals in your hair.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is important to buy quality hair products for your hair so you can maximize results. Other brands that are recognized for their &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5nb2xmc3dpbmdmcmVhay5jb20vZ3JvdXBzL3ZpZXcucGhwP2lkPTE2Njk4" target="_blank"&gt;;best flat iron&lt;/a&gt;; are BaByliss PRO, Warm Tools, and, FHI, HAI.		</conversation>		<conversation id="d5b99b408b975fd09638d29c0d593a1a">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hhaWZsYXRpcm9uai5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;HAI flat iron&lt;/a&gt;; come in a variety of styles for customers who like quality, performance, and style. Impress your friends with a new, straight style and find your HAI flat iron today.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Simply plug it in before you decide to jump in the hot shower, and it will end up nice and hot whenever you get out. The technology involved is pretty sophisticated as it dries your hair the same time that it straightens that. This one aspect totally eliminates that blow dryer from your life. Also, it uses steam hydration therapy to maintain hairs conditioned during the approach. It's fast and your hair will stay straight the entire day.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hai may be making cutting edge personal care products for over 70 a long time, so when they entered the Hai flat iron fray, they were going to make waves because skin color time they put inside research and development. There are expensive flat irons, together with what everybody considers your cheaper counterparts. If you ever don't want to pluck down $100 for a flat iron that is supposed to be the be all and end all in regards to hair straightening, your next option is to consider the next best thing you can find at an affordable price tag. The Hai flat iron certainly meets this standard by a mile.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Females, with naturally curly or rough hair, are always looking for tools and products that permit them to obtain that &quot;smooth and silky&quot; look without having to spend hours in the bathroom. Hai focuses on creating hair care items that won't put a dent inside your budget, but perform as well as the higher end tools. To the current end, there are actually currently two very popular types of Hai flat iron that gives you great looking hair at under $50.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hai Sparkle Therapy&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There's nothing worse than spending good time in the morning straightening your naturally curly hair and primping it showing the world, and only an hour when you've stepped out in the hot, summer time heat or rain, it's nothing but a frizzy mess. Makes you ought to throw a scarf around bonce and just forget about even bothering with this particular whole straightening thing. Besides, that you desire to get your unruly mane at bay. Can we really go the whole day which has no frizz?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Yes, it's with the Shine Therapy Hai flat iron. When frizz, heat and humidity are your main enemies, next get this tool to help you out fight and win your battle. This iron is manufactured to straighten your hair while making it feel like resistant to most moist conditions. A specialized feature is that this ceramic plates are infused which has a blend of conditioners and avocado oil. Other brands that are known for their &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2ZyZWVtYW5nYW1ibDUxMi5vdmVyLWJsb2cuY29tL3BhZ2VzL2hhaS1mbGF0LWlyb24taGFpci1zdHJhaWdodGVuaW5nLXNvbHV0aW9uLTYzOTg4MDYuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;flat iron&lt;/a&gt;; are BaByliss PRO, Warm Tools, and, FHI, HAI. This is why professional hair irons add a variable heat setting so you can control the temperature used on your hair.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>