<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="f28350c769c60750576064f9c51d59b8">			When writing a press release, keep it enthusiastic and informative; you don't want it to come across as salesy or like a product review. Highlight your business in a way that captures attention. Some of the free press release sites include PRlog.org, freepressrelease.com and npr.org.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;Articles - one of my FAVORITES!&lt;/strong&gt;; Articles are a great way to drive free targeted traffic to your affiliate offer. Write your best articles and submit them to some of the top article directories, optimizing your articles for keywords and phrases people looking for your product/service would likely use when searching. Link to your site from your author resource box at the bottom of your article.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The great thing about articles is that they can be used in so many ways; on your website or blog, for the article directories, even as a short report to give away to your subscribers when you put a few of your articles together in a package.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;SEO or search engine optimization.&lt;/strong&gt;; Yes, I know this sounds a little scary but it's really quite simple. Optimizing your blog or website simply means using context and keywords that help the search engines find your site when a person is searching for information, and building back-links (incoming links) to your site. While there is a little more involved, these are the basic two things you need to concentrate on.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You'll also want to write good titles for your pages and a good meta description. You can learn a lot about search engine optimization at Search Engine Watch.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Blog commenting, guest posting on other relevant blogs and pinging each time you update are a few other strategies you should be using to increase traffic to your affiliate website or blog.  As you can see, there are plenty of ways to market your site and get traffic even when you don't have a dime to spend!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Before we go into the ten affiliate marketing secrets to supercharge your affiliate site profits, you need to make sure you have a proper running website that promotes affiliate products. These tips just would not work if you are simply using a &quot;cookie-cutter&quot; duplicate affiliate website that the product owner has handed to you that thousand others have. Okay, if you have a website created with unique content to promote affiliate programs, here are the secrets to make your affiliate marketing site a successful one.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Provide unique content. You often hear people say that Content is King. This is a half-truth. Content is not King, Unique Content is. Give your prospects good informational content that really is targeted to help them. It is fine if you come across a few good articles and decide to post them on your website to add value. But be sure to obtain the permission of the original content writer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Holistic website theme. The whole theme of your website must flow well throughout the page. This means that the graphics and logo must blend well to project a natural and professional look.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. I hope you enjoy reading this article on affiliate marketing secrets and apply the methods here in your campaigns.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're thinking about a great deal more information on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb25xdWVyZWRyaWNoZXMuY29tL2FmZmlsaWF0ZS1tYXJrZXRpbmctc2VjcmV0cy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;affiliate marketing secrets&lt;/a&gt;; then see the website today.		</conversation>		<conversation id="f85dc6d27f65c140c6d6382dfb8f399d">			Getting your e-mails through the spam and junk mail gates are imperative to the success of your marketing efforts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Handle list management and analysis. A good autoresponder will help you collect and process information about the effectiveness of your efforts. Internet marketers should be able to review their subscribers, read any messages they may have been sent and analyze clicks and historical page open rates to further refine their efforts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the key affiliate marketing secrets is auto responder delivery rates. A good autoresponder provides good delivery rates and is easy to use for list management and analysis purposes, you're in good shape.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;The following is a review of three of the top autoresponders&lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Aweber&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Using Aweber correctly is one of the easiest affiliate marketing secrets to master. Aweber is a simple to use program that allows marketers to quickly and easily insert audio or video into their pages and manage subscribers, even substantial lists of them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's easy to schedule and sequence using Aweber, and the program is very straightforward and intuitive. Aweber also offers a very useful tracking function that allows you to keep track of how successful your efforts are.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Autoresponse Plus&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Autoresponse Plus is another great program. If you're looking for quality affiliate marketing secrets, you need to learn the ins and outs of this program. You pay a one-time fee for the use of this program, but it's money well spent. You'll need someone with extensive tech knowledge to tutor you to get the full use of this program, however.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Get Response&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br&gt;;Get response is another one of the great affiliate marketing secrets to success. This is an industry leading program that stacks up well to Aweber. It's easy to use, customizable and allows for a great range of uses. Isn't it amazing!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Therefore if you ask me whether it is possible or not to make a living with affiliate marketing, I think that it is more than just possible, it is definitely achievable!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;After reading that news, I went to join the list of that marketer and study his affiliate marketing secrets that allows him to become a super affiliate making a six figures income every month.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is some of the affiliate marketing Secrets I observed from that marketer&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Secrets Number 1)&lt;/b&gt;; He builds a huge list that he can promote to constantly&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Secrets Number 2)&lt;/b&gt;; He becomes the Super Affiliate for some of the most well known marketers and then do a joint venture with them&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Secrets Number 3)&lt;/b&gt;; He creates his own product and get other affiliates to work for him&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;;Secrets Number 4)&lt;/b&gt;; He constantly do joint ventures with other well known affiliates&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Secrets Number 5)&lt;/b&gt;; He builds solid relationship with his list&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you really take some time to study the affiliate marketing Secrets of successful marketers, you will find that they are practically doing it the same way.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Therefore you should spend some time to study some of the successful marketers that you look upon and try to become their super affiliates so that you can become their joint venture in the future.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is in fact the top affiliate marketing secrets to becoming a super affiliate.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In the event you would like more info on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jb25xdWVyZWRyaWNoZXMuY29tL2FmZmlsaWF0ZS1tYXJrZXRpbmctc2VjcmV0cy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;affiliate marketing secrets&lt;/a&gt;; checkout the website these days.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>