<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="14af4c85690659eef68b1a25b2b61c5">			That's an exciting step to take. Watch out, because you may get lost in all of the information that is available. Use the tips offered here to get you started with your own beauty regimen.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A healthy, nutritious diet is a natural, simple way to stay beautiful. A nutritious diet will keep you looking and feeling great. If you follow a healthy diet and nutrition plan you will not only look better, but you will feel better.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you want to brighten up your skin during the winter, consider a moisturizer or bronzer with warmer undertones. Both pink or gold ones work well. Use a cosmetics sponge to apply the product to your brow bones and the apples of your cheeks to add a glowing, radiant effect. It can make you look shiny if you use too much.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Eye cover up should be used before any eye makeup. Cover ups help to hide imperfections in the skin. Don't apply concealer too hard, or it can irritate your skin.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A good natural way to moisturize your hair is to rub two olive oil tablespoons into your scalp, then dampen a towel with warm water and wrap your hair. Get the oil out with shampoo about a half-hour later for silky lustrous hair.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use a moisturizer on your face. Moisturizers should be used on the face regardless of the skin type. Sun protection is very important so make sure the moisturizer you choose has an SPF value.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sharpen your eyeliner pencils and lip liners often. They will then be clean and safe to use. A handy trick to help make sharpening of make-up pencils easy is to put them in to the fridge or freezer for around 10 minutes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once you apply the lipstick, especially if its a dark shade, you want to put your finger in your mouth, pull the skin out then use your lips to make an &quot;O&quot; shape while sliding your finger around. This helps to take away any lipstick that has gone into your mouth, which could get on your teeth, and doesn't affect the lipstick on the outside.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When applying eyeshadow, look downward and toward the mirror. Don't attempt to pull on your eyelids. Looking down will allow you to get the first application right. Apply your shadow carefully, and you will not need to stretch your lid.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Your hair follicles are still going to be open and that will create a problem. For example, you may experience discomfort and irritation. Another product that should be avoided directly after waxing or sugaring is scented products. They can cause irritation to the skin that is difficult to relieve.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sunglasses may enhance a person's beauty, or they may hide it! The person wearing them needs to decide this prior to wearing a pair. Questions like, &quot;Should I wear sunglasses indoors?&quot; &quot;, are all things you should ask yourself.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As you can see, there are many techniques and products to make yourself appear more beautiful. Try these simple steps to increase your own beauty, and feel positive about yourself when others perceive the beautiful new you, both inside and out. You know how to look good all the time.&lt;br /&gt;;To uncover more, stop by &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5wZXRyb3NzaWFuLmZy" target="_blank"&gt;;recette apéritif&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zY2FsYWV1cm9wZS5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;shorty minceur&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>