<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="147d2b32f4b301797cbaf33ded67c099">			I mentioned I no longer attended church solutions in Toledo, but if I did it would be on the same day as Jesus Christ worshiped - the seventh day Sabbath.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I mentioned how Protestants are nevertheless bowing down to Rome, to the pagan popes and Constantine, and not following Jesus' instance. She asked if she could at least leave me a Bible tract she had in hand. When I saw it talked about going to Heaven, I asked them why they were spreading such religious lies - that the Bible under no circumstances provides Heaven as the reward of the saved, but that Jesus clearly stated &quot;the meek shall inherit the Earth.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I stated everybody has at least heard that Scripture, and they agreed. I mentioned the Bible says no such thing about going to Heaven. The other girl piped up and said it did. I asked her if she would please show me then. She sort of stomped following to me and turned to a Scripture in which it states we've all fallen quick of the glory of God and are sinners, and I stated, &quot;Yes, that's correct, but nowhere does it say something about going to Heaven.&quot; She then turned to another Scripture that also mentions our sinful state and I again said, &quot;Yes, but that says practically nothing about going to Heaven.&quot; She appeared flustered and spouted, &quot;But they display us how to get to Heaven.&quot; And I disagreed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I asked them to ask their minister why they're telling men and women they go to Heaven when Jesus taught &quot;the meek shall inherit the Earth.&quot; I encouraged them to find out what the Bible truly teaches. They virtually ran off the porch, and the fellows next door - nobody answered there - who had been listening, mentioned, &quot;You have a nice day!&quot; I said, &quot;I'm not your enemy. Don't be afraid of the truth - let it set you no cost. Tell your minister Jesus Christ stated &quot;the meek shall inherit the Earth.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;They reminded of these old dolls or toys where you pull the string and they have a number of recorded messages, like - &quot;I enjoy you!&quot; When I broke their spell, they were at a loss and confused, the truth didn't compute with their standard way of thinking. I hope they can discover the truth about staying born once more and Heaven and Hell. I've prayed for them, due to the fact I deeply appreciate how God started teaching me truths when I was a teenager.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Then a week or so later, several Mormon fellows stopped just as I was obtaining ready to go on a bike ride. They had been also dressed nicely, with their white shirts and ties and dress pants. One &quot;elder&quot; was from the state of Washington and the other &quot;elder&quot; (both had been significantly younger than me) was from Arizona. I asked if people in their states didn't will need to hear what they had to say. They essentially stated they had a lot of Mormons out there.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I talked about how I agreed we're the so-called &quot;Lost Ten Tribes of Israel,&quot; but that due to the fact they supposedly know that, it's all the a lot more reason they shouldn't be maintaining pagan holidays pretending to be Christian and Sunday as an alternative of the seventh day Sabbath and biblical festivals that Jesus Christ and the Church of God kept and hold (which portray God's strategy of salvation for all mankind). They feel to get paid for church service is priest craft and according to the Bible that is not how Christ would do factors.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shiblon.com%2Fbeliefs%2Fwhat-do-mormons-believe.php"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shiblon.com/beliefs/what-do-mormons-believe.php&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightplanet.com%2Fmormons%2Fdaily%2Fmissionary%2Fmormon_missionaries.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lightplanet.com/mormons/daily/missionary/mormon_missionaries.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dearelder.com%2Findex%2Finc_name%2FMormon%2Ftitle2%2FMormon_Beliefs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dearelder.com/index/inc_name/Mormon/title2/Mormon_Beliefs&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="7437f74bd9824144c82a95b303bd1ef1">			These too are other elements that exist in the Mormon Church and come from powerful belief in God, Jesus Christ, the Holy Ghost and modern-day day revelation provided to their prophets, just like in bible instances. Even although you may not share the exact same beliefs that Mormons do, or comprehend their culture, substantially of what they do and who they are come from deep roots of faith and a robust belief in their church.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Increasing up as a member of The Church of Jesus Christ of Latter-day Saints (LDS or Mormon Church), I spent a lot of time defending my religion against questions and attacks from pals, household members, and acquaintances of mine in several Christian denominations. Most of these people don't agree on a lot of of the crucial aspects of their respective belief techniques, but they were united in their belief that the teachings of the LDS Church were not Christian. I typically wondered why my belief program was singled out by so a lot of Christians as getting unacceptable and out of the mainstream. More than the years, which have integrated serving a two-year mission for the Church, receiving temple ordinances, and raising a young household actively in the Church, I've come to fully grasp that, ironically adequate, The Church of Jesus Christ is certainly exceptional when regarded as in the context of twenty-1st century Christianity.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;A recent web search for topics related to Mormonism brought me to a internet web-site for an organization known as Christian Apologetics and Research Ministry (CARM). I saw that they had a page on their website entitle &quot;Mormon words do not imply the same thing.&quot; I took a number of minutes to see how my church's words &quot;don't mean the identical factor.&quot; The page is created up mostly of the a table with two columns, one representing the LDS Church's teachings and the other alleging a biblical contrast. Here's an example:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ADAMLDS - Father of physical mankind. Adam is also known as Michael the archangel, the ancient of days, (D&amp;C 116).Bible - the very first designed man by whom all of humanity descends. He was not Michael the archangel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;My initially thought on studying this entry was, &quot;In which does the Bible state that Adam is not Michael the archangel.&quot; Conveniently, this author left off a reference for that. Through the teachings of living prophets members of the LDS Church have a incredibly clear understanding of Adam's pre-mortal function as Michael in the creation of this earth.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This illustration of a person attempting in vain to discredit Mormonism illustrates my understanding of the Protestant point of view on what we look at to be the Restored Gospel of Jesus Christ. Let me clarify. Suppose you have been in an art museum, and you observed a painting hung on the wall in the next room. Built on centuries of guesswork mingled with scripture right after the original Church of Jesus Christ was swept from the earth by apostasy, Protestant Christianity has bred 1000's of diverse congregations believing all manner of doctrines, several of which are diametrically inconsistent and conflicting.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For those Christians who are wasting time ridiculing what we see as members of The Church of Jesus Christ, we invite you to take a number of actions closer.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.shiblon.com%2Fbeliefs%2Fwhat-do-mormons-believe.php"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.shiblon.com/beliefs/what-do-mormons-believe.php&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.lightplanet.com%2Fmormons%2Fdaily%2Fmissionary%2Fmormon_missionaries.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.lightplanet.com/mormons/daily/missionary/mormon_missionaries.html&lt;/a&gt;; ,  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.dearelder.com%2Findex%2Finc_name%2FMormon%2Ftitle2%2FMormon_Beliefs"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.dearelder.com/index/inc_name/Mormon/title2/Mormon_Beliefs&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>