<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="5de98f2b0ca244e811013d4e8276b6a8">			Before employing a new Lenormand Oracle deck of cards I advise &quot;cleansing&quot; your deck from all energies and to assist bond it together with your own power. You will find different techniques it is possible to obtain this. I personally use white sage and waft the smoke around a new deck of cards, and specially soon after somebody has somehow managed to touch them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Findependent.academia.edu%2FDonniePuckett%2FBlog%2F42826%2Foracle-de-Belline-Which-Should-I-Read-With---An-Oracle-or-a-Tarot-Deck-268"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://independent.academia.edu/DonniePuckett/Blog/42826/oracle-de-Belline-Which-Should-I-Read-With---An-Oracle-or-a-Tarot-Deck-268&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Other techniques would be to surround the cards around a white candle, or use crystals or basically just hold the pack of cards, visualising a white light soaking your cards and cleansing them and last but not least keep in mind to ask your angels, guides and your higher self to supply you with the insight and understanding and to bring forth messages that you can interpret.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.democratandchronicle.com%2Fapps%2Fpbcs.dll%2Fsection%3Fcategory%3DPluckPersona%26amp%3BU%3D937cb3374a3e4fb3b0b926fb683b71d9%26amp%3BplckPersonaPage%3DBlogViewPost%26amp%3BplckUserId%3D937cb3374a3e4fb3b0b926fb683b71d9%26amp%3BplckPostId%3DBlog%253a937cb3374a3e4fb3b0b926fb683b71d9Post%253abc0db355-9cdf-4b8b-8149-0973c20e9234%26amp%3BplckBlogItemsPerPage%3D5"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.democratandchronicle.com/apps/pbcs.dll/section?category=PluckPersona&amp;U=937cb3374a3e4fb3b0b926fb683b71d9&amp;plckPersonaPage=BlogViewPost&amp;plckUserId=937cb3374a3e4fb3b0b926fb683b71d9&amp;plckPostId=Blog%3a937cb3374a3e4fb3b0b926fb683b71d9Post%3abc0db355-9cdf-4b8b-8149-0973c20e9234&amp;plckBlogItemsPerPage=5&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whenever you get a new Lenormand Oracle deck, the cards might be in numerical order from 1 to 36. The first thing you have to do is to thoroughly mix the deck. A straightforward method to do this would be to deal the cards randomly into three heaps; re-assemble the deck; shuffle it, then repeat the method two or 3 times. It really is a great thought to mix the deck in this way right after each reading, specifically when you deal the cards instead of draw them. This may ensure that runs of cards are broken up between each and every reading.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Two of the &quot;people&quot; cards have unique significance. The Gentleman and the Lady represent the querent, respectively the male or female individual for whom the oracle is being consulted. These cards may also be used to represent the querent's problem or question in some layouts; as an example, the card most associated with the issue could be utilised - the Heart for a question about love, the Ship about travel along with the Fish about capital etc. The card made use of to represent the querent or issue is known as the &quot;Significator&quot; or &quot;Key Card.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If your layout needs a Significator positioned at a certain location, then make a decision which card to use as the Significator and eliminate it from the deck and place it in front of you, commonly this card will be placed inside the centre of the spread.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now it is actually time to mix the cards prior to spreading the layout. Either shuffle the cards (but not utilizing the card player's riffle shuffle) or spread them face down on a table and mix them around. While mixing the cards, concentrate on the querent or the querent's concern. Don't hurry this mixing, it truly is time for you to deal with the cards and connect with them. Quit mixing when it feels proper to do so.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.oracle-de-belline.fr%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.oracle-de-belline.fr/&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Next cut the cards, either with a single cut or into 3 piles which you then reassemble, still focusing on the querent or the querent's problem. Should you be employing a Significator, then bear in mind to place it within the centre of the table. You may now either deal cards or draw cards to form your layout. Personally, I have a tendency to draw cards for modest layouts but deal the cards for the full 36 card layouts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To draw cards, take the deck and spread it to ensure that the cards slightly overlap face down inside the type of a ribbon or fan across the table. Draw cards 1 at a time as necessary from the fan with your left hand (the hand closest towards the heart). Enable your intuition to guide you in drawing the cards - pick the card that 'feels right'.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're dealing the cards, you could set them either face up or face down in the suitable location inside your layout. For anyone who is drawing the cards then you have to keep them face down until the layout is completed. This would be to avoid any emotion, either positive or negative, that you simply could really feel after you see a card from affecting subsequent drawings.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Once the layout is total, turn the cards face up ready to start your reading!		</conversation>	</conversations></author>