<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="6c6464f9a1e65c94d9112121dda06bd6">			Local SEO has become the new &quot;;it&quot;; marketing technique for local businesses because it offers great response. Below are a few local SEO tips that you can use to grow your business. Some examples of this can be the searches for &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hZGhkbWVkaWNhdGlvbnNsaXN0Lm5ldC9hZGhkLW1lZGljYXRpb24tdHJlYXRtZW50LWRvLXlvdS1rbm93LXdoYXQtdGhlLWFsdGVybmF0aXZlcy1hcmU_" target="_blank"&gt;ADHD Treatment&lt;/a&gt; in some place of your city.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As a marketer using local SEO, you really have to get into the mindset of someone in your target market who is doing a search engine query. It's helpful to put yourself in their place if you want to apply SEO to your site. Whatever product or service you have, you need to ask yourself, what would your potential customers enter into the search box to reach you and purchase your product? If your store specialized in golf accessories, for example, you would try to picture how people would search for your products. People who search for the word &quot;;golf&quot;; are probably not going to be your customers, as this is a very general term. And if they put in &quot;;golf clubs,&quot;; it's still not a good match since your store doesn't sell golf items other than the accessories. Those who enter, &quot;;golf accessories,&quot;; however, are likely to be looking for what you have, so this is a good keyword to target. Many small businesses with websites bypass keyword phrases that are not the most popular but that could still generate customers. They are fixated on the top keywords that get most of the traffic, but that thousands of others are also targeting. It helps you to target the most effective keywords if you can put yourself in the customer's place. Once you perfect the art of targeting such specific keywords, you'll not only increase sales but also get higher rankings on multiple keywords. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you've used SEO for quite some time, you know how important the title tag is. New marketers are quick to forget the importance of title tags, but they can actually help you achieve a higher ranking. Your title tag is vital to local SEO. One great part about going after local searches is that the competition is much scarcer than if you were to use keywords that were more broad.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This is why all title tags must have the keywords you have decided to use, and they must also include what city and state you've decided to target. This would allow you to tell the search engines what you're exactly looking for. This is the most important aspect of SEO and you can't ignore it. Keep in mind that you'll want to keep your keywords to a minimum within your title tags, so that confusion is impossible. So, you can see this? for example you can make a campaing for &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hZGhkbWVkaWNhdGlvbnNsaXN0Lm5ldC9hLWZldy1hZGhkLXRyZWF0bWVudC1vcHRpb25zLWJlZm9yZS1qdW1waW5nLXRvLW1lZGljYXRpb24_" target="_blank"&gt;Treatment for ADHD&lt;/a&gt; in Texas or New York.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You need to make your anchor texts diverse. Long tail keywords can do quite a bit to help you with your Local SEO efforts--every SEO marketer understands just how valuable long tail keywords can be with search engine marketing. This gives you the opportunity to play around with the anchor text of your links, which means you should try to have a wide variety of anchor text diversification to expand your reach. For example let's say you sell chocolate in New York: don't just concentrate on &quot;;New York Chocolate Store&quot;;. Try to create incoming links that use other types of the same phrase like &quot;;Chocolate Store in New York&quot;; or &quot;;Chocolate Stores in Manhattan, New York.&quot;; No matter what, always remember that search engines give a lot of weight to anchor texts so you need to implement as many variations as you can so that you will be able to increase your rankings. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you use these local SEO tactics, you will find that you can get publicity for your business and more traffic to your site.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ibG9nY2F0YWxvZy5jb20vZGlzY3Vzcy9lbnRyeS8zLXNpbXBsZS1sb2NhbC1zZW8tdGlwcy15b3UtY2FuLXVzZS1ub3c_" target="_blank"&gt;Important SEO Tips to Help Your Business&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy56ZXN0eS1pcmMubmV0L2luZGV4LnBocD9wPWJsb2dzL3dyaXRlc3Rvcnlwb3N0" target="_blank"&gt;Local SEO - All You Need to Know&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy53b294aWUuY29tL2Jsb2cvMzc0Mi9iZXN0LXRlY2huaXF1ZXMtdG8tZ2VuZXJhdGUtbG9jYWwtdHJhZmZpYy1mcm9tLXRoZS1zZWFyY2gtZW5naW5lcw__" target="_blank"&gt;Using Local SEO for Targeted Traffic&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>		<conversation id="fd78987fb737f00d630aa84a02f10be5">			Have you attempted every means necessary to achieve a higher level for your site when it comes to the search engines? Why aren't you seeing the outcome you want? There exist brand new owners of websites whose attempts at getting increased in the search engine rankings don't work because they don't do what they're required to. The ranking rules search engines use are always being reworked and so the ways to get websites optimized for ranking well are never the same. If you are aiming to beat your competitors and maintain the first listing for Google, it's best not to make the mistakes you're about to read about. Working on these will help you get better results from your efforts, regardless of your budget. So if you can ranks some keywords like  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hZGhkbWVkaWNhdGlvbnNsaXN0Lm5ldC9hZGhkLW1lZGljYXRpb24tdHJlYXRtZW50LWRvLXlvdS1rbm93LXdoYXQtdGhlLWFsdGVybmF0aXZlcy1hcmU_" target="_blank"&gt;ADHD Treatment&lt;/a&gt; you need to put close atention to this mistakes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Graphics and images are a good way to give your site instant appeal, but be careful about putting too many on your site or you'll be damaging your SEO efforts. Too many images and graphics means you're leaving less room for the search engine friendly content, which can reduce your overall search engine rankings. Even though your images might have text on them, they're not the same as the plain text on your site. Any text you have showing within images can't be read by the search engines, which means they can't use those words for SEO purposes. If you do decide to use some images, keep in mind that putting your site's keywords in the image's ALT tag can help you. This way search engines would be able to read this attribute in the image, which will ultimately help your ranking. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you do use images, make sure they all have ALT tags. While a photo loads, ALT tags describe what it is.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You should also know that ALT tags in your images help you get a higher place within the searches. People usually don't remember this about optimizing websites. So you should include keywords with your ALT tags so that you appeal to both human readers and search engines. So, remember that you need to avoid all this errors if you want to rank high for your keywords whatever they may be since &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hZGhkbWVkaWNhdGlvbnNsaXN0Lm5ldC9hLWZldy1hZGhkLXRyZWF0bWVudC1vcHRpb25zLWJlZm9yZS1qdW1waW5nLXRvLW1lZGljYXRpb24_" target="_blank"&gt;Treatment for ADHD&lt;/a&gt; to Cars BMW.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Another SEO problem is choosing a bad title and description, as these can also affect your search engine rankings. Your title and description are used by the search engines to determine your site's theme and rank it accordingly. Compared to a few years ago, search engines and their algorithms for determining rankings have evolved, so pay attention to these elements. Therefore, always use good ethics when conducting your SEO practices. There exist quite a few webmasters who don't know that they're hurting their chances for success by making these mistakes. If you just fill your site with various keywords, it will look like it's a spam site. Similarly, having copied content will tarnish your reputation and get you in the bad books of the search engines. So, if you are going to go about SEO on your own, or you're in the market to hire someone to do it, the best SEO practices are the only ones to use.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>