<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d880407a64d911a937db03377f1faf6e">			If you intend to shop for this item, you are able to usually have them at reasonable prices online. A good example could be the Philip PD7112/37 7 inches LCD Dual Screen Portable DVD is actually accessible for $120.99 as well as the 9&quot; inch of the model is $164.11.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Choosing a quality dual headrest car DVD player is a wonderful treat that you can give yourself and your family enjoying every moment for being out and about. Outfitting your car or truck with entertainment makes trips fun again.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;On this episode of Car DVD player 101, we are going to have a discussion on the question: what is ATSC? How does it are employed in an automobile DVD player.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ATSC stands for &quot;Advanced Television Systems Committee.&quot; Actually it's a list of standards on what sound and video are encoded and transmitted, which now includes 18 popular digital formats.T he United states of america could be the first country in The united states to give up analog broadcasting signal which supplies an inadequate quality of picture and sound compared with perhaps the lowest quality standard of ATSC. Canada and Mexico are now considering create a sweeping switch from analog signals to ATSC.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;HDTV is the top amount of ATSC standards, but whether you could view a high-definition picture and hear an obvious sound is dependent upon two factors. First the station which you followed must be broadcasting a high-definition signal that meet ATSC standards, secondly you have to have the best device to obtain and examine it so that you should get a overall picture on the equipment that you just forked out money for.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vertical Scan Lines&lt;br /&gt;;Vertical scan lines make reference to the quantity of lines of horizontal type a tv is capable of showing to produce a picture. Because the quantity of lines increase, more details is displayed, resulting in better picture quality. Traditional analog TVs can show approximately 480 lines, while high-definition television is capable of showing up to 1080 lines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Horizontal Pixels&lt;br /&gt;;Each horizontal line in a TV comprises of individual dots (pixels). The higher the quantity of pixels, the finer the TV picture becomes. Horizontal pixel measurements using better technology can range from 250 for the VCR up to 500 for any DVD player. Typical digital TV broadcasts have at least 640 pixels.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Aspect Ratio&lt;br /&gt;;Aspect ratio identifies precisely the television screen's width over its height. A 16:9 aspect ratio refers to a wide-screen picture format, while a 4:3 identifies an ordinary TV format.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Scan Mode&lt;br /&gt;;Interlaced scanning is a method that can cause a TV picture with alternating lines of information and is the main cause for flickering. Progressive scanning is a technique that creates a TV picture with consecutive lines of data that ends up with flicker-free image quality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Frame Rate&lt;br /&gt;;Motion picture with your TV is generated with a group of still pictures that changes from picture to picture in a extremely fast rate. This rate is measured from the variety of still pictures (frames) displayed within one second of their time. The larger the frame-rate, the smoother the image displayed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In this next topic we can learn more about how HDTV works.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.importpris.no%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.importpris.no/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f4bb30166d7d45af6370da559114df9f">			Upload your favourite things on Portable DVD Player and share any documents you wish to anyone you would like! Watch any video type you wish from DivX to DVD yet others. Features like DVD-RS memory and different connectors for a multichannel audio system in your house...&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here is our set of Best Portable Car DVD Players entirely on Amazon:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&amp;nbsp;Philips PET1030 10.2 inch with Car Kit&lt;br /&gt;;  &amp;nbsp;NU CineTrek 8.5 Inch - Car Kit&lt;br /&gt;;  &amp;nbsp;AudioVox D1988PK 9Inch - Slim - Car Kit&lt;br /&gt;;  &amp;nbsp;Philips PET708/37 - Dual Screen - Car Mount Kit&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;With this episode of Car DVD player 101, we're going to possess a discussion on the question: precisely what is ATSC? How can it are employed in a car DVD player.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;ATSC symbolizes &quot;Advanced Television Systems Committee.&quot; Actually this is a number of standards on how sound and video are encoded and transmitted, which now includes 18 widely used digital formats.T he United States may be the first country in North America to quit analog broadcasting signal which offers an unhealthy quality of picture and sound in comparison with the lowest quality standard of ATSC. Canada and Mexico are considering produce a sweeping switch from analog signals to ATSC.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;HDTV is the top amount of ATSC standards, but whether you could potentially see a high-definition picture and listen to a clear sound depends upon two factors. First the station which you followed really should be broadcasting a high-definition signal that meet ATSC standards, secondly you want the right device to get and view it which means you should get a overall picture around the equipment you shelled out money for.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Vertical Scan Lines&lt;br /&gt;;Vertical scan lines refer to how many lines of horizontal type a tv is capable of showing to make a photo. Since the quantity of lines increase, more info is displayed, resulting in better display quality. Traditional analog TVs can show approximately 480 lines, while high-definition television is capable of showing around 1080 lines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Horizontal Pixels&lt;br /&gt;;Each horizontal line in a very TV comprises of individual dots (pixels). The higher the quantity of pixels, the finer the television picture becomes. Horizontal pixel measurements using advancements can vary from 250 to get a VCR up to 500 to get a DVD player. Typical digital TV broadcasts have at the very least 640 pixels.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Aspect Ratio&lt;br /&gt;;Aspect ratio identifies exactely the TV screen's width over its height. A 16:9 aspect ratio identifies a wide-screen picture format, while a 4:3 is the term for a regular TV format.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Scan Mode&lt;br /&gt;;Interlaced scanning is a method that induce a TV picture with alternating lines of knowledge and is the source for flickering. Progressive scanning is a method that produces a TV picture with consecutive lines of data that brings about flicker-free picture quality.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Frame Rate&lt;br /&gt;;Motion picture on the TV is generated using a combination of still pictures that changes from picture to picture at a very fast rate. This minute rates are measured because of the variety of still pictures (frames) displayed within one second of your time. The higher the frame-rate, the smoother the picture displayed.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In your next topic we are going to find out about how HDTV works.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.importpris.no%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.importpris.no/&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>