<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="eb8fea908e347a5b2658213d3d23724">			For example, if you have a great hourglass figure, you will need to highlight your natural curvaceous - do this by wearing tailored tops and trousers. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Color and Material &lt;/b&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; In order to wear flattering clothes when we are overweight, we need to choose the right material and colours. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Generally, you have got to select materials that are generally lightweight; a heavier material will add bulk for your frame and make people appear larger. Avoid fabrics that cling, as they tend to take some action in all the drastically wrong places, and this holds true even when worn relating to the smallest of figures. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Darker clothes enjoy the most slimming effect. When setting up an outfit, choose colours which can be complementary, rather than another, as the contrast effect breaks up the line of your body completely, and the longer that line, the taller people appear, the taller you appear, the slimmer you look. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;1940's Women's fashion was an occasion of great restrictions with design, fabric, and trim materials. The war forced clothing designs to become simple yet it also forced manufactures to become creative with what they could use and invent new materials. The 1940's introduced new women's fashion inventions many of which are still approximately today. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;ol&gt;; &lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; This girdle. &lt;/strong&gt;; Prior to the 1940's a women's shape was that is generated by metal boned corsets. In the 1940's that girdle was invented as some sort of tummy tuck underwear. It shaped just the middle down to the body and created the smooth hourglass silhouette with vintage fashions. The girdle was distressing and was eventually replaced by nylons or no shaping undergarment whatsoever. Today the girdle returns with body shapers, regulate top stockings, control top underwear and other suck and smooth base garments. They name can have changed but these garments are just updated girdles in disguise. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; Wedge shoes. &lt;/strong&gt;; Leather and wood was needed for the war so shoe designs must get creative. The answer was cork. A cork sole was used for shoe heels and then wrapped in a pretty fabric, mesh or simply reptile skin. It was economical and allowed a taller heel then that which was considered a safe heeled water pump. Today wedgies come in and out of fashion, particularly in summer, when wedge sandals hit the beaches. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; Rayon &lt;/strong&gt;;. If you didn't fully understand, Rayon is a man made fabric. It was invented and became extremely popular in the 1940's. Up till then wool, silk, and cotton was what clothing was made of. Silk and cotton were needed for the war so Rayon was used instead. It would be lightweight like silk or even heavy like wool. Today rayon is still used in fine clothing, especially in summer. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; Nylons &lt;/strong&gt;;. Before the 40's women's stockings were created from silk. They were very delicate and needed frequent mending and hand washing. Dupont then invented nylon thereby &quot;Nylons&quot; became a well-known for stockings. Today nylon is nevertheless used to make a myriad of hosiery and fabrics. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; That Zipper. &lt;/strong&gt;; Thanks to new inventions of the 1940's women can zip up clothing rather then using buttons, snaps and lacing. &lt;/li&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;li&gt;; &lt;strong&gt;; Plastic. &lt;/strong&gt;; Although various kinds of plastic had been around since the 1920's it wasn't until the 1940's that they really took center stage in the fashion world. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXZpbnRhZ2Vzb2x1dGlvbi5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwL3ZpbnRhZ2UtaW5zcGlyZWQtZ2xhc3MtZm9yLXRoZS1mYWNlLTIv" target="_blank"&gt;;Top tips for snagging the perfect vintage designer piece&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZpbnRhZ2VmYXNoaW9ubG9uZG9uLmNvLnVrL2FsZXhhbmRlci1tY3F1ZWVucy12aW50YWdlLWluc3BpcmF0aW9uLW92ZXItdGhlLXllYXJzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Vintage inspired glass for the face 2&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXZpbnRhZ2Vzb2x1dGlvbi5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwL3RvcC10aXBzLWZvci1zbmFnZ2luZy10aGUtcGVyZmVjdC12aW50YWdlLWRlc2lnbmVyLXBp" target="_blank"&gt;;Alexander mcqueens vintage inspiration over the years&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="86de5218e9caa882b2817ab6f25f00ae">			Popular items easy to sell by the load are necessities. If you want an almost foolproof product or service to wholesale, clothing has to be your best bet. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Some sort of concrete business plan is your next step. This is where people allot the budget if you choose to open a wholesale clothing business. Research on the kinds of permits you might need to secure. Determine if you will need storage space or just are an intermediary between producer and retailer. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;- Maybe there hardest but most important step to to become wholesaler is building some sort of contact list. Since you will be working as a company to retailer, you ought to build a contact list of both manufacturers and retailers. Choose quality manufacturers to attract major retailers to work with you. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Going in the business of wholesale shirts and also other products may not earn you benefits immediately. In fact, it may take time before you quite possibly earn back your gain. Hard work and patience is the key to success for almost any business venture. Making a concrete company plan is only the first step but it is on the right direction. Once you might have finalized your plan, you only need to follow through and bide time until your efforts to. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Dog clothing is more popular than in the past. Dressing your pup in clothes can be a cute and fun way to show off his character but outfits serve a practical purpose, too. They help to protect your dog in the elements by keeping him or her warmer, dryer and by giving protection from the sunshine. Whatever your reason for buying your dog clothes, you can get more for your money when you have learned to shop smart. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Apply most of the same rules you use when buying yourself or for your kids when shopping for doggie clothes. This will help you create smart decisions so you'll actually put all of the items that you buy on your dog instead of in a drawer. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Here are a few dog clothing shopping tips that will help you shop smart: &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?? If you ever don't think she will be comfortable or happy being dressed in that ruffled dress, then don't buy it just because you think it's its adorable. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?? Search for outfits that suit their personality. If he sits beside you during athletic, a jersey with ones team's logo on it would perfect. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?? Buy clothing based on your home. You don't need some sort of thick wool sweater if you happen to live in Texas where the winters are mild. If you live in an area where it rains a lot, you can stock up on raincoats and boots but in any other case, does she really need three sets of each one. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?? Clothing with buttons and zippers are certainly not good for everyday employ. If it's for a unique occasion and for a short time during which time you'll be watching him, they're fine. Otherwise, the dog clothes held together by Velcro is a much better buy because they are safer for a pet. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;?? Make certain and buy the correct size clothing. Your dog needs clothes that can fit and just like most people, she can lose or gain weight frequently. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXZpbnRhZ2Vzb2x1dGlvbi5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwL3RvcC10aXBzLWZvci1zbmFnZ2luZy10aGUtcGVyZmVjdC12aW50YWdlLWRlc2lnbmVyLXBp" target="_blank"&gt;;Top tips for snagging the perfect vintage designer piece&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3RoZXZpbnRhZ2Vzb2x1dGlvbi5jb20vaW5kZXgucGhwL3ZpbnRhZ2UtaW5zcGlyZWQtZ2xhc3MtZm9yLXRoZS1mYWNlLTIv" target="_blank"&gt;;Top tips for snagging the perfect vintage designer piece&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZpbnRhZ2VmYXNoaW9ubG9uZG9uLmNvLnVrL2FsZXhhbmRlci1tY3F1ZWVucy12aW50YWdlLWluc3BpcmF0aW9uLW92ZXItdGhlLXllYXJzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;Top tips for snagging the perfect vintage designer piece&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>