<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="b02cec3932eb6c852822c5fbc00e74a2">			When a person has been in the online industry for a long time, they begin to appreciate the potential that is in the social networking sites. There are so many professionals that are using these sites to achieve their objectives. However, a person needs to take a Twitter marketing course in order for their efforts to pay off.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Over time, people have been able to see some of the tools that they could use being discarded. Experts assumed that as long as they had a huge followings their attempts were successful. They thought that they could not benefit from following other people instead..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All the professionals used this strategy for their businesses in the hope that it would work. They assumed that if they targeted the larger audience they were bound to find someone they could work with. Their strategy was based on the assumption that someone is going to follow them as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Others decided to use the email list to decide who they were going to follow. As the functions of this site kept on being refined they realized that such a strategy would never work in their favor. Even if they had a good number of following, the majority of them were not their intended audience..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When they started using applications that would help them know who to follow, they still could not get the right audience. Since this is a personal platform their efforts were ineffective. With the passing of time people begun to understand what needs to be done. Even if they would be in a position to connect to a large number of people, it would not be easy for them to build meaningful relationships with each one of them..&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;They begun to understand why they could not get the response they needed from their followers. On such sites the person needs to understand how apathy works. The numbers of messages they receive are so many for someone to go over each one. As long as they have a few relationships that they could nurture that was all they needed. It is not easy for someone to chat with all the followers who are online at the same time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;There are so many other reasons as to why these strategies are ineffective. For better results, the service providers need to interact with a limited number of followers. Look for people who have a common interest with you for better results. They also need to make sure that they respond to messages from their followers. A person can only get in depth knowledge of this by taking the Twitter marketing course.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.marketingwarzone.com%2Ftwittermarketing"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;http://www.marketingwarzone.com/twittermarketing&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>