<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="4">		<conversation id="c85f6820735dca9b3653531950f8eea1">			Do you want to turn that second spare room into a walk in wardrobe but your boyfriend wants a games room? But what happens when you have guest over to stay? Well don’t fear all you need is a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzb2ZhYmVkLmNvbS9uZXdzLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;UK sofa bed!&lt;/a&gt;; . Perfect for when you’re married friend’s visit, comfortable for when the mother-in law pops over for a stay and ideal for when you just want to sit in front of the television and relax, the sofa bed really does tick all the boxes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So, your boyfriend has been out with his friends and has come home, collapsed into bed and started to repeatedly snore, matching the tone of a pig. So what do you do? You cannot sleep with that noise vibrating in your ear!
&lt;br /&gt;;This is where a sofa bed &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzb2ZhYmVkLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;sofa bed&lt;/a&gt;; comes in handy. Just imagine it; you can leave your boyfriend snoring alone, grab a duvet and pillow and have one of the best night sleep that you have ever had!		</conversation>		<conversation id="3dca09e79505209cffc43ee84369b932">			Finding a decent sofabed isn’t easy.  Especially if you want it to be comfortable too. Even a trip to London and trawling around some of the most famous furniture shops won’t necessarily be enough. Well, the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzb2ZhYmVkLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;The Sofa Bed&lt;/a&gt;; company has always specialised in making beautiful, comfortable sofa beds and now we’re bringing London to you. The London sofa bed that is.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The London sofa bed is beautifully stylish and extremely comfortable.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The London is the latest addition to our range of great sofabeds. It been a whole year in development (we like our sofabeds to be perfect so will take as long as we need to get everything just so) but has finally taken its place alongside the Cambio and Metro.    Have a look at the London page of our website – or the whole sofabed range is on the Sofa Beds page.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The London has an air of quality from the moment you see it. Its modern styling and lovely proportions make it ideal for an apartment in the city or the sitting room of a country cottage. In fact one thing about the London is that it looks bigger than it is, so giving an impression of space.  But it’s not only about the impression of space, the sofabed has to be right for the space, which is why we make the London in 5 sizes.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The London is a fabulous and comfortable sofa, with a lovely seat depth and supportive back.  In fact sitting on it and looking at it would be easy to forget that it’s a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzb2ZhYmVkLmNvbS9zb2ZhLWJlZC5odG1s" target="_blank"&gt;;sofabed&lt;/a&gt;; too.  But it is of course and the strong mechanism simply opens out to reveal a fantastically comfortable bed.  Because we’ve designed our sofabeds for everyday use we also give you a choice of three mattresses; Coil Sprung, Pocket Sprung and Memory Foam.   Each one is a proper, thick mattresses just the same as you would find on a bed.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Our Cambio sofa bed has shown us that there’s a need for sofabeds with storage. Not to be left out in the storage stakes the London has storage arms. Each one lifts up to reveal enough space to store your pillows and perhaps a light duvet when your sofa’s a bed and possibly even your clothes when your bed’s a sofa.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The London sofabed features storage arms.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Like many in London itself this is a sofabed that likes to dress to impress. It’s available in beautiful leathers and fabrics.  The full range can be seen on the Fabric page, which is also the place to order your free sample swatches.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;As always though there’s only one way to really get to know the London, and that’s to see and feel it for yourself. The Sofa Bed Company is based just outside Nottingham – 15 minutes from the M1 – and we welcome visitors to the workshop. All you have to do is Contact Us to make an appointment. When else would you be able to say that London awaits?		</conversation>		<conversation id="b54b9005c738f17be1af3febfee87f57">			Quality &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzb2ZhYmVkLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;sofa beds&lt;/a&gt;; can combine convenience with luxury.  No longer are sofa beds uncomfortable, mechanical monsters, you can get some classy looking furniture which has some thickly padded foam inserts that is great to sleep on.  Even memory foam has now made it into a sofa bed and additional, innovative extras such as storage space in the arms or matching single beds stored in foot rests.		</conversation>		<conversation id="96ff931a2a72f58e1c5ebfaf1e60666">			Many London flat owners have a space issue, there isn't much room to move around or place any new things due to high prices for larger apartments or extraordinary prices for a house of your own!  When people come over to stay they usually end up on the floor or on the sofa.  &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy50aGVzb2ZhYmVkLmNvbS9zb2ZhLWJlZHMvbG9uZG9u" target="_blank"&gt;;London Sofa beds&lt;/a&gt;; are an ideal solution to give guest a comfy place to kip, they can double up as a sofa in the day and a bed at night.  Some sofa beds can be broken down into pieces so they fit into tiny lift, tight corners and awkward door frames.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>