<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="b15264139d494ae196b50081c0dbd82a">			Valentine's Day, also known as St. Valentine's Day, is one of the western traditional days. {p2}&gt;; The so-called Valentine's Day of nowadays could be traced back to ancient Greek where people admired Pan very popular.Why the Most Expensive ipad accessories in This Season are So Ugly?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pan is a God of fertility and is described as a combination of man and goat; he is bad in temper and moody that makes people tremble when he was mentioned. In fact, the English &quot;;panic&quot;; 's literally meaning is &quot;;of Pan&quot;;,this kind of applicance is very vivid. Pan should play whlie guarding herds. However, he was easily distracted. He had many romantic affairs with many fairies and goddesses. A sculpture describes that Pan has a close relationship with Aphrodite, the Goddess of Love, and the God of Love, Eris, hovers above them, which is just like the Cupid portrayed on the Valentine's card.Why the Most Expensive ipad accessories for Now are So Strange?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many Romans also worship a god who was called Faunus. He has been described as half-man, half-goat look. Romans worship Faunus by carnival-loving approach on February 15 - Faun's Day. During this holiday season, a number of men wearing strand will running on the mountains, waving whips goats.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you want to conceive children, just standing beside the runway. The Romans believed that if a man beaten a woman with whips, her infertility will heal with no medicine. Brewer's catch phrase and fable dictionary says, &quot;;St. Valentine was a Roman priest committed to prison due to the assistance to the Christians who suffered.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Acturally celebration custom of Valentine's Day have something to do with Valentine by pure coincidence. In fact, this festival may concerned with Faun's Day of ancient Rome or mating season of birds. The special for Valentine's Day is lovers give presents for each other. For today, people would perfer Valentine's card to show their love. And the card are usually decorated with Cupid or heart shot by the love arrow and so on.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Concerning the relationship between Cupid and Valentine's Day, the above dictionary says, &quot;;Cupid is the Roman God of love, the same as God Eros in Greek.&quot;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He usually the representative of by a cute little boy, there are two wings in the back, eyes under a piece of clothes, hand-held bow and arrow. &quot;;World Book Encyclopedia&quot;; provides further information show that there are different virsions of the origin of Valentine's Day. The Encyclopedia states: It is said that during the period AD 200, Roman emperor Claudius II had prohibition of marriage of young men. He believes that unmarried men can be better soldiers. A priest named Valentine contravened the emperor's command, and officiated a marriage secretly.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;According to &quot;;Catholic Encyclopedia,&quot;; in AD 496, Pope St. Kira elisios I abolished the Faun's Day in AD 5th century to and made February 14 as St. Valentine Day. Today, we call it &quot;;St. Valentine's Day&quot;;--also called Valentine's Day, which become popular. After the 14th century, people began to commemorate this day. Valentine's Day originate from the ancient faith regardless of the true origin and is named after saint of Christian country. Valentine's Day is also exploited by the business community and become another excuse of money grabbing.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tags:   ipad accessories,ipad accessories,		</conversation>		<conversation id="1838c9ca08d2b8489ba884e663949519">			Eating more coarse grains and fruits detoxification method: Coarse grains and fruits can promote bowel movements and prevent constipation, so that we can discharge wastes and toxins. If our body gains refreshment and vitality, we will look more beautiful in our appearance! Such things as Soya bean milk, vegetables, fruit, green tea, water are full of nutrition, and at the same time,they can emit the toxins from our body.ipad accessories , the Necessity of Grandmother for During Spring
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Expelling method with natural lemonade: Lemon is a good thing, in every morning drinking a large glass of lemonade with empty stomach is the method I have been using to shed virus. For What Reasons People all Choose Them?! Most Amazing ipad accessories Are on Exhibition It is both simple and practical. What's more important, you can not only get rid of the toxin, lose weight but be prevented from catching cold. But you must be persistent, otherwise it wouldn't be useful at all. Lemonade can rid the body of harmful substances. It can whiten the skin, eliminate toxins, empty bowels, quench thirst and dilute the desire to eat. It needs no special diet, killing two birds with one stone!Surprise! Newest iphone accessories at an Affordable Price
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The method of not eating meals for one or two days to emit toxins: Maybe you think that you have been paying attention to hygiene in your daily life,and what you eat is healthy, right? In fact it is not. Toxins are everywhere, pollutants in the water, as well as our eating too many preservatives, chemicals, pigments and so on. So if we need detoxification, we should select one or two days a week for the asting day. It's very effective. At this time, the body does not accept food and will reduce the burden of various organs, but we must add enough water.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Furthermore, you can also choose green juice. It is popular among Japanese and Taiwan stars. And a lot of women binge on green juice. Green juice is made from squeezing barley young leaves or wheat young shoots. Or you can also buy the ready, made barley wakaba to drink. It can help to expel toxins, purge the bowels, improve the constipation and resist radiation. Besides, you'll feel fresh and dynamic if you keep drinking it for some time because there is so much dietary fiber in it. And drinking it for a long term will make my skin submitted to allergies and acnes better. What is suggested is KND green juice. In fact, fanl would be a great choice were it not for its startling price.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brown sugar method: Now I would like to introduce an ointment which is only made from brown suger and honey. This intment can make your complexion look healthier and more beautiful.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Step 1: pour approximately 1 teaspoon of brown sugar into the mixing bowl. STEP2: put the honey into the mixing bowl, the amount of the honey should be three times as much as the brown-sugar.If your skin is smooth and delicate, you can add more honey in the bowl. STEP 3: Place about five minutes to precipitate after stirring well.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Complete: honey whose top layer is incorporated into brown sugar is good detoxication scrubbing cream. Smearing on the wet face and washing after slightly massage.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Tags:   ipad accessories,ipad accessories,iphone accessories,		</conversation>	</conversations></author>