<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="56b6b8717513c18e5e9a45ea3b83c021">			Ipage was founded in 1998 and till now, it's served a large number of customers featuring its quality webhosting service. It has established niche internet marketing and has thousands of clients to its credit that bank upon its services. On the subject of reliability as well as reliance, iPage is a name that comes to your mind first amid other webhosting companies fraught out there. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatamericanwebhosting.com%2Fipage%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatamericanwebhosting.com/ipage/&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This is because of the reason why iPage simply believes in offering genuine and quality web hosting service rather than using tricky online marketing strategy to scam clients and betray their trust.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatamericanwebhosting.com%2Ffatcow%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatamericanwebhosting.com/fatcow/&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;And let’s remember, If you are signing up for the ipage website hosting, you will be contributing for a greener environment too. Ipage offers coupons for their clients and customers, and you'll get unbelievable $2.99 monthly instead of the regular price. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatamericanwebhosting.com%2Fjusthost%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatamericanwebhosting.com/justhost/&lt;/a&gt;;  &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The control panel of ipage comes with rich look user interface and smooth user menu navigation. It is very easy to use even for novice user as ipage provides many helpful tools like drag and drop site builder, one click installation tools etc. The ipage hosting is available at a very cheap rate such that the customer can get their own website hosting very easily.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Go to &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fgreatamericanwebhosting.com%2Fipage%2F"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://greatamericanwebhosting.com/ipage/&lt;/a&gt;; for more info.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>