<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="c83597a81ba349f05bb75a01a4f2f922">			Read this report to understand how these two credentials differ, and why (or why not) you may choose to skip them altogether, or select a single over the other.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you take a look at the a variety of details and figures that seem in Table 1 below, you may be inclined to consider the CompTIA Security+ certification as well as the (ISC)two Systems Security Certified Practitioner (SSCP) credential are way more or less interchangeable parts. They cost roughly the identical, they cover roughly the exact same subject places, and each 1 entails answering roughly exactly the same number of queries. But these exams are not interchangeable, and serve somewhat various purposes and audiences, because the discussion that follows Table 1 will show.&lt;br /&gt;;Table 1: Standard Details &amp; Figures for Security+ and SSCP&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Name&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sponsor&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cost&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Concerns&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Time&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;(mins)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Topic Domains Covered&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Security+&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CompTIA&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;$250-270&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;100&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;90&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Network Security; Compliance and Operational Security; Threats and Vulnerabilities; Application, data, and host security; Access control and identity management; Cryptography&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SSCP&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;(ISC)2&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;$295&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;125&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;180&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Access controls; Malicious code and activity; Monitoring and analysis; Networks and communications; Risk, response, and recovery; Security operations and administration&lt;br /&gt;;Closer Appear #1: Security+&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CompTIA describes the target audience for the Security+ certification as IT security professionals who possess a minimum of two years experience with IT administration with a focus on security. A good candidate will also have day to day technical knowledge security experience, and possess broad knowledge of security concerns and implementation where the items listed in the Subject Domains Covered column in Table 1 are concerned (all quotes come from the Security+ Exam Objectives for exam SY0-301the most current version, scheduled to take effect in 2011available for download from the CompTIA Security+ Web page).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The CompTIA Security+ topic domains take a moderate dive into modern topics and issues commonly associated with data security, without necessarily going into excruciating detail. Thus, for example, the Network Security domain breaks down into six sub-topics:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Network devices and technologies, such as firewalls, routers, switches, load balancers, proxies, security appliances of many kinds, and other hardware are explored and explained from a security perspective.&lt;br /&gt;;    Methods for applying and implementing secure network administration principles are discussed, including rule-based management, firewall rules, VLAN management, secure router configuration, access control lists (ACLs), and alot more.&lt;br /&gt;;    Methods for distinguishing and differentiating among network design elements and combinations are dissected, with an emphasis on enhancing and enforcing security. These encompass DMZs, subnetting, VLANs, network address translation (NAT), remote access, network access control (NAC), virtualization, and cloud computing technologies (PaaS, Saas, IaaS).&lt;br /&gt;;    Working with common protocols to enforce, implement, and enhance security. Protocols mentioned are IPsec, SNMP, SSH, DNS, TLS, SSL, TCP/IP, FTPS, HTTPS, SFTP, SCP, ICMP, and IPv4 vs. IPv6.&lt;br /&gt;;    The range of commonly used default network ports is investigated, where the following services merit specific mention: FTP, SFTP, FTPS, TFTP, Telnet, HTTP, HTTPS, SCP, SSH, and NetBIOS.&lt;br /&gt;;    Secure implementation of wireless networking is explored and explained. In this context, the following techniques, algorithms, and tools are covered: WPA/WPA2, WEP, EAP, PEAP, LEAP, MAC address filtering, SSID broadcast management, TKIP, CCMP, antenna placement, and power level controls.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All in all, the Security+ provides a good general nuts-and-bolts survey of modern info security topics, tools, techniques, and best practices. It tends to focus in on specific instances of these things, and it doesnt always emphasize a deep understanding of security consciousness, perhaps because thats believed to come with additional time and experience beyond its target candidate population. Nevertheless, the six topical domains for the Security+ do cover most of the key issues and concerns in understanding, implementing, and maintaining proper data security.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tY3RzLXdpbmRvd3MtNy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;mcts certification&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;comptia security&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5yZWFkeTRleGFtLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;mcsa certification&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="44c7bf01e71ee33d20e54d97134e4f68">			Read this article to know how these two credentials differ, and why (or why not) you may choose to skip them altogether, or choose a single over the other.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In case you check out the many details and figures that seem in Table 1 below, you may be inclined to think about the CompTIA Security+ certification along with the (ISC)two Systems Security Certified Practitioner (SSCP) credential are a great deal more or less interchangeable components. They cost roughly the identical, they cover roughly precisely the same subject locations, and each 1 involves answering roughly exactly the same number of questions. But these exams will not be interchangeable, and serve somewhat different purposes and audiences, because the discussion that follows Table 1 will show.&lt;br /&gt;;Table 1: Standard Details &amp; Figures for Security+ and SSCP&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Name&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sponsor&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Cost&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Questions&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Time&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;(mins)&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Topic Domains Covered&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Security+&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CompTIA&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;$250-270&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;100&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;90&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Network Security; Compliance and Operational Security; Threats and Vulnerabilities; Application, data, and host security; Access control and identity management; Cryptography&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;SSCP&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;(ISC)2&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;$295&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;125&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;180&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Access controls; Malicious code and activity; Monitoring and analysis; Networks and communications; Risk, response, and recovery; Security operations and administration&lt;br /&gt;;Closer Appear #1: Security+&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;CompTIA describes the target audience for the Security+ certification as IT security pros who possess a minimum of two years experience with IT administration with a focus on security. A good candidate will also have day to day technical knowledge security experience, and possess broad knowledge of security concerns and implementation where the items listed in the Topic Domains Covered column in Table 1 are concerned (all quotes come from the Security+ Exam Objectives for exam SY0-301the most current version, scheduled to take effect in 2011available for download from the CompTIA Security+ Web page).&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The CompTIA Security+ topic domains take a moderate dive into modern topics and issues commonly associated with info security, without necessarily going into excruciating detail. Thus, for example, the Network Security domain breaks down into six sub-topics:&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Network devices and technologies, such as firewalls, routers, switches, load balancers, proxies, security appliances of many kinds, and other hardware are explored and explained from a security perspective.&lt;br /&gt;;    Methods for applying and implementing secure network administration principles are discussed, including rule-based management, firewall rules, VLAN management, secure router configuration, access control lists (ACLs), and even more.&lt;br /&gt;;    Methods for distinguishing and differentiating among network design elements and combinations are dissected, with an emphasis on enhancing and enforcing security. These encompass DMZs, subnetting, VLANs, network address translation (NAT), remote access, network access control (NAC), virtualization, and cloud computing technologies (PaaS, Saas, IaaS).&lt;br /&gt;;    Working with common protocols to enforce, implement, and enhance security. Protocols mentioned are IPsec, SNMP, SSH, DNS, TLS, SSL, TCP/IP, FTPS, HTTPS, SFTP, SCP, ICMP, and IPv4 vs. IPv6.&lt;br /&gt;;    The range of commonly used default network ports is investigated, where the following services merit specific mention: FTP, SFTP, FTPS, TFTP, Telnet, HTTP, HTTPS, SCP, SSH, and NetBIOS.&lt;br /&gt;;    Secure implementation of wireless networking is explored and explained. In this context, the following techniques, algorithms, and tools are covered: WPA/WPA2, WEP, EAP, PEAP, LEAP, MAC address filtering, SSID broadcast management, TKIP, CCMP, antenna placement, and power level controls.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;All in all, the Security+ provides a good general nuts-and-bolts survey of modern information security topics, tools, techniques, and best practices. Nevertheless, the six topical domains for the Security+ do cover most of the key issues and concerns in understanding, implementing, and maintaining proper info security.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tY3RzLXdpbmRvd3MtNy5jb20v" target="_blank"&gt;;mcts certification&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5jZXJ0dG9wcGVyLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;mcsa 2003&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tY2l0cGtpbmcuY29tLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;mcitp&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>