<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="2e7c19dd133a2f1071183b585f55ddaf">			Becoming bankrupt is an option that should be avoided as far as possible because of how difficult it can be to recover from it afterwards. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.creditrepairfeed.comusually"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.creditrepairfeed.comusually&lt;/a&gt;; occurs in one of two ways. Either a person declares themselves bankrupt because they are unable to pay debts, or a creditor applies to make someone bankrupt because they are owed more than 750 by them and have been unsuccessful in their attempts to reclaim the owed money.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is up to a court to make the decision on someone should be made bankrupt or not. Once a court does declare a person bankrupt, the details of the person’s case will be sent to the Insolvency Service of the government. This Insolvency Service will arrange a receiver who is local to the person who will then appoint a trustee to help handle the case.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The person being made &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.creditrepairfeed.commust"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.creditrepairfeed.commust&lt;/a&gt;; attend an interview with their appointed receiver and provide evidence of all of their finances. This includes any debts they might have excluding student loans and court fines, any assets they have and any existing money they have. The receiver will then make contact with the creditors whom the person has debts with and explain what will happen next.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a person to be made bankrupt they have to agree to cooperate with the receiver which includes handing over any bank and credit cards. They have to cease making any payments to companies where they have outstanding debts and let the receiver and trustee take control.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The appointed trustee is responsible for making sure that creditors receive as much of the money they are owed as possible. Any assets the person has will be sold, added to any existing finances they have and then split between the creditors accordingly. Once this is done the person is not debt free however. Should they have any spare income for the next three years, they may still be ordered to contribute that income to any debts still outstanding.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>