<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="7d7bad4779cfb733f88a6fb0785129f2">			Those who wear contact lenses often feel confused about contact lens solution and eyedrops. Here we’ll have a brief introduction on their differences in the hope for your better use.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Contact optical lenses drops dip in glasses, acted as disinfection and wiping off protein. Eye drops is only suited to wear contact lenses process when you fell not very well. In wearing contact lenses, it is not suggested to become too dependent on eye moisture liquid, which can only alleviate eye fatigue and can not substitute the water in your own eyes. Generally, it is suggested to drop lubricating solution no more than 5 times a day,1 or 2 times per day is good. Because to rely completely on lubricating solution can weaken the function of tear secretion.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are a few differences in composition of the different contact lens care solution. Take the multi-purpose solution as an example, the main ingredients include: disinfecting and cleaning composition, wetting agents, electrolytic solution and taurine. It can disinfect and clean contact lenses safely and effectively, the ingredient makes the minimum damage when it disinfects and cleans contact lenses. Two kinds of wetting agents, theirs composition be close to tears, and it is also used in the treatment of Dryness of eyes products.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Moreover, these ingredients can form a layer of moist protection membrane on the surface of eyeballs to increase the comfort level of contact lens and long-time maintain the lubrication between eyeballs and lens. Physiological sunglasses electrolyte solution and taurine, so that contact lens care solution and human tears, the physical environment more matches, so you can wear contact lenses to ensure the health and comfort. Primarily, eyedrops is not a kind of medicine but a type of solution that is germfree, homotonic and buffered. It is exclusively used to lubricate contact lenses and is to some extent effective in relieving xerophthalmia caused by wearing contact lenses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The moistening eye drop contains HA high moisture moistening factor which is a natural part of contact lens. It contains moisture 1000 times more than body it self. Continuous and large amount of moisture makes it possible to keep eyes wet. The formation which is similar to tears is moderate and healthy without stimulation. The watery liquid is so mild that it is pleasant to the eyes as gentle as natural tears.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The contact lens care solution is not able to wear contact lenses to use, because drug ingredients are likely to precipitate into the lens to change the lens characteristics. In addition, since there are men sunglasses various adding ingredients in lubricating solution, some people is likely to be allergic such as irritability. You should use the product within 30 days when you open it. This product is only suitable for eyes, and it is not for the store of contact lens. Above all, these are the differences between lubricating solution and contact lens care solution. And experts suggest people to correctly use them.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is not right to replace contact lens care solution with eye drops or to replace eye drops with contact lens care solution. They must be used separately.		</conversation>		<conversation id="8a65db4329d2749562c4652757eb55bd">			Kids optical mainly have therapeutic effects on eyes, and also play a beautifying role to a certain extent. To protect children glasses is the fundamental measure to ensure the normal use of children glasses. How can children protect their glasses well? 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Glasses should be placed appropriately. While temporarily putting off them, children mustn't allow lenses to directly contact with desktop. When sleeping at night, be sure to put the glassed into glassed case so as to avoid friction, squashing or falling off. The glasses case can't be too soft, or the legs of glasses may deform after a long time of pressure. It will affect your eyesight because of the slant angle. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Never wipe lenses with clothes or fingers casually when there is dust on the lenses. which will wear lenses, reduce the transparency, for a long time, glasses lenses would be opaque as if they are blocked by a layer of mist, If there are greasy or other dirty on the glasses, moisten the surface of an object by exhaling, and wape softly with the glass clothes. If kid sunglasses are damaged or unable to correct vision, go to the hospital in time to get inspection, optometry and make a new one.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When taking a PE class or doing some other tensive exercises, the glasses should be taken off and put in the box. Because children are lively and naughty, glasses frames had better be made of plastic or poly glass. Such frame is reletively wide, comfortable for children to wear and difficult to damage, and not easily hurt children's eyes. Let alone its competitive price, it is very popular among most people.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The mirror holder size must be suitable, some parents and the child think the mirror holder big attractiveness, also has thought mirror holder small somewhat not easy to fall, all these are not overall. The eyes of the kids can be diverted from the optical center if the mirror support is too big or too small. They not only would not achieve the role of vision correction, but also accelerate the development of refractive errors, and even affect the normal development of facial features. So the size of men sunglasses should accord to the child's head, face, orbital eyes' development. And change the glasses while growing up.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e683206b06f2deeda5d60fea2c8c6474">			You will squinting at what you're really looking at, plus the words start out obtaining blurry then it will be time to acquire some great examining glasses. There are various several types of glasses; one can find bifocal reading spectacles, folding studying glasses as well as reading sunglasses. It's really a matter of you finding ones, you require, and you ought to look at buying them equally you should any good stylish sunglasses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But basically all examining spectacles in the latter group two areas. Many are full frame examining spectacles and half eyes looking at glasses. Total reading eye spectacles are ideal for folks who spend much time looking at things close up. 55 that after you appearance up everything appears to obtain blurry with this type of optical eyeglasses.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Half eye studying spectacles will let you appear ott with the frames, or under them to see off inside the distance. It is the form of reading spectacles that most folks start out with when they've by no means used glasses just before.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Most folks keep a number of studying eyeglasses because they aren't very costly. Handy folding reading through glasses are great for dark locations like restaurants, reading sunglasses are good for people trips towards the beach.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Elect you may need optical glasses, you are greater off obtaining custom created eye eyeglasses as opposed to those which are prepared manufactured at the pharmacy, since they're manufactured to specifically fit your eyes, but readymade studying glasses can be really well-known since they're so affordable and come in quite a number of versions. Some individuals elect to buy 1 customized set of eyeglasses and various distinct models of readymade plastic studying spectacles for when they're out of your home or in areas wherever a lot more high priced spectacles may be bothersome, or can get lost.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Whichever you choose seriously isn't important, but what is crucial is that you get your eyesight checked and you utilize glasses countless them. For anybody who is often forgetting in which you placed them after that you can get reading through eyeglasses chains, or a studying glasses necklace which keeps them in place, around your neck for when you have them.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>