<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="ac20fe7ca0d48563aca3c525e2217740">			Has it crossed your mind that ladies golf bag accessories are an impressionable magnet? Not only do you notice a fashionable item but it draws your attention to the owner. From there you develop a range of questions, including where the accessory originated from; what other color options are available; how to order the same item for yourself?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Many times my cute colorful ladies golf accessories have garnered the attention of new business contacts, new social dates and great future networking opportunities. Anytime I attend a corporate golfing event or fundraiser, I always make it a point to be prominent. I make my beautiful ladies golf apparel and accessories work for me. Your apparel and accessories tell a story; they express your personality and when trying to network, it's in your best interest to be noticeable, in a subtle way.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I always take my monogrammed item, hoping I'll be one of the few who thought of this. I flaunt it around and make sure it's in plain view so people will remember and associate it with the event I attended. Sure, it's such a small leap of faith but it has worked in my favor a few times. The other attraction at a golfing event is your accessories. Golf bags and totes, feminine fashion inspired golf head covers or perhaps a trendy water bottle cover will often get noticed and spark a conversation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Trying to acquire that new social date? Well keep in mind, drawing the attention of the opposite sex is an absolute guarantee with the right golf accessory. Many of the ladies golf accessories are styled to be striking, exciting and fashionable. And what do these things do? Attracts and draws attention to the obvious. It has nothing to do with the game itself only the psychology of the fashion and how it plays a part in your strategy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Utilizing trendy ladies golf accessories for gifts is a safe bet for the golfing devotee. By choosing something stylish that stands out, you'll set your gift apart from the rest. Something noticeable that sets the trend and keeps them aware of your fashion sense will often designate you as the authority on ladies golfing style. You might just find other lady golfers following suit and asking where you've purchased your treasures. Now whether your strategy is to pick up some extraordinary fashionable golf accessories for the look and feel of exclusive new trends or you want your peers to take notice of your summer couture with exciting colors and extensive options.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2xhZGllc2dvbGZiYWdndWlkZS5uZXQ_" target="_blank"&gt;;Womens Golf Bags&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>