<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="89aca61278714867b18acfd0b58dfdaf">			0 = ewwwwww!
&lt;br /&gt;;1 = Definetly not attractive.
&lt;br /&gt;;2 = Decent
&lt;br /&gt;;3 = Fine
&lt;br /&gt;;4 = Fine as hell!
&lt;br /&gt;;5 = I'd do you.
&lt;br /&gt;;6 = Pretty damn sexy!
&lt;br /&gt;;7 = Lovable, I LOVE YOU!!!
&lt;br /&gt;;8 = I wanna make you.....		</conversation>		<conversation id="603953c99c8e9b9ffcc21acaacb75565">			Blue Eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;People with blue eyes last the longest in relationships. They are kind, pretty or handsome,very good kissers and are really hot. They always fall in love with their closest friends and never understand why. They are very funny, outgoing and don't care what people think or say. They are very satisfying and love to please. LOVES to party.Are straight up WARRIORS when necessary. If you repost this and you have blue eyes you will have the best kiss sometime in the next 5 days.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Black Eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;People with black eyes spend the shortest time in relationships except for the one with their current addiction. They are leg humping friendly to borderline sleazy. They always fall in love with anything that that has two legs, a pulse and a wet spot. They are great kissers----until they vomit all over you. They are very easy to please unless they haven't had their latest fix of alcohol, meth, cocaine, or prescription medicine. If you don't repost this and you have black eyes you will either O.D., spend the night in jail, or wake up next to some skank you've never seen before within the next 2 days.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Green Eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;People with green eyes have the most passion put into relationships,honest and trust worthy, they have long lasting relationships. People with green eyes are also the most beautiful,hot, and sexy. They are fun and outgoing, love to make people laugh, random as hell. They long for the touch of another. They are very laid back. People with green eyes are very sexy and very attracted towards other people. LOVES to partyy. Tend to cover up true feelings, get scared over relationships.They are amazing at kissing. They love to make friends Anf loves to cuddle and makeout. You will meet/stay with the person you're going to spend the rest of your life with if you repost this.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hazel Eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;People with hazel eyes are very loveable. They are really hot and are awesome to be around. They don't enjoy 'pet names'. They don't care what people think or say. They are lovers, not fighters. But if you mess around, they'll knock you out. They are very satisfying and they love to please. They can exceed your pleasure standards. They are very laid back, chilled and love to just be around. If you repost this and have hazel eyes then you will be happy soon with the person who is on your heart.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Brown Eyes
&lt;br /&gt;;Either sexy as hell or are adorable. They love to make new friends. Their relationship tends to be very honest because if they aren't truly in love, then the relationship won't work. They fall easily for their best friends. Will do anything for that special person. Kind and polite. Enjoys being with their guy/girl. LOVES to party. Good in bed. Can make ANYONE laugh or cheer them up. Loves to please the one they care for or love. Is not the kind of person that you want to piss off, thats for sure! Repost this if you have brown eyes and you will find the one that you are meant to be with in the next 7 days		</conversation>	</conversations></author>