<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="d071607578b709b49e95405b836a36c1">			In the world of organic gardening, there are plenty of great resources available to both new and experienced organic gardeners alike. There are many e-guides, books, videos, and other resources available. This set of tips contains some of the best advice for helping a good organic gardener become a great organic gardener.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Having a garden of perennials can be an easy and quick process. It isn't as hard as it may seem; you basically just slice down under the turf, flip it over, and spread wood chips four to three inches. Allow the newly turned soil to sit for two weeks, then plant your perennials.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prepare the ground for a perennial garden quickly and easily. It isn't as hard as it may seem; you basically just slice down under the turf, flip it over, and spread wood chips four to three inches. Allow the newly turned soil to sit for two weeks, then plant your perennials.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When it is time to gather your produce, you should use an older laundry basket. It makes a great strainer for your vegetables. You can clean and rinse the harvest when it is the laundry basket and the water will go out of the holes.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Want to kill weeds naturally? Take layers of newspapers and use them for weed control. The main thing that a weed needs to thrive is sunlight. By covering them with a layer of newspaper, you are essentially suffocating the weeds due to a lack of light. The paper will break down quickly and cleanly, adding to your compost. Try adding some mulch on top of it to make appear more attractive.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you are doing work in your garden, be efficient. If it takes you thirty minutes to find a needed tool, then you are doing something wrong. Take the time to prepare the necessary tools, and then store them in a easily accessed place once you are done gardening. It may be necessary to don a tool belt or cargo pants with extra pockets.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Slugs are a nuisance that can be easily remedied with the use of an organic beer tramp. Bury a jar in the garden with it's mouth open and level to the ground. Fill the jar with beer within one inch of the top. The slugs will be attracted to the beer, and will then become trapped within the jar.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When planting trees and shrubs, dig irregular holes with rough sides. If there are any glazed sides in the hole, it restricts the growth of the roots.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You are aware of how helpful compost is in growing your organic garden, but do you have any idea what is actually in it? Compost is made up of things like old produce scraps, leaves, twigs, grass clippings and wood-chips that have broken down into something similar to soil in texture. This is an ideal substitute for commercially sold fertilizers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If sustainability and organic gardening are appealing to you, leave a portion of the property you own undeveloped to give wildlife a place to thrive. One side effect of this is that where animals thrive, so do birds and insects that help nurture and pollinate plants, which will increase the quality of your garden.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now that you have read this article, you should know more about how to grow a wonderful organic garden. There is so much information about this and it is crucial that you learn about it and apply it to your gardening. If you keep this information in mind, you should be able to grow a great organic garden in no time.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kcmlmdHdvb2R1ay5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;driftwood&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="53db0e470842f84bff4717c7081618c3">			It has probably crossed your mind to hire a professional to landscape your yard. However, it is cheaper and fun if you do it yourself. All you need to have is the right information on what to do. Read this article to learn some helpful tips that will have your yard looking better than ever before.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Even small yards can be made beautiful. Use the space to create concentrated areas of interest. A stone garden bench or a birdbath surrounded by flowers and bushes is very attractive. Planning your flowers to bloom at different times will give you something pretty in your yard year-round.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Use local plants when landscaping. These are easier to tend to since they are already used to your climate. These means that you will have to take less time to help keep them growing. Your local gardening store will be able to advise you about the types of plants that will thrive in the area that you live.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;For a bigger variety and cheaper prices, shop online. There are a wide variety of websites that offer quality landscaping products at reasonable prices. Always read other customers' reviews when ordering products in order to get a good product. Make sure you compare prices between websites.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Landscaping goes well beyond simply planting trees and grasses. You can add visual interest by including structures of iron, cement, will wood. To increase beauty in your yard, as well as visual interested, put in archways, birdbaths, decks and pergolas. There are many different elements such as these that will fit your budget.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Prior to going shopping for your landscaping necessities, make a plan of what you need. Sketch out how you'd like the landscaping to turn out, and make exacting measurements so you know how much of each material or plant type you need to fill the space. Buying on impulse will leave you feeling empty as your wallet becomes lighter and you end up messing up your plan.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When planning your landscaping, include a variety of different plants. By doing this, your protect your lawn from diseases or insect infestation. If you use all the same plants, they will all be attacked and lost. Landscaping with a diverse selection helps keep plants healthy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Shaping your shrubbery and trees can go a long way when you're landscaping. Keep your trees and shrubs well-groomed by pruning them occasionally, as this will make your garden look much more attractive. This is an easy way to make your landscaping stand out.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Don't forget that landscaping includes paths and walkways as well. Plain concrete sidewalks are not attractive and signify a lack of effort. Replace old walkways with colored stones, gravel or brick pavers. You can find these varieties of colors and shapes, and they cost around the same as concrete would anyway.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're designing your landscape on your own, then try out mulch for your flowerbeds. Mulch prevents moisture from leaving your plants, and can be especially helpful if heat is a considerable issue in your area. Mulch holds on to a reservoir of moisture and lets the plants use the water as they need it.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Landscaping can be a hobby for everyone, not just a specialty for professionals! With a little elbow grease, some research and time, you can have a beautiful yard and do it all yourself! Your yard will be the envy of the neighborhood. That is something that every homeowner wants!&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kcmlmdHdvb2R1ay5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;surrey driftwood&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>