<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="1069b6b62a366a1f3672a77fb34c8456">			If you have dry eye syndrome, health conditions like glaucoma, cataract and also diabetes, you will be strongly advised not to undergo the treatment. Reputable clinics report that at least 50% of those who are available in for an initial assessment are rejected. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Enjoy does LASIK? How will laser eye surgery job? &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;First phase with the operation &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;To start, you are positioned on a reclined chair, and a numbing drop of solution put in your eye. Afterwards your cornea is cleaned of floating foreign matter, and instrument called a cover speculum is put over your eyes to maintain the eyelids open. The ring is place right on the eyeball. Suction is actually then applied around your cornea. You'll experience blurring and dimming of your vision. Then the surgeon uses a microkeratome (surgical knife) to make a thin, circular flap in the cornea. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Second phase &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;After, the microkeratome and ring are removed. The doctor then asks you to stare at the gentle. This is to get their eye stay focused on the fixed object, so that this doctor can proceed to the final phase of that operation. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Lastly phase &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The pre-programmed laser then sizes and shapes corneal tissue, thereby reshaping it. After the cornea may be reshaped, the flap is replaced back using a preventative shield is placed over your eyes to safeguard them from irritants. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Your operation would have taken you lower than a minute, with improved vision apparent in 24 hours. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Post operative care is as important as the process itself. So don't drive for a few weeks. Don't do get hold of sports. Go for the post operative examinations the eye surgeon has scheduled together with you. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Follow this do's and don'ts faithfully, so you'll be able to answer the question: Sow how does a safe laser observation surgery work? With some sort of bright smile and clear vision. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;A lot of people wonder the amount Lasik laser surgery costs but regardless of this, we all know the result. We do not need to ask for Lasik charge information to know that this can be a very expensive procedure. Nevertheless, we usually get blinded with the numbers. We do not see what's past that. This and other types of surgeries that include technology are expensive not because these are fancy methods but because good quality is not cheap. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Precisely what does this mean? When you get a Lasik laser operation or some other surgical operation, sometimes price does not matter. Usually, the reason why these kind of procedures are expensive is because of the fact that these doctors and/or hospitals will need to invest on the right equipment. They cannot just pick any. It is common-sense that they'll be dealing with sensitive areas such as our eyes and also other organs. They will need to proceed with utmost care. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Aside from the equipment, the money are going to be used to find efficient surgeons and technicians. Since these surgeries deal with delicate parts, the training for these are typically expensive. Hiring just about almost any graduate of any medical course is suicide for any hospital or institution. &lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;If you decide to have a Lasik surgical treatment, make sure that the hospital or clinic you check out is accredited. &lt;br /&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;Detailed information on &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kcm1vdHdhbmkuY29t" target="_blank"&gt;San Diego&lt;/a&gt; can be found at main website		</conversation>	</conversations></author>