<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="aeca179a1cc26bd8d0d4e31bc776e502">			What is the one expenditure that keeps you away from taking your dream vacation? Many individuals would agree that the ever rising price of hotels is what keeps them away from going on a vacation to a destination of their choice. In this day and age of economic turmoil, hardly anyone has been spared from financial crisis and most are cleverly saving their hard earned cash. But, what if you could get a ‘never before heard' cheap hotel deal? Would that make you alter your mind about taking the dream vacation that you wish to take so badly?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are already shaking your head in disbelief at the possibility of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcXVpZG9vLmNvbS9kaXNjb3VudC1sdXh1cnktaG90ZWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;discount hotel rooms&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;, spend a minute thinking over what William Shatner had to say in those funny commercials on Priceline.com. If you have already tried the service and have not been able to save the promised 50% with a discount hotel deal, its because you do not know how to best use the service.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;No, Shatner wasn't lying when he said that you can save half of what you usually pay for accommodation by using priceline.com to find a discount hotel deal. However, you need to know how to use the site to your advantage. The principle is awfully simple, you bid on the accommodation of your choice in a city that you intend to travel to. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you have placed your bid you would come to know whether your bid was accepted or it was rejected. If your bid is rejected, this is where several people run into a problem because you can not just keep changing the price until you get what you want. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;But the smart traveler “in the know” does not halt there! There is a very little known workaround in place that will aid you to get the most amazing discount hotel lodging. It would take you all of twenty minutes to learn this often overlooked technique but it will give you savings of possibly hundreds or even thousands when you travel on vacation.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You would simply have to put in a couple of minutes researching on-line and looking at the rates being offered by several accommodation providers in a city of your choice. Then, just use the technique together with the data that you’ve gathered to save enormously on discount hotel lodging.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Forget all about staying at low grade motels just because you cannot afford a four or five star hotel. You will be able to stay at &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rpc2NvdW50bHV4dXJ5aG90ZWwuYmxvZy5mcmllbmRzdGVyLmNvbS8yMDEwLzEwL2Rpc2NvdmVyaW5nLXRoZS1zZWNyZXRzLW9mLWZpbmRpbmctY2hlYXAtaG90ZWwv" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;cheap luxury hotels&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; for up to 50% off and save thousands doing it! How would you use an additional $1000 in savings? 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;This approach to beat the priceline.com system is easy, simple and totally legit, yet it can give you fabulous results and would aid you to save hundreds or even thousands on your next trip. So, get ready to have a blast without burning a hole in your pocket on your next vacation by checking out Luther’s system.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e14508db977aec3f6656bbec38981d43">			A cheap hotel room is so much a part of a regular tourist nowadays that newer ways are being invented by very intelligent individuals to help travelers in their respective quests. The traditional means of finding a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcXVpZG9vLmNvbS9kaXNjb3VudGx1eHVyeWhvdGVs" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;cheap hotel room&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; is to go online and sift through all of the thousands of options to try to find the reasonably priced ones. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Though, there is a new method that is much faster, much more reliable, and saves you much more cash, each time. Its called “Beating Priceline”. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The travelers that have used this method have saved an unbelievable 50 percent on their whole vacation. Additionally, once somebody has learned the way to apply this method, he or she could keep applying this method on hotel bookings for the remainder of their lives.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;While this method has been available in the back waters of specialized forums on the internet, only now is it being made public for everyone in an easy-to-understand, easy-to-implement format.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Beat Priceline technique takes advantages of more obscure tricks in how the Priceline web site and bidding system is built so that daily people can easily get the hotel rooms they want at rock bottom prices. This is not just a tutorial on how to use the Priceline site; this is a comprehensive manual on how to beat Priceline and get the best possible price anyplace.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One of the keys to the method is in knowing precisely how to do research on Priceline to find what you want and avoid what you do not want. Many people that first try the bidding system simply give up if they do not get what they want on the very first try. But the experienced travelers know precisely how to beat the system so they could keep re-bidding until they get what they want.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Did you know there is already a “cheat site” where you can go to see what low bids are succeeding on Priceline? Clever use of this extra resource is even part of the complete method of getting the best price on hotels each time.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These new advanced fail-safe methods for saving hundreds, even thousands, on hotels each year are so easy to learn that even beginners are saving hundreds of dollars in 20 minutes of learning. If you’re someone that stays in a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rpc2NvdW50bHV4dXJ5aG90ZWwuYmxvZy5mcmllbmRzdGVyLmNvbS8yMDEwLzEwL2hvdy10by1maW5kLWx1eHVyeS1ob3RlbC1yb29tcy1hdC1kaXNjb3VudC1wcmljZXMv" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;discount hotel rooms&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; more than two nights a year, then you owe it to yourself to learn and apply these techniques. Few vacationers have saved more than $5,000 in hotel bills by Beating Priceline.		</conversation>		<conversation id="6bb17fc365264c255d5552bef230c71">			When it comes to traveling, most individuals will decide to go with the economic option and settle for a lower priced hotel room. Others decide to pay more to enjoy their stay but wind up staying at a hotel far away from their preferred location.  
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;What if you never had to resolve between great price and location ever again? What if you can really get &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcXVpZG9vLmNvbS9kaXNjb3VudGx1eHVyeWhvdGVs" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;discount luxury hotel&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;; rates?
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You cannot find many savvy tourists who know how to get discounts on the rates of luxury for the price of regular rooms.  Believe it or not, it does not help much at all to know the management, to be a long time client of the hotel chain, or even to build up reward points on your credit card.  It is all about researching and reserving your room on-line in the right way.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;How much cash can you really save? Staying at a luxury hotel at a hotspot, such as downtown Miami, can cost up to $300 per night.  But with the right techniques, you could pay closer to $100 a night.  That's not a typo - nearly $200 in savings per night.  If you planned to stay there for 3 nights, that's savings of almost $600.  And this is only for luxury hotel rates. If you choose to stay at a mid level or economy hotel, you are savings will still be great and your overall rates a lot less. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So how could you get these types of savings? You can get these types of savings by using Priceline.com using a very specific method that only insiders know about. The company has been in business for many years and several individuals recognize them by the TV commercial where William Shatner says that you can be saving up to 50% on hotel rates. The crazy thing is he’s telling the truth! Only most individuals do not know how. Now you can learn exactly how.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you use Priceline.com to get some great savings using their Fee Chop discount, you are certainly not saving anywhere near as much as you could.  The trick is to utilize their &quot;Name Your Own Price&quot; feature in a very particular way to book your room.  If you follow the prompts as outlined by Priceline.com, which is how 95% of people do it, you don’t have a good chance of getting the lowest possible price. However, if you use the more obscure insider method, then you can almost guarantee an amazing price each time.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Ninety-fir pct of individuals using Priceline will compromise in some way, whether it is booking a room that is a lower star level than they really want or staying at a hotel far away from their preferred location.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You will not need to compromise on anything with this insider method. You could in fact get every single aspect which you want.  You could stay at luxury hotels for the price of a regular one.  If you're planning for a romantic weekend, this will come in handy and your significant other would wonder how you even got the room. The method is also invaluable for people who travel often, such as executives and salesmen.  Several professionals know they are going to be traveling lots so they settle for cheaper hotels or rooms.  But now they can enjoy their travels and stay at better hotels for cheaper rates.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;In conclusion, do not be fooled by the sticker price you see on Priceline or any other on-line sites when you make a &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Rpc2NvdW50bHV4dXJ5aG90ZWwuYmxvZy5mcmllbmRzdGVyLmNvbS8yMDEwLzEwL2ZpbmRpbmctYS1jaGVhcC1ob3RlbC1yb29tLWJ5LWJlYXRpbmctcHJpY2VsaW5lLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;strong&gt;;discount hotel booking&lt;/strong&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;.  You do not need to settle. You could get discount luxury hotel rates if you know the right strategy.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>