<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="30a02b6c5cb645f4d37ab14481136c04">			Introduction and History – There are nine main cruise chip lines that offer cruises from California as their starting point. These cruise lines are Carnival, Celebrity Cruises, Crystal Cruises, Holland America, Norwegian Cruise Lines, Radisson Seven Seas Cruises, Princess, Royal Caribbean International, and Silversea Cruises. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are two main ports that these cruise lines utilize; Los Angeles and San Diego.  The San Diego B Street Cruise Ship Terminal on Big Bay has approximately 180 cruise ship visits a year and has become a major ship cruises from California starting point. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;San Diego is the second largest city in California and the eighth largest in the United States. It is the birth place of California and is located on the coast just north of the Mexican-U.S. border. It has a natural deep water harbor that is home to a large U.S. Navy base. Juan Cabrillo claimed the area in the name of Spain when he arrived in 1542. It became part of Independent Mexico in 1821 and following the Mexican-American War became part of the United States in &lt;br /&gt;;1850, and the admission of California into the Union.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The three biggest companies to offer cruises from California are; Holland America, Norwegian Cruise Lines, and Royal Caribbean International.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Holland America Line – Holland America has been in business for over 130 years and are experts when it comes to cruising. One of their ships that sail out of San Diego is the HAL Westerdam. It was built in 2007 and is more than 3 football fields long and towers 100 feet above the water. It can carry 1,916 guests and has a crew of 800. Holland America are famous for having loads of space aboard their ships and carry hundreds less passengers than other liners. This allows the crew to give a superior level of service to their guests. Holland America is a “premium” line and is probably not for the budget conscious.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Carnival Cruises – This is another well known and trusted cruise company and one of their liners that offer cruises from California is the Carnival Spirit. It was built in 2000 and has a crew of 900 and can carry 2,124 passengers. The Carnival Spirit has 12 decks and 80% of her staterooms have water views! Even more remarkable is that 80% of these water view staterooms have their own private balcony! Every possible luxury can be found on board including a variety of dining facilities, bars, night clubs, swimming pools, casinos and health clubs.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;• Norwegian Cruise Lines – The NCL Norwegian Pearl is a brand new state of the art liner. It features a variety of accommodation including exclusive Courtyard Villas and Garden Villas. These Villas provide you with private courtyard, private access pools and private gardens. There is also private hot tub, sundeck, exercise room, cabanas and much more. There are also family friendly connecting staterooms and suites. There is a rock climbing wall and a bowling alley located in the Bliss Ultra Lounge. This lounge contains a bowling alley/sports bar/night club complex and is a favorite amongst guests. Cruises from California can be as exciting or as laid back as you want.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdXJpb24ubmV0" target="_blank"&gt;;chester zoo vouchers&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="f690a6438fc181f6bbd1e069fae34179">			Introduction – Remembering that a business is only as good as its employees, it makes good business sense to consider some employee recognition ideas. Studies have shown that employees who are recognized and rewarded for their efforts are more likely to be engaged and productive than employees who are not. The following is a small list of employee recognition ideas that can be readily implemented for little or no cost.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1. Employee of the Month- this is a proven tried and tested way to make an employee feel that his or her efforts are not going unnoticed. A framed photo of the employee can be placed in a prominent place in the office or business.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;2. Staff Appreciation Program – you can award points for things like reaching targets, punctuality etc. When an employee reaches a certain amount of points they could be awarded a travel voucher, dining voucher or gift certificate. This is a very successful way to achieve targets and encourage loyalty and a good work ethic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3. Employee Feedback- this could be as simple as a “suggestion box” and it is important to employees that their ideas are being looked at and that management encourages these suggestions. Sometimes a compromise can be reached if ideas have merit.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4. Thankyou and a Handshake – quite often it is the simple things that can mean a lot. A manager who personally thanks an employee for their efforts and shakes his/her hand can make a huge difference to an employees self-esteem and confidence .&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5. Professional Development – rewarding employees who have completed further study to enhance their qualifications and workplace opportunities. Rewards could be a promotion or a pay increase. This has significant benefits such as high employee retention rates and more productive employees who can take on more challenging tasks within the company.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6. Birthdays – Management can foster great employer/employee relations by simply remembering a staff member’s birthday. An inexpensive card and a happy birthday greeting from a manager or supervisor are always appreciated. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;7. Lunch Breaks – if a member of your workplace has performed well, give them an extra long lunch break or let them go home an hour earlier. This is a proven winner in keeping employees happy and motivated.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;8. Personal – if for example you know that an employee likes sports and has been doing a good job, you could get them tickets to a sporting event. If an employee really likes cooking, you could purchase a cook book and write a note of appreciation on the inside cover. Again, it is sometimes small acts of appreciation and recognition that mean a great deal to the employee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;9. Newsletters – implement a company newsletter and devote a section to employee recognition and appreciation. This is a transparent and powerful way to achieve loyalty and have a happy and productive employee.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;10. Communication – refer to your employees and workers by their first name, and actively listen to what they have to say.&lt;br /&gt;;There are of course many more employee recognition ideas, the preceding list is just a sample to show managers and supervisors that it can be very easy to foster good workplace relations.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5hdXJpb24ubmV0" target="_blank"&gt;;chester zoo vouchers&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>