<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="236a1635abf02c0d9f25ba772eab1f7b">			There are many terrible stories associated with people taking vacations. Many times you will find that what happened in those stories was because the person was not properly prepared. This shouldn't be a problem. This article will give you tips so you have an enjoyable vacation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To get the most enjoyment while vacationing, make sure to take projected weather conditions into consideration. Always check what the weather forecast will be at your destination. Freezing rain on a Florida beach, or unseasonal sunshine on an Aspen ski trip, will ruin the best laid travel plans.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When flying on a plane, you should plan ahead because an airline won't always be able to meet your basic needs, even when the flight lasts for many hours. Bring your own pillow, blanket and headphones if you think you will need them. You may also want to think of bringing your own food so you can eat what you want.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Air travel requires a bit of planning. Airports located in large, unfamiliar cities can be difficult to find. The traffic around airports can also create serious delays. Pack up all your suitcases the night before you travel. Complete and execute all of your plans well in advance of your flight. One of the worst ways to start a trip is to miss your flight.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The use of travel agencies has declined for a reason; everyone books trips online because it is so convenient. You can use travel sites to effectively plan an itinerary without much research. You can take care of plane tickets, car rentals, hotel bookings, and more, all without looking up from the screen. Choosing a hotel is a snap when travel sites link you to photos and guest reviews. Many travel sites even guide you toward finding discounts.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you travel with eyeglasses, make sure that an extra pair is in your luggage. This provides with a spare pair if your current pair breaks on the plane. Put them in your suitcase, so that if your bag was stolen, you still have them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The shoes you wear when you go flying should be comfortable, lightweight, and easy to take off and put on. Remember that shoes need to come off at the security checkpoint. The most important thing is comfort. You are not going to have to do as much walking as you will sitting in most cases, so the heavy-duty support isn't really that necessary. Sandals or flip-flops are footwear that is ideal for air travel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Contact lens cases are a great thing to take whenever you go on vacation. They are great for packing small amounts of lotions or hair gel.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you want to adjust quickly to an unfamiliar time zone, don't allow yourself to fall asleep until nighttime locally. Though you may be exhausted, succumbing to sleep earlier than you should may end up making your jet lag worse because you have not allowed your body to recalibrate. It's easier to overcome jet lag if you adjust to the local time as quickly as possible.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Hopefully, these tips have helped you plan for your next traveling experience, whether it is to a far away foreign country, or just a road trip somewhere in the state where you live. Traveling is a rewarding and fascinating adventure which can be full of surprises; therefore, treat yourself to the vacation that you have always dreamed of.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWV0YW5kZ3JlZXRnYXR3aWNrYWlycG9ydC5jb20vbG9uZG9uX2dhdHdpY2tfdHJhbnNwb3J0YXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;; meet and greet gatwick airport&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWV0YW5kZ3JlZXRnYXR3aWNrYWlycG9ydC5jb20vZG9jdW1lbnRzL2xpbmtzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;meet and greet gatwick&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWV0YW5kZ3JlZXRnYXR3aWNrYWlycG9ydC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;; meet and greet gatwick airport&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="42153e6dc17c8ebc37f109fe9a7c6383">			There is much more to traveling than just boarding a plane. It can be a truly exciting experience. There are a lot of great travel spots when planning a vacation. Will there be a once in a lifetime trip waiting for you? Following are some travel tips that can help you to get started.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Pack travel candles in your luggage if you plan on staying at a hotel. These can improve the smell of an impersonal hotel room. Not only is it romantic, it will relax you and help you to fall asleep. These candles are available in travel sizes and in drip-free formulations.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Take the time to read reviews on the Internet about any resorts or lodgings in which you are interested, so you will know what to expect when you make your travel plans. By looking for feedback from people who have used the same business, you can avoid booking a stay somewhere that is likely to leave you unhappy.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are taking your dogs with you while you travel, make sure to thoroughly brush them out before you put them in your car. Doing so helps to reduce loose hair. Also be sure to include all necessities for your dog like bowls, leashes and clean up materials.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Travel can be a great way to educate your family members. You can travel to other countries if you prepare yourself accordingly. This could be a great opportunity to expose your children to other cultures. When you spend time abroad, you give yourself and your family a greater understanding of another culture and the world at large.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're traveling somewhere where you'll need tickets, like amusement parks or a play, look for ways to have them ahead of time. There is a small fee associated with purchasing tickets online; however, the time saved at the ticket booth will make it worth the cost. Some parks now have tickets that contain a specific time in order to avoid lines.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Review any hotels or resorts you plan on staying in through online reviews and travel sites, so that any potential issues can surface before you finalize your itinerary. By looking at reviews prior to booking your trip, it will save you from picking the wrong place.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Educate your family by traveling. Even taking a trip to a developing nation can be a safe way to teach kids about the lives of people outside their home country. The best way to foster tolerance for other cultures in your children is to spend time in other countries with them.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When you enter a new country, avoid exchanging currency. Use a different method, instead. Bank ATMs are a great place to get your foreign currency from. These machines will usually have the best exchange rate available.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;You should write all of your contact information inside your luggage, include your name, address, and home and mobile phone numbers. Even if the luggage is lost and the tags are detached, you still may be able to find it. It's a simple precaution that could save your luggage.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you can use something from this article, chances are you will find more excitement and adventure than ever before on your next vacation. No matter if this will be your first vacation or fifteenth, your trip will be positively affected by following this advice.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWV0YW5kZ3JlZXRnYXR3aWNrYWlycG9ydC5jb20_" target="_blank"&gt;;meet and greet at gatwick&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWV0YW5kZ3JlZXRnYXR3aWNrYWlycG9ydC5jb20vbG9uZG9uX2dhdHdpY2tfdHJhbnNwb3J0YXRpb24uaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;; meet and greet gatwick airport&lt;/a&gt;;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5tZWV0YW5kZ3JlZXRnYXR3aWNrYWlycG9ydC5jb20vZG9jdW1lbnRzL2xpbmtzLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;meet and greet gatwick&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>