<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="d106e9881d1fa8b12ed2f3fc1bac120a">			The course most commonly is of a extended duration where in it detects most of the diabetic symptoms and a patient gets treated accordingly. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;Learning acupuncture can seem to be daunting. There seem to be many details and lots to do all at once. This is mostly since courses that teach acupuncture are badly organised (yes, I am in your midst of writing a better one). However, that is the topic for another posting. This article is about finding the right path of learning. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;To find your own individual manner of learning there is only one way. That is to remember how you have learned things in earlier times. Make a list of ten things you have learned - a variety is best, (things that took a protracted while or were instant, things that were convenient or were hard, different areas of your life - sport, friendship, conversing your native language or anything else). Examine these things to find out what helped you discover and what didn't. Then try to look for common elements about how you will learn best. You will then possess a list describing your own way of learning which you could apply to learning acupuncture. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When i do this I discover that what helps me discover best is clear and simple instructions: just do this, just keep doing which. So with acupuncture I look for the vital skills together with concepts. The details that i use I'll remember and whatever else I can look up. Others of course will be the opposite. A friend of mine at acupuncture college loved the important points - all the ins and outs of the different points were what he loved. My approach to learning was completely useless with regard to him. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;I'd also like to provide some general approaches to help learning. The most useful I've found is three styles associated with learning: head, heart and hand. Head means options and abstractions, heart suggests people and feelings, hand means moving and working at. All of these will usually be part of learning. However each people usually has a choice. The more we may use this preference the easier our learning is going to be. Because acupuncture has ideas, it is about healing people along with the concepts refer directly to our experience it can be learned pretty easily by a person with all of these preferences. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you're a head person like me it will help to organise the principles. My way of achieving this is: health, sickness, treatment. Health consists of the channels (and their own organs) and fundamental fluids, sickness is what interferes with health (the devils and thieves) together with treatment is diagnosis, point selection and needle process. There are only about 40 ideas you have to know (yin and yang, that five elements, the 12 options and organs, the six devils, the six robbers, the four examinations plus a few miscellaneous). &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Forty can look like a lot but it's only one a week cheaper than a year. It can also help to write a shorter bit about the idea and stick it up where you notice frequently - above the sink, on the back of the toilet door, wherever. In this way it becomes part of your life and not something you have to sit down and focus on - it's rather a lot easier. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy4xMm1lcmlkaWFuc2FjdXB1bmN0dXJlLmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;acupuncture Columbus OH&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>