<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="108eade5b31120d2a965fa039f744af">			&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5kb2NzdG9jLmNvbS9kb2NzLzExNDA5NjY5OS9Cb290LUNhbXAtTWFya2V0aW5n" target="_blank"&gt;;boot camp marketing&lt;/a&gt;;, [url=]fitness bootcamp marketing[/url]&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It used to be that if you needed a sets of jeans, you left for The Gap and decided on between Levi's and Gap brand jeans. Through an average personal training session costing around $60, not to mention the actual gym initiation fees and travel expense, the price tag on one-on-one training can soon hurt your wallet. Many people are intimidated to attend gyms due to several muscular and fit most people, overwhelming equipment, and just overall too much chaos going on. Well online training offers the opportunity to meet your goals without feeling embarrassed or uncomfortable. Flexibility can also be described as a huge advantage, meaning online training can be done without any set schedule or routine. Although this could be a disadvantage if the client lacks motivation, accountability, and discipline to be able to consistent to the method you assign them. This is due to them wanting a physical presence there with each other and guiding them with the workout. Also online trainers is unable to always judge your progress and watch your posture when performing certain workouts, which will really frustrate a potential client and possibly lead to worse problems. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There are bigger questions to address with online training that could put the trainer and also the client at a potential risk. The three essential elements of personal training are: A first assessment, observing the shoppers training, and giving relevant feedback to make sure that progress. These processes are generally severely compromised through internet training. If you attempt to choose an online trainer, make sure the trainer has a similar protocol assessment for an actual trainer at some sort of gym would. I recommend a phone consultation before paying, think of this for an initial screening process and you can really get a feel for any trainer to see if you do want to work with your ex. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;When buying training packages for a gym, you are subjected to a waiver, removing all liability from the club along with the trainer the majority of the time. With online training, there are often times no waiver or authorized agreements provided. I can't stress this enough to check if you do go with an online trainer that they do have a release of liability waiver. Which brings me to my own next point, what about the legalities of online fitness? What if the client were to get injured while using your program you supplied also, you are in a different county or state? Which are the legal responsibilities then? Well, a legal agreement may be addressed between the coach and client by several ways: valid contract and valid contacts. A valid contract can be a signed agreement agreeing to terms and conditions of online training and the commitment between both get-togethers. A valid contact shows that there's a reasonable amount of contact between the client and trainer over and above the click of a button to purchase a training program. To guarantee the best service, a phone consultation or skype should be set up, along using a printed contract should be mailed to sign and return to the proper address. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;If you are an online trainer, take the following steps to establish evidence of a valid contract, assumption of risk, informed permission, and fulfillment of your legal duty for a personal trainer. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>