<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="eb19a368d2495d95c34551034a9a8a47">			BUSINESS came to a halt on Thursday evening in Masvingo when an alleged adulterous woman threw herself before a moving haulage truck in protest over her husband’s decision to take her back to her parents’ home after allegedly infecting him with a sexually transmitted infection (STI).
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The woman, Ms Ruth Rusere (24), of Village 7, Gokomere, Masvingo, who has a one-year eight months-old child was however saved by touts who nearly caused a scene when they stood guard in the middle of the road, oblivious of the risk of oncoming traffic.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The incident which attracted a huge crowd happened near Croco Motors along Masvingo-Harare Road at around 4pm when Ms Rusere was walking with her husband Mr Torerai Dende (36) and his cousin, Mr Claitos Chikorera (48), both of Fuwe Village, Chief Nhema, Zaka, towards where they wanted to board lifts to Gokomere.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Without warning Ms Rusere jumped into the road just before an oncoming haulage truck, leaving her husband and his cousin but was pulled back to safety by an alert tout, who identified himself, as Rasta.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“I saw this woman jumping into the road and sprawl on the tar just a few metres from a speeding haulage truck. I quickly rushed to grab her hand and pulled her to safety, much to the relief of her husband who had remained on the other side of the road while holding the woman’s baby,” said Rasta.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Narrating the episode, Mr Chikorera, who revealed to Chronicle that they had been married for only three months, said it all started last week when his wife visited him in Harare where he works as a security guard.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“Our marriage is only three months old and I only finished paying lobola last month. After paying lobola, I allowed her to remain at her parents’ homestead in Gokomere for a few weeks.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“After close to three weeks, she followed me to Marlborough, Harare, where I stay while working as a security guard. After two days enjoying my conjugal rights, I discovered that I had developed some rash on my manhood and that meant my wife had infected me with an STI,” said Mr Chikorera.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;He said he interrogated his wife after showing her the infection and she allegedly gave the name of another man whom she only identified as Tau, from her home area in Gokomere.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“I asked her and she told me the man responsible but said she was not aware that she had the disease. However, she refused that we seek treatment together and I ended up going alone and got treated at the clinic.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“We then came to my home area in Zaka where I told my parents who also advised me to take her to her parents. When we were still in Zaka, she drank poison, an insecticide, in an attempt to commit suicide but I rushed with her to a nearby clinic where she was treated and discharged.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“I have since communicated with my in-laws and they have advised me that I should bring her to their home so that we can solve the issue together. However, my wife seems to be reluctant to face her parents as she is ashamed of what she has done to me but still, that does not mean she has to end her life. She just jumped into the road while we were walking towards the bus stop.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“She has a young baby who still needs to be breastfed. Although the baby is not mine, I have been the one responsible for the child’s upkeep. We are yet to have children of our own. I have my own from a previous marriage,” he said.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Mr Chikorera reported the matter to the police but said the law enforcers did not seem concerned, as they argued that the woman was not mentally challenged, so they could not arrest or detain her.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;“I am afraid that she can refuse to go to her parents and if she remains adamant I won’t know what to do,” said a visibly shaken Mr Chikorera.		</conversation>		<conversation id="a7cdfea42b6eb8cf9d2de356afb316fc">			OPEN air worshipers in Masvingo city are facing imminent ban amid fears of disease outbreaks as some religious groups conducted prayers where there are no sanitary facilities.
&lt;br /&gt;;This follows a resolution by Masvingo City Council to act on open air worshipers who violate council by-laws that prohibit people or religious organisation to conduct their prayers where there are no ablution facilities.
&lt;br /&gt;;The resolution also comes against the backdrop of concerns raised by members of the Traditional Medical Practitioner Council on members of apostolic sects who conducted their prayers on open spaces where there are no toilets and water.
&lt;br /&gt;;Contacted for comment, Masvingo City Council Mayor Alderman Femius Chakabuda said it was the local authority’s mandate to ensure that to ensure that people including relious groups did not use council land without authority.
&lt;br /&gt;;“No one should occupy council land without given the authority and this also includes religious groups. To make matters worse some religious groups are seen conducting their prayers on open space where there are no toilets, let alone water. This is cause of grave concern to us, as city fathers,” said Ald Chakabuda.
&lt;br /&gt;;He said the city council would embark on a blitz that would see open air worshiping stopped adding that they were not against people praying.
&lt;br /&gt;;“We are not opposed to people’s religion because we are also God-fearing men and women. We are only worried on seeing people gathering and conducting their prayers where there are no toilets and with the advent of diseases like cholera and typhoid there is a great risk. Besides people should get the authority first to use the bushes they are using since all the land around the city is within our jurisdiction as Masvingo City Council,” he said.
&lt;br /&gt;;Ald Chakabuda advised religious groups to apply for permission to use school grounds and some halls instead of open air spaces.
&lt;br /&gt;;“We are asking all open air worshipers to make applications to hire school grounds and our halls for use during their prayer sessions as opposed to the use of open spaces. There has not been any report of cholera or any water borne diseases but if we keep ignoring such unhealthy practices, there is a high risk.”
&lt;br /&gt;;Director of Housing and Community Services has since been instructed to revive the operation that bans open air worshiping to ensure that religious groups complied with Council requirements by using places with sanitary facilities.
&lt;br /&gt;;A similar exercise was carried out in 2009 when a semblance of working order was restored.
&lt;br /&gt;;The issue of open air worshipers is becoming a cause of concern with a number of local authorities also facing similar challenges. Repeated efforts to stop religious groups from using conduct their prayers on open air spaces have been meant with stiff resistance from the worshipers themselves. 
&lt;br /&gt;;Bulawayo City Council has at one time suggested that religious groups use disused beer halls but most have shot down the idea arguing that the environment would not be conducive for prayers.
&lt;br /&gt;;Ends		</conversation>	</conversations></author>