<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="f75241645fb3a3d61b10b6fe67e34265">			And, looking at the new Nokia PureView 808 - with it 41 MP file size- that is launching soon, it does look like the Mobile mob want to make a land-grab rather than seek peaceful co-existence.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So Camera manufacturers, with their intricate lenses, flash systems and mechanics are all starting to look a bit last year. The modern consumer wants fast, intuitive, easy technology, that duplicates what he sees and then adds some pixie dust. He doesn't want to have to think too much. He didn't learn his photography in a dark room. For him it isn't a craft - much less an art. Picture taking is something he does with his friends, shares, posts and publishes instantly, comments on and tags. It is a social phenomenon. So why have a camera, no matter how slim and chic, if you can have a phone-cam-text-upload-vid box that does it all? And so the mobile phone market will gradually consume compact cameras.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;So what are the camera guys to do?&lt;br /&gt;;Well, it looks like they have already started. Whilst  Canon and Nikon will see out the general interest in D-SLRs and continue to satisfy the specialist market, I think the other manufacturers see their futures in Bridge and Compact Systems. It makes sense, as they fit the brief. Bridge cameras have all the advantages of an SLR, without the need to carry different lenses. They look and act like proper cameras and work within the shutter speed and aperture parameters that we are all familiar with. And whilst the purists will shudder, they are capable of taking excellent quality images. Over the next few years, I predict that the Bridge cameras will come more to the fore, getting even bigger lenses and file sizes, and developing into niches of their own (studio, sport, landscape etc). They will no longer be a stepping stone between compacts and &quot; proper &quot; SLRs, but a destination in their own right.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.bestdealsforcameras.com%2Fwp-content%2Fuploads%2F2012%2F04%2Ffujifilm-X-Pro1-Angle.jpg%26gt"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.bestdealsforcameras.com/wp-content/uploads/2012/04/fujifilm-X-Pro1-Angle.jpg&gt;&lt;/a&gt;;; The really exciting development recently has been the compact system cameras. Here the manufacturers are taking advantage of the new technology and finally ditching the old. With live view LCD screens, there is no need for the SLR mechanical view finder anymore and this enables the manufacturers to make the new cameras smaller without losing quality. The fact that they still offer changeable lenses means that they still have that specialist feel about them. It is interesting to see how they are developing. Nikon seem to be experimenting with their V1 and J1 cameras, pushing the limits with 60FPS burst speed and motion capture. the cameras themselves look modern and stylish. Fuji and olympus seem to favor the classical look and tend to stick to core requirements. In all cases the file sizes are getting bigger and the quality is getting better.&lt;br /&gt;;So, as the Mobile mob are moving into the camera market, camera manufacturers are repositioning and consolidating their new growth areas. In a few years the landscape will show a large standard market of mobile phone cameras, probably with large files, but only digital zoom functions, a wider specialist range of Bridge cameras and compact System Cameras, which will have effectively taken the place currently occupied by the larger, chunkier D-SLRs. Hopefully camera makers will be able to survive on people's recognition that, whilst recording events is fine with a mobile, you need a proper camera to take pictures. The question is, with stills cameras becoming so adept at video, what will the video camera manufacturers do?&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5iZXN0ZGVhbHNmb3JjYW1lcmFzLmNvbS9ibG9nLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;canon cameras&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>