<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e3f7016f16b6030d3dd49725ad7afff2">			SHAW CAPITAL MANAGEMENT  -  On January 19th 2010, the first ethanol-fired power plant whirred into action in Brazil. National oil company Petrobras (NYSE: PBR) and American systems giant General Electric (NYSE: GE) pitched in resources to turn an existing 87 MW plant into a flex-fuel power station that can alternate between natural gas and ethanol (which are both considered alternative fuels, even though only one is renewable).
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;GE wants to see how its turbines can be adapted to work in flex-fuel plants in Brazil and in developed countries like Japan, where clean-burning power plants are gaining momentum.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Brazil's water-dependent hydroelectric infrastructure teeters during the dry season in places where natural gas isn't easily accessible. It just so happen that wind power peaks at the opposite time of the year as the water in running rivers that drives dam-based generation.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ethanol and wind could supplant natural gas as the primary alternative source of electricity generation during the dry season in Brazil and President Luiz Inacio Lula da Silva said in the Brazilian press that Brazil could be selfsufficient in natural gas after several pre-salt (read: incredibly deep) offshore fossil fuel pockets are tapped.
&lt;br /&gt;That capacity is at least five years away. Ethanol is there now, and after wind power auctions started last December, 773 wind turbines will be turning across Brazil by 2012.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shaw Capital Management Korea News: Shell, Petrobras, GE, and Cosan will surely push hard to get the government in Brasilia to initiate a nationwide &quot;;ethanol electricity&quot;; campaign to ensure that oil and automotive fuel aren't the key determinants of sugar ethanol's success.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As in so many other areas of the world, those communities that are now underserved by fossil fuels can benefit most from such clean energy advances.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The US Administration completed its revised Renewable Fuels Standard (RFS2). RFS2 will move towards a national goal of 26 billion gallons of biofuel production by 2022.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;At Shaw Capital Management we give you the information and insight you need to make the right investment choices. We look forward to working with you and being the open architects of your financial well being.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Shaw Capital Management Korea - Investment Innovation &amp; Excellence.  We provide the information; insight and expertise that you need to make the right investment choices. Shaw Capital Management Korea typically offers its clients such services as asset allocation and portfolio design; traditional and non-traditional manager review and selection; portfolio implementation; portfolio monitoring and consolidated performance reporting; and other wealth management services, including estate, tax, trust and insurance planning, asset custody, closely held business issues associated with the establishment or expansion of a family office, the formation of family investment partnerships or LLCs, philanthropy, family dynamics and inter-generation issues, etc.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Every investor will achieve better long-term risk-adjusted results by working with a true open architecture advisor.
&lt;br /&gt;Our philosophy is simple: almost every investor will achieve better long-term risk-adjusted results by working with a true open architecture advisor.
&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Before Shaw Capital Management Korea  launched the open architecture revolution, investors had to make the unhappy choice between selecting an advisor who was independent, but unsophisticated (the traditional pension and endowment consulting firms), or selecting an advisor who was sophisticated but had conflicting interests (global banks, trust companies, money management firms).		</conversation>		<conversation id="9ab5dc87187a04cb119dbd800d9f0399">			Kian Ghazi, CFA
&lt;br /&gt;Managing Partner
&lt;br /&gt;Hawkshaw Capital Management
&lt;br /&gt;THIS PRESENTATION IS FOR INFORMATIONAL AND EDUCATIONAL PURPOSES ONLY AND SHALL NOT BE CONSTRUED TO CONSTITUTE INVESTMENT ADVICE. NOTHING CONTAINED HEREIN SHALL CONSTITUTE A SOLICITATION, RECOMMENDATION OR ENDORSEMENT TO BUY OR SELL ANY SECURITY OR OTHER FINANCIAL INSTRUMENT OR TO BUY ANY INTERESTS IN THE INVESTMENT FUNDS OR OTHER ACCOUNTS MANAGED BY HAWKSHAW CAPITAL MANAGEMENT, LLC (“HAWKSHAW”). HAWKSHAW OWNED STOCK IN LEARNING TREE AND LESCO AT THE TIME OF PUBLICATION (NOVEMBER 1, 2006). WE HAVE NO OBLIGATION TO UPDATE THE INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN AND MAY MAKE INVESTMENT DECISIONS THAT ARE INCONSISTENT WITH THE VIEWS EXPRESSED IN THIS PRESENTATION. WE MAKE NO REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTIES AS TO THE ACCURACY, COMPLETENESS OR TIMELINESS OF THE INFORMATION, TEXT, GRAPHICS OR OTHER ITEMS CONTAINED IN THIS PRESENTATION. WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL LIABILITY FOR ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN, OR THE MISUSE OR MISINTERPRETATION OF, ANY INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THIS PRESENTATION. PAST PERFORMANCE IS NO GUARANTEE OF FUTURE RESULTS AND FUTURE RETURNS ARE NOT GUARANTEED
&lt;br /&gt;Our Investment Strategy
&lt;br /&gt;Just like most of you, we are value investors.
&lt;br /&gt;? We search among a targeted group of stocks for asymmetric risk/reward potential.
&lt;br /&gt;? Our mission is to establish concentrated investments in good businesses that are
&lt;br /&gt;mis-priced as a result of what we believe are overly pessimistic expectations or
&lt;br /&gt;underappreciated potential.
&lt;br /&gt;? We demand a high margin of safety – consisting of 3 components:
&lt;br /&gt;? Own quality businesses with high incremental returns on capital.
&lt;br /&gt;? invest only when the stock trades at a substantial discount to our conservative
&lt;br /&gt;appraisal value.
&lt;br /&gt;AND…
&lt;br /&gt;? Perform grass-roots, “scuttlebutt” research to help confirm (or refute) our thesis.
&lt;br /&gt;What is Scuttlebutt Research?
&lt;br /&gt;? Speaking with Proprietary, Non-Wall Street Contacts
&lt;br /&gt;? Customers
&lt;br /&gt;? Competitors
&lt;br /&gt;? Suppliers
&lt;br /&gt;? Other industry veterans
&lt;br /&gt;? Co-Sourcing our Company/Industry Analysis to Understand:
&lt;br /&gt;? Strengths and weaknesses
&lt;br /&gt;? Headwinds and tailwinds
&lt;br /&gt;? Level of competitiveness
&lt;br /&gt;? Power of buyers and suppliers
&lt;br /&gt;? Barriers to entry
&lt;br /&gt;? Threat of substitutes
&lt;br /&gt;Hawkshaw – a slang term from the 1800’s meaning detective. 5
&lt;br /&gt;I Know What Many of You Are Thinking…
&lt;br /&gt;? “I don’t do scuttlebutt research, and my returns are just fine.”
&lt;br /&gt;? “I’m a long term investor, not a channel checker or data point chaser.”
&lt;br /&gt;? “It simply produces anecdotal information that creates a lot of noise.”
&lt;br /&gt;? “It’s too time intensive relative to the usefulness of the information.”
&lt;br /&gt;“What a man believes upon grossly insufficient evidence is an index into his desires – desires of
&lt;br /&gt;which he himself is often unconscious.”
&lt;br /&gt;- Bertrand Russell		</conversation>	</conversations></author>