<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="43a92db5d418b31a771158b129d2a7b7">			Quick weight loss is with regards to everyone trying to get thin and show great in the least time possible.It can be tough but there ARE ways you can speed up the procedure of &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2Zhc3Rlc3R3YXl0b2xvc2V3ZWlnaHR0LmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;easy way to lose weight&lt;/a&gt;;and losing weight in a healthy way. Experienced home-made Salsa with one meal.&lt;br /&gt;; &lt;br&gt;; 6. Using Walden Farms Greens Dressing &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;These are some of the different things I did this first week relating to the HCG diet that are not part of Dr. Simeons Original Protocol. As stated above, I only had a couple stalls this first week, with the second being in the change in protocol. As I go through this I most certainly will continue to update you on my progress and also share many of the recipes I use using everyone. &lt;br /&gt;;.&lt;br /&gt;;The secrets to quick weight loss have been known for some time, but because it will likely be frowned upon, quick weight loss hasn't been advertised as something much more try and achieve. We are always being told that if we choose to go for quick weight loss, we will put your weight straight back on! We're told that rapid loss of weight is not real weight loss! But how can that will be true? If the scales say that you have lost the weight, then you definately have lost the weight! If your old clothes say that you have lost the weight, then you definately have lost the body fat! If losing weight quickly is what you want to do, then the secrets to do that are here! All I ask is that you really never stop practising these, even when you reach your target weight. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;b&gt;; Quick weight loss Tips &lt;/b&gt;; &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;1) Mineral water! You should aim to drink eight or higher glasses of cold water daily! If you can drink it straight from the fridge rather than the tap, all the better since fridge water uses up more calories. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;two) Eat more meals! Sounds odd doesn't it? Plan to eat four small meals a day and your body won't get into starvation mode and slow down your metabolism. If your body understands that you will feed it often and in a small amount it will burn fat quicker and easier. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;3) Schedule your largest meal at lunchtime! Whatever you do, don't have your largest meal two hours before you head to bed. Give your body time for you to digest and begin burning the calories before you head to bed. &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;4) Make a minumum of one of your meals for the day a variety of your favourite fruits! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;5) Find a way to add exercise to your daily routine, but whatever you do don't go off and start some big exercise regime that you really cannot sustain. If you're not necessarily particularly active, start off of with simple walks, even taking the stairs rather than the lift will help! &lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;6) If you're using a weight loss program to help you with your weight loss and you will have a bad day and fall heli-copter flight program, don't give in place! Get straight back into it and work that application to success. Remember, no one is perfect and you should have times/days when things don't check out plan.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>