<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="2">		<conversation id="e91c7b856a1a1472122ae4497187fccd">			Memory is the is the capability of a person to keep hold of and recall the various information’s and expereinces.The memory process starts with the encoding of information, its storage and then its retrieval 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Process of memory
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The process of memory starts with encoding of information the information is received, processed and combined and kept as storage in the permanent record of brain. It is then retrieved by calling back the required information in response of any demand that comes up.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Types of memory
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Sensory memory is for 200-500 milliseconds which is forgettable after that a second of observation. This is due to the fact that they see more item than they actually recall. Iconic memory and echoic memory are two types of sensory memory. The iconic memory stores the image for a short period while the echoic memory stores the sound for a short period.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Short term memory is for several seconds to a minute duration that stays without any effort. The capacity of this memory is very limited. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Long-term memory can store large amount of information for long durations sometimes even a life span.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Levels of processing of memory
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The storage of information in memory depends on the level of processing. The following types of processing can be done to improve memory. The organization of information should be done by sorting them into any piles of numbers by categorization of them. They can easily recall the categorized words than other long piles. The people should present the information in a different and distinct way so that they can recall that easily. Presenting the information in a loud way is also a distinct way. The amount of effort that has been given to memorize the information also helps in recalling the information easily. The difficult information can be easily recalled as people lay more effort in memorizing difficult information than the easy information. The elaborated things are also remembered for longer times.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Methods to optimize memorization
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Rote learning is a technique in which the focus is on the memorization without knowing the meaning of it. The repetition is used to learn things in this method. Associative learning is that technique in which the content is learned by relating it to the information that is already present in mind.Meaningful learning: This learning is memorized by knowing the meaning and usefulness of the information. Cramming is the memorization technique which is remembered for short period. The spacing effect memorizes the information in a list form which is kept in mind for longer period of time. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Factors that influence memory
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The emotions effects the memory as any emotional incident tends to stay in our mind for longer period as we relate it with any part of our life too .This is the reason why `autobiographies are easily remembered as they have lot of emotional events.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The previous knowledge can be used while memorizing new things as when a relation is established between new information and old information then it will not take more time to memorize new one.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXJlbWVkaWVzLXdvcmxkLmNvbS9kaXZ5YS1tZWRoYS12YXRpLmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;memory enhancement&lt;/a&gt;; also read about [url=&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.home-remedies-world.com%2Fpackage-mental-retardation.html"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://www.home-remedies-world.com/package-mental-retardation.html&lt;/a&gt;;]mental retardation treatment&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXJlbWVkaWVzLXdvcmxkLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;Herbal Remedies&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>		<conversation id="8fde5851e135af441e18dc67f0e4b303">			Obesity is a situation of a human body in which the fat is too much on the body. Please note that there is difference between obesity and being overweight. Overweight means that the body weight is too much. The increased weight can be due to several reasons like weight of muscle, bone or water in the body. Both these terms means that the weight of a human body is more than what is appropriate according to his or her height. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obesity takes time as it appears when the person eats more calories than required by his or her body. The amount of calories that a burn eats and burns differs from person to person. It depends on lot of factors like genetics, workout, eating of high fat food. The obesity widens the chances of many diseases like diabetes, heart attack, stroke and arthritis.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Causes of obesity
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There can be different reasons for obesity. The obesity starts when you are eating more calories than required by your body and you cannot burn those over taken calories. The increased intake of alcohol, lack of exercise or workout. Another reason that can be behind obesity is eating same kind of food stuff over longer periods. You should not follow the same eating pattern as you used to when you are a kid. Lack of healthy meals, sedentary jobs, lack of time to exericse, underactive thyroid gland, some medicines like birth control pills, anti-depressants etc makes the person obese. Females gain weight during their menopause and during their pregnancy.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obesity tests
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The two better known tests to measure the risks of health are body mass index and measuring the circumference of waist. The fitness expert will also put some questions related to medical history, eating habits and routine of exercise.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;BMI is measured by knowing a person’s height and weight.BMI is used to assess how much fat on the body you have as extra pounds.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Waist measurement is another way to assess how much excess fat on the body is present. The extra fat on the middle and stomach area increase the chances of diabetes also and the people who have bigger waist line than their hips are also prone to many diseases. The measurement of skin fold can be taken to know the percentage of body fat.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Blood tests can be done to know if there is any kind of thyroid or hormone dysfunction that can be a reason behind obesity.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Treatment of obesity
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The obesity can be treated by changing your eating habits, lifestyle like quit smoking and make exercise and yoga a part of your life, taking medicine regularly if obesity is due to some disease, some prescription drug to reduce the fat are also available in the market that are safe to use, undergoing laparoscopic surgery if obesity is too much that can not be controlled by other ways. You can set realistic goals in every area like you can not skip all your meal but instead skip your afternoon meal and have low fat diet with no sugar.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Obesity is a threat to your life s control it on time to save yourself from many diseases like high blood sugar,hypertension,arthritis etc.So if you are obese do not wait for anything just start losing weight.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Read about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXJlbWVkaWVzLXdvcmxkLmNvbS9kaXZ5YS1tZWRvaGFyLXZhdGkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;control obesity&lt;/a&gt;; also read about &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXJlbWVkaWVzLXdvcmxkLmNvbS95b2dhLWZvci1vYmVzaXR5Lmh0bWw_" target="_blank"&gt;;Yoga for Overweight&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5ob21lLXJlbWVkaWVzLXdvcmxkLmNvbS8_" target="_blank"&gt;;home remedies&lt;/a&gt;;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>