<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="20s">	<conversations count="3">		<conversation id="83a20e9f95be62f544e7115fb570b680">			Inexpensive ways of deterring thieves:
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Several easy and inexpensive methods can be used to deter thieves, in order to make your home premises safer. Nevertheless, the majority of home alarms systems feature the same components, with the brand name and a few minor components being the difference. They feature an electronic keypad, internal motion detector, audible siren and physical perimeter detectors.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Several factors need to be taken into consideration before acquiring a system. First and fore most, it is important to ascertain the desired features and accessories. A home with pets may need to consider home alarms that do not pick the motion from the pets. Furthermore, a house with several windows would require an alarm that can effectively detect when the windows are being opened or when glass windows are being shattered.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Secondly, the &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvdXNlYWxhcm1zLmNvLnVrL2hvdXNlLWFsYXJtLXByaWNlcw__" target="_blank"&gt;;house alarms prices&lt;/a&gt;; are an important consideration. There is often a charge associated with installing the system as well as a monthly fee. You must however be weary of sacrificing the safety of your family on the premise of lowest prices; it is advisable to get in touch with reputable companies. Although the home alarm systems provided by different companies feature the same components, the difference lies with the monitoring service being provided. Comparing quotes from different companies enables homeowners to obtain value for their money.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2hvdXNlYWxhcm1zLmNvLnVrLw__" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/173462740_421079_46869145.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Wireless burglar alarms are an important crime prevention product. There is a wide selection of wireless burglar alarms to choose from including wireless house alarms, wireless panic alarm system, driveway alarms and shed &amp; garage alarms. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2tub2wuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS9rL21hcnRpbi1jcm93ZS9ob3VzZS1hbGFybXMtYW4taW5leHBlbnNpdmUtd2F5LW9mLzJhNm1hdDFmNXduZjkvMzM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Wireless house alarms&lt;/a&gt;; systems are inexpensive to purchase, easy to set up and can be programmed to directly send information to mobile devices alerting the owner of possible entry into his/ her premises. There are different types of wireless house alarms available, including particle sensors, smoke sensors and motion sensors to systems. Furthermore, the systems are fitted with optical sensors that trigger an alarm and offer a view of the happenings.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The use of Closed Circuit Television (CCTV) for home security is gaining popularity. The video camera is an important aspect of this surveillance system. The dome shaped cameras are mounted on ceilings and are particularly useful in secret surveillance. The bullet shaped cameras are common for outdoor use. Furthermore, they are weatherproof. Other important features common in &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/martincrowe/blog/blogid=5621325" target="_blank"&gt;;CCTV systems&lt;/a&gt;; include night vision, automatic operation and motion sensors.		</conversation>		<conversation id="e63aee5a768987b4b8e4e3bac6c10a42">			Types of iPod docking stations:
&lt;br /&gt;;Most of the people enjoy listening to music using their iPods and to do this, the iPod docking station helps. The iPod docking station charges the iPod while it is connected. You can consider purchasing a USB wall charger that can facilitate charging without a PC.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;There is a wide variety of iPod docking stations featuring different styles and sizes. Major electronic brands such as Apple, TDK, Sony, Bose, Philips and Logitech offer several docking stations, addressing different needs.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Since their creation in 2001, iPod have gained popularity among teens and college students, taking over the market that was previously dominated by MP3 players. The iPod uses the iTunes software to synchronize several media including music and video to several iPod music players via speakers. Apple has introduced different product models including the Nano, iPod Mini, Classic and Shuffle. In addition, Apple has been able to produce iPod docking stations with speakers that can be used for both playing and charging. IPod docking station with speakers can be purchased from most of the electronic stores, nevertheless, it is important to verify before hand whether the docking station is compatible with your device.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The best docking station:
&lt;br /&gt;;There are important factors that need to be taken into consideration in order to obtain the best iPod Docking Station- including features, performance and price.  Reading &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pcG9kZG9ja2luZ3N0YXRpb24uY28udWsvaXBvZC1kb2NraW5nLXN0YXRpb24tcmV2aWV3cy8_" target="_blank"&gt;;iPod docking station reviews&lt;/a&gt;; can help in ensuring you get value for your money.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pcG9kZG9ja2luZ3N0YXRpb24uY28udWsv" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/173462740_8843877_46869771.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Apple iPod Dual 50Wx4 docking station enables users to tune in to their favorite FM station, their iPod and other audio device. Furthermore, the Bluetooth technology allows for making hands- free calls.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Sony’s RDP-XF100IP portable iPod Docking Station features a radio. The Bose docking station is renowned for its rich and superior sound quality; it allows iPods to sync and to be charged. In addition, it is modern and attractive which adds style to the room. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2FydGljbGVjaXR5LmluL2VudGVydGFpbm1lbnQtbW92aWVzL2lwb2QtZG9ja2luZy1zdGF0aW9uLWdldHRpbmctdmFsdWUtZm9yLXlvdXItbW9uZXkuaHRtbA__" target="_blank"&gt;;Best iPod Docking Station&lt;/a&gt;; features a rechargeable lithium ion battery that makes it useful even in the absence of electricity. Furthermore, it comes with an auxiliary jack that can be used together with other devices such as MP3 and CD players.
&lt;br /&gt;;Nevertheless, the price for iPod docking stations range between £40 and £400.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;IPod portable media players:
&lt;br /&gt;;There are many models of iPod portable media players to choose, based on the taste and budget of an individual. The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/martincrowe/blog/blogid=5640772" target="_blank"&gt;;iPod Docking Station with DAB&lt;/a&gt;; is gaining popularity. This innovation allows listeners to make more choices. The radio is tuned easily while the screen offers a display of the station. Furthermore, the controls of the radio are easy to use. You can also tap to set radio stations of your choice, change the radio station or tap to pause/ resume.		</conversation>		<conversation id="519acda37c01a78da4c6f965eb3374bc">			Lyric Theatre Australia:
&lt;br /&gt;;The Lyric Theatre has played an integral role of providing arts and entertainment, since 1926. The theatre is renowned for year- round world- class performances by internationally and nationally renowned artists. In addition, the venue has also been successful in facilitating local productions, charitable and civic events. The Lyric theatre represents a rich heritage that brings together the young and old. Any one looking for an opportunity to enjoy excellent comedy, dance, drama, musicals, family fun and more- can count on the Lyric theatre. The theatre seats 500, offers a 22x30 ft stage and whisper- perfect acoustics. Furthermore, it has entrances on 2-downtown streets, balcony and spacious lobby. The theatre has hosted numerous events including movies, dance recitals, classical theatres, country bands, jazz concerts and school programs. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;span class="textAlign textAlignCenter"&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL2x5cmljdGhlYXRyZS5jb20uYXUv" target="_blank"&gt;;&lt;img src="http://www.pan.net/en/p/oo/173462740_12021182_46870627.jpg" /&gt;;&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;;
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL21hcnRpbmNyb3dlLndpa2lzcGFjZXMuY29tL0V4dHJlbWVseStTcGVjdGFjdWxhcitBbmQrQW1hemluZytUaGVhdHJlK0V4cGVyaWVuY2UrQXQrTHlyaWMrVGhlYXRyZQ__" target="_blank"&gt;;Lyric theatre Sydney&lt;/a&gt;; has been in existence since 2001. It has been successful in distinguishing itself as a fine performance venue in Sydney. It features an impressive concert venue offering excellent acoustics, comfortable and roomy seating. The theatre offers a capacity of 2000. Furthermore, all persons including persons with hearing impairment or on wheelchairs can access the theatre. The theatre offers disabled parking bays close to the car park entrance. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The Lyric theatre Sydney prides of a ten-year history that has welcomed legendary performance drawn from countries throughout the world. Michael Crawford, Bon Jovi, Tony Bennett and Julio Iglesias are some of the big names that have graced the venue. Moreover, Elton John announced recently that his upcoming tour should be taking place in the Lyric theatre Sydney. The world premiere of ‘Pricilla Queen of The Desert’, ‘Phantom of the Opera’ ‘Mamma Mia’ and ‘Oliver’ are musicals that have dazzled the audiences of Lyric Theatre. 
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5pZGVhbWFya2V0ZXJzLmNvbS8/YXJ0aWNsZWlkPTI4MTc5NTcmYW1wO0NGSUQ9ODk4MTQzNzYmYW1wO0NGVE9LRU49NjE3MzgxNzM_" target="_blank"&gt;;Lyric theatre Brisbane&lt;/a&gt;; is a stunning 200-seat theatre offering exceptional acoustics, an orchestra pit &amp; magical atmosphere, large main &amp; rear stages and elegance. These qualities make the venue a preferred destination for international, interstate and local performance. It features a traditional horseshoe shape. In addition, the auditorium offers continental seating and two levels of balconies.
&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The stage area features main, rear and side stages, as well as proscenium arch &amp; apron. The pit can be raise to offer a thrust stage while the rear stage can be isolated in order to allow the use of the main and rear stages concurrently.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>