<author lang="en" gender="female" age_group="30s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="e11444318f771937d140086e5ba79d63">			&lt;img src=&quot;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=http%3A%2F%2Ffarm8.static.flickr.com%2F7103%2F7338992664_02cf184e8d.jpg%26quot"target="_blank" rel="nofollow"&gt;;http://farm8.static.flickr.com/7103/7338992664_02cf184e8d.jpg&quot;&lt;/a&gt;;; align=&quot;left&quot; width=&quot;290&quot; style=&quot;padding:10px;&quot;/&gt;;Blogging is available to all, but few do it successfully. Almost everybody seems to have a blog. You have to be decisive and proactive to have a good blog. Use the techniques and methods in this article to assist you in creating the right blog for you. &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3d3dy5zcXVpZG9vLmNvbS9zZW95b3Jrc2hpcmU3OTI_" target="_blank"&gt;;link&lt;/a&gt;; and &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL215YW5pbWVsaXN0Lm5ldC9ibG9nLnBocD9laWQ9MjE1NjIx" target="_blank"&gt;;more info&lt;/a&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It's important to lay out your blog in a way that makes sense. Put important links at the top of the site for easy access. Doing so facilitates site navigation.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Make sure to do as much research as you can on the blog's topic. If you don't know much about the topic, you might inadvertently share incorrect information, or information that is misleading. In addition, even if you can &quot;fake&quot; knowledge of the subject well enough to write about it, you won't be able to respond to comments appropriately if you don't know anything about the topic.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;One key aspect of blogging is to enjoy yourself while doing it. Your blog can bore readers if you don't pour your passion into it. Decide on the topic you are most passionate about, and have a good time sharing it with others! If you're enthusiastic about what you're writing, others will get caught up in your enthusiasm as well.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Lists do have a place in a well-written blog. For instance, when writing about cooking, include lists of ingredients or the kitchen tools needed to create a memorable dish. If you write about rebuilding the engine of your 1967 Volkswagen, include a list of parts needed. A list will provide the reader with your content in a visually appealing and easy to digest format.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;The choice to include advertising on your blog is one which should not be made without careful consideration. For many bloggers, putting ads on their blog is the quickest and most reliable way to derive some profit from their efforts. The problem with allowing advertising is, well, it's advertising. Many times your viewers will recognize that you are attempting to make money from your blog if you allow advertisements.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;It is very important to maintain consistent with your blog, so you will want to keep a regular posting schedule. Your readers have plenty of blog-reading options, and they may as well take advantage of a different one if you post inconsistently. People won't hold it against you at certain times, such as around the holidays, but there's no getting around the fact that you need to post frequently and consistently.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Always try to incorporate figures, charts and graphs if possible. This helps make your blog posts more appealing and increases the quality of your posts. These little additions make a big impact on your blog readers.&lt;br /&gt;;&lt;br /&gt;;Now you can make a blog and you do not have to worry on how to be a great blogger, because time will eventually do this for you. Use the knowledge you have gained from this guide and you will have a lot more followers than what you have imagined.		</conversation>	</conversations></author>