<author lang="en" gender="male" age_group="10s">	<conversations count="1">		<conversation id="93c0b63356c87df34a0b8a50daf21b5b">			While it's true that whenever two people get married they vow to be with one another until death, life is fairly unpredictable and some things might go wrong. After all, it is nearly impossible to predict what kinds of incidents are going to take place years down the line. At any rate, the process of divorce was set into place for many who wanted to end the marriage. Although during its early days divorce was highly unusual a result of a great number of causes (the main one being social backlash), it is significantly more common to discover people who are looking to go through the procedure. When you are in a situation where you need to go for a military divorce, then prior to looking for a Virginia Beach divorce attorney it is important to first take time to be aware of the implications of such divorces.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;A Look at Military Divorce&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Different from civilian divorces, military divorces put into play various situations which complicate the whole divorce process. To start things off, there are Federal laws which prevent someone who is active duty in the military to be divorced with no knowledge of it, as they are protected against being forced to answer a divorce action, or any other civil suit, while on active duty. As a matter of fact, the procedures can be postponed for as much as sixty days after the time of active service; or an active duty service member can decide to waive any delaying if they indeed want the divorce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;When it comes to the spouse, the Federal and state laws are basically the same. If the spouse is on active duty, she must personally receive a summons to the court as well as a copy of the divorce Complaint; if not, the Virginia court will most definitely have no authority over the court case. Whenever the case remains uncontested, the spouse may be served an affidavit whereby they thoroughly recognize the steps taken in terms of divorce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Typically, the requirements to get a military divorce state that one individual concerned is required to be living or stationed in Virginia. The grounds used for the divorce are exactly the same ones as in a civilian case. As far as property division, the standard Division Of Property Laws employ, not to mention that the government has also put in place the Uniformed Services Former Spouses' Protection Act which has the purpose to figure out who should get how much military retirement benefits upon divorce. However, the military retirement funds may be the subject of an exception if the spouse has been married for less than ten years while the military spouse was on active duty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;In case there are children involved in the case, the child support laws and regulations say that alimony plus child support are not to be greater than 60% of a military member's pay. The regular process is used to set how much a member pays for child support in case of a divorce.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Acquiring a Virginia Beach Divorce Lawyer&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;As you can see, a military divorce is different from a standard one as you will discover other specifics to iron out. Fortunately though, finding a Virginia Beach divorce lawyer is one of the easiest things to do out there. To start things off, you could always visit the different law firms in the city and look at the attorneys they have for you. Although you will probably find a competent divorce attorney in town this way, it will require a great amount of time to examine all the possibilities before making a final decision.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Additionally, you can also find a Virginia Beach divorce attorney by looking on the internet on legal directories which allow you to easily reach practically every single lawyer in your city. These websites can be best described as directories containing lists of lawyers and attorneys, and it should be added that they have been neatly organized for your convenience.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;All in all, keep in mind that a military divorce has a few nuances which need to be dealt with differently than in a regular civilian divorce. Unless you are quite familiar with the laws around this subject, it is recommended that you take the time to find a Virginia Beach divorce lawyer to help you through the whole process; after all, divorce is a painful thing to experience psychologically… why make your life even more difficult by going into the legal aspects?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZhYmVhY2hkaXZvcmNlYXR0b3JuZXkubmV0" target="_blank"&gt;Military Divorce Lawyer Virginia Beach&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href="http://en.pan.netcom/go/out/url=-aHR0cDovL3ZhYmVhY2hkaXZvcmNlbGF3LmJsb2dzcG90LmNvbQ__" target="_blank"&gt;Military Divorce Lawyer Virginia Beach&lt;/a&gt;		</conversation>	</conversations></author>